(rumbling)
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(explosions, soldiers yelling)
Sergeant Stephens?
Sir.
I want every wounded man
taken down the line
before it starts to get dark.
We've bloody well lost enough
of them for one day.
When did this arrive?
Sir.
Ah, good news.
(commotion outside)
We're to be relieved today
by the Devons.
The men can finally
get some rest
and I've got a few days'
leave coming to me.
What will you do
with them, sir?
London first.
To remind myself what real food
tastes like.
Then north for a couple of days,
I suppose.
Naturally, there's a girl
I want to see while I'm there.
So I should hope, sir.
It's strange, isn't it?
To think about our lives
just going on as before?
While we're here,
in this.
It's more than strange.
When I think of my life
at Downton,
it seems like another world.
ANNA:
We normally have everything
done before the family wakes up
but it's all
at sixes and sevens today.
I'll go through it
with you tomorrow
when we're back to normal.
I do know how to run a house.
Come along.
It goes under the epaulette.
I'm sorry, m'lord.
If I'd known, I'd have asked
Mr. Bates about it
before he left for London.
Because I'll be in uniform
a lot of the time, in future.
Does being Lord Lieutenant
mean you're back in the army?
No, not exactly.
The Lord Lieut is responsible
for the army in the county
while the war's on.
But no.
I'm not back in the army.
It appears they don't want me.
(dog barking)
Morning.
I don't suppose there's
any news of Bates?
We expect him back
any day, m'lord.
He wrote to Anna that they had
the funeral last Monday.
William's a good chap,
but he's not Bates
when it comes to uniforms.
I may not be a real soldier,
but I think I ought
to look like one.
Quite, m'lord.
ROBERT:
We don't often see you
in here for breakfast.
Isobel said she was
coming up to help
and your mother threatened
to look in.
No doubt they would love it
if they found me
still in bed.
I don't believe it.
Please say
it's something nice.
General Robertson's invited me
to be Colonel of the North
Riding Volunteers.
Well, this is the best bit:
"It may please you to know
that the idea was given to me
by General Haig."
Well, if Haig's involved,
it means I'm back
in the army properly.
How can that be?
You were told you weren't wanted
for active service.
You can't jump
in and out of the army
like a jack-in-a-box.
ROBERT:
I don't see why not.
Churchill went back to the front
after the Gallipoli business.
If he can do it,
why shouldn't I?
Sybil, are you all right?
Sybil, darling?
Would you excuse me?
I think I'll just...
She's had more bad news.
I do think I'm getting
better, don't you?
Up to a point, m'lady.
If you could just get the clutch
right down to the floor.
But I am.
Not quite, m'lady.
It doesn't seem to want to go.
I think it wants to,
if you ask it properly.
That's better.
You'll be putting me
out of a job.
Won't the call-up put you
all out of your jobs?
I'll cross that bridge
when I come to it.
(horn honking)
What are you giving them to eat?
Not much.
They know the money's
for the hospital,
so they can't expect
Belshazzar's Feast.
I'll make some cheese straws.
What's the matter with you?
Nothing much.
Me Dad still won't
let me enlist.
Your father has no one but you.
Of course he doesn't want you
to enlist.
Who can argue with him?
So I stand by
while the lads on the farms
and in the gardens go to war.
Even Thomas is at the front
in the medical corps.
Well, that'll have come
as a nasty shock.
Oh, you can make fun of him,
Mrs. Patmore.
But he's fighting for his king
and country and I'm not.
Well, I dare say you won't
have long to wait.
Well, I hope you're right.
Do you?
Because I don't.
I hope very much
that I am wrong.
It's kind of you
to let us have it here.
They'll enjoy it so much more.
And you can charge so much more
for the tickets.
ROBERT:
Good morning, Mama.
This is very early for you
to be up and about.
War makes early risers
of us all.
I thought I would help
with the flowers.
Bassett has plenty,
but... thank you.
You don't mind my taking over
the flowers, do you?
Cora's flowers
always look more suited
to a first communion
in southern Italy.
Well, what else have you planned
for tonight's revels?
Anything we can think of
that will raise money.
Hot buttered toast
with a countess,
at tuppence a slice?
You drop the cushions
on the floor to plump them up.
I know.
Ethel, are you settling in?
I would be.
If Anna'd stop teaching me
how to suck eggs.
I was head housemaid
in my last position.
You were senior housemaid out
of two in a much smaller house.
Are they to come
in here tonight?
Only at the interval.
And keep them out
of the drawing room.
I thought Mr. Bates
would've been back by now,
or he could've stood guard.
Who is this Mr. Bates?
His lordship's valet.
He's been in London
because his mother died.
Only everyone talks about him
as if he were a king.
Do they?
That's nice to hear.
Anna.
Help me do battle
with this monstrosity.
It looks like a creature
from The Lost World.
You should let
William do that.
He's got enough
on his hands,
getting the uniforms
out of mothballs.
I must remember to put Anna
on alert for dinner tonight.
You have to
ease up a bit
or you'll give yourself
a heart attack.
There's a war on.
Things cannot be the same
when there's a war on.
I do not agree.
Keeping up standards is the only
way to show the Germans
that they will not beat us
in the end.
Well, give me some warning
the next time we're expecting
Germans at Downton
and I'll see what I can do.
Thank you.
Oh, we thought we'd come
in here for a little talk.
Oh, well, I'm sure
we won't be disturbed.
Please.
Well the thing is,
I've had a letter from Matthew.
Of course he doesn't tell me
what he's actually doing.
No, he wouldn't.
But I'm glad he's all right.
I miss him.
ISOBEL:
Well, that's the point.
You must know he's been
down here a few times
since the war started.
CORA:
We had heard.
Downton is hardly
a metropolis.
ROBERT:
Is he still determined
to go back to Manchester
when it's all over?
He doesn't talk much
about life after the war.
None of them do.
I suppose they don't want
to tempt fate.
Until now, that is.
He writes that he is engaged
to be married,
to a Miss Lavinia Swire.
Well, I...
I suppose we all knew
it would happen one day.
Do you know her?
Not yet.
Apparently, they met when he was
in England last time.
It all seems rather hurried.
You can't blame them for wanting
to live in the present.
Anyway, he's been in London
on leave
and now he's bringing her here
to meet me.
He'll be here tonight
and tomorrow,
then he leaves on Thursday
while she stays for a bit.
So will you miss the concert?
Well, that's up to you.
We'd all hoped that he and Mary
would sort things out
between them.
But if that's not to be,
then shouldn't we try
to get back to normal?
Even if he's not keen
to live in the village,
he's still the heir.
And you're still
his family.
I quite agree.
We can't know if Matthew
will come through it.
Either way,
I would like to see him
and I want to wish him luck.
The trouble is Mary's back
from London today, as well.
She gets in at 5:00.
ISOBEL:
Matthew's driving down
in Lavinia's car.
They won't meet on the train.
Oh, that's a relief.
I hate Greek drama, you know,
when everything happens
off stage.
CORA:
But should we tell her
not to come?
We might still catch her.
Isobel's right.
We must use this engagement
as a new beginning.
You bring our Lieutenant Crawley
to the concert,
and stay for dinner
afterwards.
I was hoping you'd say that.
ISOBEL:
Oh, there you are.
I'm just going home,
but I'll be back at 4:00...
Sybil?
My dear,
what's the matter?
Tom Bellasis has been killed.
What a terrible thing.
I remember him at Imogen's ball.
He made me laugh out loud
just as her uncle
was giving a speech.
Sometimes it feels as if all the
men I ever danced with are dead.
I just feel so useless,
wasting my life
while they sacrifice theirs.
You've been a tremendous help
with the concert.
No, I... I don't mean
selling programs
or finding prizes
for the Tombola.
I want to do a real job.
Real work.
Well...
If you're serious, what about
being an auxiliary nurse?
There's a training
college in York.
I know I could get you
on to a course.
It may be something
of a rough awakening.
Are you ready for that?
I mean, have you ever made
your own bed, for example?
Or scrubbed a floor?
O'Brien, what is it?
Mr. Platt is taking her ladyship
and Lady Grantham
down to the village.
She wondered if you'd like
to go with them.
That's very kind.
Thank you.
Go on.
What else would I need?
Well, if you're serious,
what about cooking?
Why don't you ask Mrs. Patmore
if she could give you
one or two basic tips?
When you get to York,
it might be useful to know
a little more than nothing.
They want to use her as a maid
of all work at the hospital.
I suppose it's cheaper when Lady
Sybil can live here for nothing.
But it doesn't seem quite right,
somehow, to take advantage.
No, it does not.
I hear the young men that
are being brought in now
are very disfigured.
How terrible.
Limbs missing
and faces blown apart
and Lady Sybil's been
nurtured so very gently.
And what types would
she be working with?
Still, you'll know
what's best to do.
Yes.
I certainly will.
Where's the batter
for the pancakes?
It's in the cold larder.
Are we having
pancakes tonight?
Are we 'eck as like.
Upstairs dinner.
Crêpes Suzettes.
(Ethel gasps)
I've always wanted
to try those.
Could you save me some?
If they don't
finish them all.
Save you some Crêpes Suzettes?
ETHEL:
If you don't mind.
What are we having?
Lamb stew and semolina.
Do you eat a lot of stews?
Don't you fancy that, dear?
ETHEL:
Not all the time.
Oh, I see.
Um, would you like to sleep
in her ladyship's bedroom
while you're at it?
I wouldn't mind.
I hate sharing a room.
I didn't in my last place.
There were only two maids
and a cook.
I'm just saying.
And I'll "just say"
if you don't look out!
You've got a cheek,
on your first day.
I don't see why.
I want the best,
and I'm not ashamed to admit it.
And you think we don't?
I think it's hard to change
at your age.
I don't blame you,
but I suppose, in the end,
I want to be more
than just a servant.
I'm sorry, but if Dr. Clarkson
needs free labor,
I'd prefer him not to find it
in my nursery.
But Sybil isn't
in the nursery.
No, and in case
you hadn't noticed,
she hasn't been there
for some time.
You know what I mean.
Well, no, not really.
You can't pretend
it's not respectable,
when every day we're treated
to pictures of queens and
princesses in Red Cross uniform,
ladling soup down the throat
of some unfortunate.
CORA:
But Sybil won't be ladling soup.
She'll have to witness
unimaginable horrors.
When she's an innocent.
Her innocence
will protect her.
For once, I agree
with Cousin Isobel.
VIOLET:
Sybil must be allowed to do
her bit like everyone else.
CORA:
What about you, Molesley?
Are you ready for the call,
if it comes?
It won't be coming for me,
m'lady.
I had a letter
from the War Office
to say I'm not suitable
for service.
Why not?
I... I really couldn't say,
m'lady.
As you can imagine,
Molesley's father is beside
himself with joy.
VIOLET:
God moves in
a mysterious way,
His wonders to perform.
Bates!
No one told me you
were on this train.
They didn't know, m'lady.
We'll give you a lift
to the house.
Why didn't you say
you were coming?
I didn't know until today.
Anna, I borrowed a case
from Lady Rosamund.
I bought some things
while I was in London.
Very good, m'lady.
Well, it would be
our secret.
A surprise.
You don't mind, do you?
Oh, it's not that I mind,
m'lady...
And I only need
the basics.
How to boil an egg,
how to make tea.
Don't you know
how to make tea?
Not really.
(giggling)
SYBIL:
You're right.
It is a joke.
But when I start my course,
I don't want to be a joke.
Will you help me?
'Course we will.
Won't we?
If you say so.
Let's get started.
Do you know how to fill
a kettle?
Everyone knows that.
(gasping)
Not everyone, apparently.
When can I talk to you?
After the concert.
Outside in the courtyard.
There's bound to be a gap
before they start dinner.
Are you going up
for the concert?
Maybe.
Can I sit with you?
Don't be daft.
We've got a dinner
to make.
I've not got time
for concerts.
I've had a letter
from me dad.
He won't change his mind.
He says he can live with it
if I get called up,
as there's nothing we can do,
but if I enlist
and anything happens,
he'll never get over it.
He loves you.
He may love me,
but he doesn't own me,
and he's not being fair.
Glad to be back?
I'm never sure.
When I'm in London,
I long for Yorkshire,
and when I'm here,
I ache to hear my heels
clicking on the pavement.
I'd forgotten
about this nightmare concert.
Why didn't you warn me?
I'd have come back tomorrow.
But you'd have missed Matthew.
I was going to tell you.
Matthew's on leave
and he's in the village,
so Papa and I thought
it would be a good time
to mend our fences.
He's coming tonight,
with Isobel.
And his fiancée.
What?
Edith, I don't know
how helpful you're being.
Matthew's engaged.
He's brought her to Downton
to meet his mother.
Well, how marvelous.
You don't mind?
Why should I?
We're not going to marry,
but I don't want him to spend
the rest of his life in a cave.
Exactly what Papa
and I feel.
Please try to be
happy for him.
Of course I'm happy.
Good luck to him.
Anyway, there's someone
I want you all to meet.
Have you ever come across
Richard Carlisle?
Sir Richard Carlisle?
The one with all those
horrid newspapers?
We met at Cliveden.
But how old is he?
Old enough not to ask
stupid questions.
Anyway, I can't wait
for you to know him.
If only Papa hadn't
closed down the shoot.
CORA:
Most people have stopped
shooting now that the war's on.
But I'm sure Papa
would be happy
to have Sir Richard
come and stay.
Are you?
I shouldn't have thought
he was Papa's type at all.
Are you coming?
I'll be down in a minute.
Are you all right, m'lady?
Oh, Anna...
It's awfully grand.
You'd better
get used to it.
It'll be your home one day.
I'm not sure "home"
would ever be quite the word
to describe it.
My dear fellow,
welcome back.
It's so very good
to see you.
May I present
Miss Lavinia Swire?
LAVINIA:
How do you do, Lord Grantham.
ROBERT:
How do you do, Miss Swire.
So, that's Mary's
replacement.
Well.
I suppose looks
aren't everything.
I think she seems
rather sweet.
CORA:
I'm afraid
meeting us all together
must be very intimidating.
I do hope so.
Now, please
come this way.
Thank you.
It's good to see you.
Hello, Miss Swire.
I'm Mary Crawley.
Of course you are.
I mean, I've been
longing to meet you
because I've heard so much
about you from Matthew.
Oh, that is...
Nice things, I hope.
What else would
she hear from me?
ROBERT:
Please.
I can't say.
It's been such
a long time.
Who knows what you think
of me now?
I think...
I'm very glad to see you
looking so well.
All right, you win.
We are at peace again.
(music starts)
(music continues in distance)
Have you found
something nice?
Why, particularly?
As a welcome home,
for Mr. Matthew.
(grunts)
Oh, what's the matter?
I thought you'd come
round to him.
Well, last time he was here he
hadn't broken Lady Mary's heart.
Lady Mary broke her own heart.
That's if she has
a heart to break.
I don't think we're ever
going to see eye-to-eye
on this, Mrs. Hughes.
She refused him when she
thought he'd have nothing.
And when he was heir again,
she wanted him back.
I thought caution
was a virtue.
Caution may be.
Self-interest is not.
Perhaps Miss Swire
is a gentler person.
If you ask me,
this "Miss Swire,"
who, it may interest you
to know, is not to be found
in Burke's Peerage
or Burke's Landed Gentry,
has an eye to the main chance.
That's not snobbish, I suppose?
I like to see things done
properly, Mrs. Hughes,
and I won't apologize for that.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
What is it?
A white feather, of course.
Coward.
ROBERT:
Stop this at once!
This is neither the time
nor the place!
These people
should be aware
that there are cowards
among them.
ROBERT:
Will you please leave!
You are the cowards here,
not they!
ROBERT:
Leader,
will you continue?
(music starts)
I'm in a uniform.
Wrong kind.
That was horrid, William.
I hope you won't
let it upset you.
WILLIAM:
No, your ladyship.
Why are these women
so unkind?
Of course it is horrid.
When heroes are giving
their lives every day,
it's hard to watch
healthy young men do nothing.
By the way, Sybil,
very good news:
they do have a vacancy.
It's very short notice,
because someone dropped out.
You'd have to be ready
to start on Friday.
May I ask
what this is about?
SYBIL:
Cousin Isobel
has got me a place
on a nursing course
in York.
I want to work
at the hospital.
We don't have
to talk about it now.
She just turned up
at my mother's house.
Not long before she died.
So, what does it mean?
I think it means, at long last,
I'm able to get a divorce.
Mr. Bates...
Is this a proposal?
If that's what you want
to call it.
And you might start
calling me John.
Well, why are you sure
she'll do it now
when she's refused
for so long?
Mother left me some money,
much more than I thought.
Vera's a greedy woman.
She won't refuse
what I can offer her.
Will we have
to leave Downton?
Not until we want to.
I've spoken to his lordship
and he will find a cottage
for us near the house.
You told him you want
to marry me?
I did.
Before you spoke to me?
You don't mind, do you?
Of course I mind!
In fact, I'd give you a smack
if I didn't want to kiss you
so much I could burst!
Branson says I'm ready
for the road.
That's not what he told me.
How delicious.
I love these.
How did you
and Matthew meet?
Oh, in London.
My father works in London
so I've always lived there.
But I love the country, too.
Of course you do.
Daddy's a solicitor,
like Matthew.
My, my.
You're very well placed
if you're ever in trouble
with the law.
ROBERT:
Did I tell you I've
been given a Colonelcy
in the North Riding
Volunteers?
So I'm properly
in the army again.
Congratulations.
He won't go
with them, will he?
When they're called
to the front?
MARY:
I hope not,
but he seems to think so.
What's it been like?
Do you know,
the thing is...
I just can't talk about it.
Have you missed us?
What do you think?
You don't mind my
bringing Lavinia?
On the contrary,
I'm glad,
glad to see you happy.
What about you?
Are you happy?
I think I'm about
to be happy.
Does that count?
It does if you mean it.
You'll be the first to know.
What are you reading?
Photoplay,
about Mabel Normand.
She was nothing
when she started, you know.
Her father was a carpenter
and they'd no money.
And now she's
a shining film star.
Ethel, I've a message
for you from her ladyship.
You're to go up
and see her now.
What?
Where?
In the drawing room,
of course.
They're all
in the drawing room.
What have I done wrong?
Nothing.
Quite the reverse.
She's very pleased
with the way you've begun
and she wants
to thank you.
Now?
Yes, now.
She's asked for you.
How much longer are you
going to keep her waiting?
(giggling)
I don't know much
about life in the country.
But I do understand
how the law works,
so I believe I can be
helpful to Matthew there.
But you'll be
immensely helpful.
Don't you think so, Mary?
Of course.
(door opens)
Beg pardon, m'lady,
for keeping you waiting.
What?
I'm ever so grateful
for your appreciation
and I want you to know that
it's a privilege to work here.
Ethel,
what are you doing
in here?
Her...
her ladyship sent for me.
And who gave you
this message?
Miss O'Brien.
She said I wasn't to keep
her ladyship waiting.
CARSON:
You may go back downstairs
now, thank you, Ethel.
ETHEL:
Right.
Thank you, m'lady.
VIOLET:
Well.
Do we think she's mad, ill,
or working for the Russians?
(giggling)
MATTHEW:
She has plenty of time
to learn.
Cousin Robert will be in
charge here for many years.
Lavinia will be
a lawyer's wife
far longer than
she'll be a countess.
That's if I get through
the war in one piece.
Of course you will.
Don't even think like that.
How long are you staying
in the village?
Just tomorrow.
I take the 6:00 train
on Thursday.
And then you'll be
in France.
Wherever I'm going,
I'm so pleased that
we're friends again.
I still don't understand
why it was funny to make me
look a fool.
You weren't even there
to enjoy it.
Oh, don't worry.
We enjoyed it all
right from down here.
Miss O'Brien,
her ladyship has asked me
to take the incident
no further.
Don't tempt me to disobey.
Did I see Lady Sybil
in the kitchen yesterday?
She wants to learn
some cooking.
She says she's going
to train to be a nurse,
so she needs to know how to cook
and clean and everything.
Has she told her ladyship
about this?
It's supposed to be
a surprise.
Mr. Carson,
it speaks well of Lady Sybil
that she wants to help
the wounded.
Let's not give her away.
ETHEL:
Why shouldn't she learn
how to cook and scrub?
She may need it
when the war's over.
Things are changing.
For her lot and us,
and when they do,
I mean to make
the most of it.
(scoffs)
I take it they ate all the
pancakes last night, then?
They did.
(service bell rings)
(whistles)
Here you are.
ISOBEL:
What are we aiming at?
They'd like us to take
100 wounded men.
Three times the number
the hospital was built for.
Well, that settles it.
We'll have to convert
the second Day Room.
So there's to be no
convalescence at all?
I'm afraid not.
Once they can stand,
they must go.
If only there were somewhere
nearer than Farley Hall.
I can't get there more than
twice a week at the most.
Ah, should he
be doing that?
Why not?
I only meant
with his condition.
ISOBEL:
What condition is that?
CLARKSON:
His lungs.
Old Lady Grantham told me
he's had a lot of trouble
with his lungs.
And why did she tell you that,
particularly?
She wanted me to write
to the War Office.
She was anxious to spare him
the humiliation
of being refused
on medical grounds.
And who else did she wish you
to take under your protection?
William Mason,
the footman
at the big house.
He has a bad skin
condition apparently,
and hates people to know.
She wanted to spare him
the physical examination.
I'm sure she did.
What in Wonderland
do you call that?
I mean, I do not
fully understand
what you are
trying to do, m'lady.
I knew it wasn't supposed
to look like this.
No, m'lady.
I would go so far as to say
there is no food on the earth
that is supposed to look
like that.
Why does everything
go so lumpy?
Tell you what,
chuck it out
and we'll start again.
I don't think we should sell
your mother's house.
Not yet.
We could rent it out.
Then we can save.
When I've some time off, I'll go
up to London and get it ready.
Maybe I can come with you.
We could do it together.
I've got an idea that a bit
later on, if we want to...
If we want to start a family.
I thought, when the time is
right, we might sell.
And we could buy
a small hotel,
just... just a little one,
maybe near here.
Then we could
work together
and have the children
with us.
What is it?
Nothing.
It's just... in my whole life,
I never thought I could be
as happy as I am at this moment.
(footsteps approaching)
Don't worry.
I haven't come to undo your
good work of the other night.
You must have been up
before the servants.
They were rather
surprised to see me.
I wanted to give you this.
It's my lucky charm.
I've had it always.
So you must promise to bring
it back, without a scratch.
Won't you need it?
Not as much as you.
So look after it.
Please.
I'll try not to be a hero,
if that's what
you're afraid of.
Just come back
safe and sound.
Did you have a happy
time yesterday?
I showed Lavinia the places
I like most.
To give her a few memories.
Mary, if I don't come back...
But...
No.
If I don't...
then do remember
how very glad I am
that we made up
when we had the chance.
I mean it.
You send me off to war
a happy man.
Will you do
something for me?
Will you...
will you look after Mother,
if anything happens?
Of course we will,
but it won't.
And Lavinia?
She's young, she'll find
someone else--
I hope she does, anyway--
but until she does.
(trainman whistles)
Good-bye, then.
And such good luck.
Good-bye, Mary.
And God bless you.
Lady Mary was very much part
of the story, I can assure you.
ETHEL:
But how do you know?
VERA:
Well, you see, I worked
for Lady Flintshire...
Ethel.
I hope you've offered
our visitor some tea?
I'll go and ask Daisy.
What is the first law
of service?
We do not discuss the business
of this house with strangers.
But she's not a stranger.
She's Mr. Bates's wife.
Has anyone told him
she's here?
So you're Anna.
I am.
You're the one
who went to call
on my late lamented
mother-in-law.
Yes, I did.
I know you did.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Vera.
I was up in the attic,
sorting out some cupboards.
Don't worry.
I've been having
a nice time here with Ethel
and Miss Smith.
Mr. Bates, Ethel told me
about your visitor,
so I've had the tea
put in my sitting room.
I thought you might take
Mrs. Bates in there.
That's very thoughtful.
It is.
But then, you're all so kind.
I'm beginning to understand
why my Batesy's got so spoiled.
I'm sorry to trouble you,
my lady.
What is it, Carson?
Something has been going on,
and I don't feel quite easy
that you've not been
made aware of it.
Goodness.
What is this dark secret?
Lady Sybil has spent the last
two days in the kitchens.
What?!
She asked Mrs. Patmore
for some cooking lessons.
MRS. PATMORE:
Now steady.
Even the most
experienced cook
can burn themself
if they're not careful.
Do you think it's ready?
I know it's ready.
Go on, you don't
want to spoil it.
It seems she's made a cake for
your ladyship, as a surprise.
But I'm uneasy with surprises
at the best of times.
And I wonder
if the whole exercise
is entirely appropriate.
Ta-da!
No, I'm not comfortable
with this, my lady.
I'm not comfortable at all.
CORA:
I was worried
about Lady Sybil,
but I'm not
worried anymore.
So you don't mind, my lady?
No.
I do not mind.
And I'm very grateful to you.
And Carson, the cake
will be a surprise
whether you approve or not,
so please don't give me away.
Sit down.
I don't want to sit down.
Suit yourself.
Look, I'm not saying
it's all your fault
for how things were
between us,
but I couldn't
go back to that.
I'll take the blame.
I'll go to some hotel
in Malton with a tart.
So why hold on?
Because I tried it on my own
and I don't like it.
You've got money now.
We'll be comfortable.
You're out of your mind.
What makes you think that
I would allow that to happen?
You went to prison
for me once.
I must say, this is very good.
Does Lord Grantham
have his own blend?
Is that all?
Not quite.
You see, if you don't
come back to me,
I'm going to the newspapers
with a cracking story.
And I'd like to bet the
Granthams won't survive it.
Oh?
And what nonsense is this?
The nonsense I heard
when I used your name
to get a job
with Lady Flintshire.
His lordship's cousin...
I know who Lady Flintshire is.
Well, when I arrived,
her maid asked me if it was true
about Lady Mary Crawley
and the Turkish diplomat.
They thought I'd know, you see.
Being your wife.
I hope you told them you knew
nothing about it.
(laughs)
Oh, as if.
I said, "Why don't you tell
me what you think you know,
and I'll tell you
if it's true?"
Goodness me, wasn't
my patience rewarded?
The public's bored
with the war, you see.
They like gossip,
and a diplomat dying
in the bed of an earl's
unmarried daughter?
Well, that takes the ticket
for the Tale of the Year.
It's a pack of lies!
I assume that's loyalty
and not ignorance?
Because you see, I heard
that Lady Mary needed her maid
to help her carry him.
And, yes, you've guessed it.
Your precious Anna's going
to figure in the story, too.
Not to worry too much.
It's not a criminal
offense, is it?
Just a social one.
You bitch!
Please.
Be my guest.
But then you must excuse me
while I run into town
and have it photographed.
What do you want from me?
Firstly, you'll hand
in your notice.
Tonight.
I'll put up at the pub
in the village.
And what reason do I give?
You don't need a reason.
Just tell them
that you're going.
Then tomorrow we
head back to London.
We'll stay in your mother's
house for the time being
'til we get ourselves sorted.
And in case you're wondering,
whatever my future plans
may be, they will involve you.
Bates, when you first came here,
I fought to keep you!
Everyone was
against me, everyone,
from her ladyship to Carson!
They thought I was mad!
But I said to them,
"After all that we've been
through together, Bates and I,
I owe him my loyalty!"
I appreciate that,
m'lord, but...
But what?
But loyalty doesn't
matter to you?
It does matter, m'lord.
Not enough to make you
change your mind!
Not even enough
to make you stay
until I've found
a replacement!
I can't.
You won't take any
more money off me.
You leave empty-handed!
I don't want money, m'lord.
I'm sorry, Bates.
That was a low shot.
Of course you can have
whatever is owing to you.
I thought we were friends,
that's all.
I thought we'd crossed
the great divide successfully.
Well, well.
I've had my say.
It's your life.
But you've
disappointed me, Bates.
I cannot remember being more
disappointed in any man.
ANNA:
I don't believe it.
You say my life is over
and your wife will collect you
first thing and that's it?
Have you mentioned this
to anyone else?
Only Mr. Carson
and Mrs. Hughes.
The others can find out
when I've gone.
I know you've not told me
the real reason.
You're wrong.
Vera has reminded me
that I'm a married man,
that I must give my vows
another chance.
I had no right
to involve you in my life.
Yes, but you see, that's
just what I don't agree with.
You had every right.
I know you.
You're doing
something gallant here.
Making a sacrifice
for my honor.
But I don't want you to.
I don't care.
Don't you understand?
I don't care what people say.
I'd live in sin with you.
Look, if she's threatening
to ruin me, then let her.
It's nothing to me.
The only ruin that I recognize
is to be without you!
Forget me and be happy, please.
I couldn't.
Not ever.
You should and you must.
I am nothing.
DAISY:
William?
I thought everyone
had gone up.
I'm just looking for that
magazine Ethel were reading.
I hope you've noticed I'm not
scared of electricity anymore.
Well, not much.
I couldn't touch a switch
when it were only upstairs,
but I've got used to it now.
I hate to see you
like this.
Even though I'm
a dirty coward?
You're not.
Not to me.
But why don't I enlist?
I could.
I know I promised my Dad
but he's not my owner,
he's not the law.
Am I frightened?
Is that it?
Honestly?
Don't be so hard
on yourself.
No one wants to go to war.
Oh, I wish you'd cheer up.
Please?
I'd do anything
to cheer you up.
Like what?
Like this.
You just feel sorry for me.
William, I've kissed you.
You've wanted me to
long enough.
Well, now I have.
Enjoy it.
Does this mean
you'll be my girl?
Daisy, because
if you were my girl,
I know I could
tackle anything.
(rumbling and explosions nearby)
But we were supposed to be
at rest for ten days at least.
The orders arrived
this morning, sir.
The King's Own were hit bad,
so they're out and we're in.
They've been shelling the
trench since we got here.
Anybody hurt?
Rankin's dead,
and Kent,
and Corporal Wright
was hit.
Thank God the stretcher
bearers were there.
Let's see
what the damage is now.
All right?
Morning, sir.
(heavy shelling continues)
Look out!
(explosion)
Thomas?
It is Thomas, isn't it?
Corporal Barrow now,
Mr. Crawley.
You'll never guess
where I've just been.
VIOLET:
Where's Anna?
She's not feeling very well
today, your ladyship.
I've taken over
for the time being.
Oh, that's so kind of you.
Just make sure Lady Sybil
packs things she can get
in and out of
without a maid.
Oh, I don't need that.
I'd never wear it.
But you must have
something decent.
Suppose you're invited
to dinner?
I know this is hard
for you to grasp,
but I'm not there
to go out to dinner.
I'm there to learn.
Take one.
Just in case.
We'll miss you.
Don't be silly.
It's only two months,
and I'll come
home if I can.
EDITH:
Why don't I drive you?
She's taking enough chance
with her life as it is.
Oh, Granny.
What is this driving mania?
EDITH:
It'll be useful.
They won't let a healthy man
drive us around for much longer.
And if Sybil can be a nurse,
why can't I be a chauffeur?
VIOLET:
Well, I shall leave you.
I have been summoned
by Cousin Isobel for tea.
Good-bye, Sybil,
and good luck with it all.
Thank you for being
such a sport.
It's a big step
you're taking, dear,
but war deals out
strange tasks.
Remember your
Great-Aunt Roberta.
What about her?
She loaded the guns at Lucknow.
CORA:
I'll come with you.
I'll tell William
to fetch the bags.
CORA:
The first of you
to leave the nest.
EDITH:
Poor Mama.
She always feels these things
so dreadfully.
That's her American blood.
I'm so glad we've settled
everything with Cousin Matthew.
Aren't you, Mary?
Oh, please stop treading
on eggshells.
I've other fish to fry.
I make no apology.
It would be a terrible thing
if poor old Mr. Molesley's
son were killed.
Wouldn't it, Molesley?
ISOBEL:
I'm sure it would, but...
VIOLET:
And then I heard
William's father
would be left on his own
if anything happened to the boy.
And what would
become of Carson
if the last of his staff
were to go?
That's not the point.
Do you want Molesley to die?
ISOBEL: Of course I don't!
VIOLET: Well...
I don't want my own son
to die, either.
But this is a war,
and we must
be in it together.
High and low, rich and poor.
There can be no
"special cases."
Because every man at the front
is a special case to someone.
CLARKSON:
Mrs. Crawley is right.
I understand your motives,
Lady Grantham,
and I do not
criticize them.
Thank you.
But I shall write
to the Ministry at once,
correcting
the misinformation.
Good day.
I'll see myself out.
Molesley, you understand
why I said what I did?
Indeed I do, ma'am.
You won't be called up at once.
Not while there are
younger men to be taken.
VIOLET:
But they'll get you
in the end, Molesley.
And you can blame Mrs. Crawley
when they do.
I wish you'd stop working
for one minute.
At least put the light on,
or you'll strain your eyes.
It's getting dark
so early now.
Has she gone?
She has.
So, we've lost Mr. Bates
and Lady Sybil in one day.
I can't believe it.
I suppose I'll have to look
after his lordship now,
on top of everything else.
And I don't want any jokes
about broomsticks
and sweeping the floor.
His lordship's got
his regimental dinner
in Richmond tonight.
That means he'll be
in the full fig.
You'll manage.
You know, when Mr. Bates
first came to this house,
I thought,
"He can never do the work."
But now I can't imagine
the place without him.
Did you see this coming?
Because I didn't.
I have a confession.
I let them have their tea
in my sitting room.
That was nice of you.
It was quite nice,
but I had my reasons.
There's a grating on the wall,
which means you can hear
what's being said in the room.
Now if I was a gentleman,
I wouldn't want to know.
But you're not.
Fortunately.
It'll be hard
to let you go.
My last link with home.
Not as hard as it is for me.
Branson...
I know I shouldn't say it, but I
can't keep it in any longer.
I wish you would.
I've told myself
and told myself
you're too far above me,
but things are changing.
When the war is over,
the world won't be the same
place as it was when it started.
And I'll make something
of myself, I promise.
I know you will.
Then bet on me.
And if your family casts you
off, it won't be forever.
They'll come around,
and until they do,
I promise to devote every waking
minute to your happiness.
I'm terribly flattered.
Don't say that.
Why not?
Because "flattered"
is a word posh people use
when they're getting
ready to say no.
That sounds more like you.
Please don't make fun of me.
No.
It's cost me all I've got
to say these things.
Right.
I'll go.
I'll hand in my notice
and I won't be there
when you get back.
No, don't do that.
I must.
They won't let me stay
when they've heard
what I've said.
They won't hear.
Not from me.
Bloody hell.
There must be more to life
than this.
You all right, Corporal?
I think so.
Yeah, more or less.
My God.
They won't believe it,
back home where I come from.
I thought, "Medical corps.
Not much danger there."
How wrong can one man be?
Here.
I think it comes down
to luck.
If the bullet's got your name on
it, there's nothing you can do.
If not,
then thank God
you were lucky...
Take these bodies away!
Come on, Corporal Barrow.
I cannot tell you how pleased
I am to be here tonight, sir.
Oh, we are very pleased
to have you here, Grantham.
You see, just to know
I'm with you all,
to sense that I belong here.
Well, it's as simple as this:
I no longer feel like a fraud.
Mr. Molesley?
What are you doing here?
I was waiting
to see you, Doctor.
How can I help?
It's just I was wondering
whether you'd written
that letter.
The one you spoke
of this afternoon.
To the War Office?
Not yet.
I'm sorry you were involved
in all that.
I should have checked with you
first before I interfered.
That's just it.
You see, I think if you
had checked with me,
you'd have found exactly
what Lady Grantham described.
I don't quite...
I have trouble
with my lungs.
I get so...
breathless sometimes, and...
I've noticed
it's getting worse.
They haven't written to William
yet-- the Ministry, I mean,
but they have discharged me.
Won't it just make
extra work for them
to have to fail me
all over again?
Very well.
I shall correct my statement
as regards William,
but make no mention of you.
Thank you, Doctor.
It's all right.
But Molesley...
I hope you will help the
war effort in other ways.
Yeah, of course.
When might the regiment
be wanted, sir?
The talk at dinner suggested
it would be soon?
Oh, pretty soon, I'd say.
Well, I'm as ready now
as I'll ever be.
For what?
To go to France
with the regiment.
Why would you do that?
Because I'm their
colonel, of course.
Well, there must be some
use for me over there.
My dear fellow.
We're not as heartless
as that!
The position is
only an honorary one.
Nobody expects you
to go to war.
An honorary one?
We thought it'd
cheer things up a bit
to have the Lord Lieutenant
at our table.
And so it does.
We're very glad
to welcome you here.
I see.
We old codgers have
our work cut out for us
keeping spirits
high at home.
Someone must.
Oh, indeed, sir.
Is that Taxi Cavendish?
I must catch him
before I go.
So Lady Sybil got off
all right in the end.
I'm afraid we have to admit
she knows what she wants.
Yes. She certainly does.
I don't suppose the war
will leave any of us alone
by the time it's done.
I'd a letter from Thomas
the other day.
He writes that when he thinks
about how things used to be,
it seems like a dream.
It's not much more
than two years ago,
but he says it might
as well be a century.
So you hear from Thomas.
Is he well?
Please give him my regards.
He's well enough, m'lady.
But I don't think
he'd mind coming home.
Oh, how I wish
he could, O'Brien.
Of course, if Bates hadn't
been so bloody selfish,
he would have let us plan
for his departure properly.
Your lordship,
I have information that
I have no proper claim to.
Well? What is it?
Well, if your lordship
can assure me
that you will keep it
to yourself?
I promise, Carson.
You can drop the last veil.
Well, I feel it
only right to tell you
that Mr. Bates's leaving
was not selfish.
Quite the reverse.
It felt selfish to me.
As for the wretched Anna,
bedizened with
dishonest promises.
Mr. Bates left because,
had he not done so,
his wife was planning to
engulf this house in scandal.
Scandal?
What scandal?
The point is, my lord,
Mrs. Bates would have
made Downton notorious.
The price of her silence
was her husband's return.
But I must know what story
she was planning to tell.
I'm sorry, my lord,
I could not speak of it
without injuring you
and betraying myself.
But you are saying
that Bates fell on his sword
to protect the reputation
of my family?
Ethel?
What are you doing?
Seeing to the plugs
for the night.
What?
Polishing the electric plugs
and checking them for vapors.
And why are you doing this?
Because you were too busy.
She said you usually did it,
but could I manage it tonight.
And "she," I take it,
would be Miss O'Brien?
Go to bed, Ethel.
And next time she gives you
an order, ask me first.
CORA:
Is anything the matter?
Nothing.
Except that today has shown me
I'm not only a worthless man,
but also a bad-tempered
and ungrateful one.
Well, we all know that.
Can I help?
I wonder how Sybil
is feeling.
The war's reaching its long
fingers into Downton
and scattering our chicks.
But I'm glad we made peace
with Matthew.
I agree.
Let us thank Sir Richard
Carlisle for distracting Mary
at just the right moment.
By the way, she wants him
to come and stay.
So we can all meet him.
She wants us to invite
a hawker of newspaper scandal
to stay as a guest
in this house?
It's lucky I have
a sense of irony.
(crying)
ANNA:
Not you, too.
What's the matter?
Why ask?
You don't care.
Ethel.
Perhaps if you stopped going on
about all the marvelous things
you're going to do
when you leave service.
But you've got
to have dreams.
Don't you have any dreams?
Of course I do.
Big dreams.
It's just that I know now
they won't be coming true.
(door opens)
What do you want?
I think I left
my book in here.
Is that all?
You were praying.
Don't be ridiculous.
What were you praying for?
Please go.
I'm tired.
(door closes)
Dear Lord, I don't pretend
to have much credit with you.
I'm not even sure
that you're there.
But if you are, and if I've ever
done anything good,
I beg you to keep him safe.
You look very comfortable
there, Corporal.
Would you like some, sir?
We've got condensed milk
and sugar.
I won't ask
how you managed that.
Go on, sir.
That's nectar.
Are you sure
you can spare it?
Gladly, if we can talk
about the old days
and forget about all this
for a minute or two.
Do you ever hear from anyone?
Oh, yes.
Miss O'Brien keeps me informed.
Lady Edith's driving.
Lady Sybil's training
as a nurse.
Miss O'Brien tells me
the hospital's busier than ever,
with the wounded coming in.
Is that true?
Certainly is.
They had a concert
when I was there,
to raise extra funds.
I'm curious, sir.
Do you think I could ever get
a transfer back to the hospital?
Seeing as it's war work?
Well, you'd have to be sent home
from the front first.
And then you might have
to pull a few strings.
Thank you for that.
Thank you very much.
What would my mother say?
Me entertaining the future
Earl of Grantham to tea.
War has a way of distinguishing
between the things that matter
and the things that don't.
(breathing nervously)
(yells in pain)
Thank you.
Thank you
for my deliverance.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org