Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Follow me.
Come on, you...
Can't get a shot.
Come on...
Come on.
There's a storm right now.
A hundred and sixty
miles per hour.
And we still
have gusts around 190.
So this area, this territory,
is certainly very much in danger.
Fifteen inches of rainfall possible
across parts of Puerto Rico.
And life-threatening mudslides
and really more flash flooding.
This is where we will see
the storm surge, storm winds...
There will certainly be damage.
The entire territory will
be absolutely under the control
of this category four,
maybe category five storm.
Shh.
You got something we want.
Walk normal.
You walk normal.
If you say anything
I'll shoot you
and the person next to you.
How can I help you?
Thank you.
He... he wouldn't even
tell me his name.
It was... it was arranged
through a third-party.
- I don't know anything...
- Calm down, calm down.
It's okay.
What's the address?
Here's Puerto Rico: 3.5
million Americans live there.
And here it comes,
right along the shore.
But San Juan is still
going to have winds
of 130 to 140 miles an hour.
There will be weeks
without power.
There may be weeks
without water.
I need to sit.
I need...
Please, I need to...
John. John.
Let's go.
Where's Babie?
The old prune panicked.
Babie was aborted.
Come on. Let's go.
Whoo.
- Hey, Pete.
- Hey.
Cardillo, I need the keys
to the prisoner holding cell.
Yes, sir.
There you go.
Mom make bail?
Cardillo!
- Wow. Yeah?
- This is Officer Pena.
She'll be assisting
with the evacs.
- Hey.
- Congratulations.
The two of you
will take the van.
You'll be scouring
every last motherfucking inch
- for anybody that's left.
- But...
You find 'em, you take 'em
to the safety shelters.
- I'm really looking forward to...
- That's not my job.
It is today.
Get your ass out there.
Good luck.
Okay. I'll wait for you outside.
Fuck.
Hey.
We're going to get you
those burgers, huh?
Hey, man. Do you mind
leaving some for the rest of us?
Excuse me?
You took all the meat.
Oh, God.
Come on, man.
Need just some meat for my kid.
What do you wanna do, man, huh?
You wanna fight me
in front of your kid?
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
That man just grabbed
a pack of ground beef
right out of my son's hand.
What?
What are you talking about?
Sir, I'm gonna have to take
your cart and ask you to leave.
Whoa, whoa!
Any advice?
About?
This precinct.
The residents.
Oh. Don't trust 'em.
But... that applies everywhere.
Not just the places, um,
don't speak the fucking language.
Oh, yeah?
Well, uh, I'm actually trying
to transfer into this house.
Or Rio Píedras, I don't know.
Something with more action.
- Yeah.
- It's slow as hell up in Zone Two.
That's why I volunteered today.
- Okay.
So how are we gonna play this?
Play what?
What if people refuse to leave?
Well, then they die
horrible fucking deaths.
But this good news is,
is it ain't our fault.
We're not picking anyone up.
- Yeah, but, uh, Lt. Cunningham said that we have to...
- Okay, okay, okay.
Let's just say that we go out
and we grab a guy, right?
He doesn't wanna leave.
He wants your name,
he wants your badge number
to file a complaint.
Yeah, let him.
I'm doing my job.
Oh, like, that matters?
You want a transfer
or a promotion,
and the bosses, they're gonna
look at your record, right?
Oh, see you got a complaint.
Could be bullshit.
Doesn't matter.
You wash your hands at the sink
and you get splash back,
it still looks like
you pissed yourself.
Okay. So we're doing nothing?
That's the idea.
Maybe we'll get
some donuts later.
10-52,
Plaza del mercado de Rio Píedras.
Don't.
Show sector Adam, Boy,
Charlie responding.
All right.
You insist.
All righty then.
What happened?
Um, he was trying to clear out
the meat section,
and he got into a fight
with a customer.
Mm... clear out
the meat section.
What, the entire section?
Is there a law against
how much meat I can buy?
Sure isn't, but how much meat
were you trying to buy?
Just for the record.
- A hundred pounds.
- Oh, wow.
- Quite the party.
- Yeah, that's a lot of meat.
- Yeah.
Uh, where's the victim?
Guy left.
Didn't wanna press charges.
All he wanted was to make
hamburgers for his little kid.
- Well, that's adorable.
- See, the guy didn't wanna press charges.
Y'all gonna let me go, right?
Yeah, well, you tell me what you need
all that meat for, I'll consider it.
Huh...
That... is a little suspicious.
Let's go.
- Y'all arresting me?
- No.
We're putting you
on a bus to a shelters.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait a minute.
- Y'all can't do that.
- No?
- I'm pretty sure we can.
- I have to stop past my place.
- Yeah?
- Yo, officer, I'm being serious.
- This is very important.
- No.
Are you just gonna give me
one-word answers?
- Maybe.
- All right. Let's go.
- You know what, fuck you.
- Oh, no.
- Fuck you, too.
- Oh, yeah?
- Fuck you.
- You walk...
Whoa!
That escalated quickly.
Yo, officer,
I got some people at my place
- that are refusing to leave.
- Yeah, who?
Well, there's this old guy
who never leaves.
And a cop.
One of you guys.
How do you know
they don't wanna leave?
Well, the old guy,
he never leaves.
And the cop was just bragging
about how he wasn't
going nowhere.
Look, I have a pet. That's why
I'm here at the supermarket.
- You have a pet?
- Yeah.
- What kind of pet?
- A hungry one.
Uh-huh. What's its name?
Her name is Janet.
Yeah, I don't... I don't like that.
Well, Janet doesn't like cops.
Look, guys...
Y'all can arrest me,
do whatever the hell you wanna do.
But I need to see her and get
her some water before the storm.
Please.
You said there's a cop
that won't leave?
Yeah.
All right.
Let's go feed your fuckin' cat.
That the super?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's him.
- What's your name?
- Luillo.
Alright, Louie Joe. This guy says you got
residents that are refusing to evacuate.
- That's right.
- He said you got a retired cop and an old guy.
- Old guy in 15E.
- And the cop?
Barrett, 53B.
All right, let's grab Barrett,
and then we'll swing back down
and grab the old guy, okay?
- Okay.
- You gonna let me feed Janet?
- What apartment you in?
- Thirty-three-B.
- Is that true?
- Yes.
All right, do it quick.
We'll grab you in five minutes, alright?
Fine. Gracias...
Does that say "out of order"?
- What is that?
- Si.
- Si. Si.
Perfect.
Alright.
You know,
you should learn some Spanish.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you're in Puerto Rico.
- That's how we say it. Puerto Rico.
Can you get them
to fuck off?
We're evacuating the building.
Thank God.
I need your help.
Look, even the PD's
taking this seriously.
Yeah, current PD's
full of pussies.
Care more about
liability and politics.
I'm staying here.
I'm not leaving.
I'm not going anywhere.
You gonna take that risk?
Well, Hurricane Irene
started like this,
came to nothing.
She wants to take me
to Centro Medico.
That third-rate shithole.
I mean, that's death depot.
We used to take OD cases there.
I don't recall seeing
any of them ever again.
Well, unfortunately, sir,
it's either that or the evac bus.
Excuse me, senorita.
You all right there?
You worked in Rio Píedras?
Yeah, I used to run that house.
Do I know you?
I know you.
'Cause I just put in
a transfer there.
Is that right?
Where do I know you from?
I know you.
- I know you from someplace.
- Uh... from this evac.
- Sir, can we get your stuff?
- Yeah, let's get going.
You're Cardillo.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, Cardillo.
You had that thing
about a year ago, right?
Yeah?
How'd it go down?
It got me down here.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not worried about it..
They catch the guy
that made the call?
Eventually, yeah.
Yeah?
Did you beat his ass?
- Dad...
- Did I what?
Did you beat his ass?
Hey, back in my day
we had this moron called
Willie Bosket.
He used to call the stationhouse
to report a rape or a robbery.
We'd all rush down there, the guy'd be
on the roof with a BB gun, sniping us.
About the third around we caught
him and broke a few fingers.
- Nice, Dad. That's real nice.
- Hey, it stopped him. Okay?
- Yep.
- Hey, the other cop, the partner.
That was your girl, right?
Troy, honey, uh, I think
I like my odds better here.
I'm a stubborn asshole,
she takes after me.
I'm standing right here,
you know what I mean?
Hey, what do you think
I got fuckin' Alzheimer's...?
It's a Category 5 fuckin' hurricane goin'
on outside, and you forgot about that.
You think it's a five already?
Hey, lay it out for me.
How did it go down?
Tell me.
Alright, I'm gonna go
grab the other old guy.
- Sir, I highly advise...
- Other old guy?
- ...that you go with your daughter.
- Yes, thank you.
Or in this case,
your guardian.
- Oh, a fuckin' comedian, yeah.
And it's only out
of respect for the badge
that you're not on a 51-50 hold,
face down on the ground,
- hog-tied and fuckin' cuffed...
- Whoa, whoa, hey!
What, you gonna shoot me, too?
Okay, you hear me,
you crazy old fuck?!
- Shut the fuck up!
- You cop-killing cocksucker!
- Hey!
- Where you goin?
- Where you goin'?
- You stay!
Yeah, and don't go
with that guy.
Not without a
bulletproof vest.
Honestly, you are
so fuckin' stubborn.
This guy's your fuckin' partner?
Yep.
You're a very brave girl.
Hey, hey! What are you...
What are you doing?
You're just gonna leave?
Your dad doesn't
wanna leave, ma'am.
I can't force him.
Isn't that what
you're here for?
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me
to carry him down?
Hey, you know what,
I don't care what you do.
He needs his dialysis machine,
but once the storm knocks
the power out in this building,
nothing's going to work.
No machine is gonna work.
I have a bed for him
reserved at the hospital,
but if we don't get there soon,
we lose it.
You really a doctor?
No, I just like wearing
pajamas all day.
Look, all I'm asking you to do,
is to go back in there with me,
and help me get him the fuck out
of this building.
Well, Officer Pena's
with him, okay.
She'll take him down.
He doesn't exactly respond
to female authority.
Alright.
You know this old guy, right?
Yeah, I've seen him around.
Do me a favor,
and help me with him.
And once we get him out
we'll come back up,
and we'll grab your father.
Okay?
Alright. Come on.
Around the corner to the left.
Down there.
Straight ahead.
This guy always have
this much security?
Not that I recall.
Sir?
Hello, sir, it's Troy Barrett.
You know my father, Ray.
Hello, sir.
What can I help you with?
You need to come with us, sir.
No, I cannot leave.
You're gonna be
flooded out here if you stay,
you're on the first floor.
It's too dangerous.
Has your father left?
We're gonna evacuate him
right after you.
Cardillo to Pena.
The sooner you come with me...
We're gonna get him,
we're gonna get everyone
safe out of the building.
Pena, are you there?
Cardillo, you copy?
Crickets, huh?
All your comms
are down in this shit.
Hey, listen, sweetheart.
You don't need to babysit me, okay.
So you ran Rio Píedras, huh?
Yeah, you're not leaving.
Okay.
Okay, you don't take a hint,
do ya?
I'll be clearer. You can go now.
Thank you. It's...
- So...
- I'm good, thank you.
I'm trying to transfer into that
house, but it's being held up.
So... you think
you can put in... a word for me?
Pena, do you copy?
I know it feels safer
to stay here,
but we gotta
get to higher ground.
You cannot park there!
I'm safer here, I'm safer here.
I'm not leaving.
I cannot leave my home.
Hey! Hey!
You can park back there.
Keep it moving!
Get out!
You cannot park there!
I'll take care of this.
What is it with the stubborn
bastards in this building?
- You have to come with us.
- I'm sorry, I'm not going.
Officer!
- Hold on just a second. I'll be right back.
- Okay.
- So you can go.
- No, this is an evacuation.
Please, just go.
They are closing the roads.
Please, keep going.
Come on, man.
Take it easy. Take it easy...
Let's go! Let's go!
We gotta go now!
- You alright?
- Why?
We've gotta go right now.
Come on! Come on!
Right now!
Okay. Come here.
Come on! Quick, quick!
Ernesto...
It's a fucking cop!
No, no, no. Don't shoot.
You might hit the old man.
Migs, you need to
catch up with them.
Top floor.
- Who the hell were those guys?
- I have no idea.
We have to
get back to my dad.
No, it's too far.
We won't make it.
They'll see us.
Well, then where are we going?
Up.
Come... Come on. Come on.
What are we gonna do
about the fucking cop?
Don't get excited.
They're trapped.
Those stairs only lead up
and the only exit
is on this floor.
Dillon, start your way on top
and work your way down.
Pride, Ernesto,
you two guard the front door.
Nobody gets in.
Nobody gets out.
Okay? Go.
Let's go.
Janet! I'm sorry, baby.
I'm coming.
I got caught up
in the supermarket.
Alright. Here we go.
I know, I know, I know, I know.
Open the door, right now!
Open the door.
I'll meet you downstairs.
Open the door, Griffin.
Griffin, open the door!
You gotta let us in, right now.
Fuck that!
How I know you're not
setting me up?
Back, back, back...
Griffin,
you think this is a trap?
I let you go earlier.
Listen, I've got Troy and your
downstairs neighbor here.
You don't understand right now. We are gonna
get our motherfuckin' heads blown off!
Open the door.
Shit.
We on the same side?
Hey, do me a favor, alright?
Put your ear to the door.
I'm gonna tell you something.
- Put your ear to the door!
- My ear's to the goddamn door!
Okay.
Open the fucking door!
Central, 10-13.
Shots fired.
Okay...
Who's killing who?
- Just quiet down. Be quiet.
- No you quiet down!
You in my house.
Shots fired at...
What's the address here?
- Six... sixty-five...
- Six-five-eight.
Six-five-eight...
Fuck! Land line.
I need a land line.
- Do you have a land line?
- Sorry, man, I didn't get the fuckin' bundle.
- Who the fuck's got a land line, man?
- Oh, fuck.
You know, you guys
bust into my place
without any consideration.
I don't give a fuck who shot who.
Super Louie Joe...
Well, he's super fucking dead,
okay!
Oh, shit!
Give me that bowl of food!
- What?
- Give me that bowl of food!
- What food?
- Give me the bowl of food!
- What?
- Give me that bowl of food!
Help!
- Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
- What?
Don't shoot.
Don't shoot?
Just bring me that bowl of food.
- What?
- Bring me the bowl of food!
It's right behind you.
Bring me the bowl of food.
Okay...
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
Stop, stop...
- What?
- Take off your uniform.
Take off my fucking uniform?
Yeah. She hates cops.
I trained her.
If you don't want her
to bite your fuckin' ass
take your uniform off.
Okay.
Tell me your story.
What do you mean?
What kind of story?
A Disney story.
What do you think?
I want your story.
Like your best collar.
If you want a rec,
you gotta gimme something to work with.
There was a warrant out on a murder
suspect about five months back.
I'm on patrol driving by the
Burger King off Avenida Ashford.
And see a guy
in the parking lot.
Six-two, 160, long hair.
We park and approach.
But as I'm getting closer,
I realize it's not the guy.
Slow. Nothing too quick.
Oh, my God.
Alright,
now you gonna grab my hand.
Alright.
And when I say,
pull me out as fast as you can.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
- Alright.
- Okay, here we go. Okay.
Go!
Close the door!
What the fuck is that?!
Oh, shit.
I lost them.
You lost them?
They gotta be somewhere
around in the building.
- There's no other way out.
- No. Shut the fuck up.
Alright? No excuses!
Okay? Go find them.
Now, go!
And that's your fucking pet?
Fucking got a killing machine
for a fucking service animal.
Okay, we got a problem.
What kinda
bedside manner talk is this?
"We got a problem."
You don't wanna ease me in?
Uh.. could really use a saw.
Yeah, this would be a great
point for an amputate.
No, you're not
cutting my leg off!
We didn't have time
to ease you in.
What do you need?
Uh, a splint
to secure the femur.
Anti-septic, penicillin,
gauze, stitches.
I know a doctor.
Congratulations.
He's here in the building.
- Dr. Berman.
- Yeah, what apartment? Where?
It's uh... 63B.
Shit...
Alright, I'll go get that stuff.
- Well, I'll come with you.
- No, no, you gotta stay here with him...
No, I'll come with you.
The sooner we take care of this,
the sooner I can
get back to my father.
Alright.
Hey, come over here.
Come here.
Come, I need your help.
I need you to take
both your hands
and apply pressure
to this wound, okay. Hard.
Talk to him, keep him awake.
It's just as important
as applying pressure
to the wound. You got it?
Okay.
- Griffin...
- Hm?
There any back stairs?
Alternate routes up?
There's only one set of stairs.
And the elevator,
but the elevator's out.
Yeah, of course it is.
But there's another way.
Scaffolding.
So... Oh, yeah... the guy
we're looking for has tats
and this guy's clean.
But something was off.
He looks nervous.
My radar starts going off
and that's when I see it.
What?
A giant bulge
sticking out of his...
- you know...
- What, his crotch? What?
No, his ass.
I see the top
of a plastic baggie
sticking out the top
of his pants.
I ask him what it is,
he goes nuts.
We cuff him, took him back
to the stationhouse,
and when we strip search him
we find 93 baggies
of crack cocaine.
Biggest narcotics collar
that month.
- Biggest.
- Wow.
So what you're telling me is you
stumble onto a narcotics collar,
oh, because some moron had a family-sized
baggie sticking out of his ass?
That's your best collar?
You didn't even have
probable cause.
- Never mind.
- No, you know, I'm just saying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They should be done by now.
I'm...
I'm gonna go check on them.
- Yeah...
- Yeah, you can do...
You can do, you know, whatever.
I'm such an asshole.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
So, two flights up
and three units over.
Yeah.
Are you a good shot?
Yeah, why?
Do me a favor.
If I fall, shoot me.
I don't wanna wait four-and-a-half
hours to die of a brain hemorrhage.
Yeah, what if I fall?
You're a hard-headed.
You'll survive.
- Ready?
- Blow it.
Watch it, sweetheart.
Take your hand
off your gun, slowly.
Hands in the air.
Where are they?
Where are who?
Your partner and the old man.
Follow me.
- I'll show you.
- Go.
Better not be fucking with me.
Come on.
Hey! You mind pointing
that gun somewhere else?
Hey, shut the fuck up.
Is this it?
This is it.
You go first.
If this is a fucking ambush,
I swear to God,
I will fucking kill you.
Hey, asshole!
Oh, yeah. Come on, now,
help me drag him inside.
He's a heavy motherfucker.
Yeah, come on.
Come on, buddy.
Boss!
Get down there.
I'll go check on Chaz, bro.
Don't worry.
She won't break through.
What's your name?
Paul.
Paul...
What's the accent?
German?
- German, yes.
- Mm-hm.
I'm Jason.
I'd offer to shake your hand,
but I really need you
to keep pushing down.
Of course.
Give me the gun.
Oh, shit.
Hey, it'll be okay.
Yeah...
They're on the fourth floor,
heading up.
- Where's Ernesto?
- He's dead.
Bigger splits
for the rest of us.
Ah...
You recognize the name?
Alexander Dillon.
No.
No, should I?
You want to work the good cases,
you gotta know the players.
- Who is he?
- He's part of a crew.
He does high end heist jobs:
jewelry, museums, armored trucks.
The shot caller's
a real psycho piece of shit.
Calls himself John the Baptist.
I got a buddy downtown,
a lieutenant I trained,
he works the major
crime zone three.
He's been chasing these clowns for a...
for a month.
You okay?
Are you alright?
Yeah. Hey...
Can you do me a favor?
Get my pills.
Oxy, oxy...
whatever the fuck you call it.
I can't pronounce it.
Uh, not that room.
The next door down.
That's my wife's art studio.
The next door down
is the bathroom.
So did you read the paper?
Today? No. No, why?
So this crew targets
this blue-haired old bag.
But the bop the old girl before
they could finish the job,
the greedy fuckers.
That was this guy Dillon?
It's empty, by the way.
Ah, yeah, thanks.
This guy? Yeah.
My buddy thinks
he's one of them, yeah.
I haven't worn this in 15 years.
What if it still fits?
What... what do you think
these guys want?
Yeah...
I might have a pretty good idea.
But if you're trying to make
an impression, now's the time.
Let's go.
- What apartment is this?
- 44B.
All right... up and two over.
She's this woman,
came into the hospital bunch of times.
Claimed cops used to hold her down
and inject rat blood in her eyes.
What? Roberta Gradischer?
- You know her?
- Oh, yeah.
Wait a second.
It was you.
Right? It was you.
That's what my father
was referring to downstairs.
Uh.. partially, yeah.
Oh, my God.
She used to say it was two cops.
- Smith...
- No, Smythe.
Smith and Smythe. Exactly.
Did you treat her?
After four times, I had to
give her an eye dropper.
Told her there was
holy water in it.
That's funny. She actually
brought that down to the lab.
She wanted us
to test it for rat poison.
See? She didn't trust me either.
She wanted me
to file a police report.
On me?
Wait... let me see that.
- Come here.
- Oh, it's not... It's not.
- Oh, it's fine.
Come here.
- It's a surface wound...
- Yeah, it's fine.
No, it was a police report...
It was for the commissioner.
Yeah, she, uh...
She thought that the police
commissioner was stealing her coupons.
No... shit.
She's fuckin' nuts.
You mind if I ask you something?
I mind if you ask permission.
You wanna ask something, just ask.
What the hell did you stay for?
I mean, you had to know
the storm was gonna be bad.
Right?
Do you know what
a fecal transplant is?
- A what?
- A fecal transplant.
It's exactly
what it sounds like.
Doctor takes someone else's
shit, puts it in your body.
- What the hell for?
- Yeah, right.
It's good for colitis,
or something.
Troy wants me to do that.
I also got
some other bullshit going on.
Kidneys, lungs...
They're fucked.
It's gonna kill me, eventually.
I'm on a million pills.
She takes me to the hospital,
it's over,
and I'm not going out that way.
Jackpot!
So you are or aren't
full of shit?
Shut the fuck up.
I ran out of my prescription.
- What's that?
- Oxy-moron. It's good for the pain.
- Want one?
- I'm good.
Okay.
Now I'm ready.
Let's go, smartass.
Okay.
- Wait, wait, wait...
- What?
- Where we going?
- Oh... apartment 44A.
Ex-DEA agent lives there.
He's armed to the teeth.
He's like a survivalist.
If we're gonna stand
any kinda chance at all,
we need all the firepower
we can get.
Remember, shoot to kill, kid.
I got your back.
You got mine, alright?
Here we go.
Get the fuck in.
Fuck.
Drop it.
Slowly.
Now toss it.
Come on.
Don't you move
or I'll blow your head off.
Where's the old man?
He's up my ass,
you wanna tickle his feet?
Come on.
Can't get a shot.
Wow! Oh, good. Come on.
- You shot me!
- Come on!
Come on!
I couldn't help it.
You were in the way.
Where the hell did they go?
Did you see?
You're kidding me.
I couldn't see anything.
You're supposed to be
my eyes, kid.
Okay, watch out.
Hey, hey! Don't.
I got a key.
Are you fucking kidding me?
This guy's a friendly.
I think it's this one.
Yeah, there you go.
Everything I told you, right?
Huh?
One-stop shopping,
ladies and gentlemen.
Holy shit.
Choose your weapon.
Take your pick.
You a Nazi?
You don't like people like me.
Oh, no, I...
I don't...
feel that way anymore.
I didn't think
there was no Nazis left.
I guess there gotta be some.
But they must be old as shit like your ass.
Can you hold this?
Bullet passed
straight to the calf.
Tibia, fibula clear.
Lucky me, huh?
No... I'm a good shot.
Yeah...
Yeah, one Thanksgiving,
my dad...
he went out and bought
a bunch of frozen turkeys.
Not for eating them.
But he brought them home to just
shoot the fuck out of them all.
Just filled those birds
up with lead.
Just...
Target practice.
And I was really excited,
'cause...
I always wanted to be a doctor.
And I loved it 'cause...
I got to pick all the bullets
out of the birds and...
stitch up all the holes.
Wow.
So what were you and my dad
really talking about downstairs?
Well...
I used to be on the detective
squad out in New York.
Real busy.
Never a down moment.
I loved it.
And, uh, I hear a call
for a gun run one night.
And, uh, I'm close,
like four blocks away.
I don't even hesitate.
Take it.
But I'm with Jasmine.
Uh, she's my, um...
I get it.
That's actually
just down the way from here.
Come on, baby, please...
She asked me
not to take the call.
Jasmine was a cop, too,
But I told her, you know,
stay in the car at home.
And to call for backup.
I'll take care of it.
So I go in there.
I see a barrel.
I amped up,
I squeeze the trigger...
And I'm just...
Jasmine.
Where was the guy with the gun?
There was no gun.
Hey!
- You call this in?
- Yeah.
You have any weapons?
I'm gonna search...
This asshole just
called in a fake gun run
'cause he figured that we were taking too
long to respond to his noise complaint.
That's not on you,
you know that.
I know.
But it happened to me,
you know.
I put her in that position.
I always said I'd never
hook up with a cop.
What, why?
Because of your father?
Yeah, I'm not really that
into kissing my dad, you know.
Well, daddy issues, huh?
He always wanted a boy.
Troy.
You really believe that?
You met him.
I did. Yeah.
He's a fucking asshole, but...
I also met you...
and I'm pretty sure
he doesn't think that.
Well done.
We'll have you back like
you've never been shot before.
God, you got the touch, Doc.
Alright.
- You're good.
- Thank you.
When we, uh, get out of here...
do you, um...
be open to...
you know, helping me
take these stitches out.
I'm gonna need 'em out for sure.
No, no, I'm... I'm serious.
Like, uh...
I'm... I'm very particular
when it comes to making sure
I get my stitches out
and all that.
- Oh, yeah.
- You know, needles and such.
Well, I am particularly
good at that.
I appreciate that.
Anytime.
Boss, you gotta see this.
Ah, that looks nice.
Nice Uzi, that's a good one.
Have one of these.
This could be handy.
I like this little baby, here.
Don't you want an M4,
maybe a shotgun?
Don't fucking move!
Whoa, okay.
So this is the spot?
Why, you asking us
or telling us?
I'm asking, fuck-face.
I'm just trying
to clarify is all.
Yes...
This is the spot.
Put your weapons on the floor.
All right, nice and slow now.
Make the man happy, sweetheart.
Arms... arms up.
Weapons on the floor, that's it.
Nice and calm now.
Okay.
Okay?
Ah, fuck. Fuck!
- Hey.
- Hey!
Nice fucking work, kid.
I think I got a spare hole here.
Yeah, fuck.
They opened me apart.
Yeah, help me up.
You lie down you die.
Help me up.
Okay. Okay.
It's empty!
It's fucking empty!
I know it's fucking empty!
Shut the fuck up!
Okay. The old man
knows where the art is.
We find the old man,
we find the art.
- Let's go.
You trained Janet
to attack the police?
Yeah.
Why?
I was walking home from work...
and two cops, they stop me.
Said I match a description
to this robbery.
I know what the description was.
Black male... 18 to 40s,
5'6'' to 6'8''.
I've been stopped like 20 times,
and I didn't commit any robbery.
I was sick of it.
So I kept walking.
Said a few choice words...
pushed off of them.
Next thing I knew
I was waking up in the hospital.
But I filed a notice of claim...
sued the city...
and got a big ass settlement
and I moved down here.
And I rescued Janet.
Feels like dirty money.
Like I took something
that ain't belong to me.
You know what I mean?
I do.
Okay, Ray...
Oh... Oh, that's a hole.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
it was my fucking fault.
I'm sorry.
I was trying to do something
to give us a shot.
Shut the fuck up!
Jesus.
You did what you had to do,
and you did good.
- So hold it, alright?
- I'm sorry.
If we get outta this,
I'll recommend you
for any damn unit you want.
Except Warrants. Fuck Warrants.
Wow. That hurts.
- Are you okay?
- Okay, let's go.
Okay...
We'll go floor by floor
until we find him.
What happened to them?
Well, he's not taking a nap.
Alright, you ready?
Not really, but,
hey, what else are we gonna do?
Where's my vest?
Fat lotta good that did, huh?
They don't make it big enough,
do they?
- Thank you, sweetheart.
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Okay...
Ray!
Get up! Now! Get up.
I'll shoot you in the fucking head.
Get up.
Get up!
Move!
Go in there.
In there.
Dad.
- Hey.
- Oh, shit.
Hi, sweetie. Hi.
I've been looking
for you two all over.
Where you been?
Hey, Cardillo, these clowns
are pretty heavy tooled up.
Be careful alright?
I'd appreciate it if you could
cap a couple of them, too.
Sons a bitch...
It's okay...
Hey, honey...
Honey, don't.
No, honey, stop.
- Relax.
- I have too many holes in me.
Just sit with me for a sec, huh?
Please, sit with me for a sec.
Good shooting.
I saw you down there.
Good work.
Hold my hand, darling.
Hold my hand.
Yeah, that's good.
Come here.
We gotta go.
Um...
I love you, Dad.
Hey...
Will you let me know
how it feels
for a bullet
to go through your skin...
and into your brain?
Why don't you go
and fuck yourself?
You know where your partner is?
How about the old man?
It was worth a shot.
Adam-Boy-Charlie.
Over. Do you copy?
Is it over?
We're in the eye of the storm.
Open up.
It's safe.
Alright.
We need weapons.
Guns, knives,
anything that kills.
Hey, we're in the fucking
same boat now, huh...
Yeah...
And your father?
It was getting real dark
in here for a minute.
Are you okay?
We should get out of here.
"Poppy Flowers."
Vincent Van Gogh,
$55 million.
It's here in this building.
Officer Cardillo.
This is Cardillo.
I'm here with your partner,
Officer Pena.
Is she okay?
Say hello.
I'm okay.
I'm okay, Cardillo.
I'm sure you can see,
we've hit a lull in the storm.
Which gives us about 15 minutes
to finish our business
and safely exit.
I would suggest
for Officer Pena's sake,
that you refrain
from calling for back-up.
Officer Cardillo...
I haven't called.
Then I'll keep this simple
for expediency.
I want you,
the old man and the art.
I can't finish this here.
- What is it?
- He's bleeding out.
I gotta get him to a hospital,
now.
Officer?
You can have me and the art...
but you have to release
Officer Pena.
That's so cliché. So cliché.
You know, I figured
you were the smart one.
Aww...
Come to apartment 44A.
Leave your guns.
If you're not here
in five minutes,
I'll execute your partner
and throw her out
the fucking window.
Don't make the same mistake
you made in New York.
How do you know about that?
I know everything.
I'm John the Baptist.
Where are they?
Where the fuck are they?
- I... I don't know.
- Don't you fucking lie to me.
They came here looking for you.
Did you hear what
he said they're gonna do?
They're gonna fucking kill Pena,
and then they're gonna
hunt us down.
This storm is gonna
start back up,
and then we're gonna be trapped.
They'll be shooting fish
in a fucking barrel.
They have been in my family
since the war.
- Are you a Nazi?
- No.
My father was.
And he passed
these paintings to me.
That's blood money.
Are they in the building?
Are they in
the fucking building?
Tell him!
Two minutes.
Here.
Take this.
- Why?
- You're gonna need it.
What about you?
We're gonna go on up there
and finish this.
- Okay.
- I know you know how to shoot.
You get out when you can.
Both of you.
Hey...
Don't take the scaffolding.
Yeah.
All right, buddy.
Let's go.
Okay.
Come on.
We gotta keep moving.
One minute.
Where is it?
- Let her go first.
- I don't think so.
Where is it?
C'mon, forward.
Open that door, slowly.
Slowly.
You moved it all in here, cool?
Ray was the only person
I trusted.
It's that way.
After you.
And if there's anything
other that art
on the other side
of that door...
Yeah, I know.
Go in.
Wow.
See that?
Don't!
Please...
take the paintings down.
Let me get the keys to your van.
- Oh, not my ride.
- Give me the keys to your van.
Take off your uniform.
I just met you.
Yeah, we're gonna get
a lot closer now.
Hey... Hey.
You got this?
Let's have a moment.
Contessa's back.
Are you satisfied?
Alright, shut the fuck up.
I don't know.
I love the duck room.
Decoys, right?
Decoys...
These are decoys?
Does that look like
a fucking masterpiece to you?
No...
You want the real shit?
Old man Nazi, fuck,
he hid them
in people's apartments.
Just hiding them...
right in plain sight.
Yeah...
Let's go find them.
Well, you got a way with words.
- I'll give you that, bro.
- Come.
- We're cool.
- Don't worry, I'm gonna let you shoot him.
Okay.
It's okay.
Come on!
Hurry up!
If there's water coming in
there's a way out.
Come on, let's do this.
Shit.
The old man talked
his way into all the apartments?
Yeah, he owned the building.
Not anymore.
Oh, my God.
This is the crown jewel.
"The Concert."
Johannes Vermeer.
Isabella Stewart Gardner
bought this painting
at an auction in Paris
in 1892 for $5,000.
And now it has an
estimated worth; 200 million.
Art sucks.
Take it down.
Hey. Carefully.
Okay. Okay.
Hey, look at me.
Look at me.
We're gonna be okay.
We're not gonna die.
- Okay.
- Okay?
There's gotta be a way
out of here.
Hey, hey. This...
Hold this light.
- What are you doing?
- I'm going down.
Point the light down.
I'm going to find a way out.
Okay.
One, two three.
Oh, shit.
What's in there?
I don't know.
Nothing.
That's a lot of locks
for nothing.
Open the door.
Hey, hey, hey.
Anything?
I got you.
Oh...
- Anything?
- I found it.
Take my... Take it.
- Okay.
- Okay. We're gonna get outta here.
Here we go.
One, two, three...
- Are you sure you wanna do this?
- Open it!
Alright.
Suit yourself.
Knock, knock.
How we holding up there, sir?
You doing alright?
I'm thankful to be alive.
Thank you, Doc.
Excuse me, sir.
Uh, I'm here to take a statement
on an incident that happened at an
apartment building not far from here.
Who woulda thought...
that I'd be this happy to see
a cop walk through them doors.
How'd you get out?
Well, uh...
I fed your cat
while you were out.
We have a 10-31 in progress.
- That's our cue.
- On our way.
Yeah. Hey, Doc, um,
do you wanna look at my leg?
Mm, we already played doctor,
didn't we?
Are you going to take
my stitches out?
You gonna take me out?
Bet your sweet ass I am.
I... I didn't mean it
like that, obviously
Respect to your,
like, workplace.
No pressure.
- No pressure.
- This is that moment...
- Yeah.
- ...where I'm gonna...
This can wait.
Yeah, of course.
- I would not... not...
- No.
- I don't wanna cross any lines.
- No. I know.
Okay. Can I...
If I beg you?
Alright. Let's go.
Rock me like a hurricane.
Hey...
- I got you something.
- Okay.
Fuck.
Now I gotta figure out
how to sell this shit.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org