Previously on Absentia...
Alice, what is this?
I'm pregnant.
Our whole life together,
it's just a consolation, isn't it?
I'm going to my sister's.
Jack, I need your help.
I had something in my hand...
Was it this?
Yeah. That's the key
to finding who had me.
Please, Jack.
They found six bodies
in those woods, Em! Six!
And you knew they were there. How?
_
The only way to stop it
is to do the experiment on someone else.
No, no! Please! Please, no!
That means you will be in charge
of adding the water to the tank.
I don't want to do this, please!
I hate you! I hate you! I hate you!
Easy. Easy, Charles.
Here's what I'm trying
to understand, Jack.
You helped us track her down,
and you're willing to
go to jail for her?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Jack Byrne, you're under arrest
for harboring a wanted fugitive.
Alice?!
Ma'am, I'm sorry but we really
need to ask you some questions.
- Ma'am, please?
- Maura, you've got to talk to the cops.
It's the only way we
can find your sister.
- Just try to relax.
- Maura, where are you going?
How could you let this happen?
Do you finally believe
it's Emily now, uh?
Or are you still standing by her side?
This is all your fault.
I'm... I'm... I'm gonna fix this.
Mr. Durand, they're
waiting for you outside.
Thank you.
Mr. Durand, do you have a statement?
What happened?
_
Hey...
what you got there?
_
I've stood here before...
as a... as an FBI agent, I've...
I've appealed to you for help
bringing criminals to justice.
I'm not speaking today, as an agent.
My family has been taken from me.
And I know the person
who has them, and I...
I... I know and I think
that she's listening now.
Emily...
Emily, I know you're hurting,
and what you went through, no-one...
no-one should have to go through,
but I beg of you don't take this
out on Alice and Flynn.
Remember who you used to be
and do the right thing.
Bring my wife
and our son home.
Please, bring them home. Thank you.
Transcribed & synced
by kinglouisxx & chamallow
Proofreading by PetaG
for www.addic7ed.com
Help!
Help! Help!
Flynn! Honey! Oh, my God, Flynn! Flynn!
Wake up!
- Flynn!
- Mom?
Get down!
- Mom, don't go!
- It's okay.
- Here, drink.
- I don't wanna...
- I wanna go home.
- I know you do, honey,
but we can't do that right now.
Please drink the water.
Come here.
- Where are we?
- I don't know.
- What is this place?
I know your father
is looking for us right now,
and he's gonna find us.
We just have to stay
strong 'til he gets here.
And then, this will all fade away,
just like waking up.
Can you hold 'til then, Flynn?
Can you stay strong for me?
Don't worry.
He's looking for us right this second.
Soon, this will all be over.
Jack Byrne, your bail's been posted.
You're free to go.
Watch your back out there.
Jack!
Do I know you?
You do now. I'm the one who
bailed you out. Laurie Colson.
Could we go some place
and talk for a moment?
Uh... yeah.
- There's a little place up here.
- Okay.
So, I've been following the case.
- Yeah, you and the rest of the country.
- No, not like them.
I think there's another side to
this story and no-one's telling it.
See, I believe your sister is innocent.
And I think I can help you.
Wait a second.
You're that reporter Emily stabbed,
- aren't you?
- Oh, uh... well...
What is this? Is this...
is this some kind of stunt?
No, wait, please, it's not a stunt.
Yes. Yes, I am that reporter,
but this... this was my fault.
- You know, I never should've been there.
- Okay.
You'll notice I never pressed charges,
- and believe me, I could have.
- So, what do you want?
To tell Emily's story.
With your help.
I want an exclusive with you, Jack.
I'll pay you back the bail.
No, forget about the money.
All I ask, is that you just take
some time to really consider it.
Mull it over... okay?
If it's still a no,
no hard feelings.
You know, if I gambled and
lost, then I can live with that.
But I'm betting that you
want someone to tell her side.
So,
anything you need,
okay? Anything at all,
call me.
_
We just got an ID on one of the bodies.
Hello?
Okay, forensics are
processing the bodies.
They say the remains have co-mingled,
but they've managed to ID the
body that Emily uncovered.
Doctor Lu-Fang Shen.
Our earliest records
show Shen working at MIT
followed by a position at Barrett House.
It's, er, short-term based
for foster kids, it was...
ended up functioning as an orphanage.
- That's Emily's orphanage.
- We need to look into it.
Well, it's defunct. Shut
down over a decade ago.
- Well, let's look for old employees.
- Dr. Shen has a brother.
Erik Shen.
Emily, it's me. They... they
arrested me, I couldn't call you.
- I'm... I'm sorry. I couldn't call you.
- Jack, Flynn's gone.
- They took him.
- I know, Em. I know.
And Nick thinks that I did it.
And now he's gonna be
wasting time looking for me...
- I know. Emily...
- Can't even turn myself in,
- 'cause no one's gonna believe me.
- Emily, listen to me.
This is why you need to find him
before it's too late, okay?
God, Jack, I'm so tired, man.
I'm so tired. I can't do this.
Emily... Emily. You have
to stay focused. Listen to me.
Now, tell me, what did you
find out about Shen?
Um...
Shen started experimenting on kids,
after he left MIT.
There's two of them,
from what I could find out but...
they were being tortured
the same way that I was.
One of them was a boy.
His name was Charles,
he was at my orphanage.
And the other one
was a subject "B".
I think one of them
might be holding Flynn.
Okay. So... is there anything
you need me to do?
I need to find Charles.
Eric Shen?
Yeah.
My name is Nick Durand, FBI,
this is Detective Gibbs.
We'd like to ask you a few questions.
I guess you guys are real thorough, huh?
I'm sorry, I don't know what you mean.
Was there anything in Lu-Fang's effects?
Anything to help the case?
We've never been here, Mr. Shen.
Not you, but the other agent.
She came the other day,
asking about my brother
and his research.
I gave her the key to my storage room.
Clear. Okay, let's get to work.
We need to find out what she was after.
Dad, Emily needs help.
Okay? I need your help.
Well...
Proud of you, son.
You are?
Everything you're doing for Emily,
everything you've done for me.
Of course, I'm proud of you.
I know you think I went hard on you.
- Dad...
- No, it's okay.
We can be honest.
Well, growing up, yeah, I...
I guess I felt, after Emily...
there was no space left
in the family for me.
You know, the love
and the attention went to her.
It doesn't matter now. It's in the past.
It does matter. Matters to me.
I never meant to make you feel that way.
You were always doing so well.
Emily, you remember how she was.
I guess I thought she needed it more.
- I need you to know how...
- Dad...
I know.
Okay, I got a plan.
- Flynn, wake up.
- What?
Here, take it. This one's not so moldy.
Boo!
Do you realize what a cliché you are?
At least I'm not in senior care.
How you doing, Irv?
I need a favor.
I'm busy, Warren.
Like you think the
pigeon's gonna miss you?
Come on, Irv. It's for Emily.
Heard about that.
You gonna help me?
Course, I'm gonna help you,
Warren. What do you need?
I gotta find a person. A kid actually.
Lost in the system?
Worse, sadly. You still have friends
in Family Services?
I do. If they're still alive.
- You gonna call 'em?
- Yeah.
- Well, when?
- When I finished feeding the bird.
Well, how long's that gonna take?
It's done when it's done, Warren.
Fuck!
Jack, talk to me. 'Cause I
can't do this anymore, man.
Everything I touch just goes wrong.
And now they got Flynn.
- Emily...
- And I just gotta sit here and hide
- like some kind of a fucking coward.
- Emily,
Dad's here. He has news.
Dad?
Emily, we have the lead
you're looking for.
- You found Charles?
- We found Charles. Last name Avallone.
He's in a mental facility.
Low security. But you'll need
to break in. It won't be easy.
I know.
I love you.
I love you too, Dad.
Help!
Help.
Mommy stop squeezing, it hurts.
Sorry. It's fine. Everything's fine
Please, no, no...
No.
This is not real.
This isn't real.
- Get some rest, Pop.
- Yeah, yeah.
His blood pressure's
never been this high.
If you want your father to stay healthy,
you need to keep his
stress to a minimum.
I understand. It won't happen again.
Jack, what are you doing here?
- I'm just visiting my father.
- I'm gonna tell you something, Jack.
Something that's gonna help us find her,
- because all of this is on you.
- I don't know anything.
Don't, don't, don't. Don't lie to me.
All of this is on you.
- Now, you realize that, don't you?
- Nick... I really don't know...
Stop! Stop! Stop lying to me!
You helped her, so she could
take my wife and my son.
- Her son. Her son.
- Jeez, she is sick.
- She's sick!
- No, she's hurt.
She is hurt, and you hurt
her. Don't you get that?!
She didn't take your family, Nick.
Deep down you know that's true.
Don't you think I want
to be on her side, Jack?
Don't you think that I want that?
But all of the evidence, all
of it, it all points to her.
So if you have some way that
is doesn't, just tell me.
Fine. I'll go talk to your father.
No. No, no. He's been
through enough. Nick! Nick!
Tell me where your daughter is.
You got a burner in here, uh?
You helping her?
You got some nerve coming in here!
My grandson and daughter are out there!
Why aren't you out there,
where a man should be?
You need to pick a side, Warren.
You need to pick a side. Your...
your daughter's or your grandson's.
You were never good enough for her.
She ran rings 'round you as an agent,
and she's running rings 'round you now.
And when she's cleared her
name and caught this killer,
she'll have made you
and the whole damn Bureau
look like the morons you are.
You're gonna want to hear this.
Do you know what will
happen to you if you disobey me?
- Bad things.
- What kind of bad things?
- Not breathing.
Who shall I hurt?
Shall I hurt B?
No.
Shall I hurt you?
Yes.
How many more of these are there?
Well, there's a whole box.
Most of them are damaged.
But this is the clearest one.
What do you make of all this?
You think Emily's one of those kids?
I mean, she's the right age, but...
I don't know. Let me...
Let me listen to that last part.
You are a brave boy. Repeat after me.
I'm brave.
You are my favorite boy, Charles.
Who shall I hurt?
You? Or her?
Do you want your mother to suffer?
Who will it be?
You... or her?
Do you want me to hurt her?
Hurt me.
You got anything on
the boy from the tape?
Well, the team is going
as fast as they can.
The orphanage was demolished
and replaced with a strip mall
and the records are over 35 years old,
and that's just the ones
that weren't destroyed.
Nick?
We're here. I'll report back.
What can I do for you, gentlemen?
We're the ones that
called about information
on former professor Lu-Fang Shen.
Have a sit.
As I told your colleague on the phone,
we simply don't keep records
of our professors'...
personal lives.
All I can give you is in here.
Yeah, we're looking for more
off the record information.
How long have you worked here?
Bill, is it?
21 years this April.
So you remember Shen.
Look, we're not looking to
get you in any trouble here.
I'm just trying to get my family back.
Your information could help save them.
I remember him.
He was a big problem for the university.
He conducted psychological
trials for research,
- and some of them are in the records.
- And some aren't.
What kind of experiments?
I don't know the details.
But I do recall that some students
filed complaints.
There were... adverse effects.
We shut it down.
So you swept it under the rug
to avoid a scandal?
Why did MIT hire him to begin with?
Hmm?
What did he specialize in?
What kind of work did he do?
Okay, there was...
One bit of scandal but...
Conspiracy theory if you ask me.
- What was it?
- Right.
He was rumored to be involved
in Government research programs.
Secret programs.
That's not uncommon with our institution.
- Yeah.
- Tell us about these rumors.
Flynn! Flynn!
Flynn!
Are you okay?
It's okay.
Why... Why are you wet?
Hey, it's okay.
Just tell me what happened?
He put me in a tank.
Did you see who it was?
No, but I... but I heard him.
- Was it anyone you know?
- I... I couldn't tell.
He made me hold my breath under water.
And that hurt.
He said that if I did it,
you wouldn't have to.
It's all right. You don't have to.
I'll call Nick.
Nick, we got a solid match.
There was a Charles at Barret House
during the target time frame.
Charles Avallone.
Sending you the details now.
He's at Edgewater psychiatric facility.
It's a 15-minute-drive from here.
Let's go.
Psst!
Hey!
Come here.
Hi.
Are you real?
No.
I didn't think so.
I like your robe.
I like candy.
Okay.
Hey! Hey!
Stop. Stop. Hey, you. Stop.
They didn't notice you, but I did.
You're not supposed to be here.
I have to tell everyone
we have a visitor.
Hey, everyone!
I'm looking for somebody...
Charles Avallone.
He's in here. Do you know him?
I know everyone.
So what's your name?
- Nick.
- Emily.
I'm sorry, are you Jenny's roommate?
Yeah.
I think she's having problems
with the bouncer outside.
Oh, shit. Okay, I'll be right back.
So, what's your name?
Nick.
Emily.
So does her roommate really
have trouble with the bouncer...
or are you just making that up?
Kind of cocky, aren't you?
I made it up.
Nice.
Do you like to dance, Nick?
- No. Really.
- No? Come on. Let's go.
We're close. Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm good, I'm fine.
Good. Keep sharp.
Finding Charles is easy.
He's in lock down.
In a dungeon. Behind the locked door
at the end of the hall.
But be careful. He hurts people.
He's very strong.
That guy has the key to the dungeon.
At medicine bell,
I'll make a distraction
and you'll steal the key.
We have to be really really quick.
I'm Agent Nick Durand,
need to speak with one of your patients,
Charles Avallone.
We'd also like all his records
and visitors logs.
You have approximately 8,4 minutes.
Bye!
Thank you.
What's going on?
Don't worry. It happens a lot.
Charles.
Charles, wait!
Charles!
Thank you.
You were mean to us.
You're a bad person!
You made us hurt.
I remember you.
Emily.
I'm sorry, Charles. I'm sorry.
I don't want to hurt you.
I just need to know what happened.
Did Dr. Shen hurt you?
- He was a bad man.
- Yes. Yes, he was.
Did he hurt anyone else?
I need to know what happened. Please!
We will never help you!
You are not good, you don't get help!
Did Dr. Shen hurt anyone else? Tell me!
Who was with you and Shen?
- B.
- Yes, B.
You were subject A.
The other child is subject B. Who is it?
B... B is for "Books". Give us our book.
No, stay with me!
Give me my book!
Charles, stay with me.
Who are you protecting?
Give us our book! We need our book!
- No.
- No!
Charles is out!
He's fighting a woman!
Help!
Help us out! He's fighting a woman!
He's fighting a woman! Help us out!
They're fighting! They're fighting!
Help! Help, they're fighting!
Charles is fighting with a woman!
Charles is fighting with a woman. Help.
Help!
Emily! Don't move!
Emily, don't make me do this.
Just tell me where they are.
Don't, don't, don't, don't.
I told you not to move.
Put your hands where I can see them.
Emily, put your hands
where I can see them, and turn around...
slowly.
Why are you doing this?
Can't you see you're hurting him?
How can you say that to me?
I am trying to save Flynn.
This is over.
I'm done believing you.
You need to let me go.
Put the gun down... now.
Transcribed & synced
by kinglouisxx & chamallow
Proofreading by PetaG
for www.addic7ed.com