Two new cases.
Nora's a widow. 80.
Acute renal failure.
She's choosing
not to do dialysis.
Joel has
an inoperable brain tumor.
I gave them both your number.
Joel?
You had sex with our target.
We arrest her. End of story.
Is this your mom's?
She's not a drug dealer.
She's a doctor.
Naomi collapsed onstage.
Honey, what did you take?
That stuff that was
in your shed.
Please don't tell my mom.
I fainted.
I think naomi's lying.
These bottles.
They were right here.
It's for casper.
He needs to be put down.
I need more pento.
Wanted to make sure
that you were using.
And that you weren't selling.
I, troy dixon,
choose to take my life.
Pentobarbital with champagne.
Okay, ladies, let's see this.
And up, down.
And up.
And four,
Three, two, one.
Let's just twist. Whoo!
Twist it out! Come on!
Shake 'em!
Whoo! Here we go!
Legs feeling better, nora? Much.
The swelling's gone down.
The water always helps.
Well, see you next friday.
Good-bye, edith.
Edward and I used to come here
every weekend.
We'd sit here
just where you two are right now.
And watch the birds.
How was your swim, nora?
It was lovely,
Just to be in the water
one last time.
And thank you
for accommodating me,
Meeting me here.
I know it's a risk, but this is
such a beautiful place to die.
A little risk makes life
exciting, doesn't it?
Do you have any questions
or concerns?
Anything on your mind?
You've been wonderful.
I'm just happy
to have this choice.
Edward was a scientist.
He always used to tell me,
Energy is not created
or destroyed.
It just is.
I believe every bit of him is
still around,
Just in a different form.
That's beautiful.
It's true.
She's gone.
I'm sure.
Never gonna let it go, are you?
See? This is how it should be.
Say good-bye when you're ready
in a place you love.
It should be, but it's not,
so let's skedaddle.
Someone will find her, right?
God, yeah.
One hour, this place will be.
Swarming with people.
She left us a tip.
$5 each. Classic grandma.
Aww.
What about joel?
What about him? Come on.
I was reviewing the journals
on gbm tumors last night,
And there are several
new treatment options.
My god, you had sex with him,
And now you think you two are
gonna live happily ever after.
He's dying.
And you are such a woman.
I'm not a woman. I'm a doctor.
I'm doing my due diligence.
Yeah, you are,
duly and diligently.
Mary.
Hi.
Hey.
Do you want anything?
The coffee here is... it's bad.
It's very bad.
I'm used to bad coffee.
You know, hospitals and all.
I used to work in a place like
this when I was in med school.
Covered my coffee,
covered my rent.
Really?
So no help from mom and dad?
No mom, no dad.
I'm sorry it took me a couple
days to get back to you.
But I still want to help.
Great.
I mean, that... that is great.
So, as you know,
glioblastoma progresses quickly.
Everything looks fine,
and then you get one bad cell.
And then it multiplies,
and it multiplies...
And it multiplies, yeah.
So, why are you telling me this?
Joel, the thing is,
people are working on it.
It's actually quite exciting.
And a friend of mine is doing
a clinical trial next month.
He's looking for candidates.
You're serious?
Yeah.
Jesus.
Now she's trying to save me.
Just roll with me, okay?
I'm gonna break her.
Joel, wait!
You'd be perfect
for one of these trials.
I mean, you're young.
You're strong.
You know, I've had
so much chemo and radiation...
Enough to kill everything
inside of me except the tumor...
In my brain, which is probably.
The only part of me
I ever really liked.
I'm only trying to help you.
You really think
there's something to fix, mary?
There's nothing to fix, okay?
I'm dying.
So, this... this whole thing
you're doing, it's...
It's mean.
Joel.
I need to ask you something,
mom.
What is it, love?
Can you make me
a grilled cheese sandwich?
'Cause I'm really hungry.
You little.
How you doing, yvonne?
No more hospitals.
No more treatments.
No more.
I want to... I want to go home.
Okay.
I'll speak to the doctor today
and try and get you discharged.
I can connect you with
the hospital's palliative care.
No.
Charlie, no.
Charlie, what is it?
My mom wants to know.
How much morphine
it would take to...
I'm sorry.
I can't tell you that.
I have someone
that I can refer you to.
An independent
end-of-life counselor.
Who can give you
further recommendations.
Just trust me.
This one's urgent.
Yvonne kowalchuk. Als.
It's bad. Late stages.
Well, end stages, really.
She was released this morning,
And her son's been
caring for her.
I quit.
It won't last.
You underestimate my willpower.
Um, how old is her son?
Charlie. 15.
And he understands?
He supports his mother's
decision wholeheartedly.
He's a great kid.
Nora.
Nora? I thought
this would be for joel.
Joel is still with us.
This isn't a same-day
delivery service, okay?
I haven't yet confirmed
he's a good candidate.
He's terminal. He wants to die.
I know, and he's exhibiting.
Highs and lows,
erratic behavior.
I just want to make sure
he knows what he wants.
Okay. Whatever.
But I am personally vouching
for yvonne, okay?
It is imminent, so, please,
no foreplay.
I promised charlie, all right?
So, you do have feelings.
Buried somewhere deep down,
yeah.
I'll see her later today.
Thank you.
Good luck with withdrawal.
Hello? - Dr. Harris.
I'm dr. Adrian carmichael.
I'm calling on behalf
of joel collins.
I understand
you're working with him.
Yes, joel came to eden general
seeking palliative care.
Yes, I know. He called me.
He told me that
you're pushing him.
Towards clinical trials.
Not pushing,
but I mentioned them, yes.
I want to make sure he's aware.
He is aware.
Look... We've treated his tumor
with aggressive radiation.
And chemo... the whole nine.
Okay, but did you ever discuss
a more radical treatment.
Like stem cell trials, osmrs?
I assure you.
We've tried everything.
I do hope that eden general can
accommodate his needs.
He's suffered enough.
You're right.
Thank you.
Good job.
Yeah!
I miss it, man.
I miss it.
As soon as my wife divorces me,
I'm going back to undercover.
All right, come on.
Wendy is great.
Yeah, wendy's standing
between me and my damn dreams.
Your dreams?
Yeah.
You ever see
those heated driveways?
No, I...
Melts the snow right off.
Well, I want one, bad.
But wendy thinks
it's frivolous, unnecessary.
Yeah, that's because I'm the one.
That's shoveling
the damn driveway.
Every time it snows.
You need better dreams, my man.
I bet you know almost every
entry in that journal by now.
Yeah, almost.
You spoken to his father yet?
Not since the first meeting.
But he's coming in tonight
for a debrief.
I want to deliver.
Tonight?
He's a judge. He's a busy man.
Man.
Hey, when you get mary,
and you will,
You need her to tell you
exactly what she's going to do...
An incriminating statement
that will hold up in court.
I know, man.
I've done it before.
All right, good.
Just go give her
those puppy dog eyes,
Get this bitch to kill you.
Jumpy.
Hey, we're packed
to go to dad's.
You guys have any fun plans
tonight?
Whee! Shoes on the bed!
Me and naomi are going
to tristan's.
He's having some people over.
Naomi and i.
Me and naomi.
How is she?
She's telling everybody
at school.
She had a near-death experience.
What's a near-death experience?
It's just a way
of getting attention.
You know, if anything happens
again with her,
You can come to me, right?
Yeah.
Hey, mama?
Yeah? Where's casper?
Put those in the bin. Thank you!
Whoa, you okay? Yep, I got it.
Hey, mary. Hi.
Naomi, how you feeling?
You know, still breathing.
You know you can take that off.
Yeah, I know.
I just kind of like it.
Our cat is dead.
No.
I wanted to wait a little bit.
Before I told her,
but she asked, so...
Hey. What's going on?
Casper died.
Really?
But he was only, what? Seven?
Cancer. It was all over.
I had to, um, put him down.
I think you did the right thing.
You know,
when they're suffering,
It's the only option.
Can I have ice cream
since I'm sad?
Give me a hug. Of course.
Love you. Bye.
I'm sorry.
God, I loved that dumb cat.
You should've told me.
He's in a better place now.
I have to get that.
Hey.
Um...
You're late
on your child support.
I just gave you two grand
in cash.
Right.
But when am I getting the rest?
I'll bring it
when I pick up the girls.
Yeah?
Are you on your way to yvonne's?
Yeah. Leaving in five.
Okay. I'm heading there now.
Hey, des, never get married.
You're the only woman
I want in my life permanently,
Which is why I keep rejecting
your sexual advances.
I have another call
I have to take.
I'll... I'll meet you there.
Hi, joel.
I'm sorry about earlier.
You said don't buy a gun.
What? You said don't buy a gun.
You said that you would help me.
I want to help you. I do.
You know what? It's fine.
It's fine. I got this.
Good-bye, mary.
Joel!
What are you doing?
What I should've done
in the first place.
You don't want to do this.
Yes, I do.
Not like this.
You should help me.
I'll help you.
You can lie down.
Thanks.
The money.
I don't want it.
Why?
I just don't.
What am I gonna do with it?
Please take it.
Come on, I don't want charity.
Please. Please.
What medications are you taking?
Carbamazepine. Anti-seizure.
When did you take
your last dose?
This morning.
Is there anyone
you want to say good-bye to?
Do you want to take a moment.
Or make any phone calls?
No.
Can you tell me again?
Tell you what?
Tell me how you're gonna do it.
What do you mean?
How you're gonna kill me.
I mean, I know you... you told me
how they do it in switzerland,
But just... i really want to hear
how you're gonna do it.
I need to wash my hands.
Yeah, the sink's right there.
Where's your bathroom?
Down the hall.
So, you took carbamazepine
this morning?
Yeah.
Can I see the bottle?
I need to know
what I'm working with.
I threw it out this morning.
I thought it was my last dose.
I need to get your file.
It's in my car.
Why do you have to get my file?
I need to confirm
your medication.
Maybe you could take a moment.
To think about what
you're grateful for...
All the good things in life.
You're gonna need a drink,
so why don't you.
Grab a beer from the fridge?
I'll be right back.
I've been waiting half an hour.
Des, he's a cop!
Who? - Joel!
I'm at his apartment right now.
I almost killed him.
How the hell do they know?
You think it's your nurse?
Never. She would never do that.
Look. I'm leaving now.
But we can't do yvonne.
Not tonight.
So go in, make nice,
and tell her.
We'll be back next week.
Get out, now.
.Yeah, talk fast.
She's by her car.
Can't see what she's doing.
I'm going in.
No. No, no, no. I'm coming down.
I'm coming down.
Mary! Hey! Hey!
God.
Hey. What are you doing?
So, did you think about it?
Think... think about what?
What you're grateful for.
Yes.
Yes. I'm grateful for you.
Here.
Joel, listen to me.
You're obviously upset
and struggling.
But, you know, to be honest,
you kind of scare me.
Why do I scare you?
I wanted to help you
and counsel you,
But the gun,
the erratic behavior, i...
I just don't feel safe.
I have to go now.
No, please don't go.
Just take the money.
Please. Mary.
Mary!
Things w-
She knows.
Nah. She likes you better alive.
This is gonna be
a hell of a debrief.
Yeah, what time
are we meeting judge grant?
He's waiting for us now.
And the second I turn 18,
I'm gonna move to new york.
Yeah?
Hey, so, we said
we'd be home an hour ago.
We should probably...
It's fine.
They haven't even called us yet.
It's fine. It's fine.
So, have you seen that movie
"cabaret"?
No. You've seen that movie.
Of course you've seen
that movie.
Well,
I'm gonna be just like them.
Yeah.
Dancing and singing for money.
I get it. Yeah.
You're gonna be a star. Right?
Yeah.
Okay.
What are you doing?
It's cocaine.
Stole it from my dad.
You want some?
No, I don't. I do.
Hey, naomi,
you were just in the hospital.
You had a...
You had a really bad night.
What does it feel like?
It makes you feel
like you're a star.
Okay. Okay?
That's...
I don't want to wake her.
She doesn't sleep much
these days.
That's okay. I understand.
The thing is, charlie,
we have a bit of a situation.
My mom wanted me
to show you this.
I've had a blessed life.
I have my beautiful boy,
charlie.
And when this is all over,
he'll go live with his dad,
And maybe he'll even get
a better haircut.
I've lived exactly the life
I wanted to live.
When it's time,
I want the choice to die...
The way I want to die.
How much is it again?
Charlie, we...
I'm afraid we're gonna have to
postpone your mom's appointment.
I don't get it.
We can't help your mom.
Not today.
Annie said you'd do it today.
She made a mistake.
But mom's ready. I'm ready!
I know. I know.
I'm... I'm sorry.
What?
Hey. Hey, don't leave.
I'm sorry, charlie.
I said don't leave!
How'd it go with yvonne?
Not great.
I'm here with charlie now,
And he's...
He's pointing a gun at my head.
What? It's a small gun,
But it's still a... a gun,
nonetheless.
Tell her to come over. Please.
He said he wants you
to come over.
Annie promised.
She said you'd help us tonight,
So you're gonna help us tonight.
He said we're gonna help him...
I heard.
What's she saying?
She said, "."
My mom can't breathe.
She can't even move.
You have to help her.
Guys, I had to get rid
of the pento.
What? What?
What is it?
Charlie,
we don't have the drugs.
Stop messing with me.
I'm not, all right?
So you can stop
pointing the gun at me.
I'm gonna leave now.
Okay? Don't go.
Easy. I said don't go!
Please don't go!
Aah!
Everything's all right, mom.
It's okay.
Des? Des!
Des, are you okay?
I'm so sorry.
I didn't think it was loaded.
I... i've never even
held it before, i...
My god, des, say something!
Get me a towel!
Shoulder wound.
I'd call it a graze,
but it hurts like hell.
You said it was a graze.
Is that true? Is that right?
Yeah, sure.
Please. I have no one else.
I really think
we need to help charlie.
Okay, um, des,
You need to give me the name
of your dealer.
That's a bad idea.
You know another way
to get pento on short notice?
All right.
His name's grady.
I'll send you his address,
let him know you're coming.
Mary...
Mary, he's not a good person.
I can handle it.
Send the address.
Hi.
I'm mary, des's friend.
Hi, mary.
Can you take your shirt off?
Are you kidding?
No. I'm not the one laughing.
I'm not taking off my shirt.
Mary, in my business,
if I sell to the wrong client,
Then they make me live in a cage
for 20 years.
So, your politeness
and your modesty.
Is not a high priority for me.
You don't need to trust me
to take my money.
Take your shirt off, mary.
Happy? Yeah.
Of course.
I have a very good life.
And I'm very happy
that you're not wearing a wire.
You don't have track marks.
The pento's not for me.
It's for des.
I just gave him a full box
the other day.
He lost it.
He lost it?
Can I buy more from you?
I mean, that's what you do,
right?
Do you have any kids?
I really have to get back
to des.
He's in rough shape.
I have this little
step-niece, maya.
She's six.
She's sleeping over.
And she just plays.
Color for hours.
Love that kid.
She's the cutest little thing.
You're kind of cute too.
You look good.
Sid,
Would you get dr. Mary harris
of 228 maple drive.
What she came here for tonight?
You can count it if you want.
Nah, we're good.
Hey, mary?
Smile.
Judge grant,
sorry to keep you waiting.
I don't mind waiting
if it's for a good reason.
"Joel" just met with dr. Harris.
And? We're close.
Close?
I don't understand how it is.
That you guys don't have
enough evidence.
Aren't these meetings
being recorded?
Yes, but unfortunately
we don't have.
Anything incriminating
on tape as yet.
The... the suspect's working
under the pretense.
Of being some kind
of end-of-life counselor.
What about the nurse
ethan mentioned in his journal?
Annie chung. Works in the
intensive care at eden general.
The nurse is
just the liaison, sir.
I mean, she connects
the patients to dr. Harris.
We burn her,
we burn the whole operation.
Sir, look.
We know this is difficult,
But the best way
to bring dr. Harris down is.
To catch her in the act.
Gentlemen,
my son had another year.
He could've done
a clinical trial.
a million things.
What he could not have done was.
Give consent,
which makes this murder.
I assure you, sir,
If dr. Harris helped your son
die, we will prove it.
Good.
Charlie!
Gonna need another towel.
Look at that.
Does it hurt?
No. It feels lovely.
Seriously, I-i didn't mean to.
Shoot me? Yeah, funny, that.
And yet here we are.
There's probably a lesson
about guns.
Embedded in all of this,
charlie?
My mom got the gun
after my dad left,
Said it made her feel safer
at night.
She's close.
How can you tell?
I was a doctor, too, charlie.
Well, plastic surgeon.
It was all very pleasant.
Until I did something stupid.
And they took my license away.
Thank christ.
Charlie.
It's okay.
It's all gonna be okay.
Can I come in?
I got it, I got it, I'm fine.
Let's just do this and get out,
okay?
She can't swallow.
This is our first injection.
It's not quite
how I pictured it.
What are you doing?
It's her favorite song.
Jeez. Des.
You ready to do this, or what?
I love you, mom.
I want it to be peaceful.
It will be.
Like slipping into a dream
at the end of a long day.
I promise.
You got lucky.
Yeah. That's exactly how I feel.
Our last job.
At least we went out
with a bang.
Our last job? Well, I assumed,
Since your gentleman turned out
to be an officer.
Standing there with charlie
tonight, des,
I know what it feels to be him.
I know. Except in my case,
There was no one there
willing to help.
Listen to me.
Right now,
they don't have anything on us.
So we just need to be smarter.
You know what?
I had a few ideas
while I was bleeding to death.
Aging baby boomers are
gonna want to die.
In the same manner.
Bourgeois comfort.
Now, the swiss, they know that.
That's why death tourism's such
a massive business over there.
And? And we should be starting.
To buy up property,
getting ready to go legit.
I'm serious.
I'm having a...
An entrepreneurial seizure here.
Let's be a...
A start-up for shutting down.
"The spa you'll never
want to leave...
And you won't."
Des... if you're traveling.
The river styx,
why not take a yacht?
Where's the cat?
I think I might have...
Left the window open.
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
But there's a reason I've never
been responsible for anyone.
Or anything else.
Except for lives, as a doctor.
Yeah, look how that turned out.
Well, it's a long way to fall.
Why did you do that?
I'm mad at you.
My god, don't be mad at me.
I hate it when you're mad at me.
Where'd you go last night?
I looked for you,
and you were gone.
Yeah, I left,
Because watching you
be a train wreck.
Is just really, really tedious,
so I...
God, seriously,
The cocaine wasn't even
that good.
I mean, all that happened was,
like, everything sped up,
And my heart...
Come here. Feel my heart.
Yeah.
You... you didn't faint.
That other night
at our recital, did you?
What?
You took the... the stuff
from my mom's shed, right?
I'm sorry.
I'm an idiot. I'm an idiot!
You know, I think there's
something wrong with my brain.
I...
Don't tell anyone
about the drugs, okay?
Seriously,
my mom will send me away,
And I'll never see you again.
Jess? Please?
Yeah. I won't...
If you stop.
God, you sound like your mom.
What do you mean,
I sound like my mom?
At the hospital...
I told her I took her drugs
from the shed,
And she said
she wouldn't tell anyone.
If I cleaned up my act.
Wait, she knew about it?
Yeah.
And she totally covered
for me, too.
I'm hungry. I want breakfast.
Hello?
I, um, my name's carly dixon.
I think you might know...
Or knew... my husband,
Troy dixon.
I found your number
on this pamphlet.
Are you there?
Mary. Joel.
No. Wait. You're not, are you?
Not what?
You're not joel.
Ben.
Still mary.
I liked you better as joel.
You liked me better dying?
Do you think I'm a criminal?
What you're doing is
very illegal.
What's illegal?
Talking to people about options?
About switzerland? About death?
If that's illegal, arrest me.
If you think I'm a criminal,
arrest me.
You don't get to play god, mary.
None of us do.
I don't know
what to tell you, ben.
You got the wrong girl.