Do it.
I'm sorry.
I'll do the time.
You drive me to the police
station right now.
- It's too late.
- I have to go now.
I think you and Des
have a little side business.
I want a cut.
Everything's my fault
even though
I'm the one who told you
to stay away from Grady!
I told you he came after my kid!
I couldn't live with myself
if I made a decision
based on something he said
in a moment of fear.
What should I do?
You think Grant is the son of
Lucas Grant, Judge Lucas Grant.
He could have done
a clinical trial.
He could've done
a million things.
What he could not have done
was give consent.
She's going to say
you had sex, Ben.
And no one is gonna believe her
if we get rid of the tape.
I was born sick, born broken.
So I met with Morgan.
He wants to wave the white flag.
- Am I under arrest?
- Let's go.
He wears a wire,
gathers evidence
against his partner.
We offer him immunity.
We will get back to you.
Mary Mitchell,
now known as Mary Harris,
was investigated
for the murder of her mother.
Her mother was found dead
in Chalk Lake
with her hands tied together.
Man, you don't know
who this woman is.
She's been involved in the death
of God knows how many people.
Am I crazy like Mom?
Why are you doing this?
What?
Saving people
a trip to Switzerland.
I believe
we should be in control
of our life and our death.
That's liberty.
And dying isn't a crime.
But helping people die
makes you a criminal.
You think so?
I mean... yeah.
Is there a long answer?
I should've come forward sooner.
I know that now.
I'd like to explain.
I'm a doctor.
My patient was suffering.
I couldn't just stand by
and do nothing.
God, you don't seem sick.
I'm sorry.
I meant that as compliment.
I was acting on instinct.
The last time I examined Sid,
his anxiety
was through the roof,
convinced whoever shot him
would finish the job,
even with the cops there.
So I thought if transferring
him to a room
made him feel
more secure, then...
Do you know
which porter transferred him?
The one in the gray scrubs.
You know how it is.
I just grabbed
the first one I saw.
I really just wanted
to help him.
The disappearance
of Sid Thomas-Haye
has caused a major
shit-storm around here.
The cops are all over me.
They still haven't found him?
No, but hopefully
the security footage
will get the cops off my back.
Security footage?
Yes, Dr. Taylor
saw an SUV speeding away
from the hospital.
Hopefully when they review
those street cams,
they will find that car.
Well, let me know if I can
do anything more to help.
Will do.
Dr. Harris and I have
an appointment today, 1:00.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm just surprised
he took the deal, that's all.
Well, believe it or not,
there are men who can
resist Mary's charms.
I'm just saying that
he and Mary seem pretty tight.
Yeah, well, you and I
are pretty tight,
but I'd wear a wire on your ass
to avoid a murder rap.
All right, what time
is this meeting?
Desmond said 1:00,
and you know if we're late,
someone's gonna die.
Yeah.
- Mary, Mary.
- This isn't a good time.
No, no, I need your advice.
I need your help.
What?
The Danvers woman
has asked me to pray.
- Pray with her.
- I'm not gonna do that.
I'm a man of medicine, Mary,
you know, science, reality.
- So what's reality?
- Well, he's out of options.
He's mechanically alive.
What about more surgery?
He's not strong enough for that.
- Tell her that.
- You know what I think?
There should be a rule.
I know, against asking doctors
to pray in a hospital.
Well, Dennis,
you have two options.
You can grow some balls
and tell Sonia
to pull the plug on her husband
or you can get on your
goddamn knees and pray.
- Mary, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
I have to go.
Here's a riddle.
What has a gunshot wound,
wears a hospital gown,
and can barely walk by himself?
I don't know.
Maybe Prentice and Hall
have seen him.
- That's not even a riddle.
- You're right.
It's a joke.
Ignore them.
Check this out.
There's an SUV.
It's a Yukon XL.
Can't see anything.
How do we know if it's Sid?
We run the plates, get a name,
and start asking questions.
God, you're so new.
Sid Thomas-Haye.
What about him?
Ellen hauled me in her office
to ask me all sorts of questions
since he was transferred
to my ward by you.
- What did you tell her?
- The truth.
You should try it sometime.
Did you have anything to do
with that guy's disappearance?
Yes.
Annie, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean
to get you involved,
but I've got it
all under control, I promise.
You promised when we started
this that everything
was going to be fine.
It is so not fine.
You are being followed
by the police,
and now you're helping somebody
escape police custody.
I don't even know
what this has become.
- You don't understand.
- I didn't have a choice.
Well, I do.
I quit.
- Annie, wait.
- No.
We are going to get caught.
And I cannot get caught.
My clothes were strangling me.
Is "Ben" short for something?
Benjamin. Benedict.
Benvolio.
You mind telling me why
your pupils are so pinned?
It's because
my future's so bright.
What do you want?
She likes you, you know.
You really think getting high
is gonna make this any easier?
The first person she's been with
since her marriage ended.
Really?
How are you going
to live with yourself?
I'm thinking
I'll inject narcotics
into my veins on the regular.
What's your plan, Benvolio?
My plan, my plan, Desmond,
is, I am just doing my job.
Throw yourself into the work.
That's a good, solid plan.
But it's the same thing, really.
The drugs, the law...
it's all just an attempt
to control the chaos.
You ever think Mary's the one
that creates the chaos?
Yeah, she's good at that.
But if you know her, then you
know that it's worth it, right?
The thing is, I don't know her.
What I do know is that
she's out of control,
and this is the only
way she'll stop.
This is gonna break her heart.
Say something.
Hail Mary,
full of grace...
Sing along with me, Benvolio.
My...
- It can't be.
- Hi, Mama.
Um, you're kind of hurting me.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I lost my math book.
Can you go check
under your bed, please.
Kevin, what the hell?
How many times have I told you
you can't just come in here
whenever you feel like it?
Cambie needed her math book...
This is not your house anymore.
I should be able to come home
and not worry if someone's
gonna be here or not.
Okay, fine.
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, come here.
It's okay, come here, come here.
It's okay.
It's okay. I got it.
Shh, Mary.
Mary, Mary.
- I'm sorry.
- You should take your key back.
- Found it. Bye, Mama.
- Good.
Wait, wait.
Okay, okay, Mom.
Little face, I love you.
Mary, hey.
You really need
to get some rest.
All right?
I'm sorry about what
I said the other day.
It's fine.
I just lost it on Kevin, too.
Why?
I don't know.
I guess it's all getting to me.
You know what's weird too?
I keep thinking about Ben,
like, wanting to talk to him.
- Ben the cop.
- Yeah, Ben the cop.
And it's crazy
given the circumstances,
but I really...
thought there was
something there,
but maybe it was
just the great sex.
It wasn't that great.
Saw it.
What, it was like 30 seconds?
It's impossible. I mean...
Yeah, it's impossible.
Yeah, it's impossible because
you're going to jail, Mary.
You can't move forward, right?
You can't get anywhere
without trust.
Trust no one, that's what I say.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing, I'm fine. I'm good.
You're high, God.
- Mary...
- Shit.
I told you she'd notice.
She's a doctor.
Don't lie to me, asshole.
You're high.
Lie to her, asshole.
Fine, fine, I slipped up, okay?
Not okay. When did this happen?
Today. I'm...
I'm an idiot. I'm sorry.
Why? What triggered it?
I'm an addict.
I don't need a trigger.
Everything's a... a trigger.
Is it because of what I said?
Jesus, Des, I didn't mean
to blame you.
I was just scared. I...
It's not your fault.
- She's gonna call it off.
- No, she loves it too much.
She's not calling it off
and neither are we.
Hey, it's a disease.
It's a process.
Slips are part of recovery.
That's what they say, right?
Des, I need you.
You're the only person
in my corner right now.
If you lose it, I'll lose it.
After Morgan,
we'll figure this out.
Hi, Des. Mary, right?
- Hi, Morgan.
- Hi, come on in.
Do you have visitors, or...
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
- They... they just showed up.
Guys, time to pack it up.
This is the band.
Meet Medieval Carnage.
- Hey there.
- Hi.
- They make me look good.
- You make us look good, man.
Have you seen him shred?
Guy's a genius.
I'm his drummer, Pete.
- Hi.
- What's wrong with this guy?
He invites his banger friends
the day he's supposed to die?
You guys friends of Morgan's?
We're counselors.
Kind of like palliative care.
We can come back
if you guys need to...
Need to shred or whatever.
No, no, no, let's roll.
I'm glad you decided
to get counseling.
It'll be good for you.
Yeah, thanks
for dropping by, guys.
You're gonna be fine, brother.
Yeah, mate, so are you.
Get him out of here.
I am so sorry.
- Morgan, do they know?
- No.
It's just...
It's been hard on them too,
you know, watching me die,
and they sometimes stop in
and just check and see
if I'm breathing.
I still think that we should go.
No, no, please, please,
I need your help.
I'm begging you.
Des, it's okay.
It's okay. Look at me.
It's okay.
How are you feeling?
Good.
Weird.
Feel like I'm standing
at the edge of a cliff.
Does that make any sense?
It makes a lot of sense.
We have a few things to go over,
and I have something
for you to sign.
Des, the contract?
Des?
These friends of yours...
have you known them
for a long time?
20 years.
We went to high school together.
Misfits and losers, you know.
I guess we banded
together... literally.
That's great.
Such an important part
of life, isn't it?
To have friends
you can count on.
Mary...
Friends can be such a comfort
in a time of suffering.
What's she gonna do,
talk this guy to death?
I don't know.
We hope that we can be as well.
And we would be happy to provide
more counseling sessions
whenever you need them.
That's her cover story.
Where is she going with this?
That sounds great, um,
but right now,
I'm kind of tired.
Cystic Fibrosis flare-up.
It happens.
We can reschedule
your counseling session
for another time.
You should rest now.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Please, wait.
- You know what, Des?
I think it's really
unprofessional of you
to come
to a counseling session high.
The wire, he's taking
off the wire.
Frank!
So maybe you should
just walk home
and think about
what you've done.
I'm a bastard, okay?
I'm a bastard. Don't go.
Don't go.
Please.
- You piece of shit.
- Frank!
Frank, take it easy.
Come on, man. Come on.
- Off, off!
- Get off!
Back off! Off!
- She made me!
- Of course she didn't make you!
You're going down for this.
Fine, you can go ahead,
and you read me my rights?
- Well?
- Come on.
Get the hell out of my sight.
You can't arrest me.
- Get out of my goddamn sight.
- With pleasure.
Do you realize...
do you realize how bad this is?
Come on,
I told you he was high,
all right?
- You pushed it.
- I pushed it?
No, no, no, you don't get
to put this one me, all right?
You compromised this case
from day one.
- That right?
- Remember that?
You know what?
You can do the debriefing
with Grant.
Tell him whatever
the hell you want.
- I'm done.
- Frank...
- No, I'm done.
- Frank, come on.
I'm done.
Jess.
Hey, want to skip today?
No.
- We can go to the mall.
- I have money today for real.
That's cool. Have fun.
What?
Why are you bailing on me?
- Because you're a psychopath.
- Jess.
Jess, I need you.
I love you.
No, you don't.
Okay.
Is that what this is about?
You mad I'm not a dyke?
Whoa.
I'm sorry.
What are you, embarrassed?
Well, you should be.
I thought we were
just having some fun.
I can't believe you're ruining
our friendship over this.
We could have been
like sisters, Jess,
and now you're turning
into this selfish bitch.
I'm a self...
No, you are the most selfish
person in the world.
I could search the whole planet,
and I wouldn't find
a more self-absorbed
person than...
So, transfer her upstairs,
and if she's in a lot of pain,
give her 50 milligrams
of morphine.
50?
We want to ease her pain,
not put her in a coma.
- Did I say...?
- Five.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm...
It's been a long day.
Hey, I've got something
that'll cheer you up.
Did you hear about Matt Danvers?
He woke up about an hour ago.
We've been praying and praying,
even Dr. Taylor.
It turns out I have a knack.
I could see you waiting for me.
I never lost faith.
Wow, that's...
That's amazing.
And, Matt, you feel okay?
It's all good.
It's a miracle, Mary.
Well, Sonia, Matt,
I'm so happy for both of you.
This is...
Great, great news.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Hello, Dr. Harris?
This is principal Amelia Foster
from Westbridge Academy.
Is everything okay?
It's about
your daughter Jessica.
You need to come
to the school immediately.
We have a situation.
- My God, is that...
- What happened?
Jess attacked Naomi.
Is that true?
- No, she hit me first.
- No, I didn't.
- Why are you fighting?
- What's going on?
They won't say.
The most I could get out of them
is that they were arguing
and then it got physical.
Either way, we have
a zero-tolerance policy
for violence at Westbridge.
There will be consequences.
Well, I don't think
that Naomi should be punished.
She didn't instigate anything.
Well, Jess said she did.
- Well, it's hearsay.
- Are we in court?
What is this? Come on.
How about I talk?
Given your daughter's
excellent records,
I won't suspend them,
but there will be detention,
after school for two weeks.
That seems fair.
Of course.
Okay, Naomi, let's go.
Jess, wait, I wanna talk to you.
Just leave me alone.
- Hey, slow down and look at me.
- Don't you get it?
I don't want to talk to you.
I don't want to look at you.
I don't... I don't want
anything to do with you.
Why are you here?
Because I want to help you,
because I love you.
I'm so sick of people
talking about love
when they have no idea
what it means.
You know, if you love somebody,
you don't lie to them.
You don't tell them
you care about them
when all you care
about is yourself.
- Jess.
- No, just go.
It's all you ever do anyways,
and you know,
it used to make me really sad,
but I don't really care anymore,
because when you're around,
everything really sucks.
Hey, hey, hey, Jess.
What the hell is happening
between you two?
She hates me.
Look, I know you've been
under a lot of stress lately,
and the financial pressure
I've put you under
hasn't helped. I know that.
That's all gonna change.
The house just sold
a couple hours ago,
well over asking.
So, I'll be able
to pay you back.
You can pull back on your hours,
spend more time with the girls.
Where are you gonna live?
I'm moving in with Louise.
What?
I love her, and she loves me.
Sometimes it can be that simple.
I think it's too fast.
Well, you know what?
I never thought
I'd get here, but I did.
Where? Get where?
To a place where it doesn't
really matter what you think.
Another setback.
I understand
your frustration, sir.
I mean, I've been on cases
that have taken months,
if not years, so.
And you've been given
every opportunity
and every resource
for this case.
I don't understand
what the problem is.
I want answers about my son.
Well, we are making progress.
We have identified
another potential victim.
The hospital records confirm
that Annie Chung was
indeed his nurse.
However, the wife is a little
hesitant to cooperate
with the investigation.
We are close, sir.
We're very close.
We just need a little more time.
Are you sure
you're alone this time?
I'm sure.
Not a bad way to go?
Clean sheets, nice view,
free hair products.
I always pictured drowning
in my own mucus in the ICU.
This is better.
You're quiet.
Is something wrong?
Do you think the room is bugged?
I'll need you to sign
this contract...
- Okay.
- And do the statement
on camera.
Of course.
Um...
Do you find this hard?
Bringing death to the decrepit
and vulnerable?
I didn't before.
What was hard was
watching people suffer.
Nothing worse
than an undignified death.
I guess the cops don't agree.
What are you going to do?
Come on.
Safe to say I won't be
telling anyone your secrets.
This is supposed
to be about you.
Honestly, you look like
you're in more pain than I am.
I just... can't see
any way out of this.
I mean, any way that doesn't
mean ending up in jail.
But I don't know.
Maybe that's what I deserve.
There you are. Where were you?
How did you get in?
- You gave me a key.
- You need to leave.
- I can't be around anyone.
- What's wrong?
What's wrong with you, Larissa?
You can't do better than me?
- Stop it, Des.
- You need a daddy.
I'm not your daddy.
I don't need a daddy, asshole.
Just take your things,
all your little things,
and get out!
You're a jerk!
I know.
When I was younger,
I developed this obsession
with medieval torture,
like the Judas cradle.
Did you ever hear of that?
No.
They sit you on this triangular
metal point,
and you slowly become impaled,
or they strap
you to the iron chair
with hundreds
of tiny little spikes,
or they tie you up
in the town square,
and you die
the slowest death imaginable
on display for the whole town.
Nice.
Why are you telling me this?
Because in 100 years,
they'll look back at now
and say that the most
popular form of torture
was refusing to let people die.
Dragging it out.
Give people false hope,
false relief,
hook them up to machines.
Something that should
take months
to kill them would take years.
Those people?
They're the bad guys.
But you?
You're one of the good ones.
Do you really think so?
Yeah.
Wow.
Are you going to stay with me?
Yes, of course I will.
Can you talk to me?
You know, the first time
I did this, I was 16.
It was with my mother.
She was sick?
Yeah, she was depressed.
She wanted to die
more than anything.
So each day I'd come from school
not knowing what I'd find.
And my mother was good
at a lot of things,
but she was terrible at suicide.
Maybe there was something
holding her back.
I don't know.
At first, I...
I tried to talk her out of it.
So many times.
But after a while, I realized
that was never gonna work.
Forcing her to stay alive
wasn't the way to save her.
So I helped.
She said she might
pull a Houdini,
but I knew she wouldn't.
I remember...
the relief.
No more waiting,
no more wondering.
And for a moment...
everything was calm.
I was just thinking about you.
Help.
- What?
- Des?
Des?
Des, talk to me. Are you okay?
What's going on?
Des?
My God.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Wake up.
Stop. Stop it.
- You stop it.
- Stop it.
You don't get to do this.
You don't get to call me
crying for help,
not after what you said.
I know, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Tell me why.
We had a fight.
You weren't returning my calls.
And that detective,
he said you were with Ben,
and I got scared.
You thought I would have
turned on you?
Well, maybe you should have.
Let's face it, Mary.
I'm a liability.
One way or another I ruin
every good thing in my life.
Stop trying to make me
feel sorry for you.
It's not gonna work.
We're done, Des.
It's over.
I need a partner
who can handle this.
I can.
I only started using again
because I felt so guilty.
I'm done now.
I promise.
Des, I can't trust you anymore.
I guess that's it then.
I'll find a job
washing cars or something.
Think you'd be my reference?
It's a peace offering.
I managed to pull
a few strings, man.
We got a search warrant
for Troy Dixon's property
plus a production order
for all of his financials.
Yeah, how'd you convince him?
Well, you know,
I just flashed these
old puppy dog eyes on him.
So, we're good?
We're good.
Did the owner check it out?
No, said the Yukon
showed up overnight.
Figured it was hot,
called it in.
- Lucky us.
- Maybe Sid's hiding out here.
Living in a scrap yard?
Maybe he ditched it and ran.
There you go.
God.
- Jesus.
- Poor Sid.
- Call it in.
- I'll check the vehicle.
Yeah.
Thanks for that.
- This is Officer Hall.
- Need forensics
at the scrap yard on West 15th.
Got a 187.
Look what I found.
Well, look who it is,
the angel of death.
I'm here to talk business.
Are you ready to give me my cut?
I need a new partner.
50-50.
The two hour finale event of Mary
Kills People, continues now.
The only crime that Mary is
guilty of
is trying to protect me.
Save me.
She can't help herself.
It's what she does.
We're not the same you and I.
You create pain.
Help me please. He drugged me.
He's going to kill me.
Where are you?
Mary?
==sync, corrections by dcdah==
for www.addic7ed.com