Previously on "Manifest"...
Save the passengers.
I'm pregnant.
I just thought this would
be something special
to bring us all together
when everything else is so scary.
NSA, drop your weapon!
Somebody help me!
You're Dr. Saanvi Bahl, right?
- I'm sorry. And you are... ?
- Troy Davis.
Oncology lab tech.
I have an appointment...
with a therapist.
Michaela and I, we're
meant to be together.
Back off!
Where's Zeke?
NYPD's looking for him.
I'm here to ask you
to call off the hunt.
- It was an accident.
- You got shot,
and your new boyfriend ran off.
The Callings said you
guys are gonna die!
You need to be with Michaela.
She doesn't have much
time. And neither do you.
He's never gonna know
about his Death Date.
He's innocent.
We have to make it possible
for him to come home.
I didn't mean to hurt you, and I did.
What happens the next
time I get a Calling?
This is what I need to
do... own up to my actions.
Zeke turned himself in.
He knows he's guilty.
You're not the only one who
can come back from the dead.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
We got to clear the airway.
Let's get him onto an I.V.
Please step back, ma'am.
Excuse me, is that... Is
that Vance? How bad is it?
Can you just tell me
how bad it is, please?
You okay, sir?
My arm hurts like hell, but I'll live,
thanks to you pulling me out of there.
Sir, we need to get you to a hospital.
No, people inside our own government
were willing to kill me.
If I'm gonna take them down,
I want them to think they succeeded.
You know the drill.
The world needs to think I'm dead.
Well, I was convinced.
The whole world was.
You would have loved your funeral...
- Bobby.
- Hmm.
Well, I'm sorry I couldn't
tell the truth to you...
well, both of you,
but no one knows except my guys,
my wife, and now the two of you.
You want to bring her
up to speed, or should I?
Well, I wasn't planning to see you
until I knew who the Major
was, but your bloodhound brother
accelerated our little reunion.
Yeah, well, that's our Ben for you.
So far, I've identified a-a
black ops financial pipeline
that appears to be funding
a shadow 828 investigation.
Suffice it to say, I've
been following the money.
And in the past week,
that money has doubled.
Why? What's the Major planning?
Well, that's why I asked you here.
I was hoping one of you could tell me.
A budget spike like that had
to be the response to something.
Did anything significant happen
to the 828 passengers this week?
Hmm, not that we know of.
You want me to do some poking around?
Stone, the last time you poked around,
you ended up in the back of a van
with a hood over your head.
Right. Yeah. I'll leave
the espionage to you.
But I have been connecting with more
and more passengers every day.
In fact, I've got a meeting
in an hour with an 828er.
He's a freshman at Astoria.
He called me twice yesterday.
Seems like he's got
something to tell me.
Good.
'Cause after all this is
over, I can stop being dead,
and I would really like you all to live.
And maybe we can get to the bottom
of where the hell you all
went for 5 and a half years.
- TJ.
- Hey.
Hey.
Thanks for meeting me on campus.
No problem.
I'd forgotten how quiet a campus gets
between sessions.
I used to be a professor.
You don't teach anymore?
No, I'm trying,
but with all the
attention and suspicion,
the opportunities
just haven't been there.
Yeah.
828 changed my life a lot.
Me too.
It changed everything for me.
I used to love it here.
Did well in my classes,
joined the cross country
team, the Latin club.
I was in it.
And my mom was proud...
which made me proud.
And then you went to Jamaica.
You know, this was probably a mistake.
I'm sorry that I bothered you.
TJ.
Listen, you asked me here for a reason.
Is it because you're seeing things?
Hearing things, maybe?
Both.
And they've gotten...
Hey, it's okay. You can
talk to me about this.
I-I get them, too. A lot of us do.
"Callings".
Sometimes they can be pretty terrifying.
Like seeing your own death?
Yeah.
Yeah, like that.
This morning, I had a vision
of being inside my own grave.
You think it's a Death Date Calling?
You still thinking
about the "save the passengers" Calling?
Yeah, me too.
It felt like the plane was crashing.
So maybe it's showing
us how we're gonna die?
Um...
Well, your dad seems
to think that it's about
saving the passengers
before the Death Date.
It felt more urgent
than that, didn't it?
I know. We have to talk to Zeke.
He was on the plane in our Calling,
even though he wasn't in real life.
- That means something.
- Yeah, I know.
Well, once he's out on
bail, we can talk to him.
- He had the same Calling, so...
- He didn't.
How do you know that?
In the Calling, he
couldn't hear us or see us,
and neither could anyone else.
We have to save him,
just like we have to save
the rest of the passengers.
Okay, I'm gonna try again
to talk to him, alright?
Okay.
I'm gonna miss having you
live with us, Auntie Mick.
Well, I'm gonna miss
stealing your waffles, buddy,
but I got to go back to my apartment.
It's time.
Are you sure about this?
Once we know, we can't un-know.
It's gonna be okay, no matter what.
Paternity, right? Yeah.
So, we just need to get
a single vial of blood
and then I'll swab your cheek
and we'll send them both to the lab
and we should have results
back within one to two days.
Great.
- Are you afraid of needles?
- No.
Stop.
Who... ?
You okay?
Um, uh...
Stop.
Grace?
Stop!
- Grace!
- I'm... I'm sorry, we have to go!
Wait, you... you... you...
you can't... you can't just...
We have to go.
Honey.
Honey, are you okay? What just happened?
I just h-heard my own voice,
over and over,
telling me to stop.
Oh, my God.
You just had a Calling.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
I don't understand.
How could I have a Calling?
It doesn't make any sense.
I wasn't... I wasn't on the plane.
But I was.
That still doesn't explain...
Oh, my God.
The pregnancy.
It's the only thing that makes sense.
So...
that would mean...
it's your baby.
It sure seems that way.
God, Ben, it's your baby.
Come on.
Let's get you home.
That inmate is refusing visitors.
Ezekiel Landon?
Can you try again?
That inmate's refusing visitors.
Uh, does this help?
Sure, assuming the ADA sent you,
advised the inmate's lawyer,
and you have a case number.
No, I'm not officially on the case,
but I'm an interested party.
I'm a friend of his. You...
Next.
Thank you. Have a good day.
Wycoff and Holland, look
into the automobile theft
- at Clark Towing.
- I got it.
And, Raines, your warrants came through
on the 15th Avenue bust.
And of course, welcome, Detective Stone,
back from medical leave.
Okay, let's get to it.
Detective Stone. Hi.
- Hi.
- Drea Mikami.
I just want to say it's
such an honor to meet you.
- Oh.
- Your conviction record
is almost too good to be true.
I was wondering, maybe,
if you had a second, we could sit down,
and I could pick your
brain about how you...
Um, Mikami, do you mind?
Uh, kind of. Yeah.
Detective Stone, I see
you've met your new partner,
Detective Mikami.
- Um...
- Hold on.
- Captain. Captain.
- Wow, this is... This is great.
- Yeah, give... one sec.
- Uh, Captain?
Detective Stone and I...
we used to be partners.
Yeah, and that
partnership triggered a lot
of internal investigations
and unwanted attention from One PP.
So now I'm in charge,
and Detective Stone has a new partner.
Don't start sleeping with this one.
Hey.
You know this is not gonna work.
You need me to have your back here.
You know what? Actually, I think
I just need you to let this go.
Maybe it's for the best. Clean break.
Definitely need this nap.
I forgot how exhausting
it is to make a new human.
Well, I am a big fan of your work.
We should still confirm.
I'll go see Saanvi as soon as I'm up.
Hmm.
It's that kid TJ,
the one that had the Death Date Calling.
I was supposed to meet
him again tomorrow, but...
Yeah. Go.
Alright.
TJ?
TJ?!
Ben?
I didn't know what to do.
I didn't want to call the police.
Alright, what is it? What happened?
It wasn't me I saw in the grave.
- What?
- It wasn't me.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God, TJ, what happened?
I have no idea.
I was trying to follow the Calling,
to see if I could make
any more sense of it
after we talked this morning.
A-And it brought you here?
And I just started digging.
God. What do I do?
Apparently, the Calling
only trusts you to take my blood.
This changes everything
I thought I knew.
Scientifically speaking,
Callings have now been
transferred genetically
through the baby.
So, if it is Ben's baby...
will the Death Date also transfer?
We have no proof of that...
okay?
Detective Vasquez, 129th.
Catch me up.
You are looking at
late teens, early 20s.
Rigor is abating,
suggesting that she's been
dead at least 36 hours.
Blunt force trauma and suffocation.
We found a student
key card in her pocket.
Campus security is going
to run it for an I.D.
Thank you.
You're campus security, right?
I want to know every time
and place that key card
was used this week.
Copy.
Jared, I called 911.
How'd you get put on this?
Oh, I saw your name
as a reporting witness.
I thought I should
just come check it out.
Uh, this is TJ.
He was on 828, and he...
found the body.
Oh. How, exactly?
It's okay.
He'll understand.
Well, I was walking, and,
I don't know, I just had a feeling.
So I started digging, and I found her.
I know how crazy that must sound.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
So, he's saying that a Calling
he had led him here,
and you believe him?
Yeah, how else could he
have found the girl's body?
He could have found her
by putting her there.
Come on, Jared. You think he killed her?
Look, I don't think anything, Ben.
I'm gathering the facts, okay?
That's my job.
You're a better cop than a criminal.
Sorry, what?
You swiped that file off Vasquez's desk.
- Is that his court docket?
- Yep.
Are you and Vasquez
in some kind of detente
I need to know about?
Uh, need to? No.
- Got it.
- _
My last partner retired.
Aviera. Good guy, but super old-school.
How did Aviera feel about
being paired with a rich kid?
Where'd that come from?
That watch is three months' salary,
you say things like "detente",
and you have a photo on
your desk of a horse...
English saddle, not Western.
So, yeah, you're moneybags.
Okay, not me, exactly,
but my mom kind of
killed it on Wall Street.
I'm guessing this isn't
quite the trajectory
she had in mind for you.
Being a cop?
No. But I love it.
And I want to learn from the best.
So maybe lesson one is why you
read arraignments so carefully?
Lesson one is this.
What is the foundation
of any good partnership?
- Trust.
- Great.
So, you can trust me not to tell anyone
about your Upper Eastside past.
Tribeca. Deal. What do I do?
Cover for me while I
deal with something.
Go. I'll return the contraband.
Oh, whoa.
Hey.
These are some serious books.
Yeah. SAT prep.
I'm starting to realize
exactly how much I don't know.
Not all answers can be found in books.
Here. Hang on to this.
I love your jacket, by the way.
Olive?
Who was that?
I don't know.
Oh, no, honey.
We can't be talking to Believers.
No, mom, she's super nice.
- I dropped my book.
- Sweetie, we have to be really careful.
If they find out there's an 828 baby...
If it is an 828 baby.
- It is.
- Wait. Wait.
So, i-it is dad's baby?
- You took the paternity test.
- Yeah.
I mean, not exactly,
but, yeah, it's dad's.
Wait, what?
I'm... How do you know, then?
Um...
I had a Calling.
What? Wait? How... How is that even... ?
I-I don't know.
Something to do with the pregnancy.
Sweetie, this is... this is great news.
We can all be one family,
just like we'd hoped.
Not really.
Now I'm the only one.
Olive.
All rise.
Ezekiel Landon, you are charged
with one count of reckless
endangerment of human life...
- Where's his lawyer?
- I have no idea.
He won't talk to me.
Yeah, me, neither.
I can't lose him again.
What if I can't afford the bail?
We're gonna get the money.
One count of assault
in the first degree.
And you wish to defend yourself?
I do. Can I make a statement?
Go ahead.
Your Honor, I've made a
lot of mistakes in my life,
and I've hurt people,
good, decent people
whose only flaw was believing in me.
I hurt my little sister, my parents,
and I hurt someone...
someone I never wanted to hurt.
I don't want to spend the time
I have left fighting these charges
and dragging out the pain
for those I care about.
What are you doing? Stop.
As to the count of assault
in the first degree,
I plead guilty.
Zeke, stop! No, you can fight this!
- Your Honor, it was an accident.
- Order in the court!
Zeke, you can fight
this! It was an accident!
No! Zeke! No, no, no, Zeke!
As to the count of illegal
possession of a firearm...
- Zeke, stop!
- ... I plead guilty.
What are you doing? You can fight this.
- Ma'am, please.
- As to the count of fleeing
- the scene of a crime, I plead guilty.
- It was an accident.
Your Honor, it was an accident.
None... None of it
was supposed to happen!
As to the count of reckless
endangerment of human life...
... I plead guilty.
- Hey.
- How are you holding up?
- Yeah, I've been better.
I just can't believe
Zeke pled guilty to...
How's Grace?
Taking it easy.
She's still thrown by the
whole getting a Calling thing.
I can't wrap my head around that.
it doesn't make any sense.
I feel like we say that a lot.
It's true.
- Is that him?
- Mm-hmm.
Hi, I'm, uh, Michaela. You must be TJ.
Hi. I hear Detective Vasquez
brought you in for a follow-up.
Though he's kept us waiting long enough.
It's fine.
TJ's a glutton for punishment.
He's a cross-country
runner who studies Latin.
Ooh!
My office, Detective.
What's that about?
Um, probably my unscheduled appearance
at Zeke's arraignment.
You don't have to wait with me.
Yeah.
If you're here, I'm here.
The question is... do you want to stay?
I want to see it through.
I mean, there's got to be a reason
why I got this Calling, right?
Why it was sent to me and
not you or your sister?
Yeah, maybe.
We still haven't figured
out exactly how it works.
Well, at least you have each other.
Hmm.
Just like me with my mom.
She was cool.
More like a best friend, you know?
If your best friend constantly
makes you eat salmon
and listen to Madonna.
Sounds like you guys were close.
Yeah.
What happened to her?
When the plane went missing, um,
she must have felt like she didn't
have anything left to live for.
And she OD'd on sleeping
pills a month later.
Oh, TJ, I'm so sorry.
My mom died when we were gone, too.
While I was gone, the
school emptied my dorm room,
and my mom's landlord tossed her stuff.
So I don't have anything.
Not even a photo of her.
Hi, excuse me. I need
access to a DNA Sequencer.
Dr. Bahl!
Troy Davis, remember?
- I tightened up the beard a little.
- Yes. Hi. Right.
How are you doing? You know what?
I think I left my I.D. in my office.
Don't worry. I can vouch.
Y-You need a DNA Sequencer.
What do you need it for?
Anything interesting?
I would love to help.
Oh, it's just a theory
that I'm working up.
Is it about that blood marker?
From your pediatric patient?
I'll just put down "research".
And by the way, I would love to help.
Yeah, you mentioned that.
Just, uh, have the machine delivered,
and we can play the rest by ear.
Thank you.
♪ Diamonds dancin' on the chain ♪
♪ I swear all these is lame ♪
♪ Came from murder and robberies ♪
♪ Better not think about robbing me ♪
♪ She suck me, I'm all in her artery ♪
♪ These hatin'... be watchin' me ♪
♪ Run to the guap ♪
♪ I'm headed straight to the top ♪
♪ ... you broke, you a flop ♪
♪ It's PNV, I will not stop ♪
I didn't realize I needed permission
to attend an arraignment.
Captain Riojas was...
Let me tell you how
it works in my precinct.
We have rules.
And making a scene at your
own assailant's hearing
violated several of them.
He's not my assailant.
Not an assailant, not your boyfriend.
You keep correcting me, and we just met.
He shot a cop.
That's confirmed by Detective Vasquez,
who witnessed it, and
by the defendant himself,
who pled guilty.
Right, but it's not that simple.
It's exactly that simple.
It's a nice, simple, closed case.
The only one who's trying to
make it difficult here is you.
He didn't mean to.
Well, he sure as hell meant
to plead guilty, Detective.
So drop it.
Mick.
You want to tell me why you've
been making that kid wait all day?
Oh, you're referring to the
kid who swears he doesn't know
anything about a homicide victim
he just happened to dig up?
No, he doesn't, Jared. Ben told you.
He... He had a Calling.
TJ never met her.
His fingerprints are all
over the victim's room.
- His prints were in her room?
- _
Okay, no, there's
an explanation for this.
Just because he was on that plane
- does not mean he's not a murderer.
- Jared, you're doing it again,
where you're looking
for the worst in people.
No, I'm looking for the evidence.
He knew exactly where the body was.
Okay, his fingerprints
were found all over a room
of a victim he swore he never met.
You know the drill.
Mick, you know I got to do this.
No, actually, you...
Jared, come on, stop.
- Oh, my God.
- Finally.
- Stand up and turn around, please.
- What?
- Stand up and turn around.
- Jared, what's going on?
You have the right to remain silent...
- Come on, Jared. What the hell?
- You said he'd understand!
Listen to me, Ben. I didn't do it.
Please. I didn't do it. Please!
- Jared, he's innocent! Jared!
- Ben!
- Mick, you've got...
- I didn't do it!
Please, listen to me!
Do something, please!
Ben! Ben!
Hey, look at me. Look at me.
You feel that?
What the hell you talking about?
Get him out of here.
No, stop!
Please let go! No!
Jared's still interrogating TJ.
It could take hours.
- Well, I'm not leaving.
- Okay.
I told TJ I was here
for him, and I meant it.
Now, can we discuss what happened?
I've never seen anyone shake
like that during a Calling.
I know. It... It felt like turbulence,
like the plane Calling Cal and I had.
When he told you to save the passengers?
Yeah.
It happened right when TJ was arrested.
He's a passenger.
It's telling you to save him.
He's clearly innocent.
No, actually.
- Not clearly.
- What?
Look, TJ told us that
he'd never met her,
but his prints were all over her room.
Ben, I've gone over and over the file.
Her name was Frannie.
She was an art student.
Well, he didn't do it.
That's not what the evidence says.
Well, find new evidence!
Ben. You're too close to this, okay?
Oh, and you weren't close to the guy
who shot you and ran off?
Don't bring Zeke into this.
You know he's innocent.
So is TJ!
Ben, you've known him for one day, okay?
You are way too trusting, and I...
and I love that about you, but...
it's a weakness, okay?
TJ tells you a sob story, and...
He is a passenger.
And you know what? You're right.
I do trust him.
Because right now
passengers are pretty much
the only people I can trust.
So, please, dig deeper.
Okay.
But if I find more proof
that... that he murdered this girl,
then it's my job to make sure
he never sees the light of day.
Can you take me to see Auntie Mick?
At the police station?
Cal, what... what's up?
I need to talk to her.
There's... There's something
we're supposed to do together.
It's important.
Well, then, you're in luck
because your older-and
oh-so-wiser twin sister
just happens to be sitting
right in front of you,
ready to listen.
That's okay.
But if mom or dad call,
tell them I need help.
Cal.
I-I can help.
At least let me try.
What is it?
It's about a Calling.
You wouldn't understand.
Okay.
- It's just that...
- No, no, no.
I get it.
Having fun with your new toy?
Yeah, I'm just getting set up.
I can show you how I set up
my test runs on this baby.
It's a little different
from other Sequencers.
I'm just running some test results
before I even get started.
Maybe we could get a coffee or something
while you're waiting.
I figure we're overdue, anyway.
I suspect we may have more in common
than just being keen researchers.
Might be fun to find out.
I'm sorry, what?
Just rambling.
♪ I'm a ramblin' man ♪
Okay, so, I have to go.
Which means you have to go.
Right. Okay.
After you.
I already told the other cops.
I don't know him.
Frannie and I have been sorority
sisters for three years,
and I've never seen that guy before.
Do you know why Frannie stayed on campus
in between sessions?
She's a Visual Arts major.
She was almost done getting ready
for her first solo show
at the campus gallery.
It's supposed to open this weekend.
- Is this Latin?
- I think so, yeah. Why?
Maybe that's the crossover.
Maybe they were both in Latin.
Those notes aren't Frannie's.
She didn't take Latin.
Why does she have someone
else's stuff in her room?
She had a ton of other
people's junk around.
She pulled it out of
the trash for her art.
She made collages out of found objects.
These must've been the discards
that didn't make it into the show.
Cross country, Latin... This...
This is TJ's stuff. He
was telling the truth.
He was never in this
room, but his stuff was...
his old stuff from before 828.
Michaela, you okay?
Yeah, um... Sorry.
Just...
Weird. That's Frannie's key card.
She must have dropped it
when she was sorting through stuff.
Frannie had her key card
on her when she died.
Must've been a replacement.
Campus security records
didn't have any reports
of her card being lost.
Or them issuing a replacement.
You think they'd keep track of that.
If you needed to get a new
card, where would you go?
Someone looks happy.
It's just a good day.
How nice! Personal or professional?
Work.
Have you met me?
Though I think this lab
tech just asked me out today.
He came by my office
claiming to be checking in
on the Sequencer, but...
I'm sorry. Checking in on the what?
It's a DNA Sequencer.
Oh, got it.
I had a new realization
about the Callings...
that they might be
transferable, genetically,
so I needed a new machine
to look at the DNA sequencing
so I can isolate the... I'm sorry.
Sorry, this is so boring.
If you're excited about something,
then I am happy to listen.
It is really exciting.
Actually, you know,
Troy could be helpful
with the sequencing
because the calibration
needs to be so precise.
As long as I don't let
him see any of my research.
_
Hey, I don't want to do the SATs,
and I really don't need the lecture.
Come here, love.
I know how it felt when
we were the only two people
not having the Callings.
And I can only imagine
how you must be feeling now
that I've had a Calling.
Honey, we will always be a family.
Nothing can come between us.
Not even the Callings.
Mom, do you think I'm resentful
because everyone else gets
the Callings and I don't?
- You're not?
- Mom, I'm not resentful.
I'm terrified.
Because the Callings gave
Cal and dad the Death Date.
How do you know that you and
the baby don't have it, too?
And in five years, you'll all be gone.
And I'll be the only one left.
I had thought that maybe the baby...
I really don't see why
I'm cramming all of this SAT stuff
just to be standing there
alone at my college graduation
wishing that all of you were alive.
Honey, I'm sure we'll be at...
Mom, you're not sure about anything!
And you are lying if you say you are!
Hi, there.
Detectives Mikami and Stone, NYPD.
Just wondering if we
could, uh, talk to you
about Frannie King?
Yeah, of course. Whataya need?
The card that she had
on her was a replacement.
Just want to know when it was issued.
Hmm.
There's no entry in the log.
Do you know who was on
shift the night before last?
That'll be Wilkins.
Wilkins.
What's going on?
Uh, that student who
died... Frannie King.
She come in for a key replacement?
No.
You sure?
'Cause even if it's not in the log,
the key card machine's a computer,
so it records every output.
We just got to download it.
You know, a girl did
run in here for a card.
She was in a hurry to
get back to her room.
I guess I forgot to log it.
Why was she in a hurry?
No idea. She didn't talk much.
She just took the card
and headed towards the west gate.
Not towards her sorority?
I don't know if she was in a sorority.
I just saw her leave, and that was it.
Sorry, so, you noticed
that she was in a hurry
and where she was going, but you...
you didn't notice
the giant sorority letters
on her sweatshirt?
That's kind of selective
in your observations.
Sorry, but that's all I remember.
I need to get going.
Yeah, one more quick question, actually.
When did you get the shiny new boots?
It's really hard to get blood
out of leather, isn't it?
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
I assume you're gonna clue
me in as to what just happened.
That's lesson number two.
Ben. It's over.
They found the perp's
boots in a Dumpster
outside of his house
covered in Frannie's DNA.
I should have been able
to help her, though.
- It's my fault.
- No, no.
She was dead before you
ever got the Calling.
TJ, you couldn't have saved her.
Why would the Calling want
me to find a dead body?
Without you, Frannie's body
may never have been found.
At least now her family
can get some closure.
Yeah, the guard left his previous jobs
under suspicion of
harassment and stalking.
I mean, he was likely a serial predator.
You saved whoever would
have been his next victim
or victims.
But why me?
Why did I get this Calling?
I think we may know.
Come on. I'll show you.
Thank you.
Come on.
Give me a second.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry I pushed too hard before.
It's another one of my weaknesses.
No, no. The, uh... The only
thing that I'm mad at
is the fact that you were right.
So, I'm sorry, too.
Congratulations on an
amazing solve, Stone.
I've been looking back at your cases,
and you've had a lot of
solves from anonymous tips.
A lot.
So many, in fact, an ADA
might start asking questions.
You see, I like a paper trail.
I like a long paper trail.
It means that my cops
are doing their jobs.
So, tell me, detective,
how'd you solve this one,
in two hours, no less?
Anonymous tip.
It's your case, Vasquez.
You buy that?
I do.
Really?
Because I don't buy it for a second.
Going forward, I don't want you two
anywhere near the same cases.
The school held onto
your stuff for years
before they threw it out.
But when they did, it was found again...
... by Frannie.
That's why the Calling
led you to find her.
'Cause she found you.
I can stay if you want me to.
No.
No, I just, uh...
I don't know how to thank you.
Hey.
Go see your mom.
Ben Stone?
Suzanne?
You're kidding me. How long has it been?
Well, for you or for me?
What are you doing here?
- I'm a dean. Well, can you believe it?
- Yeah, I can.
You were the smartest
student in Number Theory.
Well, my group study partner
was a real inspiration.
What about you?
Besides shattering the laws of physics,
what have you been up to?
Actually, dean, I'm on
a job hunt, so if you...
Ben. Sent me your CV... today.
My e-mail's on the department's website.
Okay. Will do.
Hey! Uh, you're the...
Yeah, the girl with the
two tons of SAT books.
No, you were so much
more than just that.
You were the girl in the killer jacket.
Thank you.
I'm Maxine Taylor.
Olive. Olive Stone.
Wait. "Stone", as in...
Yes, but, you know, I don't
really want everyone to...
Yeah, no worries! Come in.
Adrian's about to speak.
And you have to tell me where you shop.
Deal, if you tell me where
you got your hair done.
Oh, this is all DIY.
I can hook you up.
I don't suppose you know anything
about DNA Sequencers.
I assume you're talking about
the one Saanvi's been using.
She made a new discovery
about a genetic change to the 828ers,
but she's been doing
the tests in her labs
to keep it all under wraps.
How would you know about that?
Because it's clearly not under wraps.
I've been tracking the accounts.
Looks like the Major just ordered one.
How the hell does the Major
know about Saanvi's discovery?
Shots fired. Officer down.
Hold on, Michaela.
I'm so sorry.
Run.
"Dear Zeke..."
"I don't know how to say
this, other than I need you".
It's happening again!
Just hang on. Just hang on.
Zeke! Zeke! Zeke, please!
Zeke, can you hear me?
Hey!
Can you hear me?
- Zeke, I'm right here, okay?
- Michaela.
Hey, hey, hey, I'm right here.
I'm right here.
Michaela.
Zeke, I'm right here. Zeke!
Cal?
Is that you? Michaela?
It's not working. Let's double the dose.
No, please. I need...
No, the Calling.
No!
I'm sorry.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org