Previously on "Manifest"...
Terribly sorry, folks.
That was not on the radar.
You've all been missing,
presumed dead, for 5 1/2 years.
- Who is she?
- Lourdes.
That makes sense. She always
told me how lucky I was.
I'm not ruling out that just
maybe he came back to be saved
and I came back to save him.
Earlier today, I heard
a voice in my head.
Keep it to yourself.
What do you think, the government
just sent us home and forgot about us?
It's as if the plane never left the sky.
Do I have to say out loud
that that's impossible?
Why you and me? What makes two
head cases like us so special?
What's the probability
it's just you and me?
Just four days
after its bewildering
reappearance,
Montego Air Flight 828
is no more.
Thankfully,
no one was injured in the incident.
The aeroplane,
which first mystified the world
after it disappeared
in April 2013...
The plane
exploded shortly after midnight
here on the tarmac
at Stewart Airport.
Cause unknown.
Sources close
to the investigation
say a group
of the plane's passengers
were spotted
on surveillance camera.
There's more hot spots.
Can you see them?
Yes, sir.
Knock those down.
You don't understand.
My son is in jail.
I've been trying to find him
for three days.
They say I have to call him now,
this minute.
He doesn't even know I'm alive.
17.
What'd you tell him?
That I don't know anything.
Good. You don't.
We want to stay
far off their radar.
But aren't you seeing things,
hearing things in your head?
They think it's my fault.
They always blame the pilot.
Look, pal.
I don't know how else to say it.
I had an urge to see the plane,
I showed up, kaboom.
How exactly did 20 people
have the same... urge?
I sell sporting goods.
The hell you asking me for?
Hi. I'm Saanvi Bahl. You're Cal's family?
Ben Stone.
This is my sister, Michaela.
How do you know Cal?
I'm a doctor.
I do cancer research.
Cal's new treatment
came from work I was doing
before the plane disappeared.
You were on the flight?
I know.
It's some coincidence...
If any of this
can be a coincidence.
18.
Sir, what is our status here?
Are we under arrest?
No, you're merely detained.
Actually, we're not.
I'm NYPD.
I know how this works.
We've told you
everything that we know,
so if we're not under arrest,
then you need to let us go.
And radar signal established.
Ladies and gentlemen,
if you've given your statements,
you're free to go.
However, the events
surrounding Flight 828
are a matter
of national security.
You're instructed to observe
a strict media blackout.
Discuss this matter with no one.
Not reporters,
not your families... no one.
You could've played the cop card
eight hours ago.
Oh, you're... you're welcome.
I want eyes on all of them.
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
Drop me at the precinct?
Yeah, after we
swing by the house.
Grace must be worried to death.
I'll take the train, papa bear.
Hey, not a word to anyone.
'Cause NSA guy said so?
No, because it's safer that way.
We're obviously scapegoats here.
And until we figure out what happened
to us, I don't trust anyone.
- What did it feel like?
- Sir, sir.
You were on that plane.
- My friend. My friend.
My friend, are you also police
like the woman?
Uh, uh, no. Perhaps
you can help anyway.
What can you tell us
about what happened?
Sir, please, please. Please.
Help me.
Please, sir, I need your help.
- I'm sorry.
- Do you have any comment so far?
Just me.
What happened?
You were at the airport
when the plane exploded?
We went back to get our luggage.
It was a big misunderstanding.
We're okay.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I... I'm a little
self-conscious.
We were supposed to grow old
and flabby together.
Well, for the record,
you look amazing.
Brought your favorite.
Orlando's.
My God.
That smell.
I had completely forgotten.
Well, I kind of dropped the ball
on my weekly
blueberry-scone run.
By my calculation,
I owe you 291 of these,
give or take.
Thank you.
I can't find my toothbrush.
Uh, hey, bud.
Mine had Batman on it.
You know what?
I got you a whole pack
of cool ones.
Come on.
Religious leaders
and scientists alike
grapple with the mystery
of Montego Air Flight 828.
Coffee? Really?
So that's what
16-year-olds are doing.
It's mostly milk and sugar.
Hey, so, I've been thinking.
Maybe after school,
we could hang out a bit,
you know, catch up.
I want to hear about,
you know, everything.
I have practice,
and I fell pretty behind
in my homework last week.
Maybe tomorrow.
Great. Whenever.
What is that?
What?
That music.
You don't...
You don't hear that?
Maybe Alexa acting up
in the den.
Who's Alexa?
Sweetie, it fits.
It's just a narrower cut.
I think you look cool.
After treatment,
we'll go shopping, okay?
I just feel weird in this.
Come on. Let's see if
we can go drum up something
a little less weird-feeling.
Did you tell him yet?
I will. Soon.
Mom, this isn't cool.
He deserves to know.
I came by the house last night.
Grace said you'd gone out.
Hi.
Sorry, uh, Lourdes.
Hey.
Um, I got to catch up
with the boss.
I'll... I'll see you soon, okay?
Hey, Captain.
What happened to, uh,
taking some time for yourself?
I can either sit at home
staring at my ceiling
or I can get back to work.
So, here's how it is.
I want this to happen...
You've got that going for ya...
But I can't sign off until
you jump through the hoops...
The physical,
firearms re-cert, psych eval.
Since when is a psych eval
a hoop?
We're in uncharted waters here.
After all you've been through...
Is that all?
That's all.
A hollow shell
is all that remains
of Montego Air Flight 828.
While multiple
government agencies
survey the wreckage
and look for clues...
Do you have
any different-colored pens?
Uh, no, but we can get you
a whole bunch at the store...
Sketchpad like you had,
the works.
Okay.
Hey, guys.
Honey, this is,
uh, the doctor I told you about.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, hi, there.
You all being on the plane
together, it's miraculous.
Yeah, so my parents say.
They've been praying
at every meal.
But right now, I'm gonna focus
my energy on this guy.
You ready for round two, buddy?
Yep.
See you, bud.
Get 'em.
Later, Mom and Dad.
Need to take that?
No, it's just a work thing.
I'm catering this office party,
and the client's always checking in.
Of course.
I keep forgetting.
My wife, the entrepreneur.
Ah, well.
Look, you must have
a ton to take care of,
so why don't I take a walk?
No, no, no.
You don't... I can make
some job-search calls,
and we can meet later back home.
I'll take tomorrow's shift.
I'll call you later.
Do you hear that?
Hear what?
You.
That melody.
That's been clanging in my head
all day.
I need help.
Please.
First it was the plane,
the vision.
Then this morning, the music
beating against my eardrums.
No voices?
You are hearing voices?
Eh, I'm not sure
what I'm hearing... or why.
For me, music is a higher power.
So this music we hear,
you and I together,
it's for a reason.
And that reason
has to be my son.
He's the one who needs help.
I was with you in Jamaica
to play with the philharmonic.
One night.
But I left a 13-year-old child
with my neighbor,
and I returned
to an 18-year-old man...
A man that is now behind bars.
Ah, I'm sorry.
What happened?
Police say it was robbery.
But that's impossible, you know,
'cause Adio's a good boy.
If I could just talk to him,
there'd be an explanation,
I know this.
Sounds like you need a lawyer.
Ineedto see my son.
The jail said
I need to be on a list,
but I'm a resident alien
and my visa's expired.
They say it could take a month,
but Adio don't have that long,
you know?
His trial's next week.
Please, please.
You know the police.
You're a father, yes?
Boy and a girl.
Adio's already been five years
without a father.
Can you imagine not being able
to save your own child?
I've been through your file.
Seems like your world
turned upside down
five monthsbefore you got on that plane.
My friend died.
We had a car accident.
You were the driver
and you'd been drinking?
That would weigh heavily
on anyone.
Well, there was an investigation,
and I was exonerated.
But still put on desk duty.
Yeah, I couldn't drive.
I wasn't ready.
I didn't want to.
Sorry. What... What exactly
is the point here?
I'm trying to help you process
the magnitude of changes
in your life
in the last five years.
Last four days.
That's my point...
To absorb so much change
in so little time.
You don't have to hide
your emotions.
I'm on your side. Due
respect, but you're not.
Look, I know the drill here.
I break down
and you mark me unfit for duty,
but I am okay.
So how about letting me get back
to the one thing
that I do have left... my job?
I'll need to see you again.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah, bureaucracy.
What's up?
I need a favor.
Know anyone at Rikers?
15 minutes, break's over!
I didn't believe it.
Then I saw your face on TV.
Where were you?
I wish I knew.
Who did this to you?
Doesn't matter.
Whatever they told you,
I didn't do it.
Of course you didn't.
You always said
you have to be a good man.
I tried. I have.
School, no banging... all that.
I got a job at a jewelry store
on 47th Street.
Sometimes, I would close up.
One night a month ago,
I got jumped in the back room,
and when I came to,
everything was gone,
and they think
that I was a part of it.
Adio, what happened to your face
is not from a month ago.
Hmm?
I'm going to fight for you, son.
I'm going to fight for you.
Just up here.
It's the exact set you had.
It's just a different box.
It's not.
Mine had superhero minifigs.
This one doesn't.
Okay, we'll look at it
when we get home, all right?
Besides, you know, you can
mix three sets together, right?
He is risen.
He is not here.
Let go of him.
He is risen.
He is not here.
Everything left's
in the, uh, far case.
Actually, we're here about Adio.
We still doing this?
What happened
to the last detectives?
Uh, we're not the police.
This is Adio's father.
You got some nerve
walking in here.
He cleaned me out...
Entire inventory.
41 years up in smoke.
Some son you raised.
You...
Sorry.
My dad's actually a good guy.
And so is my son.
Look,
I don't know what to think.
I mean, we didn't even know
Adio was his name
until the cops said so.
Turned out,
he gave us a fake I.D.,
fake job references.
So when everything disappears,
no tripped alarm,
he's the only one here?
Tell me exactly what she said.
I wasn't focusing on the words.
I don't remember.
I... Just it was scary.
But he's fine?
As fine as can be expected
after chemo
and a crazy lady
praying in your face.
We will get past this soon
enough. I'm gonna figure it out.
I love
your problem-solving mind,
but I need to know
that Cal is going to be safe.
This'll die down.
We just need to be
extra vigilant until it does.
And what if it doesn't?
You've seen the news.
The whole world
is obsessing over us.
People can go online
and find out where we live.
We will be okay.
I mean, come on.
We got a cop
that lives in our house.
Trigger finger still works.
Yeah, what do you expect?
I had range time 10 days ago...
my time.
About this morning...
Lourdes...
I didn't mean to...
I just need time, okay?
Mick, if you held this
against me for the rest of my...
I told you I don't hold anything
against you.
Well, you could,
and I'd... I'd get it.
And please don't punish Lourdes.
I'm not punishing her, Jared,
but I saw her and you,
and I felt like puking
or fainting or both.
If you could just put yourself
in her shoes... Really?
Is that where you're gonna go?
Losing Evie was hard enough,
but then you?
Lourdes lost her best friend
when you disappeared.
She never replaced you.
And I couldn't replace you.
Now, at this point,
we have no evidence
of passenger or crew involvement
in the explosion.
But that said, we continue
to suspect some nexus between...
Director Vance, if I may.
The explosion is a bit
beside the point.
Where did that plane go
for 5 1/2 years?
Theories abound.
We could be talking about
a wormhole,
about some kind of
extraterrestrial encounter.
But more to the point,
are we in danger?
Was the plane targeted
by some kind of weapon?
Or isitthe weapon?
Do we even know
if those are the same people
that were on that plane in 2013?
We've tested comprehensive
samples of the passengers
and haven't detected
any anomalies.
This is national security
we're talking about.
They should be incarcerated
until we can determine
whether or not they're a threat.
Director Hughes, this is still America.
These people have rights.
I-I suspect
if anyone has answers,
it's someone on that plane,
most likely someone we found
standing 100 yards away
when it blew to bits,
which leaves 20 people.
Of course we were confused.
What, you cook now?
Just when I thought things
couldn't get any stranger.
Hey, thanks for the jail hookup.
How is Radd's son?
His face is bashed in.
It's not safe in there.
Yeah, well, if he gets convicted
and goes upstate,
the place he's at now is
gonna seem like a country club.
I so want this kid to be
innocent for his father's sake.
Hey, can you pull the file
and see if the cops or D.A.
cut some corners?
So it's the...
The police's fault?
I'm just spit-balling here.
Doesn't seem fair that
that flight
may have saved my kid's life
but threatened someone else's.
You heard something
like last time.
Not exactly.
But whatever that was,
whatever this is,
I've got to get
to the bottom of it.
No, Ben, not everything is
a puzzle that you have to solve.
It isn't about solving a puzzle.
This is understanding what
my life has become... ourlives.
If we can't answer that,
we're never gonna be able
to get back to normal.
Have you told Grace?
No.
She has enough going on.
These aren't the same.
Really?
Well, we can try
another store tomorrow.
All right, dinner's ready.
Olive!
Up high.
It smells incredible.
Hey, how about after dinner,
we go for
an old-school ice-cream run?
You still like ice cream, right?
I've got to study.
Soon.
Ah!
Ah, come here.
Come here.
You are supposed to be in bed!
Grr!
Rawr!
My God, we're the parents
of a teenage girl.
Be thankful you missed puberty.
Ouch.
How'd that happen?
Oh.
Scuba diving, actually.
Excuse me?
How many times
did I want us to try diving?
Well, I tried it.
Turns out, it leaves a mark.
Okay, well, you can teach me.
You know how hard this is.
It hasn't even been a week.
Of course I do.
I will.
Bye.
You too.
Do I know him?
Does Ben?
No.
Mick, nobody did
anything wrong here.
Not me, not Jared, not Lourdes.
Not me or Ben.
No, of course not.
I am going to tell him.
I just...
I need to figure out
what I'm gonna do.
Meaning...
who you're gonna be with?
Wow.
Grace, look,
I know that you guys
didn't have a perfect marriage,
but really?
He is your...
He is your husband.
I know.
And I love him.
God help me.
I didn't even remember
how much I loved him
until he came back.
But you have to understand
this is an impossible situation.
This is none of my business,
but you need to figure this out
before Ben does.
He's going through enough.
They said
it was the electrolytes,
but who knows
what was really in there?
Are you saying you think
the government drugged you?
I'm just trying to own my truth.
I don't know for sure
what happened,
but I'm beginning to think that
they didn't tell us everything
that was going on.
They gave us stuff
to eat and drink from a box...
I'll be right back.
What's up?
I, um...
God, this is gonna sound nuts.
But you did come back
to the plane, too,
so I'm guessing you're already
questioning your sanity.
I'm questioning a lot of things.
Have you been...
hearing music?
You mean, like, in my head?
I haven't heard any music,
but I've had a similar feeling
more than once
since we've been back.
Yeah, well, at least I know
I'm not going crazy.
Or at least
you're not the only one.
Hey, dude.
Family portrait?
Yep. Me with no cancer,
my mom and dad, my sister.
Who's that?
I don't know.
You ready?
Yep.
All right, let's go.
Police work checks out, Ben.
Adio was the only one on duty.
I mean, he said he was attacked,
but there's no signs
of forced entry
and other than
the ding on his head...
You think he's lying.
No, I don't know what to think,
but the kid had 12 grand
stashed in his apartment
and he's got a record.
I mean... Shoplifting,
jumping turnstiles?
This is minor stuff. Yeah, but it's
what a jury will look at and say,
"That kid's
heading the wrong direction."
There has to be more I can do.
I mean, why else would I have
been drawn in? Okay, science boy.
Mom was the one
who believed in miracles.
Forget miracles.
Every day Adio is in there,
his life is in danger.
Yeah, well, Mom would also say,
"God works
in mysterious ways."
You know, you can stop
goading me any time now.
I'm not convinced God
has anything to do with this.
You think God wanted Jared
to marry your best friend
instead of you?
That was a terrible thing
to say.
And yet kind of a fair question.
I'm one to talk.
Olive barely looks me
in the eye,
Grace is trying, but...
I still feel like a stranger
in my own home.
I did what I did to get by...
Fake I.D. so I can work,
shoplifted so I can...
So I can eat.
No, no, no, no.
None of this is your fault.
I left you alone.
So if you did something,
even out of desperation...
I didn't!
They beat on me just like
they beating on me in here.
Is there anything he could tell
us that might help confirm...
Look, I did like you taught me.
I kept my head down.
I worked my ass off
being a good man.
One more minute. Being a good man.
Tell them.
Just tell them.
Just tell them, Dad.
Please, please, tata.
Tell them that I'm good.
Please, sir. Tell them, please. Wait, wait.
Please. Just tell them.
Please, sir!
Give us more time!
Don't do this! Just...
Just give us another minute!
Happy birthday, Mick.
I miss you.
Um...
off-center.
Pissed.
Mostly sad.
And why is that?
Uh...
because I miss my mom.
'Cause you don't just stop
being in love with someone.
Um...
'cause my best friend
in the world,
the person I would normally
complain to instead of you
gets to love the person
that I can't.
Howisthat friendship?
Lourdes?
She sent beautiful messages
to a ghost for...
for five years,
and I come back, and I...
couldn't even hug her.
All of the people
that I would normally talk to...
Lourdes, Evie, my mom...
You feel alone.
And out comes
the disability form.
Get what you wanted?
You've accepted what's happened.
That's a good first step.
I'm recommending your
conditional reinstatement...
But I want to keep seeing you.
Hey, I heard the news.
Congratulations, Detective.
Oh, yeah,
it was a posthumous promotion.
I didn't earn it.
I can't even die
the way I'm supposed to.
Just take the win, would you?
And if anyone deserves to have
a break go in there direction...
Thanks.
I'll try not to make it
too awkward around here.
Hey.
How was your day? Good.
Hey, check it out...
Every comfy t-shirt
and cool LEGO set
on the planet Earth.
Thanks, Mom.
Whoa.
Is everything okay?
What's up, buddy?
I missmystuff...
My rock collection,
Art the Dragon.
Oh, Cal, listen...
it's okay to be sad.
I get sad sometimes, too.
I just want everything
back the way it was.
Aw, sweetie, I know, I know.
Dad, can we take that ride now?
After two years or so,
the house was exactly the same.
It was like this sad museum
and the shrink said
we needed to let go
and Mom was a wreck and I...
Honey, if you weren't a wreck
anymore after two years,
I'd say
that sounded pretty healthy.
Wasn't it.
I knew Cal wasn't dead.
You did?
I don't know if it was
some kind of twin thing,
but I could...
I could feel him... alive.
And the therapist,
the counselors at school, Mom,
everyone blew it off,
blewmeoff, but I knew.
Okay.
Does this connect
to why we're in
a pretty gross-smelling
storage facility on Long Island?
Mom listened
to the shrink, okay?
Sh-She packed all your
and Cal's stuff away in boxes,
left on the curb
for Salvation Army
and then went to work.
I called,
and I cancelled the pickup.
Well, if you've had his stuff
all this time,
why didn't you say something?
It's complicated.
Mom doesn't know
about any of this.
Olive, whose locker is this?
Olive.
Friend of Mom's, all right?
"Friend."
Dad.
Okay.
Come here.
You did the right thing.
Hey, are you... are you okay?
Stay here, okay?
Stay here.
Hello?
Y-Yeah, meet me in the back.
Yeah, uh, watches,
diamond rings, bracelets.
Fine. Yeah.
I'll take 10, but you got to
get this stuff out of state.
People are looking for it.
Whoa. How did you...
W... It's not what it looks like.
You robbed your own father
and blamed Adio.
You can take half of this.
Seriously. Come on.
I mean, that kid was going
nowhere. He was just a...
Still don't believe in miracles?
This is everything Adio was
accused of stealing and more.
How?
Don't want to talk about it.
Why? 'Cause then
you'd have to admit
something miraculous
is going on here?
Look, there's definitely
something going on,
but even if it isn't just
some series of coincidences,
which it could still be,
there has to be an explanation.
And God's not
good enough for you?
God's a catchall for things
people don't understand.
Any sufficiently
advanced technology
is indistinguishable from magic.
We just...
need more information.
Right. Technology.
Magic. Gotcha.
Guys, can we go?
Jeter retired.
We'll tell him next season.
Hey, take it easy, pal.
You don't have to
unpack it all tonight.
I just want to find... Art!
There he is.
What else we got here?
You know, you have your sister
to thank for this.
She saved it all for you.
Let's see.
What's that do?
You did this?
You made me feel crazy
for not letting go,
but I was right,
and I'm right this time.
Only this time, you'rethe one
who needs to let go.
Hi.
Sorry.
Is now a good time?
Sure.
Jared's at work.
Already knew that.
Want to come in?
No, that's okay.
I have to be somewhere.
I just wanted to, um...
I saw your posts online.
All of them.
Thank you.
You never stopped
being my best friend.
I hope
that doesn't have to change.
Let's play that one by ear,
okay?
Michaela, I never meant to...
If I'd known that you were...
What, that I was gonna
come back from the dead?
I'm the one who's out of place.
You're not.
This isn't on you.
It's okay, Lou.
You love him.
So do you.
But you're the one he married.
Of course I bless this.
How could I not?
Thank you.
I've... I've spent
all these years
trying not to feel like
a fraud, you know?
You were the one
he was supposed to marry.
No.
No, after everything
that happened...
The... the accident, Evie...
It was too intertwined.
There was...
There was too much pain.
I was gonna give the ring back.
Mick... I was coming
back to say no.
You're not a fraud.
Let it go.
Come here.
Yes, we did, people.
Welcome to New York,
where local time is 11:49 p.m.
On behalf of your flight crew,
we'd like to thank you all
for flying Montego Air.
Seriously?
No service?
Same.
I'm so sorry.
That wasn't Olive's secret
to tell.
I can't believe she would...
She did it for her brother.
Olive is an amazing young woman.
You've done an incredible job,
and I can't imagine
how hard that was.
And I don't...
It doesn't matter
where you found the strength
or with whom.
All I wanted for so long
was to have you and Cal back,
but it was a want
that hurt so much
that I had to let it go.
I know.
But I never had to.
I still love you so damn much,
it hurts.
And I know your love for me
is out of practice,
more like a memory...
but we have a second chance.
Please remember.
When they let us go,
they told us
we weren't supposed to talk,
but I know my rights.
And now that I've spoken up,
I think they're watching me.
I'm telling you, I think
the government is behind this.
I mean, if I'm
supposed to own my truth,
don't you think
they should, too?