Previously on "Manifest"...
Stop!
- What just happened?
- I just h-heard my own voice.
You just had a Calling.
Not all answers can be found in books.
Here.
We shouldn't be talking to believers.
It went sideways even
before the plane disappeared.
The person I was supposed to go with...
Just didn't work out.
Right. 8B.
The seat beside you was empty.
How the hell does the Major
know about Saanvi's discovery?
I had a new realization
about the Callings,
that they might be
transferable genetically.
It is really exciting.
Ben Stone?
- Suzanne?
- I'm a dean.
I'm on a job hunt, so if
you hear of anything...
Send me your C.V. today.
You need me to have
your back around here.
Actually, I think I just
need you to let this go.
Maybe it's for the best... clean break.
We have to talk to Zeke.
Well, once he's out on
bail, we can talk to him.
We have to save him, just like we have
to save the rest of the passengers.
As to the count of assault in
the first degree, I plead guilty.
Zeke, stop. No, you can fight this.
I plead guilty.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hi. Where are you?
You're, uh... You're making
me really nervous, babe.
Okay, I had a really
exciting breakthrough today,
and I'm dying to tell you about
it, so just please hurry, okay?
Bye.
Oh. Excuse me.
- Oh.
- Ooh. Oh.
Excuse me.
Well, well, well, Jamaica, here we come!
It's our honeymoon.
- Congrats.
- Thanks.
Hold the door.
One more coming.
Come on, baby. Come on.
Come on, come on.
There's your seat.
Welcome to Flight 727.
Oh, hey.
Nonstop service from JFK
to Montego Bay, Jamaica.
- Um, do you mind if my hubby sits here?
- No.
Flight attendants, prepare for takeoff.
Looks like sun and...
Something in me died that day,
and it still hurts.
When we came back,
I thought...
Alex might be there.
I mean, it was all over the news.
Have you thought about
what you'd say to Alex?
There's an e-mail in my
drafts folder I keep rewriting.
Why haven't you sent it?
I don't know.
I'm still so angry.
And I'm hurt.
And I'm in love.
I can never find the right words.
Saanvi, you wrote the e-mail.
Send it.
You need completion
so you can finally move on.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Maybe I will.
So, that was your thorn.
What about your rose?
Work's good. I mean, I'm exhausted.
Why is that?
Just in a hurry to prove that I'm right,
you know, that we were
all genetically changed
on that plane.
I've been running a DNA sequencer 24/7.
It's like a needle in a haystack,
but I know it's there.
I admire your perseverance, Saanvi.
Truly remarkable.
- Hey.
Who died?
- He's got another job interview.
- Oh!
It's the same job I've been chasing,
an adjunct professor at Astoria.
- There's just been a lot of hoops
to jump through. - Okay.
Which he has been doing
with flying colors.
So far. They're having me
guest-lecture on Combinatorics.
I don't get it. You were
on a tenure track before.
Yeah, well, now I
can't get on any track.
Soon as they hear I'm a passenger,
- I might as well have the plague.
- Mm.
Only reason I got this chance
- is because I ran into an old colleague.
- Mm.
She was a little more
than an old colleague.
Love you.
See you later.
Okay, I need coffee.
Oh, yeah, here you go.
Wow, why'd you d... Loving the hair.
Sort of.
Thanks.
I love it, too.
See you after school.
Oh, come on, she looks cute.
I mean, I had a buzz cut
and a nose ring at that age.
Oh, I remember, and it was disturbing.
No, it...
So, what, did you just
stop by to throw shade?
I don't know. Being here
makes me feel less alone.
What's the word on Saanvi?
Vance has been surveilling her
around the clock, but nothing.
She still doesn't know she has a leak?
Vance says it's too risky.
Still, I hate lying to her.
Ben, you got to detach.
Oh.
Like you're doing with Zeke.
Okay, fine. Yes, I'm attached.
Have you talked to him?
Um, no, buddy, not yet,
- but I've got some ideas.
- Hey.
Guess who's riding shotgun.
Yes!
Give this to Zeke when you see him.
To be wiped from the face of the Earth,
only to return is an undeniable
message to the world.
Hope, faith, belief...
all shall be rewarded.
The miracle of 828 was for all.
Now, those who feel called
to testify are welcome.
Thanks.
I'm Maxine.
Hi, Maxine.
I'm a Believer.
I was pretty broken
when I first came here.
Yeah, I'm not gonna lie.
My parents, they just...
they didn't get me, and I was lost.
But then I heard Adrian talk
about how we're all connected,
about how we're all a
part of the miracle of 828.
And Adrian says if you
accept that miracle,
we'll all be saved.
Well, it's already saved my life.
- I believe.
- Yes.
I have to get him out of there.
Decorated cop versus ex-con
carrying an illegally purchased firearm.
He was trying to protect...
Guy goes on the run for, what, 62 days?
He turned himself in...
And said ex-con admitted he shot you.
Now you go.
He's not supposed to be in there.
Your guy pled guilty, no lawyer?
That's at least grounds to
petition for a plea withdrawal.
Tell him to let the court know
that I'll be representing him now.
Thanks, Teresa, but we're
not exactly in communication.
Can we get the ball
rolling first, and then,
- once I talk to him or...
- I can start some digging,
but until I'm his lawyer,
my hands are tied.
Saanvi's server is clean.
Swept for bugs, her lab's clean.
So, where's the leak?
The Major has someone
inside the hospital?
- Presumably.
- Any clue who it is?
My guys are keeping a close eye...
Well, that's not good
enough. Saanvi's in danger.
I have a plan if you'll
just shut up for a minute.
Vance, we need to find this mole.
No.
We need to let the mole
lead us to the Major.
Everything we know tells
us what the Major wants
is to control the Callings,
to be sending the messages
you're compelled to follow...
you, your... your sister, your son.
We'd... be her toy soldiers.
So let's point her to
the ultimate soldier,
a passenger whose Callings
are stronger than Cal's even.
Yeah, but I haven't
found anyone who's...
You mean we feed the Major a fake.
Pick someone from your
board. Make it look legit.
I have an address in Pennsylvania.
You'll tell Saanvi he's there.
The ruse percolates up
to the Major, she'll bite.
So not only do we continue
to lie to Saanvi...
We use her. This... This sucks.
No one said making
the world a safer place
was gonna be easy, but the
sooner we find the Major,
the sooner we all go back to our lives.
And this leak in your friend's
lab, it's our best shot.
Set the trap.
Bye.
Oh.
Are you okay?
Thought I'd puke less this time.
Oh, here.
Only thing that keeps food down.
I'm not a fan of ginger,
but I'll eat roadkill
if it quells the nausea.
I feel you.
Not only am I bigger
than I was with twins...
I'm also sicker.
I swear my 6-year-old
thinks her mommy's hung over.
You haven't told her yet?
Once we're out of the woods.
Here, thanks.
Keep it. I can make more.
You made these?
We can't be friends.
Oh. But I offer free refills.
- Solidarity!
- Thanks.
Open her eyes.
Hey, there. How you doing?
I'm here to see Ezekiel Landon.
You gonna be on the list this time?
Look, man. I just... I
really need to see him.
Hold up.
He's not here. It seems
he's been transferred.
What's... Where?
Doesn't say. The system's messed up.
It could take a few days to update.
What did you give me?
What'd you give me, damn it?!
Okay, calm down.
It was just something to help you sleep.
- What the hell was it?!
- Mostly midazolam.
I'm in recovery! You
can't give me that junk!
Look, your doctor rounds in the morning.
We'll take it up with him.
But if you don't want any
more, you need to chill.
I'm worried, Ben. What if it's
not just an error in the system?
What if it's the Major? I mean,
she's taken people before.
Yeah, but not from police custody.
What if that's what the
Callings are warning us about?
I mean, I'm not gonna lose
him, okay? Not like that.
Mick, you're spinning.
Just keep looking.
And if the Major did take
Zeke, we will find him...
when we find her.
Talk to you later.
There you are.
Why is a public defender
asking for Zeke's arrest report?
Why do you think?
Christ, Mick.
The guy confessed.
Just let it go already.
You want to know how
I let this go, Jared?
You revise the report, and you clarify
that the shooting was an accident.
I won't do that.
It was an accident.
We both know that.
No, it was a legit collar.
I know that, and so does
everybody else in this office.
Mick, you keep pushing this,
it's not gonna end well for you.
Is that a threat?
I am trying to get an
innocent man out of jail.
Please, do not make this about us.
Seriously?
This has everything to do with us.
I blew up my entire life for you.
Yeah, I know.
I need us to do the right
thing, though, please.
I'm asking for us to fix this together.
You're asking for too much, Mick.
I'm sorry, but I'm not
gonna torpedo my career
- for some guy I barely trust.
- Just stop. Please.
I am not trying to hurt you. Truly.
But I'm gonna help Zeke,
and I'm gonna do whatever
it takes to do that.
If you don't want to help
me, that is your choice.
But be prepared.
Was that a threat?
Didn't have to be.
- Hey.
Mom had another Calling.
Really?
Yeah, I met this great mom
at the yoga studio today.
And when she was leaving,
I heard myself saying,
"Open her eyes".
And then I saw this
awful gargoyle on her car,
like, looming.
Honey, that's terrifying.
Are... Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm just...
I'm worried about her.
I can't shake this bad feeling.
This creature was terrifying,
but we looked up gargoyles,
and, apparently, they're supposed
to protect you from evil.
So I don't know.
Maybe I'm supposed to
open her eyes to that?
Maybe she's in some kind of trouble?
Maybe she'll be in the next class?
I can't wait till then.
So...
track her down.
Yeah.
She had a Metro Kids
Soccer bumper sticker.
I'll look up where the teams practice.
- What are you doing?
- Helping you.
Absolutely not. You have
enough on your plate.
We got this.
Well, is there anything
I can do to help?
No, babe.
We're good. You get your work done.
I found the website.
Awesome.
Wow. I'll leave you to it, then.
Call if you need me.
Bye.
So, she said her kid was 6.
Does it say where the
younger teams practice?
Come on, baby. Come on, baby.
Gimme aces!
What are we looking for, exactly?
I know, I know. Drug-company NDA.
I'm just a fly on the wall.
Just thank me when you get your Nobel.
I'm vibing epic fail.
We have time for another round.
Um... burnout is actually a thing.
When is the last time you slept?
- Hi.
- Hey.
I wasn't expecting you today.
I think I found a new Holy Grail.
This guy's Callings are insane, Ben.
If you didn't interview him yourself,
I would never believe it.
He's in Philly?
Okay, I need to get his
bloodwork for the lab.
When can we go see him?
Uh, I'll check my calendar.
Well, how about now?
If this guy is having
more intense Callings,
he may have a longer
strand of the mutated gene.
It might be easier for me to isolate.
What's wrong with you?
What do you mean?
Well, why aren't you more excited?
This could be our breakthrough.
The Callings, the Death
Date could all go away.
I mean, isn't this what we've
been working our asses off for?
Oh, of course it is.
I may have gotten a job.
That's really great news.
I need to give a lecture,
meet the faculty.
There's a lot right now.
Well, they would be
really lucky to have you.
Just as soon as you can.
Yeah.
He would've just transferred
in the other day or...
Are you sure there's nothing?
Okay. Thank you.
Ezekiel Landon? Nothing?
Okay.
Uh, yeah. Hi. Just checking in.
Checking in to see if you got
my message about Ezekiel Landon.
Hi there.
I'm Detective Stone from the 129th.
Uh, I'm good. Thank you. How are you?
Yeah, um, just need some help
tracking down an inmate...
Ezekiel Landon.
E- Z-E-K...
You do? You have him?
Can I talk to him?
No, no, no, please,
I just need one minute
to just talk to him about something.
Zeke!
Zeke! Zeke!
Grab my hand!
Zeke, please! Come on! Come on!
Zeke, no!
So, your fate's in the hands
of the Hiring Committee.
They're all sitting in. I talked you up.
Thanks for that.
Left out the part about us.
Doubly thanks for that.
Dr. Tobin in the middle?
Big fan of your paper
on computational math.
- Her vote's in the bag.
- Uh-huh.
Bow tie's the one to impress... Simon.
Okay.
Professor Stone.
TJ!
What are you doing here?
I saw the tweet about your
lecture, figured I'd sit in.
Why? 'Cause you needed a nap?
I'll try not to snore too loud.
Okay, I'll see you in there.
- Good luck.
- Alright.
What did I tell you all?
He's already a favorite
with the students.
Professors Gin Otani...
- Hi. How you doing?
- ... Carol Tobin...
- Hi.
- ... Simon White.
- Professor Stone.
Suzanne raves about you, Ben.
We're delighted you're considering us.
I'm glad to be here.
Okay. Well, let's get
this party started.
This will be a great
way to ease back in.
It's a pretty sleepy class.
Enrollment's about half capacity.
Okay.
Mm.
Guess my tweet about our special
guest lecture piqued interest.
You all know this is
Combinatorics, right?
I hear Game Theory's down the hall.
No one? Alright.
So, how many of you are
actually math majors?
Okay.
Uh, anyone like old movies?
- Sure.
- Mm-hmm.
Who's seen "The Matrix"?
- Oh, yeah.
Welcome back from outer space!
Thank you. I guess.
Now, the fun thing about higher math...
and, yes, I said fun... is
that it can describe something
as complex as simulated reality.
Let's say this is Earth.
Speaking of, where do
you think the plane went?
What's the probability 828
got sucked through a wormhole,
versus being hijacked by aliens?
While you propose a
fascinating hypothetical,
to assess a baseline...
Professor Stone, is your IQ
higher than it used to be?
I heard that one of the
passengers cured cancer.
Flight 828 didn't touch
down for 5 and a half years.
- Where did it fly?
- Are you, like, smarter than Einstein?
- Uh...
- Did you shrink?
Can you predict the future?
To assess a... a...
I read your thesis on
combinatorial matrix theory.
Couldn't that have been used
to map the flight plan of 828?
Great question.
We'll start simple and define
some geocentric coordinates.
Now, to compute the coordinates
of "C" using Bancroft's method,
we'll construct a four-by-four matrix
with the satellites' coordinates
and respective pseudoranges...
not to be confused with pseudo-oranges,
which taste terrible.
But we can use them to help us find
our unknown receiver quantities.
And then we will encapsulate
them in a vector "U".
It says the U6 girls
practice on the east field.
Good job, sleuth!
I wish I could see a gargoyle.
No, you don't. Trust me.
Mom, I've seen way worse stuff.
I wish you didn't have to.
Bring it in! Snack time!
Good effort, girls! Good effort!
- Orange slices.
- That's her.
Good job. Good job.
Alright.
Erika?
Hi.
Grace. Ginger lady?
Oh. Right.
Hi. I haven't seen you here before.
No, it's our first time.
Actually, I'm trying to get
my bookworm son into a sport.
Right.
I think sign-ups are closed.
Um, you're not green,
so I take it the nausea's better.
Is everything else okay?
I know second pregnancies
can be so hard.
- Pulled in every dire...
- I have to run.
My husband's waiting for me.
Holly!
Come on. What are you doing?
Open her eyes.
You had it again.
She's scared of something.
But when the person
you're called to help
doesn't want to be
helped, what do you do?
Detective Stone. I need
a one-on-one with a C.I.
Patient Ezekiel Landon.
Didn't see you on the books,
Detective. Did you call ahead?
An emergency came up.
Consider this calling.
Not how this works.
Dangerous guys in here.
I need a guard dedicated for the meet.
- Not my rules.
- Great. Well, I've got lives at stake.
So if you wanna ring up my
boss, you go right ahead.
Yeah.
I got a C.I.- visit request here.
Ezekiel Landon.
Hey. What's up?
You find something new?
Only the gene mutation.
Or at least a mutation,
which could be watershed,
maybe even the key to what
happened to us on that plane.
It's like...
It's like the magic bullet.
Now I-I really need you to
take me to your guy, Ben,
because I need to test his
blood against my trials t...
I can't, uh...
I can't do that.
What's going on?
The Major has a mole
accessing your research.
How do you know that?
I just do, trust me.
And if your discovery leaks to her...
Saanvi...
Yeah?
Okay.
What if the Major already knows
about the passenger's new Callings?
She... She came after Cal.
- Imagine what she's...
- There are no new Callings.
What?
It was a fake,
made up as bait to lure the Major.
Okay, I don't, um...
I don't understand.
Why would you lie to me?
Because you were safer not knowing.
You might've inadvertently
clued in the Major.
All of this, there is no way
this is just you and Michaela.
You're working with someone.
Vance.
He survived the accident,
went into hiding.
- Michaela and I...
- Michaela and you what?!
I am part of that group, Ben,
and you didn't trust me?
No, it's not about trust. It
was for your own protection.
Okay, I just... I need you to leave.
Did you think I wanted to
lie? I didn't want any of this.
Yeah, but you had a choice!
I didn't.
Go.
Saanvi, please be careful. This leak...
How's he not a C.I.?
Detective just blew by here
claiming he's part of some case.
Zeke.
Oh, my God. What have they done to you?
Zeke. Hey.
Hey, come on. Wake up. Wake up.
- Look at me, look at me.
- Michaela?
Oh, my God. Thank God.
Look, I don't have much time, okay?
But we got to get you out of here.
Cal and I, we had a Calling.
You were on the airplane with us.
I know.
I saw it, too.
Good.
What did they do to you?
The Callings...
I was shaking, and they
gave me drugs to stop it.
That's why you couldn't see us.
I screwed up.
You were right.
I'm not supposed to be here.
I'm supposed to be with you. I'm sorry.
I am here now, okay?
I know, but it's too late.
No, it's not. I am
getting you out of here.
You never give up, do you?
You can't be in here.
Tell them you need a lawyer.
Teresa Yin. It's on the back of that.
Tell them that you need a lawyer.
She's expecting your call!
Do you have any idea
the damage you just caused?
I told you, she found the magic bullet.
I couldn't risk it getting
into the wrong hands.
You blew my cover,
eviscerated our opportunity
to find the leak!
Look, Saanvi might be pissed,
but your secret is safe.
- I trust her.
- Oh.
Well, that's good to know
because now the only people
who know I'm alive are our
wives, Michaela, Saanvi.
I'm sorry, Vance.
We need to get in front of this.
Maybe not.
Saanvi could still
help us find the leak.
You said yourself
espionage is a long game.
Our asset is compromised.
We have a very small window
before this whole operation collapses.
Now that we've had
a breakthrough, what do we do?
Are we modifying our approach?
You're always asking me questions.
Um, 'cause I'm your lab assistant?
Not anymore.
There was no breakthrough.
It was a fluke, and we're
just tilting at windmills.
I appreciate your help,
Troy, but I don't need you.
This doesn't make any sense.
You...
Ellen? It's Saanvi.
Uh, I've had a really awful day.
Is there any way you can squeeze me in?
Hey! Hi.
You, um... You weren't in class today.
I was worried. I thought maybe you...
Are you following me?
No. No.
I'm... I'm sorry.
This must seem very bizarre. Uh...
I'm worried about you.
Call it intuition. I don't know.
I just... I have a bad feeling
that something's wrong,
and if you're, um...
if you're afraid or
you have a problem...
My only problem is you
and your freak 828 boy.
I know who your son
is. I watch the news.
I- I'm trying to help you.
Stay away.
Stay away from my family.
Your son is an abomination.
Oh, I get it! I get it now!
I was supposed to open your eyes
because you are a frightened,
small-minded woman
who's afraid of anything
she doesn't understand.
I hope you lose that baby.
The people versus Ezekiel Landon.
Thank you for finding
time on your docket
for this emergency hearing, Your Honor.
Pursuant to Section 220.6,
my client moves to
withdraw his guilty plea.
Further, I've filed a motion
to dismiss all charges.
I'll grant the plea withdrawal.
On what grounds do you move to dismiss?
New evidence calling into question
the veracity of the investigation.
Your Honor, this is absurd.
Mr. Landon shot an NYPD detective.
Yes. Detective Stone.
I'd like to call her as a witness.
Your Honor, this is a
waste of taxpayer dollars
and the court's time.
And yet the court awaits
Detective Stone's
testimony with interest.
Your Honor, I call
Detective Michaela Stone
to the stand.
Detective Stone, what do you know
about the night you were shot?
I know that it was an accident.
I know that Zeke Landon
is not a criminal.
He even tried to save my life.
I also know that Detective Vasquez
abused NYPD resources to
lift and run Zeke's prints.
He also had him followed.
He even broke into my
house without probable cause
to confront Zeke.
None of this had to happen.
Objection... Lacks foundation.
The State demands
the courtroom be cleared
and this hearing postponed.
It was an accident.
I've informed Internal
Affairs, the arresting officer,
and my captain about this
miscarriage of justice.
I am tired of being told to let this go.
I'm not going to let this go.
I am the one that took that bullet.
I am the victim.
And I am telling you
that this man is innocent.
The State requests a
sidebar, Your Honor.
Why can't I reach Saanvi?
Why do you think?
You warned her she's being watched.
She's being careful,
probably ditched her phone.
She clearly wants nothing
to do with me or this.
Let's pray she doesn't
do anything stupid.
I doubt Saanvi's done
anything stupid her whole life.
Well, good,
'cause right now her life
is exactly what's at stake.
Ben was the one person
I thought I could trust.
Yet you're not shutting
down. You reached out to me,
rather than your usual
pattern of retreating.
That's substantive progress.
You know how you encourage
me to look for the rose?
And something that I'm grateful for?
Yes, of course.
I'm grateful for you.
And also that I have my research.
Speaking of, I think I made a discovery.
I doubt I'll understand a word of it,
but why don't you tell me?
It's huge.
It may even be the key to discovering
what happened to us on that plane.
It's in my fridge in the lab.
My next client canceled.
We have time.
Okay.
The State has decided
to reduce the charges
to class A misdemeanor,
possession of a firearm.
Pretty sweet offer, Counselor.
How does your client plead?
Stand up and plead no contest.
No contest, Your Honor.
Very well, Mr. Landon. You're
sentenced to time served.
Pending processing, you're free to go.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you very much.
Guess I'm not the only one
who blew up their life.
Hope it was worth it.
No one's ever done
anything like that for me.
You didn't just storm the castle...
You burned it to the ground.
Yeah, well, you weren't
supposed to be inside.
Now what?
How does a home-cooked meal sound?
You busted me outta jail.
Least I can do is cook for you.
Yeah, that's true.
In a surprising turn of events,
Flight 828 passenger and
NYPD detective Michaela Stone
took the stand today to
exonerate her alleged shooter,
Ezekiel Landon.
How 'bout you turn that crap off?
How 'bout some manners?
Can you turn that crap off, please?
Amen to that, brother.
828 wing nuts shouldn't be allowed
to carry the badge and gun.
Put those on my tab.
This could be a disaster.
- Well, let's hope not.
- Yeah, let's hope not.
I don't know who's
happier that Zeke's back,
you or that giddy little boy.
Cal seems to think
the plane Callings will stop.
You don't?
I think it's bigger than that.
I wish I could protect
Cal from all of this.
It really hit home,
how much fear and hatred
there is out there.
That woman had so much venom.
Maybe if she knew
what miracles you guys are,
she wouldn't be so scared.
You mean if she knew about the Callings?
Well, if it were me,
I'd share my gift with the world,
make it a better place.
Where did little Miss
Peace and Love come from?
I don't know, but too
bad you can't sprinkle
some of that on the gargoyle lady.
The Calling told me to open her eyes,
but I didn't.
Maybe it's not over, then.
Who wishes to share their
acceptance of the miracle?
Um, I'm Olive.
Hi, Olive.
My dad, my brother, and my
aunt were all 828 passengers.
Since they've returned,
I've been fighting to go back to normal.
I just... I didn't feel
like I belonged anymore.
But, being here...
I now realize that we... we all belong.
All of us are special.
All of us.
I embrace the miracle,
and I-I really hope my family does, too.
I believe.
Blessed are the
children of the returned,
for they will inherit the miracle.
Blessed are the
children of the returned,
for they will inherit the miracle.
Blessed are the
children of the returned,
for they will inherit the miracle.
You were great today.
You kept the students
awake and off their phones.
I'm just glad they didn't boo me.
We want you to lead a seminar
on our next faculty retreat...
"Making Math Accessible".
Great.
Ah, the wife.
- Welcome aboard, Ben.
- Thank you.
I'll show to your new
office, Professor Stone.
What did you do?
I hired him.
"Welcome to my parlor",
said the spider to the fly.
You were right.
I found the leak.
When I found out I had a leak,
I had to see for myself, so...
You set up your own surveillance.
- See?
- I told you she could help.
What's he doing?
Siphoning samples of my
vials so I wouldn't notice.
- You know this guy?
- Dr. Mathews.
But however he's involved,
he's not the leak.
How do you know?
I only told one person about that vial.
My psychiatrist, who
Mathews introduced me to...
Dr. Ellen Regier.
I'm sorry, Saanvi. I really am.
We never should've kept you in the dark.
Kudos to your audacity, but
now the Major has your findings,
the ramifications of which I
can't even begin to describe.
Those vials were fake.
It'll take them weeks to figure it out.
You set up a trap?
Oh, she is a much better
spy than you, Stone.
How is Dr. Regier
involved in all of this?
Do you have a description?
Alright. Pretty much every
top-secret-security-cleared
female in the DoD.
Recognize anyone?
There.
That's her.
You certain?
I poured my heart out
to that bitch for months.
Yes, that's her.
"Kathryn Fitz.
Psychological warfare specialist,
30 years in black ops.
Major General".
She's not informing the Major.
She is the Major.
Now what?
Now we turn the tables.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org