MICHAELA: No one can explain
what happened to us
on April 7, 2013.
Some people called it impossible.
Others called it a miracle.
All I know is...
it was the day my life changed forever.
If you'd seen us that afternoon,
you probably would have thought
we looked like
a typical American family
returning home from vacation.
My brother, Ben, and his wife, Grace,
still in love after 15 years.
Their twins, Olive and Cal,
always bickering
like an old married couple.
And the real old married couple...
my parents.
Still in perfect health,
still trying to run my life.
It's not just about you.
This family needs
something to celebrate.
Okay, that's a pretty backwards
reason for a wedding, but...
STEVE: How's this for a reason?
Jared loves you.
And I know you love him.
Typical, right?
But what you couldn't see
is that Cal's leukemia
wasn't responding to treatment...
or that Ben and Grace
were desperately struggling
to find a cure...
or that I still had nightmares
about the car accident.
Michaela Beth, even people
that have made mistakes
deserve happiness.
[SCOFFS]
You know my favorite verse...
"All things work together for good."
I don't believe that anymore,
Mom. How can I?
Which is why, when I got the
chance to stay away from home
for even a few more hours,
I jumped at it.
WOMAN: All passengers
for Flight 537 to New York,
John F. Kennedy Airport,
your attention, please.
This flight is oversold.
We are offering travel vouchers
in the amount of $400
for anyone willing
to take a later flight.
Yes. That's me.
- No.
- It's $400 per person.
That's our next trip
down to the Mayo Clinic.
I'll stay with Dad.
There you go. Man time.
BEN: All right. All right.
So Grace and Olive and my folks
took the first flight home
while Ben and Cal and I
waited for Flight 828.
♪ ♪
Funny how one little decision
can ruin your life.
But also save it.
[KEYBOARD KEYS CLACKING]
[CABIN BELL DINGS]
Peanuts? You're welcome.
Ma'am, would you like peanuts?
Do you have anything sodium-free?
Peanuts?
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Mom's not wrong. Jared's not
gonna wait around forever.
Great marriage pep talk. Thank you.
Why are you fighting this,
when all it's gonna
do is make you happy?
It's all we want for you.
That was really sweet of you.
You must be drunk.
Definitely. [CHUCKLES]
Say yes to Jared.
Have a wedding and a honeymoon.
Turn the page. It's time.
And, yes, you deserve it.
Truly.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[ALARM BLARING]
[PASSENGERS SHOUTING]
It's okay. Everyone...
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[BANGING]
[BLARING CONTINUES]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[PASSENGERS SCREAMING]
[ENGINES WHINING]
[CABIN BELL DINGS]
DALY: Ugh. Terribly sorry, folks.
That was extreme turbulence
resulting from a sudden weather surge
that was not on the radar.
Rest assured,
engines' controls are okay.
But, please, keep
those seat belts fastened.
Is there anything
crazy-important on there?
Only six weeks' worth of research data.
Stewardess.
I'm gonna need another drink.
You and me both, sir.
You and me both.
DALY: New York approach.
Montego Air 8-2-8.
Level one five thousand.
MAN: This is New York approach.
Uh, repeat your call sign, please?
We are MA 8-2-8.
[SWITCH CLICKS, BEEP]
Repeat... Montego Air 8-2-8.
Montego Bay to JFK. Copy that?
CLARKE: [JAMAICAN ACCENT] Any time now.
Can I get your name, Captain,
and the number of passengers
and crew on your manifest?
Uh, this is Captain William Daly.
We have 191 souls on board,
all of whom would love to touch
down on one of your runways.
[CABIN BELL DINGS]
DALY: Sorry, folks.
Apologies and a half.
We are diverting to Stewart Airport
- up in Newburgh...
- [PASSENGERS GROAN]
...spitting distance from the city.
But for any of those
who are trying to make
a connecting flight, we owe you one.
Flight attendants, prepare for landing.
[CABIN BELL DINGS]
[ENGINES ROARING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[SCATTERED APPLAUSE]
[CABIN BELL DINGS] Yes, we did, people.
Welcome to New York,
where local time is 11:49 p.m.
On behalf of your flight crew,
we'd like to thank you all
for flying Montego Air.
Seriously? No service?
- Same.
- [CABIN BELL DINGS]
DALY: And the inconvenience continues.
We've been asked to deplane
right here on the tarmac.
Cool!
[SIRENS WAILING]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
[SIRENS STOP]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
♪ ♪
Who's Daly?
When do they ever do this?
Never. Something's happening.
♪ ♪
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
MICHAELA: Excuse me.
T-There are sick people here.
What exactly is the problem?
♪ ♪
The problem, ladies and gentlemen,
is your plane departed
Montego Bay, Jamaica,
on April 7, 2013.
Today is November 4, 2018.
[PASSENGERS MURMURING]
You've all been missing,
presumed dead, for 5 1/2 years.
- What?!
- [PASSENGERS MURMURING]
♪ ♪
[ENGINES ROARING]
[RADIO CHATTER]
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- Hm?
Medicine.
♪ ♪
When can we leave?
[PILLS RATTLE]
Soon, buddy. They're just...
They're gonna talk to us,
take a little look at us,
and then we can get out of here, okay?
♪ ♪
If it's really been five years,
how am I still alive?
♪ ♪
Do you feel five years older?
Neither do I.
Don't worry.
♪ ♪
VANCE: Let's start simply.
After the plane left Jamaica,
where did you land?
We never landed anywhere
until we landed right here.
Now tell me what really happened.
Took off on time. Arrived
3 hours and 19 minutes later.
Is this some kind of a stunt?!
For God's sake!
It makes no sense.
Clear air, heavy chop.
Instruments never detected a thing.
Turbulence.
Like the roof was going to
come right off, you know?
[SOBBING] I... We...
What are you talking...
I'm gonna sue this airline
into the ground.
I need to make a call, okay?
I need... I need to
call my boy... my fiancé.
My son has leukemia.
He's not about to submit
to testing of any kind.
I want my mom.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
♪ ♪
GRACE: Ben!
Ben! Ben! Oh, my God!
♪ ♪
STEVE: Ohh!
It's okay. We're okay.
- [LAUGHS]
- We're okay.
I don't understand.
How are you exactly the same?
You... haven't aged a day.
[SOBS]
♪ ♪
Olive.
Cal! Cal!
Cal! Cal, Cal.
I know, I know, I know. It's okay.
Where's, uh... Where's Mom and Jared?
I texted with Jared.
He couldn't make it over.
Work emergency.
And Mom?
Your mom got sick.
She... She fought so hard.
What do you... What do you mean, sick?
[SIGHS]
She loved you kids
more than life itself.
- You were everything to her.
- No! No, no.
I was just... I was just running
with her on the beach.
I came out here to tell her
t-that she was right about me and Jared.
[SOBBING] No, Dad. No, no!
No, I can't...
[SOBBING]
♪ ♪
WOMAN: ...as the entire world
focuses on Flight 828.
MAN: Where was Flight 828
for five years?
WOMAN: As a multitude
of government agencies,
including NASA,
Homeland Security, and the NSA,
descend upon New York,
the story of the century
now touches this
middle-class neighborhood
here in suburban Queens.
♪ ♪
GRACE: Your mom made it after...
That cheesy verse was her mantra.
[CHUCKLES]
Actually, I'm pretty sure it's
the last thing she said to me.
I'm sorry to stick you down here.
We hung onto your apartment
as long as we could,
but eventually, we had to let it go.
Hey, can I use the phone?
Yeah, of course.
[CELLPHONE UNLOCKS] Thanks.
We gave up the landline.
[RINGING]
Hey, it's Jared Vasquez.
Please leave a mess...
All set.
Thank you.
Hey, Grace?
Look, I know you
probably don't want, uh,
Miss Bad Influence
hanging around the kids.
- I would get...
- Michaela, no.
M-Michaela... this is your home.
For as long as you'd like.
That's ancient history.
It was two days ago for me.
I am still the same screw-up
that you said goodbye to in Jamaica.
The universe just gave all of us
a do-over.
Everything that happened before
goes out the window.
MICHAELA: [ECHOING] All things...
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm okay. Sorry.
[CHUCKLES] Okay.
Anything you need, please.
- I'm just upstairs.
- Okay. Thanks.
♪ ♪
[INSTRUMENT WARBLING]
[BEEPING]
♪ ♪
We interviewed every
last one of them. Nothing.
And still haven't come across
a single substance
dating from any time between
the day the flight took off
and when it returned.
It's as if the plane never left the sky.
Do I have to say out loud
that that's impossible?
Director, no one on that plane
aged a day.
I think we've taken impossible
off the table.
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
As I live and breathe.
Hey, Sarge.
Getting a lifetime supply of hugs.
Of course you are.
Come back from the dead,
you've earned yourself a hug.
Didn't expect you getting
back to work this fast.
Probably not quite yet,
assuming I actually
still have a job here.
Technically, you still remain
on desk duty.
I'm guessing we can drum up a
desk for you when you're ready.
♪ ♪
You're so young.
You look exactly the same.
Yeah.
You look even better.
I don't know how men do that.
I'm sorry I didn't come to the airport.
I'm lead detective
on this abduction case.
- Every hour counts.
- Detective? Wow.
A lot has changed
since you've been gone.
♪ ♪
Who is she?
[SIGHS]
Lourdes.
That makes sense. She always
told me how lucky I was.
Michaela, it was two years
before I even looked at another woman.
Sorry. I, uh...
♪ ♪
[MONITOR BEEPING]
You okay?
His cell count is exactly the
same. We're right where we were.
It's amazing. It's truly amazing.
So we pick up with the same
regimen, right where we left off?
Well, that would be our backup plan,
but there's a new treatment
protocol for pediatric cases
within Cal's profile.
It's a game-changer.
Game-changer how?
Well, it's still in the phase 3 trial,
so we have to apply for him
to join the patient group,
which I'll do right now.
If we get him admitted and
we get a jump on the treatment,
the odds are excellent.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Uh, can we manage
some expectations here?
You said six months. You implied
it would take a miracle.
Earth to Ben.
You all came back to us.
You are sitting here right now, baby.
[LAUGHING] A miracle just happened!
♪ ♪
WOMAN: ...coverage of Montego
Air Flight 828 will continue,
but first this NBC4 Update.
Sisters Hallie and
Samantha Pyler of Astoria
were abducted from their
backyard early Sunday morning.
The case has resulted in
thousands of calls to the NYPD,
according to 129th Precinct
Detective Jared Vasquez.
We're working nonstop
pursuing all viable leads.
Please keep your eyes and ears open.
If you hear anything,
make sure you contact
your local police department.
MICHAELA: [ECHOING] Slower.
Slower!
Excuse me. Can you slow down?
- Excuse me?
- Do I come to your work
and tell you how to do your job?
- Slower!
- [GRUNTS]
Slow down! Now!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
How'd you see him coming?!
Lady! How the hell?!
♪ ♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
You all right?
Is your mind messing with you?
[CHUCKLES] Where to begin?
Ben, I'm serious.
Earlier today, I heard
a voice in my head.
What do you mean, voice? Whose voice?
It was my voice,
but it was talking to me.
So, like a psychotic voice?
Can you not diagnose me
right now and just listen?
Look, normally I'd go
to Mom about all this,
but now I'm stuck with you.
- I lost my mom, too.
- I didn't mean that.
I know. Sorry.
♪ ♪
You want to know what I think?
I think it sounds like
you're losing your mind.
[CHUCKLES] Yeah, of course you do.
No, I'm not being glib.
Keep it to yourself before
you end up in a psych ward
having exploratory brain surgery.
What do you think, the government
just sent us home and forgot about us?
Who knows what they'll try in
order to find out what happened?
And I don't want anything
to happen to you.
That's what I think.
- [HORNS HONKING]
- [INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- Hold your horses, honey.
- What? What?!
Oh, my. [CHUCKLES] Really?
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
ALL: Surprise!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
- Saanvi?
- Dr. Cardoso. Hi.
Look, I don't understand.
I was trying to race to you
so I can get you my research
off of the portal, and...
I got your research five years ago.
Your cell-regeneration model
isn't just theoretical after all.
It works? As an actual clinical success?
We've been treating
pediatric cancer patients
for close to 30 months.
Oh, you can't be serious.
Couldn't be more. It's already
saved hundreds of young lives.
[CHUCKLES]
Dad, can I have a pretzel?
Pretzel?
I guess.
- Here you go, buddy.
- Thanks.
[HORNS HONKING]
I need a job.
If we luck into this treatment,
chances are it's gonna cost a fortune,
and work insurance won't pay for it.
We don't know that.
It pays for Olive's therapy.
She goes to therapy?
Yeah. Twice a week. For years now.
Early on, she didn't even
want to leave the house,
let alone ride in a car or go to school.
She couldn't have sleepovers
'cause of the nightmares.
I mean, most of that's gone now,
thank God.
She grew up too fast.
She had no choice.
♪ ♪
[DOGS BARKING]
[ECHOING] Set them free!
[BARKING CONTINUES]
Set them free!
♪ ♪
Set them free.
[BARKING CONTINUES]
♪ ♪
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
Set them free.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Set them free!
♪ ♪
[DOGS BARKING]
[BARKING CONTINUES]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF, BARKING STOPS]
How'd you find me?
[BARKING RESUMES]
Ben.
What are you doing here?
Setting them free.
I've been hearing it ever since
I drove by here this afternoon.
You said I was losing my mind,
Ben! Why'd you lie to me?
Because maybe I don't want
to be a circus freak!
I don't have the time for it.
I got to help Cal, find a goddamn job,
get to know my daughter,
reclaim my life!
Do you think I am
any happier about this?
Who would want to reclaim my life, Ben?
Part of me wishes we
hadn't come back at all,
but here we are.
[VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES]
To be clear, this is a felony.
Yeah, I'm a police officer.
I'm pretty sure I know what a felony is.
[DOGS BARKING]
Hey, what if they attack us?
They'd be doing their job.
[BARKING CONTINUES]
[BARKING STOPS]
♪ ♪
That was bizarre.
You think?
Now what?
I don't know.
But hearing a voice in your head
one time is a fluke. Twice?
Now happening to the both of us?
Not a fluke.
Older lady marches in this morning,
says she witnessed a break-in last night
on a commercial property across
from her residence.
Hell of a story.
You need me on this because...?
She was pretty resourceful.
Recorded the whole thing on her phone.
[KEYBOARD CLACKS]
They never enter the property,
just let the dogs out,
which were picked up
by Animal Control this morning.
Look, I could go ahead and
process the complaint, unless...
you want to handle it.
JARED: Help me out here.
Michaela, I got three detectives
and eight uniforms
waiting on my direction
to find these abducted girls,
and I'm here trying
to put out your fire.
Does this have to do with me?
Excuse me. How?
I don't know. All right?
Acting out, you know,
trying to get my attention,
get back at me.
You are such a guy.
I break open a fence,
and, yeah, it's because
you've married my best friend.
Look, Lourdes is amazing.
You're both amazing.
I was gone.
How can I blame either of you, right?
Fine. Then what?
What?
Huh.
I don't know.
How about the fact that
I take off in a plane,
and when I land, my mom is dead?
Thanks for your condolences, by the way.
How about the fact that I have
no home, no phone number,
not a single worldly possession
at all to my name?
How about that I lost 5 years,
6 months, and 28 days
of the world, of life?
How about... Never mind that my lawyer
convinced a judge that I was innocent.
I will never, ever stop believing
that I didn't commit murder
when Evie died sitting
next to me in my car.
So, yeah, as I am standing here,
I am trying to figure out
whether or not I should be
grateful for being back and alive
or just guilty, Jared.
Which is where I'm leaning.
♪ ♪
[SOBBING]
Michaela, I'm sorry about your mother.
I'm so sorry about everything.
I'm still trying to wrap my mind
around it all myself.
Believe me. But I still need an answer.
Why? Why did you and your
brother break open that fence?
I can't explain it. I wish I could.
Go inside and put some more clothes on.
- Why?
- 'Cause you're coming with me
to make this go away
and save your career.
Please.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Over here!
MAN: All right, both teams,
take a break!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
MAN: Touch and go. Touch and go.
Dad. What are you doing here?
Checking out the team.
You guys look good.
Thanks. Parents don't usually
show up to practice.
Well, this parent's got
some catching up to do.
Listen. I...
just wanted to say I'm so sorry for...
everything.
Dad, you don't have to apologize
for something that happened to you.
I made the choice to stay behind.
- It was a long time ago, Dad.
- Not for me.
Here you've been all this time, stuck,
picking up the pieces.
Even before I got on that plane,
I'd been so caught up with
trying to help Cal get better
so he could live a long life. I...
I lost sight of your life.
♪ ♪
And now you probably feel
like you don't know me.
But we're gonna fix that.
I'm not going anywhere.
♪ ♪
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Hey, you better get back out there.
♪ ♪
DR. MILLER: We have a full plate
today, so we'll just table
the rest of the reports until next week.
Is that good?
Moving on to new applicants.
How often do these reviews happen?
Oh. Almost every day.
Your survival rates
are through the roof.
Who wouldn't want in?
Okay, here we go.
This is an unusual case.
Male born April 19, 2002.
Initial diagnosis was back in 2011.
Excuse me?
Treating narrative says
the boy was on Flight 828.
Wow. Uh...
Okay, uh, unfortunately,
his diagnosis date
is outside the study parameters.
He's lived with this disease
for more than six years.
No, excuse me. For him,
it hasn't been six years.
Now, if this boy needed treatment
before he got onto that plane,
he undoubtedly would need it now.
Of course, I understand
how you feel, but...
we can't risk breaking protocol.
I think we need to deny.
Are we in agreement?
[INDISTINCT MURMURING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
- [KNOCK ON DOOR]
- Oh, there you are.
I reviewed his profile.
He is all but terminal.
Saanvi, we can't save everyone.
No, of course not, but we can try.
For the credibility of the study,
only the most viable cases
can be included.
Says who? This is your study
based on my research.
I'm entitled to a voice here.
We're months away from being bought
by a major pharmaceutical.
There's too much money
on the line for both of us,
and I won't let that be jeopardized
by an aberrant patient
whose results might compromise
our track record.
Who knows what happened to him
on that plane?
Do you want to know what
happened to him on that plane?
The exact same thing
that happened to me.
We both got a second chance.
To start over, to live.
And I can't explain to you why or how,
but I'm not ruling out that just
maybe he came back to be saved
and I came back to save him.
And I couldn't care less
about the money.
We're giving this boy his chance.
[DOGS WHINING]
Come on.
Is this really necessary?
Yeah. Yeah. You're doing this.
I'm just along for the ride.
Let's just hope he doesn't
want to press charges.
MICHAELA: [ECHOING] Set them free.
Are you okay?
Set them free! [GASPS, GROANS]
Hey, go sit in the car.
[DOGS BARKING]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING, METAL GRINDING]
Hello! Mr. Garrison?!
Hello?!
[MACHINE POWERING DOWN]
GARRISON: There those adventurers are!
Oh, yes, yes. Come here. Come here.
Oh, you good boys.
Detective Jared Vasquez with NYPD.
Oh, thank you, Detective.
Aren't you glad to see me, huh?
Set them free.
♪ ♪
WOMAN: Flight 828 now boarding.
Flight 828.
All things work together for good.
[HINGES CREAK]
Listen, Mr. Garrison. I have to disclose
that we're aware of who
broke open your gate.
- Are ya, now?
- Yeah.
They're two people who have just been
through a hell of a crisis, sir.
I'd consider it a favor
if you'd be willing
to, uh, forgo pressing charges.
Of course, I'll pay for all the repairs.
Not a problem. I'm not looking
to put anyone behind bars.
♪ ♪
Set them free. Set them free!
Set them free. Set them free.
♪ ♪
Set! Them! Free! Set them free.
Set them free.
♪ ♪
- What the hell are you doing?!
- Michaela! Stop!
Michaela!
[CHILDREN SOBBING]
Jared!
[HANDCUFFS CLICK]
[CHILDREN SOBBING, BAR CLANGS]
It's okay. It's okay. You're going home.
It's okay. It's done. It's all over.
Are you guys okay? Are you okay?
Okay. [BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SIREN WAILS]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS,
POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Officer.
Captain. Long time no see.
For you, at least.
Sounds like congratulations
are in order.
According to Vasquez, this was all you.
Happy to help.
Take a few days off, clear your head,
then come in, and we'll talk.
See if we can figure out
getting you back on the beat.
Thank you.
Those girls are alive
because you came back.
It's lucky for all of us.
[RADIO CHATTER CONTINUES]
Thanks for putting in a good word.
It's the least I can do.
So, I suppose you're not
gonna explain to me
what happened here today.
Like I said, I wish I could. I...
♪ ♪
You still take my breath away.
Say hi to Lourdes for me.
♪ ♪
[CELLPHONE RINGS, STOPS ABRUPTLY]
You okay?
Yeah.
Usually you're the optimist.
I'm doom and gloom, remember?
I am optimistic.
And so grateful.
Said the woman looking like
she's about to toss her cookies.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I have so much to apologize to you for.
We don't have to get into this now.
No, I know. I just...
I have spent every day of
the last five years blaming you.
Not only for taking that later flight,
but for making Cal so desperate
for your attention
that he wanted to stay with you.
I had maybe, what,
six months left with him?
And even that you took away from me.
But the thing is...
I realize now that...
for Cal to be here with us today...
...for Olive to have her twin alive,
to maybe grow up beside her...
Cal had to be on that plane.
He had to.
♪ ♪
Oh, what you've both been through.
The only reason we were
on that trip in the first place
was because you insisted...
and bribed me with sex.
[CHUCKLES]
[SNIFFLES]
So if anyone saved Cal...
I'm pretty sure it was you.
No.
This is bigger than us.
[VIDEO GAME PLAYING]
♪ ♪
Copy. Everything checks out.
Then tomorrow, we take it
apart piece by piece.
This isn't close to over.
MAN ON TV:
Williams into the front court.
- Dumps it off left side.
- Peel!
How are you so fast?
- Dump.
- Finished.
- Oh, come on.
- That's ridiculous.
- Cal! Amazing!
- You just learned how to play.
BEN: [LAUGHS] Nice.
Well, not bad for the tiniest
15-year-old on...
Ben? Are you all right?
Yeah, I just got dizzy for a second.
I'm fine, really. Don't worry.
Everything's great.
Drink some water. I'll get more snacks.
WOMAN ON TV: ...NBC4 update.
Sisters Hallie and Samantha
Pyler have been rescued.
The kidnapped sisters were found safe
at an Astoria metal shop
and are being treated at the scene.
[CELLPHONE BUZZES]
♪ ♪
[KEYBOARD CLICKING]
[WHISPERS] What are you gonna do?
♪ ♪
[DOOR OPENS]
Welcome home. Ears burning much?
You're the subject
of my sermon this Sunday.
How do we know if we're the called?
We know in our heart.
You okay?
Michaela?
Can I take this?
As long as you put it to good use.
Looks like your ride's here.
[DOOR CLOSES]
♪ ♪
You saved those girls.
We saved those girls.
How'd you know I was here?
I just... knew.
What is this?
What is happening?
How about this? There were a lot
of people on that plane.
Why you and me? What makes two
head cases like us so special?
What's the probability
it's just you and me?
♪ ♪
MICHAELA: And, of course, it wasn't
just the two of us.
♪ ♪
[VIOLIN PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[TELEVISION PLAYING]
♪ ♪
Ben and I didn't know
any of these people yet.
♪ ♪
But soon, we'd know them
as well as we know ourselves.
♪ ♪
As for whatever force
brought us all here...
...it had no interest
in being investigated.
♪ ♪
And as for the group of us?
This was just the beginning.
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com