Let me go now, please.
Your wife's sick.
What if I could help her?
Khatri found someone with
altered genetic qualities.
A way to repair diseases.
Speak to Khatri.
(SCREAMS)
We need to get you to the hospital.
You need stitches.
Talk to her. Calm her down.
Let me go!
Who's the extraction?
It's the sheriff.
Anything we should know?
Bit of a character apparently.
It's not this boy who'll kill the demon.
It's you. Only Dan.
Too late.
♪ The river did come to me ♪
♪ Straight into my arms ♪
♪ I try to caress it ♪
♪ But it ran through my fingers ♪
♪ Water will keep running ♪
♪ Rivers will turn ♪
Sync & corrections by emeline-whovian
www.addic7ed.com
Enjoy Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Sheriff.
Sheriff Anderssen?
Governor Munk.
The, um, the man you brought out.
The, uh, the dead man.
Yup?
He made a confession?
He certainly did.
Is that his blood?
Yep.
Did you do this?
No. He did it all on his own.
Mutilated himself.
Cut off his own genitals.
Well, who knows the full
extent of his madness?
Hmm.
Tomak,
Governor Odegard...
Bianca Mankyo,
the geologist.
- Hindemith.
Perhaps we'll never know.
It was a...
A blessing you stopped him.
A fucking blessing.
Out of my way, please.
Lars has found a body
and this eyeball in a car.
He recognized the
deceased as Trude Ekeland.
This is her eye.
Where's the car?
Top road.
You're coming with me.
When a parasite infects a host,
manipulation of the
host's genome can occur
at an epigenetic level.
Uh-huh. Go on.
The parasite and the host
are competing inside
the same genetic space
and something has to give.
What gives?
Dan Anderssen.
What's he got to do with this?
He was infested by the wasp larvae.
Should have died but he didn't.
He changed.
I've already witnessed
his increased pain thresholds,
his aggression, vitality
and most significant,
his ability to regenerate
damaged tissue.
Tissue regeneration, Michael.
Everything I do,
everything that motivates me,
my work and knowledge
is about hope.
This might be Freya's hope.
You need to bring him to me.
Yeah, you want me to bring him to you?
Open this.
More padding.
Especially around the head.
The lining's thermally insulated.
Sedative drip in here.
Delivery timer.
Keep him under once he's in the chopper.
Good. Last thing I want's
a ruckus in a helicopter.
Did you enjoy it?
Killing him?
I don't know that I enjoy
anything much anymore, Petra.
I see the thing that has to be done
and I have no hesitation in doing it.
Who decides what has to be done?
It declares itself.
I never used to see things so clearly.
But things change.
People don't.
Dan Anderssen killed Vladek.
That's not the Dan Anderssen we knew.
That's some kind of monster.
What Doctor Khatri thinks is,
is that monster,
it could be...
could be the hope we're looking for.
If I sit here with you honey,
and I don't try this one last thing...
And I lose you?
I wouldn't be your Michael.
I love you, girl.
Hmm.
Both her eyes are gone.
Did she do this to herself?
Yep.
She has a sister in Vukobejina.
It's happening again.
When everything went crazy before,
the one thing that kept me sane,
that I clung too all the...
all the time...
No matter how dark and frightening,
I trusted you...
Guarding us.
I felt safe here,
even in that madness.
And then you were so sick.
All those weeks.
And what came back...
Like Dan died
and walked over into
the land of the dead
and a demon took his shape...
and came back into the world amongst us.
I look at your face, Petra.
And for the first time ever,
I see it in you.
What?
Sami. Reindeer herder.
The blood of the tundra
flowing in your veins,
beneath your beautiful pale skin.
Did you kill Elena?
Yes.
I think I did.
She wanted me to.
Hey...
I'll drive Trude back in to town.
It's like...
Like I've had the most wonderful,
like, peaceful sleep.
Yeah?
Yeah. Vincent. Yes.
Like I can't remember
ever having before,
in all my life.
All the things I was worried about...
Work. You.
The shit I thought Khatri was up to.
It was just evaporated.
Love and goodwill, Vincent.
I know it sounds like hippy shit but I,
honestly... I mean...
(SIGHS)
And I heard a chorus, a choir.
It was celestial.
That's the word.
Shit.
Oh, he's not there.
Just the girl on her own.
Leave her!
What happened?
Shh.
Don't move, Petra.
- Your car got hit...
- I'm okay...
Hey, be still.
Let me up.
Let me go!
Let me go! Don't kill me, Dan!
Please! Let me go! Please!
Dan Anderssen!
Petra?
Sheriff around?
Petra, I am looking for Dan Anderssen.
Dan's gone.
I'm pretty sure.
You're gonna help me.
I know where Dan was...
last time he was Dan.
We'll start there then.
Come on.
I have one task:
the extraction of Dan Anderssen.
Yes, of course. I understand.
What about Khatri?
She'll be leaving, too.
I'll make my own
arrangements, fair enough.
No.
No?
You're staying.
The fuck do you mean by that?
What I mean by that,
is Schenthal Pharma
have paid you, to date, 185,000 euros
for managing this mess.
And before you go
anywhere you'll earn it.
And... If I refuse?
(CHUCKLES)
I found him here.
Not long after he went missing.
Completely...
completely crazy.
Chained to the stairs.
I was afraid he was gonna die.
He was raging, fevered,
drinking everything, purging.
- For two months.
- Two months?
Doctor Khatri said that Dan
had that parasite inside
him all that time.
Everyone else that was
infected like Dan was,
they all attacked someone.
He saw it coming.
He fought the thing, all by himself.
Why didn't you tell someone?
Because you love him?
Where did you get this stuff?
In Vukobejina.
A colleague, they knew all about it.
They acquired the knowledge
from the Sami Shaman
and reindeer herders.
It's known as reindeer
juice, or muscimol.
It'll protect me, against all this
blindness shit that's coming?
Well, I obviously used it
myself when I was there.
Jesus.
How did that work out?
Some side effects.
Side effects?
What kind of side effects?
Mild hallucinations.
What, like cannabis?
I've never used cannabis.
No, I bet you haven't.
Ah Jesus, Jesus..
That, be careful!
That's really, that's really painful.
When I was told to hold back
the fuel for the fleet,
I was in fear of my life.
I know...
First because I thought Dag Tannar
was going to knock my block off.
And then because Hildur
was glaring at me.
Like a beady-eyed herring-gull.
I don't think that's right.
And I mean no disrespect when I say this
but I always thought Governor Odegard
was a very attractive woman.
Sexy?
Yes. That's what I mean.
Hildur.
CROWD: Hildur!
When I, uh, when I put on this jacket.
I become every man and
woman in this bar.
All of us loved Hildur Odegard.
I'm just the one wearing the jacket
while you're all too busy going to work
and raising families and
doing what Hildur wanted.
Hildur Odegard was murdered.
She killed herself.
No.
She was murdered.
In cold blood.
Her killer made it look like suicide.
Murdered? Hildur was murdered?
So who murdered her?
I'll show you.
He's got the whole town with him.
All the hard drives.
- She infected?
- Yes.
How advanced is she?
Very. She's nearly done.
Right, are you going
to need all this stuff?
Incinerator.
Always liked you, Hildur.
Always thought that we had
an awful lot more in common than
we were able to acknowledge.
You had Eric.
I had Phyllisha.
Things could have been
very, very different.
Mmm.
No need for that kind of language.
I am not a murdering bastard!
It was an accident!
Shh!
Keep your fucking voice down!
From inside that office,
Hildur Odegard protected us.
Cared for us.
Your families. Your kids.
And in there now, is
the man who killed her.
Erling Munk pushed Hildur Odegard
into a hole in the ice.
What the fuck?
Lars, you saw him out there.
Yes, I did!
Ralfi, you sent her to meet him!
- Arrest him!
- Yes, arrest him!
Arrest him?
Of course, fucking arrest him!
He's the governor.
He killed the governor!
Erling Munk is
the governor of Fortitude.
Erling Munk is the chief
of police of Fortitude.
They all love you.
This is all your fault.
- She was our shepherd!
- (CLAMORING)
She saved this town,
when it all went to hell!
Yes!
I am his sheriff. I answer to him!
He murdered Hildur!
Oh, you want justice?
ALL: Yes!
You want the rule of law?
Yes, we want the fucking rule of law.
The law you want is in your own hands!
(CLAMORING)
- Get him!
- Kill the fucker!
Get him!
(SHOUTING)
Dan.
It's Michael Lennox.
(GRUNTS)
Khatri!
Doctor Khatri, wait!
Where are you going?
Please. You can't leave.
I can't help her by myself.
Hey! Quieten down.
Fuck off!
Hey, no, don't.
Fuck!
You need to find her
some reindeer juice.
More infection is on
the way from Vukobejina.
Fuck!
Stay down, out of sight till
we get to the airport.
(MICHAEL GRUNTS)
You pulled me out of
that burning cave, Michael.
This is the miracle.
This is what you're searching for.
And you're not the only one.
Hey. Hey. Sorry.
Hey, sorry. The, uh...
I need the reindeer juice.
The woman you brought back. The soldier.
You... you had some in a box.
Where is it?
My, my dad took it from us.
- Where, where did he put it?
- He destroyed it.
- Why would he do that?
- Because it's drugs.
We could go to prison.
He didn't want it around.
He didn't want us taking it
or selling it or anything.
- You're lying.
- I'm not lying.
Give me the muscimol! I need it!
I have to have the reindeer juice!
Hey! You can't come in here and yell!
My mum is sick!
It's the cure for Natalie.
For everyone that's gonna
get this fucking thing
that Dr. Khatri say's is
coming at us from Vukobejina.
If Rune says Dad destroyed it
then he destroyed it
and that's all there is.
He didn't.
He hid it.
I watched him.
Where?
Where did he put it?
Petra, open the door.
Munk's dead.
I know. It was Dan.
Open the door.
Promise me.
What?
You won't kill Dan.
He's no use to me dead.
(GRUNTS)
- Unclip your seatbelt.
- What?
Unclip your seatbelt.
- Take off your headset.
- Why?
Just take off your headset.
(DAN COUGHS)
You're hunting me.
Taser. Non-lethal.
Uh-huh.
When a polar bear catches its prey,
it eats them alive.
Did you know that?
It's true. I saw it once.
Bear took a man.
Terrible thing.
Terrible.
But at the time I thought,
"Wow, what must it be like?"
The Shamans, they think that
when a bear devours a man,
the man's spirit lives on in the bear.
Tell me your name.
What?
Your name.
So I know who's inside me.
Fuck yourself.
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
Fucking cannibal.
Fuck.
- What the hell have you done to her?
- Me?
You brought her here and look.
I know what it is. I know what to do.
There's nothing you can do for her now.
Nothing but pray.
Ah!
Natalie, can you see anything?
Can you see anything at all?
Light and dark.
That's it.
There's nothing else now.
Yes, there is. Yes, there is.
(GASPS)
♪ Little lamb, who made thee ♪
♪ Dost thou know who made thee ♪
(HUMMING)
♪ Made thee... ♪
(HEAVY BREATHING)
Michael Lennox!
Ah!
I know.
Getting shot.
Once experienced, never forgotten.
I've never been shot
but I've watched a variety of
fuckers rolling around in agony.
The pain'll ebb as you bleed out.
Oxygen to the brain depleting.
No going back from this.
You, you have to get him back.
Hand him over to Khatri.
I know about your wife.
All I care about.
Hey.
I'll see to it.
You've done all you could.
(GUNSHOT)
Is he alive?
I don't know if he's alive or not.
- He's not in his fucking box.
- It doesn't matter.
Harry, get me home, I want to see Freya.
(MUTTERING)
Demons and monsters and shaman.
I know why you came.
Make the demon human again.
Save the town.
Heal us all with your sacrifice.
So many monsters.
So much sacrifice.
Not enough for Dan.
(GROANS)
Dad...
You're back.
Yep.
I think I am.
Sync & corrections by emeline-whovian
www.addic7ed.com
Enjoy Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP