It's called Operation Pear Tree.
Our brief was to embed
an undercover officer
within an organised crime group.
Detective Sergeant John Corbett.
I'm just trying to get to the truth.
The top brass,
they don't want me to succeed.
There's a bent copper running
organised crime, I'm sure of it.
The man that broke in,
I never saw his face.
He said you'd know why he'd done it.
I assaulted your gaffer's wife.
He'll make sure I go down,
there's no two ways about it.
One zero to four five.
The order is Fahrenheit.
Sir, we'll lose all of Corbett's intel.
We know that Corbett
is a coldblooded killer.
Give yourself up!
You shoot me, then the truth
never comes out.
Lee Banks?
- Who the hell are you?
- Superintendent Hastings.
You're a rat, John.
A rat.
What if he did blow Corbett's cover?
Doesn't bear thinking about.
- This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
- How much?
£100,000.
Haven't we earned a payday?
I don't want the fiasco of Operation
Pear Tree, which was not of your
making, add a disastrous coda to
an otherwise distinguished career.
Cover it up with all this stuff. Come on.
I never asked you how your exams went.
Yeah, I got a date for my interview.
It's clear to me that the threshold
test has been passed
and therefore it is my lawful right
to arrest you on suspicion
- of conspiracy to murder John Corbett.
- No, no, no.
You will be held in custody
while we gather further
evidence against you.
What is happening here?
I am being framed!
Today was just for starters.
Now I'm going to prove
that Hastings is H.
The inquiry into Superintendent Hastings
is not a matter over which
you're entitled to exercise choice.
Cooperation is your lawful duty
as police officers
and failure to comply is an offence
under police conduct regulations.
Any of you obstructing my officers
can and will face arrest.
But let's not fall out over this.
I'm sure we can all work together nicely.
DI Fleming, DS Arnott,
can I borrow you a minute?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Seven years and counting.
No-one's worked more closely
with Ted Hastings than you two.
You have better insights into
the man than anyone else in AC12.
So, what you know, I need to know,
my team needs to know.
Ma'am, I'm not comfortable
kicking the gaffer when he's down.
He recruited you.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Mm-hm.
Stuck by you when perhaps
some others wouldn't have.
Shagging witnesses and suspects
and the like.
I sympathise with your loyalties,
DS Arnott, I really do,
but on the other hand we have found
£50,000 stashed in his hotel room
so if I were you I wouldn't go round
professing too close a loyalty
to Ted Hastings, otherwise people
might just start suspecting you
of being an accessory to his offences.
H.
A senior police officer
sitting at the top
of an institutionalised relationship
between organised crime
and corrupt police officers.
AC12 failed to bring him down.
I won't.
Wow.
£50,000.
Ma'am, Sarge, can we talk please?
- Sure. What's up?
- I've been looking into
John Corbett's past,
like you asked me to. You said
it was completely confidential
- and I couldn't share it with anyone.
- What have you found?
- May I ask what's going on in here?
- Yeah. A private conversation.
Didn't you hear DCS Carmichael?
We need to know everything.
- It's Michelle, isn't it?
- Yes.
Listen, Michelle, we're AC12.
We do this to other units
week-in-week-out
so don't try telling me how it works.
We're witnesses, not suspects.
Now, stop making a tit of yourself
and piss off.
Sorry. Go on.
It goes back to
Superintendent Hastings' service
with the Royal Ulster Constabulary.
When he was a PC in the 1980s,
he was interviewed in connection
with the disappearance
of Anne-Marie McGillis.
- Corbett's mum?
- Yeah.
- The records aren't brilliant.
- No, they never were in them days.
But they've been retained as
the disappearance remains unsolved.
You've got this on file?
Yes, Sarge,
but I've kept it security protected.
Well done, but I don't want you
getting in trouble
so you should share the file
with DCS Carmichael's team.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you, ma'am.
Christ's sake, Kate.
I'm just calling it as I see it,
Steve. The truth comes first.
What, we just help Carmichael
hammer nails in the gaffer's coffin?
Well, you heard Carmichael.
If the gaffer is found guilty,
I can guarantee it'll be us
she'll be after next.
"Oh, we must have
known Hastings was bent."
What if the gaffer's innocent?
We'll have betrayed him.
He'll come after us and we'll deserve it.
Well, I don't know about you, Steve,
but I'm not going to sit around
and wait for a kicking off
the gaffer or Carmichael
when there's police work to be done.
Stand clear of the door.
Corbett's murder, Hastings' arrest.
Fortunately, it will all be
covered by our application
for Public Interest Immunity.
Nothing need ever come out.
Unless Carmichael proves
a link between Hastings
and organised crime.
We have to go public with that.
There's pros and cons PR-wise.
Which makes me think we need to
emphasise the wording.
Wording?
Operation Pear Tree's objective
was to examine institutionalised
links between corrupt police
officers and organised criminals.
Most people would prefer us spending
that money reducing response times,
putting more bobbies on the beat.
- Anyway, I'll leave that with you.
- Where are you going?
The inquiry into Superintendent Hastings
must be above reproach.
Wouldn't hurt to make sure.
- This is never easy.
- No.
Sorry for your loss.
We're sorry to have to ask
but we're making further enquiries
into John's undercover operation.
I can't help you.
Not sure I would even if I could.
I met John a few times.
He was a very brave man.
Steph, from what Merseyside Police
have told us
about your reaction to the news
of your husband's death...
...it has made us question some
of the things you said to us
when we was last here.
You're not in any trouble.
We just want to do right by John.
Sit down if you like.
Thank you.
It was all an act before.
John told me that was how to play it
to protect him.
Going back to our visit
on the 10th of March,
we asked you about John's links
to Northern Ireland.
He grew up over there.
When his mum died,
he was took in by his auntie.
Did John ever talk about his mum?
Yeah.
We've got a name, Anne-Marie McGillis.
Anne-Marie, yeah.
What did John say about her?
John never said much.
To be honest, I don't know
how much he ever knew.
He was... He was only a kid when it
all happened, about nine or ten.
When what happened?
The story was Anne-Marie
was helping the police
and then the police betrayed her.
Let on she was an informant
and that's why she got killed.
Did John ever say there was
a particular officer involved?
When he was older,
his auntie said there was one
that Anne-Marie had talked about.
A young fella her age.
I think he took a shine to her and
she trusted him to look out for her.
He should have but he didn't.
Or worse.
What do you mean, worse?
Something John said.
This copper, he was married,
and there was a bit of scandal
about him spending so much time
round Anne-Marie's.
Maybe it suited him
for Anne-Marie to go missing.
Did John have any evidence of this?
Not that I know of.
Was there a name for this officer?
If there was, I never heard it.
Not from John.
Did John ever connect this family
history to the undercover operation
he was involved in
at the time of his death?
John never told me what his jobs
was about for me own protection.
And his.
Why are you so interested in what
happened in Northern Ireland?
Is there a connection?
We don't know.
Corbett never mentioned Hastings
to Steph.
He was only a kid when it happened.
Maybe he never knew the name.
Still, the undercover officer
recruited to investigate
links between the OCG
and corrupt officers,
all the way up to H,
just happens to be the son
of a woman murdered on
the gaffer's patch?
Well, now we know why Corbett was
so convinced the gaffer's bent.
What we don't know is if someone
else knew about Corbett's past link
to the gaffer or if somehow
Corbett managed to put himself
- forward for the job.
- Exactly.
Any chance of it being a coincidence?
Coincidence, my arse.
I see you've cleared everybody out.
That'll save the mutual
embarrassment when I'm reinstated.
DCS Carmichael had concerns
about security.
AC12 had a corrupt DI
who shot his way out of here.
- Did you manage to get any sleep?
- Not much.
Thank you. As you were.
Listen, this heavy mob that
you've just parachuted in,
they look a bit trigger-happy to me.
But our man, Police Sergeant
Kyle Ferringham,
he knows this building inside out,
you will not find a safer pair of hands.
You just said it. He's your man.
I'll stick with mine, thank you.
Second interview of Edward Hastings
in the presence of his solicitor
by DCS Carmichael, DI Brandyce
and PS Tranter.
You remain under caution.
As you know, you may be held for up
to 24 hours,
at which point you will
either be released
or charged with conspiracy
to murder John Corbett.
Pausing interview.
PS Ferringham on official business.
What's going on?
Gill Biggeloe, Senior Legal Counsel
to the PCC, attending
as an official observer to ensure
correct procedures are followed.
- Why wasn't I informed?
- You just were.
Thank you.
Ma'am.
Hi, Ted.
Resuming interview, now with PCC's
Senior Legal Counsel observing.
- Mr Hastings, how did you...?
- I thought, ma'am,
that we had agreed that
I would be addressed by my rank.
Given the gravity of the charge
against you,
I know we'd both hate to be accused
of special treatment.
Best we treat you like
any normal, regular person
who's been accused of plotting
to kill someone, don't you agree?
When did you receive confirmation
that John Corbett
had assaulted your wife?
I'm sorry to probe. I know this must
be extremely upsetting for you.
- On the 12th of March.
- When on the 12th of March?
During the operation to apprehend him.
Oh.
I see.
Talk about a pressure situation.
My heart goes out to you.
To have that trauma
at that very same moment
as being in command of armed
officers surrounding John Corbett.
Still, and, I am sorry about this,
I do need to ask you about
the events that followed.
DI Brandyce.
Document 53 in your folders.
Document 53 is a copy of the report
made by the Tactical Firearms Commander
during said operation
on the 12th of March,
written on the 13th of March
and received later that day by
the Strategic Firearms Commander.
Drawing your attention to page three
of said report, paragraph four,
"Superintendent Hastings relayed
a Fahrenheit order to DS Arnott."
- Did you give said order?
- Yes.
What's your understanding of said order?
The authority to deploy lethal force
to prevent immediate loss of life
or prevent immediate danger
to the public.
Responsibility for issuing said order
lies with the Strategic
Firearms Commander.
For the order to be issued by
any other officer is unlawful.
Corbett had already drawn his firearm,
DS Arnott was facing
an immediate threat to life,
I was concerned that DS Arnott
would hesitate
and that Corbett would discharge
his firearm.
I gave the order to save
my officer's life.
In your mind, having just learned
that Corbett had tortured your wife,
- no other motivations were at work?
- None.
And that he was involved in
the death of one of your officers,
- PC Maneet Bindra?
- Yes.
- You weren't vengeful towards Corbett?
- My first concern remained,
as it should do for all police
officers, the preservation of life.
Clearly you weren't concerned
with the preservation
- of John Corbett's life.
- I did not cause his death.
He brought it upon himself
when he went rogue.
I take no pleasure in this
but the man
had it coming to him in spades.
I'd like to return to the remarks
you made to DS Railston
following the assault on your wife.
That's Document 60 in your folders.
Document 60 is a crime report
by DS Samantha Railston
detailing statements made by
Edward Hastings on the 8th of March.
Page 2, para 3,
"Superintendent Hastings stated,
'Whoever's responsible better
start praying
"'he's up in front of the judge
before I get my hands on him.'"
What did you mean by that?
It was rhetorical.
And what would you have done
if, as per your statement,
you had "got your hands on him"?
I would have done what any police
officer would have done
and arrested him for grievous
bodily harm.
Which sounds like what any
law-abiding officer would do.
Well, I am a law-abiding officer.
And yet, on the 12th of March,
you ordered DS Arnott
to shoot John Corbett in cold blood.
To prevent an immediate loss of life!
And later that same day,
you visited Lee Banks,
an OCG member on remand
in Blackthorn Prison.
Yeah, to harvest information on the OCG.
When DS Arnott quite rightly did not
deploy lethal force against
John Corbett, did you take matters
into your own hands
and disclose to Lee Banks
that John Corbett was
an undercover police officer?
No, I did not.
Disclosing this information with
the expectation that it would be
- passed on to the OCG?
- No!
I'm really sorry to labour something that
I know you find very upsetting,
but I'd like to return
to the injuries that John Corbett
inflicted on your wife.
If you must.
Thank you.
The case was dealt with by
the Serious Crime Unit.
Document 60 in your folders.
Drawing your attention to page 2, para 2,
"When questioned, Superintendent
Hastings denied knowledge of
"any significance to the pattern of
injuries sustained by the victim."
- Is that what you said to DS Railston?
- Yes.
Thank you for being truthful with us.
I can't tell you how much easier
that makes everything.
Now, as part of our inquiry,
we've been given access
to your service record.
The service record is summarised
in Document 2 in your folders.
The service record indicates
Edward Hastings joined the
Royal Ulster Constabulary in 1982
and served as a police constable
for seven years,
till his promotion to Police Sergeant
and transfer in 1989.
Sorry, I don't mean to put you on
the spot, but seven years' policing
in Northern Ireland in the 1980s,
and you never came across
a pattern of injuries that involved
the wrists, knees and ankles?
Yeah, but, look...
You have to remember, my team
had only just discovered
that DS Railston's officer,
Commanding Detective Chief
Superintendent Lester Hargreaves,
was corrupt, having been an accomplice
with the OCG in their armed robbery
of Eastfield Depot.
So, you're offering by way of
an explanation
that you withheld information
for fear of how it would be
misused by Railston?
The assault on my wife
appeared to be the work
of the organised crime group
that we were investigating,
a threat or a warning to me
to suppress the inquiry.
I just didn't want to give them
the satisfaction
of knowing how upsetting
I found the whole event.
So, you did appreciate
the significance of the injuries?
Yes, all right, look, if you want
me to state the obvious.
Yes, a resemblance to punishment
and or torture meted out
by paramilitary and/or terrorist
organisations.
Indeed, so now, let's turn
to your service
with the Royal Ulster Constabulary
in the period 1982-1989, inclusive.
Document 62.
PC Edward Hastings served
in West Belfast.
A periodic professional assessment
submitted in the summer of 1988
by Police Sergeant Thomas Cranford
notes the following,
"Hastings appears to have a rapport
with the Catholic community
"due to his own Catholic tendencies."
Are you able to tell us a little bit
about your background?
Well, I'd really rather not.
A Catholic in the RUC,
were you in the minority?
I was, and am, a police officer.
I do not discriminate
against my fellow officers
on grounds of creed, and I would
appreciate the same courtesy.
Well, the sergeant writing up
that RUC periodic professional assessment
didn't mind referring to it.
Document 62 continued,
"Hastings' family background
is more complicated,
"which may prove valuable
in future assignments."
What did he mean by that?
- You'd have to ask him.
- We did.
Document 65 in your folders.
Statement by former Police Sergeant,
now retired, Thomas Cranford,
submitted to Anticorruption Unit 3
on the 14th of March.
"We all thought he was Protestant.
"Edward and Hastings, what else
is the fella going to be?
"Turned out that was a sensitive subject.
"His old man was a Protestant
but he'd married a Catholic,
"and when he went off, his mum
brought up young Ted that way."
Why did you leave the RUC?
Well...
...the kind of talk we just heard
being quoted didn't help.
In 1989, you suffered serious injuries.
On 29th of June 1989,
an RUC patrol vehicle drove over
a pipe bomb, causing the death
of PC Patrick O'Malley and serious
injury to PC Edward Hastings.
Two Catholic officers targeted?
Yeah, well, it doesn't take a genius
to see why I put in for a transfer.
Or were you targeted for another reason?
I don't know what you're referring to.
I'd like to examine events
in the period 1988-1989
and, specifically, a special
assignment that you took part in.
Do you recognise the name
Anne-Marie McGillis?
For the DIR, I'm showing
the interviewee Image 41,
an RUC file photograph of
Anne-Marie McGillis.
Mr Hastings?
You're going back 30 years here, come on.
Let's see if this can jog your memory.
Document 78 in your folders.
Document 78 is a report entered into
the Royal Ulster Constabulary files
on missing persons,
dated the 23rd of May 1989.
Anne-Marie McGillis was reported
missing on the 19th April 1989.
The night before, Tuesday the 18th April,
Anne-Marie left her son with a neighbour,
informing the neighbour that she was
popping out for a couple of hours
to visit a friend in hospital.
Anne-Marie never returned
to collect her son.
No witnesses came forward
to reveal Anne-Marie's movements
on the night she disappeared.
No-one known to Anne-Marie was able
to identify the family friend
who was admitted in to hospital.
The Missing Persons team concluded
that this person didn't exist,
and that Anne-Marie had deceived
her neighbour
regarding her activities
on the night she disappeared.
A number of individuals known to
Anne-Marie were interviewed
in connection with
the Missing Persons inquiry.
And one such individual was
Police Constable Edward Hastings.
Do you recall these events, Mr Hastings?
Some.
What do you recall?
Well, Anne-Marie's husband had been
murdered a few years before.
Apparently, he was active
during the Troubles.
One of those nasty little
tit-for-tat killings.
Anyway, Anne-Marie,
she blamed someone higher up
the chain of command
for her husband's death, you know...
She felt that he was sacrificed
needlessly.
Anyway, grief, I think...
...later turned to passing
information to the police
about terrorist activities.
- She was an CHIS informant?
- Yes.
And did you play a role in
Anne-Marie serving as a CHIS?
Yes, well, she...
Look, she lived on my patch.
You know, in those days,
it was very difficult for the RUC
to enter certain areas, to er...
...to put it mildly.
And I think some local women
found out my mother was a Catholic
and that I was a Catholic too.
And I think that bought a bit of trust.
You were instrumental in Anne-Marie
trusting the police
with information she was disclosing
about terrorist organisations?
I helped, that's all.
Did you have meetings with Mrs McGillis?
- Some.
- According to the file,
you didn't always meet Anne-Marie
in covert locations.
You were seen entering
and leaving her home.
Yes, you know, I'd give her a hand.
Little odd jobs,
there was no man about the house.
I'm no expert in RUC covert tactics
in the 1980s,
but I would have thought that
making it appear
that a young woman
from a Republican community
has some kind of friendship
with a police officer
is only going to invite trouble.
The sort of trouble that might
get you targeted by a pipe bomb,
or get your lady friend murdered.
I object to the term "lady friend".
What level of friendship was it?
What do you mean?
She was an attractive young widow.
Yes.
And I was a married man!
According to the file,
there were rumours you two
were conducting an affair.
Yeah, but that's what they were, rumours.
Just gossip, drummed up by
a bunch of people
no better than they should've been.
Regardless, I'm sure you can see
how your intimacy
could've put Anne-Marie in jeopardy.
That's not what happened!
Did she meet a police
officer to pass information
on the evening of
Tuesday the 18th April 1989?
Yes.
You?
What happened that night?
Well, she told me that
she'd made up some story
about going to visit a sick friend.
She passed the information to me.
And, as far as I know, she returned home.
Were you involved in her disappearance?
No.
As God is my witness, I was not.
According to the Missing Persons file,
you were the last person
to see her alive.
That is an equivocation,
Detective Chief Superintendent,
as well you know.
I'll rephrase.
You were the last person to admit
to police in an official statement
to seeing Anne-Marie McGillis alive.
I watched her walk down
the street, turn the corner.
Anne-Marie McGillis
trusted you implicitly?
Yes, I believe she did.
One theory considered by the RUC
is that you exploited that trust
- to lure Anne-Marie to her death.
- Completely false!
The theory being that, as a Catholic,
you were susceptible to
relationships with
the very organisations that
Anne-Marie was informing on.
Look Growing up back then,
in the 70's, in the city,
they were everywhere.
They were part of the culture.
This sort of organisation?
Oh, come on now, I didn't want
any part of that.
I became a police officer.
Anything familiar about their appearance?
It was a different time,
a different thing entirely.
Nonetheless, they're wearing
the clothing associated with
organised crime groups
that AC12 have been investigating
- for seven years or more.
- There's no direct connection!
Anne-Marie McGillis' remains
weren't found until 2001.
Document 72.
Document 72 is the postmortem report
on Anne-Marie McGillis.
The cause of death was
a single gunshot wound to the head.
Additional gunshot wounds were detected
bilaterally on the victim's wrists,
knees and ankles.
Lesions caused by haemorrhage
indicate these gunshot wounds
were inflicted when the victim
was still alive.
Anne-Marie McGillis was tortured
in the same pattern
as that inflicted on your wife.
Yeah, but that's how
they did it back then.
But this does not necessitate
a direct connection.
Her son. Did you ever meet him?
Er...
No. She always left her son with
some neighbours or a family friend,
something like that.
She never wanted him involved.
When Anne-Marie disappeared,
her son was orphaned at the age of 10.
He was taken in by Anne-Marie's sister
and her brother-in-law,
who resided in Liverpool.
The boy was adopted
and he took their surname.
Corbett.
John Corbett.
Corbett was Anne-Marie's wee fella?
No.
Would you like to take a break, Ted?
Yes, of course.
OK.
Is there anything I can do to help?
Just give me a minute.
Mark Moffatt? DI Fleming.
DS Arnott. Do you have a minute, sir?
Sir's long gone.
Mark's fine.
I don't know if you remember us
from AC12.
- Can you give us a minute?
- Yeah, sure.
Water under the bridge,
as far as I'm concerned.
No hard feelings.
We'd like to ask you
a couple of questions
about your commercial relationship
with Superintendent Hastings.
Ted was a...
...an original investor in
a development that went south
about six years back.
We got it back on track,
so I offered Ted a buy-in
to try and recoup his original losses.
And did he?
Unfortunately, he couldn't come up
with the funds.
According to Superintendent Hastings,
you loaned him £50,000 off-book.
50?
Yeah, that's the figure we've been given.
I don't know how Ted's got that idea.
Does the name John Corbett
mean anything to you?
No, sorry.
If that's all...
Thanks for your time.
Give Ted my best.
Well, we drew a blank on Corbett.
Yeah, you saw his reaction
when we mentioned the 50 grand.
Something's not right.
We need to find out what.
Resuming interview.
You remain under caution.
Now, let's examine in more detail
some evidence we found in your
hotel room on the 14th of March.
Image 9.
You'll recall Image 9
shows item reference MB1.
You'll recall item reference MB1
is a brown envelope
addressed to you,
containing item reference MB2.
MB2 are banknotes in the sum of £50,000.
Superintendent Hastings has already
given a full and clear explanation
regarding this item. To summarise,
it was an unsolicited advance
on future profits.
Superintendent Hastings
was extremely uncomfortable
about the loan, and telephoned
Mark Moffat to return the money.
DI Brandyce.
We took further steps to detect
the source of said cash.
I told you, it came from Mark Moffatt.
DI Brandyce.
Document 40 in your folders.
Forensic analysis of banknotes MB2
detected microscopic pollen deposits.
Pollen grains detected on MB2 were
subjected to chemical analysis.
The chemical structure of pollen
grains detected on MB2
closely resembles the chemical
structure of pollen grains
detected on items of evidence gathered
during AC-12's inquiry
into Operation Pear Tree.
Said evidence are item reference
JLM5 and item reference JD5.
Image 12, Tina.
Image 12 shows a cache of banknotes
in the sum of £25,000
detected under floorboards
at 21 Cleric Way.
Do you recognise the banknotes
shown in the image,
- Superintendent Hastings?
- No, no, I do not.
Said banknotes were detected
at a property
belonging to a Vihaan Malhotra.
Image 31.
Image 31 shows item reference JD5.
JD5 is a cache of banknotes
in the sum of £5,000
detected at 17 Hazelton Street.
Said banknotes were detected
at a property
belonging to PS Jane Cafferty.
The similar pollen structures
detected on items JD5, JLM5
and MB2 indicate a 99.5%
probability the items
derive from the same original source.
I have not been bribed!
The 50 grand found in your hotel room
came from the same pot as that
used to bribe Vihaan Malhotra
and PS Jane Cafferty.
And, according to evidence
obtained by your own unit,
those individuals were in the pay
of the same organised crime group
in which John Corbett was embedded.
I do not have a connection
with Malhotra or Cafferty.
- This bribe proves you do.
- No.
Was it an inducement or
a reward for telling Lee Banks
the identity of the undercover
officer within the OCG?
I disclosed nothing to Banks.
A disclosure which brought
about the murder of John Corbett.
No.
What was Corbett on to that you were
so desperate to keep hidden?
I'll repeat the question.
What was John Corbett on to that you
were so desperate to keep hidden?
Look...
...you have fabricated a motive
where none existed.
Who would want John Corbett dead?
- What do you mean?
- If you didn't, who would?
Well, clearly any individual
against whom John Corbett
might be gathering evidence,
including those members of the OCG
with whom he was embedded.
Were there any specific
corrupt police officers
targeted by Operation Pear Tree?
- Not that I'm aware of.
- Mm.
Document 5 in your folders.
This is a copy of a document
seized by AC-12 on the...
...23rd of February from the offices
of Operation Pear Tree.
I direct you to page 6, paragraph 6.
"It remains to be determined
"if police officers of senior
and/or executive rank
"are actively complicit
in organised criminal activities
"either as individuals
or as a conspiracy.
"A hypothesis to be examined
by the operation
"is that said alleged complicity
"is orchestrated by
a single police officer
"of senior or executive rank."
- Do you recognise those words?
- Yes. Yes. I've read the file.
There's a hell of a lot of
ifs and buts in that.
Page 6, paragraph 8,
"Detective Inspector Matthew Cottan,
"serving in Anticorruption Unit 12
from 2013 until his death,
"recorded a dying declaration
on the 18th of July 2015."
Thank you, Tina.
Who's top dog, Dot?
Caddy. No, you're The Caddy.
We know that.
- Told...
- Told!
You told someone. Someone very senior?
Prom...
Prom. Promotion? Someone promoted you?
Who? Come on, Dot.
Come in, he can't talk.
Right, blink with the first two
letters of his name.
A. B.
C. D.
E. F.
G. H.
I.
H? His name begins with H.
Right second letter? A.
B. C.
D. E...
That's it, out of the way!
I'll start bagging.
Thank you, Tina.
In his dying declaration,
DI Cottan declared
that the name of the senior officer
commanding the complicity
with organised crime began with H.
Page 6, paragraph 8 continued,
"An investigation by
Anticorruption Unit 12
"concluded in 2017 that H was
"Assistant Chief Constable Derek Hilton.
"Hilton was found dead
on the 5th of May 2017.
"However, the hypothesis must be
examined that H is
"an officer other than Hilton."
Do you recall these words?
Well, the evidence against Hilton
was overwhelming.
Clearly, if any new evidence
came to light,
AC-12 would gladly investigate.
Has any other officer
ever been accused of being H?
I'll repeat the question.
Has any other senior officer
ever been accused of being H?
- Yes.
- Who?
The accusation was a calculated falsehood
designed to sabotage a lawful
anticorruption inquiry.
Who was accused?
In an effort to sabotage an AC-12 inquiry
that was about to uncover
his own offences,
Assistant Chief Constable
Derek Hilton falsely accused
the Senior Investigating Officer,
in order to discredit AC-12,
discredit the inquiry,
and to protect his own wrongdoing.
The SIO being who?
Myself.
To be clear, you were served with
a Regulation 15 Notice.
The allegation against Superintendent
Hastings was disproved.
It wasn't disproved.
There was insufficient evidence
to prove it.
- I'd argue they're the same thing.
- They're not. They're really not.
Detective Chief Superintendent,
better to save the commentary
and stick to asking questions.
Just saying.
Actually, while I've got your attention,
I wonder if we can dig into this search
of Superintendent Hastings' hotel room.
- This has all been covered.
- Not by me.
What were the grounds for the search?
Section 18.5.
Well, why then does
Document 12 in your folders,
the arresting officer's report,
refer to Section 32
as the legal power
used to carry out the search?
DI Brandyce?
The correct search form was supplied.
Afterwards, yes, but initially it seems
that the officers at the scene of
Superintendent Hastings' arrest
were under the impression
that the search was being
carried out under Section 32.
You were there at that time,
- weren't you?
- Yes.
So, under what power did you
carry out the search at the time?
There was some confusion.
I see that, DI Brandyce.
You carried out the search
under Section 32.
There's even the original
search form in the file.
Thank you.
As we all know,
Section 32 permits the search
of a premises
the detainee was at
either at the time of his arrest
or immediately prior to that arrest.
I refer to Document 13
in your folders, the statement
given by Superintendent Hastings
on the 14th of March.
Superintendent Hastings states
that he travelled from this office,
Anticorruption Unit 12,
to the Edge Park Hotel.
Superintendent Hastings
wasn't in his hotel room
at the time of his arrest
or immediately prior.
Section 32 was the incorrect legal power.
This mistake was detected
and corrected only after the search.
As items MB1 and MB2 submitted in
evidence were detected unlawfully,
I can't see how the cache of £50,000
can be used in evidence
against Superintendent Hastings.
Well, that is for a court to decide.
Given what I've heard, the judge
will almost certainly exclude it.
And it's the only evidence
that you've got
linking Superintendent Hastings
to organised crime.
I think we should call a temporary halt,
giving my team time
to examine further evidence.
Mr Hastings,
you'll be returned to custody
and charged or released within
24 hours of your original arrest.
Approximately six hours.
Interview terminated.
- May I?
- Yes, yes, of course.
Gill, I don't know what to say.
I am not going to lie, Ted,
it is a good job that someone
was paying attention.
God knows where your solicitor
was during all that.
Everything is in here in black and white.
I know, I don't know why
I didn't see it myself.
The idea that you are corrupt
is ridiculous.
Clearly Mark Moffatt's
lying about the money.
You don't have a bent bone in your body.
This'll all go away, Ted.
Trust me.
Thanks, Gill. Thank you.
- Yeah.,
- Yeah.
DI Fleming, DS Arnott to see DSU Powell.
It's fine. I've got this.
- Ma'am.
Detective Superintendent Alison Powell
with DI Fleming, DS Arnott, AC-12.
Confirm that you grant permission
for this recording.
- DI Fleming, confirmed.
- DS Arnott, confirmed.
We'd like to fill in some background
on how John Corbett was recruited.
How was Corbett assigned as the UCO?
John was one of a number of
candidates considered for the role.
He presented with a distinguished record
of successful operations
against organised crime.
Did he come to you first, ma'am?
Did he volunteer?
What are you getting at, DI Fleming?
It's a straight question, ma'am.
There was a short list.
The candidates were evaluated.
Corbett was selected as
the right officer for the job.
Who selected him?
Look,
I made the recommendations
on Corbett, this was my operation,
but you can't put all of this on me,
I wasn't the only person involved.
Who else was involved
in selecting Corbett?
This is off the record.
How long have we got?
Just a few hours.
Going to have to blue-light it.
We just got the e-mail.
I'm calling for authentication. Thanks.
Edward Hastings, new evidence
against you has come to light.
This evidence will be submitted
in written form
and you and your solicitor
will have four hours
to consider this evidence.
- What new evidence?
- Great, thanks.
Pending further investigation,
I'll be seeking an extension of 12 hours
to your permitted custody time.
- What evidence?
- Take him to the cells.
Come on, Ted, we should do as they say.
- Thank you, Tina.
- Ma'am.
Looks like we've got him, ma'am.
You nearly cost me this case.
I'll be expecting your transfer request
first thing in the morning.
Mrs Corbett.
We've got a new line of inquiry,
we need your urgent help with it.
May we come in please?
- Yeah, come in.
- Thanks.
Subject is in the building. Repeat,
the subject is in the building.
This must be awful for you, Ted.
Resuming interview of Edward Hastings.
You remain under caution.
Have you had an opportunity
to consider with your solicitor
the new documents disclosed to you?
I have.
Edward Hastings,
when was the last time you were
in contact with John Corbett?
Never.
And have you ever been near enough
to make physical contact
with John Corbett?
Never.
I'll ask you again.
When were you last in physical
contact with John Corbett?
I only ever saw the fella once.
It was across a very busy street
during an AC-12 surveillance operation.
It must have been 100 yards away.
As you'll have seen
in the disclosure documents,
specifically Document 106
in your folders,
forensic examination
of John Corbett's body
has detected human hairs
not belonging to him.
Said hairs were attached
to follicular cells
which permitted DNA analysis.
The DNA found in these follicular cells
matches that of a person
on the police database
who is a police officer
who has submitted a DNA sample
for routine elimination
from crime scene contamination.
As you know from the documents
disclosed to you,
the DNA deposits detected
on John Corbett's body
match your elimination samples.
I've never been within
100 yards of John Corbett.
Your DNA was found on his body.
Can you explain this finding?
I can't! It must have been planted!
As a result of this evidence,
I have been in consultation
with the Senior Prosecutor
in the Complex Case Unit.
I did not kill Corbett!
She is satisfied that
the evidence against you
is sufficient to charge you
with the murder of John Corbett.
No, I'm being framed!
I'd now like to move on
to examine your motive
for murdering John Corbett.
I did not murder Corbett!
May I ask, given the gravity of
the murder charge,
why are you continuing?
I have been tasked with investigating
the highest level of corruption
between police officers
and organised crime,
- the highest level.
- I am not corrupt!
I'm the one who's leading
the fight against corruption!
The highest level is
the individual codenamed H.
Significantly, Cottan led AC-12's inquiry
into the identity of the police officer
believed to be the intermediary
for organised crime,
codenamed The Caddy.
The Caddy was identified
as being Cottan himself.
Superintendent Hastings was
the Senior Investigating Officer
on the inquiry into H.
I see an interesting parallel there.
No, no. There's no parallel there.
I'm not H.
Still, there was
an allegation that you were.
Why were you so reluctant to entrust
the investigation
into an independent anticorruption unit?
I wasn't.
Why did you shoot Robert Denmoor?
Image 76 on screen.
Image 76 shows Robert Denmoor,
a violent criminal with known
associations to organised crime.
Denmoor was incriminated in a plot
to tamper with evidence
in Operation Trapdoor.
Denmoor was shot
dead by Superintendent Hastings
on the ground floor of AC-12's
headquarters on the 4th of May 2017.
Yeah, Denmoor posed an immediate
threat to life
and lethal force was required
to stop him.
Therefore the Coroner recorded
a finding of lawful killing.
The official report records there
were a dozen AFOs on the scene,
and none of them opened fire.
In fact, according to the report,
you snatched a firearm
from a wounded AFO.
Yeah, I did.
The fatal round discharged by you
prevented questioning of Denmoor.
Prevented the loss of life.
Denmoor would have been a key witness
who could have confirmed Hilton as H.
- Yes.
- Or excluded him.
Yes, also.
You were prepared to lose
that priceless evidence,
the same judgment you demonstrated
on the 12th of March
when you ordered DS Arnott to deploy
lethal force against John Corbett.
Look, I told you, Corbett was armed,
he was responsible for the death
of Maneet Bindra,
Lester Hargreaves,
I gave the order to
safeguard my officer's life!
Corbett was notifying DS Arnott
of a meeting
with a high-ranking nominal
who could well have been H.
Corbett was a liar.
He was playing games with all of us.
He was a decorated undercover officer
whose courageous actions in the past
had brought to justice
hardened members of
organised criminal groups.
Corbett gave DS Arnott alone
the details of the meeting with H.
He did.
You ordered DS Arnott
to disclose those details?
You're damn right I did,
I was his commanding officer,
for Christ's sake.
What the hell's going on here?
And at said meeting, the same day,
the 12th of March,
at the Palisades Shopping Centre,
what happened then?
- No meeting took place.
- Why do you think that was?
Well, Corbett was about to be
apprehended by AC-12.
I suspect that he, you know, lied
about the meeting at the Palisades
to secure his own escape.
Or he was telling the truth
and the information was leaked to H.
We detected no evidence of a leak.
We examined your personal
communications records
and found no suspicious calls.
However I do need you to account
for two unexplained findings.
We've detected activity
in the vicinity of AC-12
on unregistered mobile phones,
so-called burner phones
used for illicit communications.
We've identified a specific
burner phone. Tina, thank you.
Document 92.
Document 92 is a call history
of an unregistered mobile, 07700900856.
The device shows clusters of activity
in the vicinity of AC-12
over the last six weeks
and also engaged in communication
with other burner phones.
Cross checking with door entry
download data
reveals only one AC-12 officer
was present in the building
on every occasion 07700900856
was detected.
That officer was
Superintendent Edward Hastings.
Is 07700900856 your phone?
No, it is not.
- Did you dispose of the phone?
- There was never a phone.
Have you ever disposed
of a communications device?
- Tina.
- Document 24.
Document 24 shows screenshots
from a laptop
forensically recovered
from the Flicker nightclub
used by Lisa McQueen and
John Corbett to communicate with H.
As we can see,
H issued his orders via text.
I'll repeat the question.
Have you ever disposed
- of a communications device?
- No.
- PS Tranter, thank you.
- As stated by DCS Carmichael,
we examined the communication
history of Edward Hastings.
Document 28 in your folders
is said communication history
relating to your personal
registered mobile telephone
and your work registered
mobile telephone.
From these phones we've been able
to harvest location data.
We detected suspicious behaviour
on the 5th of March.
Location data places both phones
at the Edge Park Hotel
around 15:00 hours that day.
The user then switches off both
phones for the rest of the day.
When location data resumes
the next day, the 6th of March,
the phones are back
in the Edge Park Hotel.
Why did you switch off your phones?
I... I really don't recall.
Do you recall the significance
of that date, the 5th of March?
- No.
- That night,
the OCG carried out an armed robbery
at the Eastfield Depot,
making away with seized goods
with an estimated street value
of £50 million.
Yeah, OK, look, I'm sorry.
I mean,
the date must have slipped my mind.
Where were you from 15:00 hours
on the 5th of March?
Well, I remained...
I remained in and around
the Edge Park Hotel,
on standby for developments
for AC-12's surveillance operation
on the Eastfield Depot.
This was a hugely important operation.
Wasn't it essential
that you be contactable?
Well, I... We'd established
a direct line of communication
through Airwave radio and I had
direct dial access to my officers.
My own works phone was redundant.
Why didn't you attend
the operation in person?
To ensure operational independence.
DI Fleming, she acted as
the Tactical Firearms Commander
under an independent
Strategic Firearms Commander.
The result being that
your whereabouts were unknown
until you made contact via an
Airwave radio much later that night.
That's neither here nor there.
We attempted to trace your movements
on the 5th of March.
Tina, thank you.
Starting from a radius of 100 metres
around the Edge Park Hotel,
we examined CCTV and traffic cameras.
Image 32.
Who's seen in this image?
Me.
What's the package you're carrying?
I'm reserving comment.
We were able to trace the taxi's journey
to a drop-off point
in the Moss Heath area.
Again, we examined CCTV cameras
in a 100-metre radius.
Image 33.
Who's seen in this image?
Me.
What are you doing in this image?
We know from the recovered laptop
from the nightclub
that the OCG communicated with H
via online messaging.
Examination of the OCG laptop's
hard drive
revealed a sophisticated
re-routing system via various VPNs
to disguise H's IP address.
And while we're still unable
to determine H's location,
we know for certain that
the hard drive of the computer
would contain metadata
proving it was used
to communicate with the OCG.
Evidence that he would take
great pains to... dispose of.
OK.
Well, we shall come back to it.
As we've established, the night
of the 5th of March
saw the OCG robbery
at the Eastfield Depot.
At 22:40 hours that night,
a status zero radio call was
made by PC Kieran Bloom
requesting urgent assistance
to Farmer's Lane.
How did you respond
to that emergency call?
The Authorised Firearms Officers
who were giving assistance
to the AC-12 surveillance
of the Eastfield Depot
were the nearest armed response unit.
And so given our responsibility
towards preserving life,
I authorised the AFOs
to render assistance.
As a result of your actions,
the OCG were able to flee Eastfield
with £50 million worth of seized goods.
My decision was based on saving
police officers' lives.
Priceless, I would say.
H would have wanted the robbery
to succeed, wouldn't he,
so that he could have
shared in the proceeds?
That's hypothetical.
You went to a nightclub
known to be an OCG haunt,
in the hope of effecting a meeting,
without independent authorisation.
Yeah, well, look...
You know, they'd killed Maneet,
they'd murdered Lester Hargreaves,
they'd held up the Eastfield depot.
- Time was running out.
- You pretended to be H
successfully enough for the OCG
to share with you
the proceeds of the Eastfield Robbery.
No. I was using them to find out
where the proceeds were hidden.
Who better to impersonate
H than H himself?
No. That is not what was happening!
It's like I told you,
look, time was running out.
I was desperate.
Well, it's convenient
to rationalise all this
as the desperation of a failing SIO.
But before we do,
let's consider the communications
made between Corbett and you
via a computer link. Tina.
Document 105 in your folders
and on screen.
Document 105 is a transcript
of a written message composed by you
and transmitted on the evening
of the 12th of March.
Please look at line 3, which reads,
"I can definately pull
the right strings."
Note the misspelling of "definitely".
Going back to earlier messages
believed to have been written by H,
please look at the message
transmitted on the 3rd of March,
"Eastfield Depot is definately high
risk." Again, note the misspelling.
How closely had you studied
the messages by H?
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Quite closely.
Closely enough to duplicate the
misspelling of this particular word?
Yes.
You're the SIO on one of the biggest
anticorruption operations
this force has ever seen,
and you have the headspace
to learn to spell like H?
Yes.
Isn't it more likely that you
inadvertently misspelled this word?
- No.
- No? Isn't it more likely
that you made the same mistake as H
- because you are H?
- I am not H.
Looking at another part
of the impersonated message
you composed, line 4, "I need you
to bring all this to a close."
What did you mean by that?
What H meant was that
the Eastfield goods were a liability
and needed to be taken
out of the country quickly.
It could imply another meaning,
that you were giving the order
to execute John Corbett.
No! Absolutely not!
What private material was stored
on the hard drive
of the laptop computer that
you erased on the 5th of March?
No, it's not relevant to this inquiry.
If we'd been able to find H's computer,
we'd have the proof we needed.
You disposed of your computer
because you knew that.
That it would prove beyond all
reasonable doubt that you are H.
No.
Then why did you dispose of the computer?
I was looking at pornography.
Nothing illegal, nothing extreme.
I just did not want it to be found.
That's all.
Nothing illegal or extreme,
but you went to the lengths
of disposing of the computer?
Look, it was private stuff,
so, you know...
My wife has left me, and...
Jesus Christ.
Look, I really don't want to discuss it.
And after you entered the nightclub
as part of your...
...unauthorised undercover operation,
you were next located where
the Eastfield goods
were being concealed.
It was pure chance,
an active burner phone
inadvertently left on by an OCG member,
that meant you were found.
We could be forgiven for thinking
that you didn't want to be found.
No, that's simply not true.
The net was closing in. Your
identity was slowly being unmasked.
You reunited with the OCG
in order to share in the profits
of the Eastfield robbery.
Look, no... Look, look...
I had risked my life and my career
in order to catch them.
The two most precious things
to me in the whole world,
I laid them on the line,
because I was so determined,
and I was so desperate
that AC-12 would not fail.
Do you know, one thing
I keep going back to
is that dying declaration
by DI Cottan. Tina, thank you.
Cottan, your own officer,
named the top man as H.
And now, finally, there's
overwhelming evidence that H is you.
I'm not H.
John Corbett was proving
- the trail led to your door.
- No.
That's why you had John Corbett
- murdered.
- No.
You ordered DS Arnott to shoot him dead.
- And when that plan failed,
you visited Lee Banks
in Blackthorn Prison
and revealed to him that Corbett
was an undercover police officer.
- No. No.
- But killing Corbett wasn't enough.
You needed to know what
he had on you, didn't you?
- No.
- And that was the biggest mistake
that you made.
Because in the final meeting
with Corbett,
before you slashed his throat
and dumped him at the breakers yard,
one of your hairs
contaminated Corbett's body.
NO!
Edward Hastings, H,
I have been in consultation with
the Senior Prosecutor
at the Complex Case Unit and
I will now go back to her
seeking authority to charge you
with the murder of John Corbett,
conspiracy to commit armed robbery
and malfeasance in a public office.
I think it might be helpful
if Mr Hastings is given some time
with his solicitor.
Fine by me.
Thank you, Tina, well done.
Ma'am.
Interview terminated at 21:46.
Where's the AFOs?
Kyle?
Ma'am.
I thought there was meant to be
armed support
while the gaffer was being interviewed?
Looks like it's been scaled back.
It'll be down to other
operational commitments.
- Always is.
- OK.
You've got to hand it to Carmichael.
There's a lot stacking up.
And that's with setting aside
the bundle of cash in your hotel room.
- Which I was about to return!
- All of it?
Moffatt denies any knowledge of the money
so nobody's put the exact sum to him.
But according to the files,
the amount required to buy in
to the property development
wasn't 50 grand...
...it was 100.
Now, if there is another
50 grand somewhere...
...eventually someone's going to find it.
Now, I'm on your side, Ted.
But if I was on a jury,
I'd say this all looks damning.
Now, I'm confident I can talk
the PCC into
applying political pressure to
suppress Carmichael's investigation.
Much better to blow our trumpets
about recovering the stolen goods
and neutralising the OCG.
You'll have to accept a misconduct charge
for carrying out unauthorised operations
and resign from the force.
No doubt AC-12 will be disbanded.
Thank you, yes, the threshold tests
have been met definitely.
What's going on?
The DCS is on to the Crown Prosecutor.
- Ma'am.
- DS Arnott.
- DI Fleming.
Well, the last thing I need right
now is another knife in me back.
That was never our intention, sir.
Yeah? Funny way of showing it.
We've been making inquiries
into some of the gaps
in our understanding of Corbett's
involvement in Operation Pear Tree.
Yeah. Under whose orders? Hers?
No, sir, on our own.
We're just trying to find the truth.
What's going on?
We've gathered further information
that may be relevant
- to your inquiry.
- You can brief me in private.
If it's OK with you, ma'am,
we intend to share our findings
with Superintendent Hastings
and his solicitor.
His solicitor is making calls.
Yeah, well, they've come to talk to me
and I'd like to hear what
they've got to say.
Quite right. It's up to you
if you want to be in on it or not.
Operation Pear Tree
was originally authorised
following an instruction
from Rohan Sindwhani,
the Police and Crime Commissioner.
Sindwhani had made an election
promise to tackle police corruption.
The specific remit of Pear Tree
is to examine whether complicity
between organised crime
and police officers
has been institutionalised in this force.
Detective Superintendent Alison Powell,
having no connection to Central Police,
was brought in to lead Pear Tree.
Powell identified suitable
undercover officers
from outside forces
and submitted their CVs to
Deputy Chief Constable Andrea Wise.
Following a consultation process,
John Corbett was selected to be the UCO.
Bear in mind, Corbett's background
was available to be examined
as part of the process.
This was before his service record
was erased from the database
and large portions of the Pear Tree
files were redacted.
DSU Powell informed us
that PCC Sindwhani took no part
in the selection process,
but it was agreed
his Senior Legal Counsel
would act on his behalf.
I don't need to remind everyone
there's been controversies
surrounding undercover operations.
The PCC required assurances that
Pear Tree was legally watertight.
According to DSU Powell,
the Senior Legal Counsel
strongly favoured Corbett
and was instrumental in selecting him.
Corbett had a distinguished record
handling the perils of being embedded
inside an organised crime group.
He was by far the best man for the job.
Ms Biggeloe, when did you first
become aware of John Corbett?
When we looked at the files
to select an undercover officer.
Gill Biggeloe, you do not have to
say anything
but it may harm your defence if you
do not mention when questioned
something you later rely on in court.
Anything you do say
may be used in evidence.
OK.
Well, given that the DIR's off,
I'd like to make my own
personal recording.
Any objections?
I think we need to take
a step back, actually.
Recording on.
If you could kindly bear with us, ma'am.
Ms Biggeloe, did you
ever meet John Corbett?
I refer you to my previous response.
DS Arnott.
As part of our inquiry,
we interviewed Corbett's widow,
Stephanie. On the first occasion,
she confirmed Corbett's
upbringing in Northern Ireland.
Following our interview with DSU Powell,
we went back to Mrs Corbett
with some specific questions
regarding John Corbett's recruitment
to Operation Pear Tree.
We managed to convince her to
cooperate with our inquiry
and reveal hitherto undisclosed evidence.
Following a lawful search
of the family home
under Mrs Corbett's guidance,
we recovered items concealed
by her husband.
Among the items was
an audio recording of a meeting
between John Corbett and Gill Biggeloe
which took place in January 2018,
a full month before the inception
of Operation Pear Tree.
Well, if such a recording exists,
it's inadmissible.
That is correct that if acting
on official police business,
Corbett would have required
authorisation from Ripa.
Yeah, well, he wasn't acting on
official police business,
and I can assure you that
my legal team and I
will move heaven and Earth
so that this particular recording
will be heard in court.
Playing recording.
The RUC officer who betrayed your mother,
his name's Hastings.
Superintendent Ted Hastings.
He's a Super now. That's taking the piss.
How do you know all this?
From a private investigator who's
been looking into Hastings' past.
It's all in the file, chapter and verse.
You read it and then tell me
how you feel about my proposal.
I'm in. Tell me now.
We're setting up an undercover
operation to prove he's bent.
To finally bring down the man
who had your mother killed.
And it's definitely him, Hastings?
Yeah.
Gill Biggeloe sought incriminating
material on Superintendent Hastings
and then used it to manipulate
John Corbett
into believing
Superintendent Hastings is H.
Why, Gill?
It's complicated.
We've got time.
Actually, you don't.
I'm TFC! Guns down. Stand by!
OK. We need to shut
this building down right now.
- Guns down now!
- Do as he says.
TFC now. Received, moving in.
Guns down.
Hands where we can see them.
- Hands above your head.
- Who authorised this?
We detected apparent security lapses
on entering the building.
The SFC authorised us to deploy firearms.
All your AFOs are being
disarmed as a precaution.
This burner phone,
it isn't the same burner phone
that I've been accused of owning,
by any chance, Tina, is it?
Tina, the number.
07700900856.
Oh, yeah.
There it is.
You see Gill only ever visited me
when she came to AC-12.
That's how you mistook
this phone for mine.
TFC, 6-4, any obs on OCG?
6-4, no contact yet, stand by.
Looks like the cavalry's
not coming over the hill.
Yeah, the last time Dot Cottan
sent that message out,
he was busted out in a couple of seconds.
Looks like you're not as valuable as him.
Or as valuable as you thought you were.
As valuable to who exactly?
Well, Gill told me that
she was a defence solicitor.
You're going to meet a lot of
shady types doing that job.
So you get some major piece of work
off a serious criminal charge,
they put you on a retainer.
But these retainers, they come with
strings attached, don't they, Gill?
But I suspect that she was
enticed by the glamour.
Why frame the gaffer?
It's always more palatable
to offer up a rotten apple
than to uncover
institutionalised corruption.
And as AC-12 have been a constant
thorn in the side of the OCG,
what better rotten apple than their
commanding officer, right, Gill?
The money in the hotel room,
where did that come from?
I bet you asked some of
your little criminal mates
to slip that through to Moffatt,
am I right?
There's damning DNA evidence
against Superintendent Hastings.
Hardly damning, a couple
of hair follicles? Come on.
Hang on.
Don't tell me, was that your doing, Gill?
Don't worry, Ted,
I'll spare your blushes
in front of everyone.
Gill used the bathroom of my hotel room.
She must have taken some hairs
out of the comb,
passed them on to the OCG and
they planted them on Corbett's body.
Who killed Corbett?
Did you give the order?
We all know confessing
to conspiracy to murder
will make me ineligible
for immunity from prosecution.
And the institutionalised
complicity between organised crime
and corrupt police officers?
Have you not been listening, love?
There's no such thing.
I'm just one rotten apple.
Well, never mind betraying me, Gill.
Never mind framing me.
What about John Corbett?
I mean, you let him believe
that he was chasing the truth.
Justice for his mother,
for Christ's sake, for Anne-Marie.
But instead he was chasing a lie.
You set it running,
then you sat around as you watched
the dogs rip it apart.
A tragic, senseless death.
3-7, 6-4, sit rep.
6-4, still no obs.
Received.
Ma'am, it appears we no longer need
to defend ourselves
against a threat in this building.
I suggest we make arrangements
to transport
Miss Biggeloe to custody ASAP.
Agreed.
- I'll take care of that, ma'am.
- Thank you, Tina.
Gill Biggeloe,
you are under arrest for perverting
the course of justice
and misconduct in a public office.
Sir, I'd advise you
get out the building too.
Yeah. Thank you, Kate.
I'm afraid I'm going to have to cuff you.
Could be a trek to custody. You
might want to do a loo break now.
Thank you.
Going to have to come with you,
I'm sorry.
- 3-7, 6-4.
- 6-4 receiving.
We're sending down DCS Carmichael
and the gaffer.
We'll keep Gill Biggeloe up here
until we can provide escort.
- 6-4, received.
- Thanks, you two.
I don't know what to say.
You're welcome, sir.
Just doing our job.
It's a damn sight more than that.
I could murder a cuppa.
Ah!
Help!
Drop it!
Alpha Charlie 3-7, request urgent casevac
from AC-12 for two persons,
one low-velocity GSW, one knife wound.
- Gill, are you all right?
- Yeah.
Steve.
Steve, are you all right?
I never shot anybody.
Can you confirm, premises now secure?
Yes, confirmed.
Do you think she'll talk?
She'll want to make a deal.
Too fond of the finer things
to do a prison stretch.
The OCG didn't think Gill
was worth saving,
but someone gave the order
to stop her talking.
Who?
What is it?
Out of the way.
I'll start bagging, respiratory arrest...
Gone through my solicitor,
and she's advised me
to cooperate with your inquiry
but it all depends if there's
definitely immunity
from prosecution, and witness protection.
I want to help.
Maybe I could do something
to stop others from making
the same mistakes.
Immunity from prosecution and
witness protection has been agreed.
There is one final gap
we need to fill in.
How did you know that John Clayton
was an undercover officer,
DS John Corbett?
I didn't.
Just that he was a rat.
How?
The leak about the meeting
at the Palisades.
It could have only come from him.
How did that work?
John was told the top man wanted
to meet at the shopping centre.
We had a meeting point
on one of the walkways.
It was nice and public
so if anyone spotted us
they'd think twice about
trying to take us out.
No-one else in the unit knew about
the meet except for me and John.
We had one of our blokes working
the shopping centre in security.
He said he'd seen the coppers
waiting to ambush us.
So we knew for certain the leak
had to come from John.
What did Lee Banks reveal to you
about John Corbett?
Only that there was a rat in the unit.
Hastings told Lee Banks
about Corbett, I'm sure of it.
She's lying to cover herself.
She knows if she admits
to killing Corbett
then she forfeits immunity
from prosecution.
What does Banks say?
He's still not talking.
Then, without his testimony,
you can't prove Hastings blew
Corbett's cover.
It's a dead end, Patricia.
Close the case.
- Ma'am, I think if I can just keep...
- You had a bent officer on your team.
Glass houses.
Which OCG members were involved
in the murder of John Corbett?
A few of them.
Not me.
They're all dead now.
Who inflicted the fatal knife wound
that caused John Corbett
to bleed to death?
He's dead now too.
Miroslav Minkowicz.
Are there any members
of the OCG still at large?
Not that I know of.
Where I grew up, it was easy
to fall in with the wrong crowd.
My mum, she was off her face on
drink and drugs a lot of the time.
The person who made me see
that there was another way,
to be a useful member of society,
was a police officer, PC Simon Bannerjee.
He's the reason why I wanted
to become a police officer too.
To help people.
- Sir.
We've been re-examining
Dot's dying declaration.
Now, the frame it was frozen on
during your interview
made me spot something we've all missed.
Look at Dot's left hand.
Watch again.
Right, so his fingers are tapping. So?
Dot was trying to tell us something
before he lost consciousness.
He couldn't speak due to
the gunshot wound to his chest,
but he could move his hand.
Tap, tap, tap-tap.
Tap, tap, tap, tap.
Morse code.
Dot, dot, dot, dot.
The letter H in Morse Code is four dots.
H is not an initial.
It's a clue.
Four Dots.
Four Caddies.
Four police staff
in league with organised crime.
Dot.
Hilton.
Gill.
Plus one more.
And they're still out there.
The Deputy Chief Constable
and I are pleased to report
Operation Pear Tree has completed
a thorough investigation
into institutionalised complicity
between organised criminals
and corrupt police officers.
Its robust findings couldn't be clearer,
there is no institutionalised
corruption in this police force.
This constabulary will work
tirelessly to root out
rotten apples in its ranks...
_
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN