Operation Lighthouse, re the
unsolved murder of Gail Vella on
September 10th, 2019.
Deborah, did you see this man?
He looked, erm, different.
Different, different?
The other man...
He did it.
TYRES SCREECH
LISA SCREAMS AND WHIMPERS
You all right, Terry? Tonight,
I believe there was an attempt
on Terry Boyle's life, sir.
This department is grateful
for your cooperation.
PC Ryan Pilkington.
Davidson brings him into the fold,
and he just happens to be escorting
Terry the night Terry nearly drowns.
We're losing our power
to challenge lies.
There's some people
you can't challenge.
I take pride in the courage
and professionalism
of my counterterrorism officers.
What is the motive
for Gail Vella's murder?
All right, she's a controversial
journalist, but there's no evidence
to suggest that she dug up anything
that wasn't there before.
Maybe she was working on something
that would.
I'm being framed!
I'm thinking we should get a warrant
to expand the forensic search
of Farida's house.
Don't move! Armed Police!
Drop your weapon! Drop your weapon!
Down on your knees!
I'm interested in one thing
and one thing only.
And that's bent coppers.
We want to work WITH you,
Superintendent, not against you.
You really have been working
Anti-corruption too long, ain't you?
DI Arnott? Sir, you've been listed
for routine drugs testing.
Please follow me.
Proceedings against Deborah Devereux
were dropped.
That DI was Ian Buckells.
This way, please, sir.
I'm just glad the guilty party's
been found.
Thanks, everyone. As you were.
By now you'll all know about
Detective Superintendent Buckells.
Earlier, I had a good conversation
with Chief Superintendent Khan.
I made it clear that the wrongdoing
of one rotten apple
shouldn't be held against
MIT officers who have always
and will always carry out our duty
with the utmost integrity.
ALL AGREE
Nothing's going to affect our goal -
bringing Gail Vella's murderer
to justice.
We do now have to accept that
certain leads
may have been overlooked,
specifically the possibility
of a burglary accompanying
Gail's murder.
Kate. Boss.
There was no sign of a break-in
in Gail's home.
No evidence of a disturbance
withinside the property.
It would still seem that the killer
lay in wait for her that evening.
He recognised her vehicle.
As she stepped out of the
driver's side,
he stepped up behind her
and discharged the fatal shot.
From examining the original
investigation files detected
in DSU Buckells' vehicle,
we now know that the keys
to Gail's Peugeot weren't recovered
at the scene.
This raises the possibility
that the murderer seized the keys,
which also included
Gail's house keys,
giving him access to the property.
The murderer acted with great speed,
precision
and calmness to carry out a robbery
while Gail Vella lay dead.
The fact it was late at night was
the only thing that gave him time,
but still only a few minutes.
There was also an armed robbery
on the morning of our op that led
to the arrest of Terry Boyle.
Any chance there might be a link?
Let's keep an open mind.
Terry Boyle, is he still
our prime suspect, ma'am?
We rule nothing in,
nothing out. Fresh slate.
Once last thing.
To ensure continuity, I've been made
Acting Detective Superintendent.
Thanks, everyone.
Boss. Ma'am.
Boss, I'd like to dig a bit more
into the firearms used
in the robbery at Hickey's bookie's.
Absolutely.
I'll generate an action
so it's recorded.
As I said, fresh slate.
Thanks, boss.
Congratulations on the promotion.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
TRAIN RATTLES PAST
Sir?
Kate.
Now, this probationary constable...
Ryan Pilkington.
We'll start proceedings against him,
we'll pull him out, yeah?
Sir, we don't have much evidence.
Under questioning,
he's as cool as you like.
I'd rather keep observing him.
But if he's who we suspect he is,
he could be a really nasty
piece of work.
I'm only thinking of your safety,
Kate.
Thank you, sir,
but if he's been groomed by an OCG
and embedded on the force,
he's linked to the institutional
corruption we've been investigating.
We bring him in, we lose that lead.
Grand.
We'll just place him under
surveillance.
Sir.
Look, Kate, I really appreciate
you doing this. I know it's a bit
of a risk and it's probably not what
you want to be doing.
We've got a case to solve, sir.
We do. We do, indeed we do.
But you made your choice to move on,
and I know that the disciplinary
action against me
was definitely a factor.
It put you and Steve
in a really difficult position.
Yeah, I'm not going to lie.
So, I only have myself to blame.
BUZZING
Anti-corruption Unit 12 interview
of Detective Superintendent Ian
Buckells, in the presence of
his solicitor and Superintendents'
Association representative,
by Superintendent Hastings,
DI Arnott, and DC Bishop.
You are under arrest for the
criminal offence
of Perverting the Course of Justice
and therefore have forfeited
your right to be interviewed by
an officer at least one rank senior.
You remain under caution.
Document 9 in your folders.
Document 9 is a witness statement
provided on November 10th
of this year by Deborah Devereux,
as part of Operation Lighthouse.
What's your relationship
to Deborah Devereux?
I don't have one.
Really?
DC Bishop.
Document 11 in your folders.
Document 11 is a case report,
case number KPS-84746,
submitted at
Kingsgate Police Station
on the 13th of November 2012.
Deborah Devereux was arrested
for Assault Occasioning Actual
Bodily Harm against a neighbour.
However the neighbour subsequently
withdrew the allegation.
The officer handling the case,
a DC McIntyre,
believed there had been intimidation
directed at the neighbour
and sought the advice
of a more senior officer.
Said officer ordered
"no further action"
and all proceedings against
Ms Devereux were dropped.
Said officer was Detective
Superintendent Ian Buckells.
Yeah, look.
This is going back yonks.
There'd have been a good reason
for dumping that case.
Yeah, there was a good reason,
all right.
DI Arnott. As part of our inquiry,
we've been granted access
to your communications records.
We detected this contact
in your call history from 2012.
On screen, image 33.
Image 33 is a screenshot
of the contact named "Debbie RGT".
This number was registered
to Deborah Devereux.
We detected other contacts
in a similar format -
all female first names
followed by initialisms.
Other initialisms include
FAF, NA, BJL.
Are you able to explain
what they mean, sir?
Er, I-I don't remember.
We examined your communications
history with the contact Debbie RGT.
Image 36.
Image 36 is a screenshot
of text messages between your number
and the contact named Debbie RGT's
number on the 9th of November 2012.
This communication took place
four days before proceedings
against Deborah Devereux were
discontinued on your order.
Yeah, look...
There might've been a bit of...
It was never going to go anywhere,
she was a suspect.
You know, that's never gonna happen.
2020, Deborah Devereux's name comes
up again, this time in connection
with Operation Lighthouse. Document
15 in your folders and on screen.
Document 15 is a copy
of a transcript from an interview
with Deborah Devereux.
Ms Devereux subsequently took part
in a video identification parade
in which she identified Terry Boyle.
This evidence was instrumental
in incriminating Terry Boyle
for the murder of Gail Vella.
Look, this was all happening
without me.
Chris Lomax did that interview.
Jo Davidson was the SIO.
Yes!
But it was YOUR department!
Further inquiries failed
to corroborate Deborah Devereux's
testimony. It was only
when officers began to doubt
Ms Devereux's version of events
that her past came to light.
You got her off an assault charge.
She owed you.
So then you got her to cook up
this cock-and-bull story about
poor wee Terry Boyle.
No, I haven't seen Debbie since back
when I was working Kingsgate.
Where's the evidence of me being
in touch with her
about this statement, eh?
You tell me that.
While we've detected no recent
communications between you
via these devices, contact via other
means hasn't been excluded.
Furthermore, we've established
your failure
to declare a notifiable association
with the witness
and serious concerns regarding her
trustworthiness.
I'm being victimised here.
You are being investigated,
Detective Superintendent,
investigated without fear or favour.
DC Bishop.
Document 3 in your folders
and on screen.
Document 3 is a timeline constructed
by AC-12 from
Operation Lighthouse files,
lawfully seized
on the 4th of November 2020,
of events taking place
from the night of 26th of October
until the afternoon of the 27th.
You'll see that the
Murder Investigation Team received
information late on the 26th that
a Covert Human Intelligence Source
witnessed or claimed to have
witnessed a person they knew
as Ross Turner confessing
to the murder of Gail Vella.
According to the files we've
examined, DSU Davidson set in motion
plans to raid Turner's address.
However, a delay was requested
to obtain authority from an officer
of Executive Rank. Said delay
being ordered by Detective
Superintendent Ian Buckells.
The highest-profile unsolved murder
in this force's history,
a tip-off to tell you the killer was
there for the taking -
why on Earth did you delay?!
This CHIS, we had no idea
how reliable he was.
According to the files,
the intelligence had been graded 1A.
OK, yeah, but...
look, it was a complex op.
It needed proper planning,
not everyone going off at it
half-cocked.
You should've struck when the iron
was hot.
You know, I'm long enough in the
tooth to recognise a decision dodger
when I see one.
T-That's not what happened.
Oh, really?
There was another explanation,
was there?
DC Bishop.
We now know the person identifying
themself as Ross Turner
was most likely Carl Banks,
a violent offender with established
links to organised crime.
You'll see from the timeline
that from the time the arrest
was first delayed, surveillance was
established at Banks's address,
a Flat 4F Beechwood House -
the purpose being
to prevent Banks fleeing.
However, the surveillance needed to
be removed for a period
of 3 hours and 35 minutes,
from 7.19 to 10.54
on the 27th of October.
Why was it removed, sir?
This was nothing to do with me!
Image 5 on screen.
Image 5 is the best
the surveillance team were able
to achieve on the 27th of October
without arousing suspicion.
According to the files, it was clear
the surveillance team would go on
to deploy long-lens optical devices.
As a result, the quality of images
would attain
those achievable from inside the
property.
The appropriate authority you should
have provided
was for Intrusive Surveillance.
You authorised
Directed Surveillance only,
and as a result of that failure,
the surveillance team had to be
pulled out until the correct
legal authority was in place.
This was all crossed wires -
I'm being scapegoated here.
Scapegoated?!
How dare you?!
DC Bishop.
Returning to the timeline.
Surveillance was re-established at
10.54 on the 27th of October.
MIT supported by
Authorised Firearms Officers
arrived at Beechwood House at 11.27.
They carried out their operation as
planned but instead
of arresting Carl Banks, they found
Terry Boyle in the property.
We now believe the absence of
surveillance made it possible
for Carl Banks to be removed from
the address
for Terry Boyle to be substituted.
There's no evidence for that.
No evidence?
We'll give you "no evidence".
Thank you, DI Arnott.
According to the Operation
Lighthouse files we've seen,
there are indications of forced
entry to the property
preceding the raid by MIT.
Carl Banks was found murdered.
Postmortem examination detected
signs of a serious assault
followed by forcible restraint.
That's all compelling evidence that
Banks was abducted.
Yeah, but you still don't know if
Banks was the one who confessed
to Gail Vella's murder.
Because the CHIS was also
found dead.
The only person of any interest
in Gail Vella's murder
who is still alive...
..is Terry Boyle.
DC Bishop.
Image 29B on screen.
Terry Boyle was arrested
on the 27th of October
and released on the 29th
on police bail.
He's remained under investigation
ever since.
On the night of November 11th,
Terry Boyle was travelling
in a police patrol car en route
back to his approved premises,
when the car suddenly veered off the
road into Edge Park Reservoir.
The officer escorting Boyle,
a PC Ryan Pilkington,
claimed that the driver reacted to
either a gunshot or a tyre blowout.
There's been no evidence to
support either claim.
Image 45.
Do you recognise Image 45, sir?
Yeah, it's me and Ryan.
You put him forward for
a commendation.
For risking his life.
So he claims.
God's sake.
Is there no-one you won't knock?
He saved Terry Boyle's life!
Before he was posted to
Hillside Lane,
had you ever met Ryan Pilkington
before?
No.
Image 78.
Ryan Pilkington was
a juvenile offender.
What?
How was I supposed to know?!
Blame Vetting, not me.
Ryan Pilkington was
repeatedly processed
at Kingsgate Police Station
from 2009 to 2012.
You served at Kingsgate
Yeah. I'll tell you who else was
at Kingsgate back then -
your Kate Fleming.
Did she remember him?
Eventually, yeah.
MOCKINGLY: Yeah, "eventually".
According to Operation Lighthouse
files examined by AC-12, you advised
DSU Davidson to replace PS Farida
Jatri with PC Ryan Pilkington.
What? No!
Farida's an experienced
MIT Sergeant.
This kid's still on probation.
Why the hell would I do that?
Yes, why indeed?
But I DIDN'T do it!
So, Pilkington joins MIT,
and the next thing we know he's
in a police vehicle that
mysteriously veers off the road
into a reservoir, nearly killing
the only person of interest
in the murder of Gail Vella.
Jesus Christ, are you lot deaf?
How many times?
He saved Terry Boyle!
Terry Boyle is the
last man standing.
The OCG want him done away with
to tie up the loose ends.
Did you facilitate an attempt
on Terry Boyle's life?
No, of course I bloody didn't!
Yet you were responsible
for an officer
with OCG connections joining MIT.
All of these suspicious deaths...
They seem to be the work of an OCG
in collusion
with corrupt police officers -
does that sound familiar?
Yeah, it rings a bell.
You've been singing the same song
for the best part of a decade.
No-one's been on Operation
Lighthouse longer than you.
And at no stage have you directed
the inquiry towards
the obvious OCG links
to Gail Vella's murder.
I've been 100% committed
to finding her murderer!
Yes, just doing a bloody God-awful
job of it, is that it?
No, no.
Look, if there were OCG links,
do you not think someone would have
pointed it out to me?
They have done. Image 87.
What is seen in Image 87, sir?
HE SCOFFS
Well, someone's put them there.
I didn't put them there, did I?
Image 87 shows the open boot of
Police Service Vehicle
Golf X-ray, six, nine, Yankee,
Victor, Lima.
Police Service Vehicle Golf X-ray,
six, nine, Yankee, Victor, Lima
is registered to Detective
Superintendent Ian Buckells.
In the boot are a number
of Operation Lighthouse files.
Said files have been missing
ever since the 4th of November,
when AC-12 officers entered
Hillside Lane Police Station
to seize all files relating
to Operation Lighthouse.
These files contain references
to a possible burglary
at Gail Vella's home on the night of
her murder.
They also contain references
to the hard-contact method
of execution employed by the gunman.
Now, the fact she was murdered
outside her own home,
the unique untraceable murder
weapon - all of which are consistent
with a contract killing typically
orchestrated by organised crime.
So how do you account for these
files being found
in your service vehicle?
Well, it's a fit-up, isn't it?
Someone put them there!
My officers do not plant evidence.
We work to the letter of the law,
fella - the letter!
These files show a whole line of
inquiry that's either been
disregarded through negligent police
work or deliberately suppressed
to protect organised crime.
And the fact that they're
squirrelled away
in the boot of your car suggests
the latter.
I never said
that AC-12 planted them.
I've just got no idea
how they got there, that's all.
What we have here is a pattern.
A pattern of events
with a clear OCG signature.
And in each case, there is a failure
to investigate properly.
Now, why is that,
Detective Superintendent Buckells?
I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know?!
You're the senior detective!
I don't know why I don't know.
Charge him.
All right? All right.
We sent Buckells back to custody
for charging.
Nice one. Got our man.
What's up, mate?
You should've seen his interview.
This bloke couldn't organise
a piss-up in a brewery.
Yeah, well, that's his cover.
The armed robbery at the bookmaker's
that delayed MIT getting
to Carl Banks's place.
Only one person caused that delay -
Jo Davidson.
Look, without Jo, we wouldn't have
got Buckells.
Look, you haven't seen the change
in her I have.
Now Buckells is off her back,
she's on the Gail Vella case 100%.
All I'm saying, mate, is we keep
going, gathering evidence,
with an open mind. Yeah,
I know how anti-corruption works.
I'm glad to be out of it.
What does that mean?
You spend your life nicking bent
coppers, you start believing
they're everywhere. Being on a
regular team, it's opened my eyes.
The vast majority of them are
decent, honest people,
like you and me. Jo Davidson's
really just like you and me?
Or is that what she wants you to
believe?
All I'm saying, Steve, is you spend
too much time on anti-corruption,
it starts to change
the way you see things.
Well done on Buckells.
Night, mate.
ENGINE STARTS
Night.
OK.
DOOR OPENS
Ma'am.
Last time we met, I thought
we made ourselves abundantly clear
with our request
for full consultation.
Yet you submitted
no warning of your plan to charge
Detective Superintendent Buckells.
Ma'am, as you well know,
anti-corruption inquiries
are of the greatest sensitivity,
obliging my officers and myself
to exercise the utmost discretion
in who we share information with.
Are you deliberately attempting
to embarrass me?
I am attempting to uphold standards
in public office.
Public trust can only be maintained
where wrongdoing is held to account.
My God...
You must have been living
in a different country
the past few years.
Andrea, you've been briefed.
You can't say you weren't warned,
Ted.
Not only warned,
but a final warning.
Look, ma'am, I cannot lead my unit
if at every twist and turn
I am being asked to second-guess
how my orders are going to play out
at HQ.
In that respect, we agree.
You've become unable
to lead your team.
What?
No-one wants to be vindictive here,
Ted.
You've done your 30 years.
You'll be permitted to retire
on your full pension...
..and avoid the ignominy of
disciplinary action and dismissal.
Oh, yeah, great.
Definitely no ignominy in that,
then.
Your retirement won't appear
suspicious. Oh!
The PCC and the Chief Constable
have agreed to redistribute funding
to front-line services.
As a result, AC-3, AC-9 and AC-12
will merge into a single unit
under the command
of a Chief Superintendent.
What about my officers?
They do not deserve this.
Clearly, anti-corruption numbers
must be cut.
By what - a third? Half?
More like 90%.
This is the Chief Constable
down to the ground.
At the Karim Ali inquest, he uttered
not one word of the truth.
God, give me strength - a barefaced
liar promoted to our highest office!
All your staff will be given
the opportunity to apply
for the new unit or be integrated
into other departments.
The Chief Constable is making
his announcement next month.
You've got till then, Ted.
This is a capitulation.
This is a capitulation
to criminality and corruption!
I mean, what has happened to us?
This must be a shock, Ted.
I can see you're upset.
It's not a rhetorical question,
ma'am.
What has happened to us?
When did we stop caring
about honesty...and integrity?
Ma'am.
LOMAX: All firearms used by the
armed robbers at Hickey's bookie's
were recovered and referenced
by NABIS.
None of them match to any previous
firearms offence.
This is the ejected cartridge found
close to Gail's Peugeot.
The bullet was recovered some hours
later, having continued
its trajectory and struck the wall
of a neighbouring house.
The murder weapon's never
been found.
A killer would've disposed of it
as smartly as he did his clothing.
I don't know why he left
the cartridge, though.
Yeah, I've been thinking
the same thing.
But now we know
there was a burglary,
the killer had to act fast.
He couldn't waste his time looking
for a cartridge in the dark,
and as for a bullet,
it could've gone anywhere.
To cover your tracks, you only need
to dispose of the murder weapon,
provided the murder weapon is
untraceable.
The ballistics report found
the bullet and cartridge appeared
to be non-standard.
Specially tailored ammunition.
Which suggests that the gun was made
in a workshop.
Typically from a decommissioned
firearm or replica.
It's untraceable.
OK, but none of the firearms used
in the armed robbery
of the bookie's were workshopped.
So we don't have a connection.
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe not.
RINGING TONE
Hello.
DI Fleming.
I need a production order.
Jake, you've already been charged
with the armed robbery
of Hickey's Bookmakers Limited
on October 27th of this year,
for which you're currently
on remand.
Should you be found guilty of said
offence, your cooperation today
will be submitted to the judge,
maybe taken into account
when it comes to sentencing.
It would assist our inquiry to trace
the firearms used in the robbery.
I don't know nothing about the guns.
According to your statement
of November 2nd 2020,
in the early hours of October 27th
2020, you were woken
at your residential address by one
of your fellow armed robbers,
who you've declined to name, and
briefed by him regarding the plan
to carry out an armed robbery of
Hickey's bookie's.
Did this person provide you with a
firearm?
No.
When did the guns appear, Jake?
We all met up to get organised with
the van and that.
And this is when they first provided
you all with guns?
Yeah.
Who supplied the firearms, Jake?
The guns was already there
in a crate.
Where did this take place?
Like a works place,
whatever they call 'em.
An industrial estate?
Yeah, like a big shed.
We weren't allowed inside.
Some bloke come out with the guns.
Were some of these firearms
decommissioned guns
that had gone through conversion
in a workshop?
Nobody wanted to risk one.
Didn't trust them.
So, we just left them there.
Never seen 'em again.
CHLOE: You all right, sir?
All done. Search complete.
What did they get?
They covered the place
top to bottom.
FC said they harvested
a sizeable amount of prints
and potential DNA deposits.
If anyone else was in that house
apart from Farida, we'll know.
Right, good work.
Steve.
Kate, thanks for coming.
Thank you, Chloe.
On the gaffer's orders, we placed
surveillance on Ryan Pilkington.
This image shows Ryan Pilkington
in the vicinity
of Frederico's Bar
on November 10th.
Shit! Jo Davidson and me were there
that night.
This image shows Pilkington
on Croxford Street on the night
of November 8th.
Jo Davidson's home address.
You were right, Kate,
he's up to something.
GPS data from a tracking device
we placed on Pilkington's vehicle.
Unfortunately, he's refrained
from making any contact
with any known elements
of organised crime.
He's refrained or he knows
how to drop off the radar.
Resources are stretched, ma'am.
The surveillance team
just don't have the manpower.
Er, returning to the tracker.
Hot spots coincide with Hillside
Lane, Pilkington's home address
and various locations known to be
visited by Jo Davidson.
He's watching her.
Or meeting with her.
You got evidence of that?
No.
Jo could be in danger.
She qualifies for an Osman warning.
Steve's right - we can't be certain
they're not in this together.
She could tip him off about
our surveillance operation.
I'm sorry, Kate, but no warning.
Look.
I-I just want to say that we may not
solve this in a few days
or a few weeks,
or even a few months.
I mean, there really isn't
any telling
if you're going to see something
like this through.
I'm just counting on all of you
to carry the fire.
All right? Hey.
Not late, am I? Outside OK?
Yeah, sure.
I'm sorry you had to chase.
I was just worried
you'd changed your mind.
Oh, right - you have.
No, it's...
I got made DI.
But that ain't a deal-breaker.
Just saves you having to call me
"ma'am" all day.
I just... I wonder if we can put
this transfer on hold,
you know, delay it,
just till I see
how a couple of things play out.
Well, if that's what you want.
But I can't keep my boss hanging on
forever.
Yeah, I get it.
I'll order.
Usual?
Yeah, OK.
Boss, Amanda's got an update.
Because we drew a blank
on Gail Vella's personal devices,
we sought authority to examine
computers she might've used at work.
We've managed to recover another
audio file.
That's great.
It appears to be a complete
and uncorrupted audio recording of
a phone call Gail Vella made
in the workplace, hence it was saved
on a hard drive.
Good work. Thank you.
I'll get it set up
in the meeting room. Ta.
MAN ON AUDIO: Sometimes the police
lie for understandable reasons.
The mistaken shooting of Karim Ali,
say.
GAIL: I covered the inquest.
Well, then, you'll know his widow
offered the more plausible version
of events - an armed
counterterrorism unit burst
into their flat and shot Karim dead
without warning.
The absence of a warning fit with
established police tactics
in the face of a suicide bomber.
You don't want to give them
a chance to detonate.
Yet all the police testimony
insisted they'd given a warning
and that Karim had refused
to surrender.
The inquest jury were convinced
the police were lying.
No police were prosecuted.
No-one was even disciplined.
And the officer in charge went on to
become Chief Constable.
So, as I was saying, this all comes
under the category of what I'd call
a police cover-up designed to
mitigate reputational damage.
But sometimes the reasons for
the cover-up are more obscure...
AUDIO CONTINUES
He likes the sound of his own voice,
mind.
I still can't place him, sir.
..your anonymity's guaranteed.
On the podcast, your voice will be
completely disguised.
Well, it's got to be something
pretty bad if you'd rather go
with the story that you're basically
a bunch of racists.
I-I didn't detect a race element in
Balaclava Man. Not Balaclava Man...
They're talking about
Operation Trapdoor. Roz Huntley.
Go back.
I-I didn't detect a race element
in Balaclava Man.
Not Balaclava Man. Balaclava Men.
What?
Got him.
KATE: Although they weren't used in
the robbery, the suspect described
seeing workshopped firearms.
Sounds like the type used in
Gail Vella's murder.
We also believe the meeting might
have taken place in the actual
workshop - we're attempting to piece
together where it might be located.
Great work, guys.
Really. Great work.
Thanks, boss.
Cheers, Chris.
Nice one, catch you later.
I need to talk to you in private.
Something wrong?
It's not personal. It's work.
I took a witness statement
from Ryan Pilkington
about the reservoir incident,
and there's holes in his account.
What kind of holes?
Why Lisa lost control
of the vehicle.
How come she drowned?
He's still on probation -
maybe he was traumatised,
he can't piece the memory together.
What?
He's spying on you.
How do you know?
Because I saw him outside the pub
the other night.
Look, Jo, I don't want to worry you,
but it's a trust issue.
Ryan.
Leave it.
Ma'am.
With what's happened
to DSU Buckells, I suddenly realised
you might not be awarded
your commendation.
Oh. Right.
So I talked to the Chief Super, and
he's agreed I should be the one
to submit it, so it's not tarnished
by DSU Buckells' situation.
Thank you very much, ma'am.
You showed courage above and beyond
the call of duty.
That shouldn't go unrecognised.
I'm very grateful, ma'am.
Well, in my role, sometimes
I'm forced to give with one hand.
You see, having lost
a senior detective,
I need to bring in a new officer
at DS/DI level,
but budget constraints oblige me
to post someone out.
I hope you realise
it's nothing personal, Ryan,
but you're the most junior,
and with this commendation
in the offing, I'm sure
you'll have no problem getting
recruited by one of the top teams.
Thank you for everything
you've done, ma'am.
It's a privilege serving on MIT.
Ma'am.
DI Arnott.
Last time we met,
I was in a wheelchair.
I thought you looked taller.
Relatively.
James Lakewell,
this is DC Chloe Bishop.
Pleased to meet you, Chloe.
Jimmy.
This is a voluntary interview.
You're not under arrest
for any further criminal offences
and are free to return
to your cell at any time.
You do not have to say anything.
As a solicitor,
I'm sure you're well aware.
My legal career's been
somewhat curtailed.
We want to ask you some
questions about Gail Vella.
Do you know who I'm referring to?
Of course.
Did you ever meet Gail Vella?
I didn't.
Did you ever speak to Gail Vella?
DI Arnott and I have entered
into evidence an audio recording
that was made on...
..the 6th of July 2019,
between 10.36 and 11.04am.
We've examined prisoner
communications logs
at Blackthorn Prison
which record that you made
a lawfully requested outgoing call
between these times to
a number corresponding with
Gail Vella's place of work.
We've listened to the recording.
It was you.
Now, in the recording,
Mr Lakewell, you can be heard
recounting information relating
to Operation Trapdoor,
for which you were convicted
of all charges in 2017,
and another case
which we're attempting to identify.
Always "attempting",
never "achieving".
In regards to the second case,
you can be heard
referring to a racist element.
Does that help
with your recollection?
What was Gail Vella digging into?
Was it something
that got her killed?
Listen, it doesn't bode well
to speak openly about such things.
FAINT BUZZING
A break in the old routine
is always welcome,
but I'm beginning to feel drawn
back to four blank walls
and the saturnine faces
of my fellow inmates.
Have a good day.
Lakewell didn't say much, sir.
But he's got plenty.
Why else would he
have opened up to Gail Vella?
Problem is he's dropped a hint
he's concerned about prison staff.
In what way?
We know senior figures in organised
crime don't want imprisonment
to be a barrier
to running their OCGs.
A few key prison officers
on the payroll is all they need.
I mean, look how Farida Jatri
was silenced.
So, how do we get him to talk?
I've got a plan, sir.
Ten-eight.
Alpha Charlie 4-5,
TA.
BELL RINGS
Alpha Charlie 6-4, ARVs are TA
and standing by for Windermere.
Alpha Charlie 4-5, received.
Stand by.
6-4, received,
ARVs standing by.
DOOR OPENS
Sit there.
Go, go! 4-5, Windermere POB.
SIRENS BLARE
Everything's in place.
These are copies of all
the relevant legal agreements -
the production order
for your interview in secure custody
today, the terms of the application
to the Ministry of Justice
regarding your immunity
from prosecution.
It's all ready to go.
You'll vanish into witness
protection - new name, new life.
You just spent your last night
in prison...
..if you tell us
what we need to know.
SIREN BLARES
Control, Alpha Charlie 6-4,
request sit rep.
Alpha Charlie 6-4, State Nine
en route, Windermere secure.
Received, 6-4.
Why are you so convinced I'll talk?
I never did last time.
That was before you spent the best
part of four years inside.
People with influence know
I didn't grass.
They've made sure I'm well treated.
For most offenders,
that doesn't sound too bad.
Roof over your head,
three meals a day.
A bit of respect from your own kind.
Thing is, Jimmy,
they're not your own kind.
I've read your file.
Luxury hotels, Michelin-star
restaurants, glamorous girlfriends.
I don't pretend there isn't
a downside to prison life.
But the upside is not being killed.
So why'd you risk talking
to Gail Vella?
I reckon you were testing the water,
see if you could pull it off
without getting caught.
Being killed is worth the risk,
if there's even the slightest chance
of getting your old life back.
Interesting analysis.
I pleaded guilty
and I was sentenced.
The level of authority to reverse
all that and to enrol me
in witness protection
lies way above your pay grade.
At ministerial level, I'd reckon.
Look, I never said it'd be easy.
But Gail Vella got killed over this.
What was the case
she was looking into?
As I'm sure you realise, DI Arnott,
anything I say in these
circumstances
wouldn't be evidential.
Therefore, no-one could ever know
who the information came from.
Did you see that vehicle?
Alpha Charlie 6-4,
visual with suspect vehicle.
Stand by for registration.
Received, 6-4. Standing by.
Alpha Charlie 5-2, suspect vehicle
PNC check, Sierra, Lima.
One, eight, Lima, Mike, Juliet.
Control, 5-2.
Running PNC check. Stand by.
HORNS BLAST
Alpha Charlie 5-2,
status Zero, Moss Heath Avenue.
Status Zero, Moss Heath Avenue.
Alpha Charlie 5-2, Received.
ARMED POLICE! ARMED POLICE!
Drop your weapons!
RAPID GUNFIRE
What's happening?
Can you get me out, please?
Move! Move!
Stay down!
Alpha Charlie 5-2,
we are under attack
from multiple armed gunmen,
request urgent armed assistance.
GUNFIRE DROWNS OUT RADIO
5-2, 4-5, need to evacuate,
going to get you out.
4-5, received, evac authorised,
repeat, evac authorised!
Sarge.
Stay down!
Jonesy, I can't get a grip! OK.
Give me a leg up!
Steve! It's Jonesy!
Is everyone OK?
JONESY!
RAPID GUNFIRE RESUMES
INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER
Help! I need some help!
Please, quick!
Alpha Charlie 5-4, under fire
from sniper, target Windermere.
Repeat, target is Windermere.
Obs on sniper,
overlooking our current
position on Moss Heath Avenue!
Received, ARV's on way.
Alpha Charlie 5-2, Control,
urgent message,
one police casualty, Moss Heath
Avenue, critical injuries!
Come on, Jonesy.
GUNFIRE CEASES
RADIO: Control
from Alpha Charlie 6-6.
Sitrep update.
All armed suspects are neutralised.
SIREN APPROACHES
There's been a forensic NABIS
recovery of all the OCG
weapons from the scene.
I don't even know
if this is important,
but some of the weapons appear
to have been workshopped.
It's important. Send them
to ballistics for a full analysis.
Sir.
Jonesy.
Such a good girl, it's a terrible
loss, it's a terrible loss.
And now there's no doubt
about it - the OCG were
tipped off from inside of Blackthorn
when we picked up Lakewell.
Prison officers are in their pocket.
Unless the leak came from AC-12.
Not on my watch, it didn't.
Look, you two have been through
a hell of a lot.
Now that the PIM's finished,
maybe you should just go off duty.
No, sir.
I'd like to continue.
Let's do this.
Chloe...
..that won't be necessary.
Jimmy?
My solicitor's offered to read
out my statement but,
given what's happened, the least
I can do is look you all in the eye.
I'm not prepared to submit to an
interview, not today, not any day.
For Christ's sake, fella,
one of my officers just got killed!
And it was a miracle
there weren't more casualties,
including myself and DI Arnott.
It was a warning.
I'll never be able to stop looking
over my shoulder.
Jimmy, I promise you, we'll do
whatever it takes to persuade
the Ministry of Justice to let you
into witness protection.
There are some people there's
no protection from.
People or person?
What happened today wasn't cobbled
together by a couple
of foot soldiers - the order
came from the top, the very top.
That's a logical deduction.
Yes, so who?
I'm a coward, not a fool.
For Christ's sake!
You really imagine
you'll be safe in prison?
They'll know I didn't talk,
so, yes, I hope so.
That's right, isn't it, DI Arnott,
I didn't talk?
Get him out of here!
I'm sorry.
Ah!
It's as easy as that, Jo.
Let's go inside and discuss this.
I say "discuss" -
I'll explain why I won't
be posted off your team.
And you'll listen.
Morning, boss, everything OK?
Wondered if you had an update on the
armed robbery line of inquiry?
Chris and I are trying to locate
the firearms workshop
we believe is connected to
Gail Vella's murder weapon.
Great. Boss, while I've got you,
I wanted to bring up the other
matter - my concerns with Ryan.
He only joined the force
18 months ago.
Any active links to organised crime
would have been
detected during vetting.
Jo, seriously?
Thing is, Kate, we're
already down a senior detective.
I'd hate to lose another one.
Sorry, I don't follow.
If people start asking questions
about what really
happened at the reservoir, they're
going to start wondering why you
were following the patrol car, but
failed to call for backup in time to
prevent an officer from drowning and
the attempted murder of a suspect.
Drop it, Kate.
That's an order.
What's this?
We're going to share.
Overcrowding.
Where's your bunk?
They're bringing it now.
Now, you watch what happens
to a rat.
Boss. Yeah.
We've got the DNA
from Farida Jatri's house.
Truth is, I'm a bit confused.
Maybe you'll have more joy.
Ma'am.
I don't know if you saw, ma'am,
the Box this morning had an inmate
found dead inside of Blackthorn.
James Lakewell.
What was the cause of death?
Being a rat, ma'am.
We've investigated DCI Davidson's
version of events.
An extended forensic search
at PS Farida Jatri's house detected
a small number of DNA deposits,
closely matching an individual
whose DNA is stored on the
police database.
Joanne Davidson.
Great work, we've got her.
She told us a pack of lies about her
relationship with Farida Jatri.
Not only that, sir,
it means there was ample
opportunity for Davidson to plant
the burner phones at the property.
This isn't the most
significant finding, sir.
As we know, sir, officers'
samples are stored on the system to
exclude contamination of
crime scenes.
Now, an officer's DNA isn't
speculatively examined on a
routine basis, and certainly wasn't
back when Davidson joined the force.
Because the DNA deposits detected
at the house weren't assumed to
relate solely to a police officer,
they were compared
against the whole system.
The analysis detected partial
matches to a nominal
whose DNA is stored on other
police databases.
He's identified over the page.
As we know, sir,
there's only one credible
explanation for Jo Davidson's
DNA matching this individual.
They're blood relatives.
Mother of God.
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN