So I made him
show me his dick.
And then, I swear to God,
his dick was pierced
right through the tip. Yeah!
And then I told Oliver about it,
and he got so mad.
Oh, God.
My boobs are so huge right now!
Every time I get my period,
they quadruple in size.
Look at them, I'm serious.
- Feel them! They're like swollen.
- Ew, gross. Get away.
Hey, sweetie.
You wanna feel 'em?
What?
Oh, my God!
Did anyone just see that?
Kate Messner just touched my boobs!
She seriously just grabbed them!
Lesbo much?
♪ Funny how we run around ♪
♪ And see what we got ♪
♪ We don't even know what it is we found ♪
Hello.
Hey, Mom.
Hey.
Wow!
- What's the occasion?
- There's no occasion.
Babe, you just made my day.
Child protective services drop by?
Yep. They always do,
and the fake mustache worked like a charm.
- How's school?
- Coolio.
I joined the A/V club.
Coolio. I bet you fit right in.
- And I'm dissecting a frog in science.
- Ugh.
Named it "Gorf."
- How'd you come up with that?
- Well, it's "frog" spelled backwards.
Oh. Duh. Well, rest in peace, Gorf.
And I, uh... met someone.
A girl.
Really?
Well, tell me about her.
Okay.
She's in A/V.
She's really artistic.
But... not in an obvious way, just... is.
And she's really into music
and really pretty.
She is all that and a bag of chips.
Sounds like it.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna ask her out.
I just gotta figure out how.
Any ideas?
Well, I don't know.
Hey, I hope...
I hope you'll be safe.
Oh! Oh, no. Mom, how did you
get that from me saying that...
- I know...
- Oh, ew.
You think you're not,
but you're at that age.
And sometimes in high school,
we forget to look before we leap...
like Gorf.
Or...
like when you got pregnant with me?
Mmm.
- I did not mean it like that.
- Yeah.
Mm-hmm. Gotcha.
Luke, you're the best thing
that's happened to me, you know that?
Okay, look.
You know what I think you should do?
What?
I think, when the time is right,
you should tell her exactly how you feel.
And you do it
in the most "you" way possible.
Thanks, Mom.
So...
what's her name?
For lunch today, Sloppy Joes.
But personally, I think
they should be called Sloppy Scotts
on a Jessica Betts bun.
- Oh, my God. You are so inappropriate.
- Those are your morning announcements.
Have a Boring day.
And we're clear.
Okay, okay. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I know.
Hey, focus working okay?
Oh, yeah. It's fine.
Oh, wait! I was thinking.
- Maybe you could come over...
- I got to get to geometry.
Next time, Luke.
Is he trying to open
that Surge with his mind?
No, he's just upset with me.
That's an understatement.
He's going to ask out Kate Messner
because she called him cute.
- Holy shit. How you gonna do it?
- Mm-hmm.
I don't know. Any ideas?
Do it while jumping out of a plane
without a parachute.
Wait, that's what you're doing.
Remember in Point Break when he jumps
without a chute? He's like, "Gee-yah"!
Then he jumps.
He breaks both his knees,
but it turns out okay.
- He does not say "gee-yah."
- I think he does.
Is that before or after
he gets his best friend killed?
Will you stop it, McQuaid?
She's really nice and smart.
You'd like her if you weren't
so judgmental all the time.
Seriously, I might have a chance
with this girl.
You could be happy for me.
My apologies. You have my support.
Thanks.
Where is your lady love?
Did you hear Kate Messner totally
felt-up Emaline Addario during gym?
I always knew there was
something weird about that girl.
If Kate's really a lesbian,
does that mean she has AIDS?
Like the guy from Real World?
- Yeah.
- Probably.
This is kinda freaking me out.
It should.
I wouldn't even let her breathe on me.
Will Kate Messner please report
to the principal's office?
Kate Messner,
please report to the principal's office.
Oh, my God.
Unbelievable.
Harlot!
Fallen woman! Street walker!
Say, what?
Pretty much everyone's been saying
you got felt up by some chick
in the girl's locker room.
Yawn, yesterday's goss.
Is it true?
'Tis true.
God damn it.
A lady's touch upon my bosom hath awoken
such curious
and mysterious feelings within me!
I'm not playing a scene with you now,
okay, Emaline?
Oh, how my heart yearns for her!
How my loins quake!
How free I feel on this merry day!
You know, this is why
you'll never be a good actress. Okay?
You're out of touch with your inner truth,
you can't have a genuine conversation.
Honestly, I feel bad for you.
Well, you have a tiny dick.
Oh!
We're done. All right?
It's over, that's it.
Fine.
Oh!
Bitch!
My grandma gave me those.
She has diabetes!
Dad?
Kate Messner! Come on in!
What do you want?
You asked me to treat you like
any other student, so I am. Take a seat.
Janitor Steve informed me
about some crassly worded vandalism,
graffiti really, that showed up
on a locker this morning.
Turns out that locker was yours.
It said "Dyke,"
which is a derogatory term
- for when a woman has romantic...
- I know what it means.
Okay. I'm just trying to figure out
who did this. Yeah.
You know, has anyone been mean
or picking on ya recently?
I mean, why would someone do that?
Because people are stupid.
Hey, sweetie, uh...
I wouldn't take it personally.
I bet they didn't even know
whose locker it was.
Everything else okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
Back to class, young lady.
You can do this.
Okay.
Hey.
- How's it going?
- Um...
I've had better days.
Oh, yeah?
I was just thinking about you.
You were?
I love this.
I know it's, uh,
super popular or whatever,
but track three's kinda
saving my life right now.
Hmm.
Which one's that again?
♪ By now you should've somehow
Realized what you gotta do ♪
♪ I don't believe that anybody
Feels the way I do about you now ♪
I wonder who he's singing about.
Don't you?
♪ Backbeat, the word was on the street
That the fire in your heart is out ♪
♪ I'm sure you've heard it all before... ♪
I gotta go.
Uh, I'll see ya later?
Absolutely.
"There was s-something my, my..."
"Mysterious."
Can't you just invent, like, a robot,
that will read this to me or something?
I wish. Not with my limited knowledge
and resources.
But when the do robots take over,
none of this will matter.
We'll just be brains floating in tanks.
Slaves of virtual stimulation
and synthetic automated nourishment.
What ever gets me out of remedial.
Guys, I've got it.
But I need your help.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ One, two, princes kneel before you
That's what I said now ♪
♪ Princes, princes who adore you
Just go ahead now ♪
♪ One has diamonds in his pockets
And that's some bread now ♪
♪ This one said he wants
To buy you rockets ♪
♪ Ain't in his head now ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ This one got a princely racket
That's what I said now ♪
♪ Got some big seal upon his jacket
Ain't in his head now ♪
Go, go!
♪ Marry him, your father will condone you
How 'bout that now? ♪
♪ Marry me, your father will disown you
He'll eat his hat now ♪
♪ Marry him or marry me ♪
♪ I'm the one that loves you baby
Can't you see? ♪
♪ I ain't got no future or a family tree ♪
♪ But I know what a prince and lover
Ought to be ♪
♪ I know what a prince and lover
♪ Said if you want to call me baby
Just go ahead now ♪
♪ And if you like to tell me maybe... ♪
- Testing, one, two, three.
- Dad.
Levels? Crash.
For today's video installment
of the Life and Times
of Mr. Leroy O'Neil,
that's me, I want to say
a few words about gratitude.
Some days it feels like life's gone
to shit.
Days like today,
where I'm just happy to be alive.
I'm healthy. I have a job.
I have a woman and my son,
little Luke'em Nuke'em.
He might be the smartest,
most passionate little man on this planet.
He's five. Kid's blowing my mind.
Leroy, hey, dinner's ready.
Come in.
- What are you doing?
- Look at you.
Come here.
- Come here.
- Okay. Hi.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Come here.
- Say hi to camera?
- Are you recording this?
Leroy, I look like a train wreck.
Hey, you look beautiful.
Smooth talker.
Dinnertime.
This may not be the life that, uh,
that I imagined for myself,
but god damn, it's a good one.
♪ Many mumbling mice
Dancing in the moonlight, mighty nice ♪
♪ Many mumbling mice,
- Kate?
- Good job. How was the range?
Hey, Leslie.
I heard something about you today.
Something upsetting.
Are you a homo?
No! That's ridiculous.
Of course it is!
I mean, ew, gross.
Either way, I hope you overcome this.
I'll pray for you.
Thanks.
Play this.
What's on it?
Can't tell you that.
- Come on. Is it inappropriate?
- No.
- All right. What's in it for me?
- Really?
Yeah.
- Um, Luke?
- One sec.
- What's in it for me?
- Luke.
- Just...
- All right.
Six pack of Jolt?
- Was that so hard?
- Thank you.
New information has come to light,
and your odds with Kate
are potentially compromised.
I think you should reconsider doing this.
What are you talking about?
New information. It's just a rumor.
- It's probably garb. But I just heard...
- Ooh, you're jealous.
Jealous?
Yes. Jealous.
That's why you've been negative
about this, right?
That's absurd. I'm always negative.
Listen, we're still gonna be friends
after I get a girlfriend.
You just gotta stop worrying so much.
Oh, man!
Everyone's gonna shit when they see this!
In a good way.
See.
They're gonna shit.
In a good way.
Good Morning, BHS! I'm Jessica Betts.
And I'm Scott Pocket.
♪ Scott Pocket ♪
Before I begin, today we have
a special video presentation.
It comes to us from a fre...
Roll tape!
♪ Today is gonna be the day
That they're gonna throw it back to you ♪
♪ By now you should've somehow
Realized what you gotta do ♪
♪ I don't believe that anybody
Feels the way I do about you now ♪
♪ Backbeat, the word was on the street
That the fire in your heart is out ♪
♪ I'm sure you've heard it all before ♪
♪ But you never really had a doubt ♪
♪ I don't believe that anybody
Feels the way I do about you now ♪
♪ And all the roads we have to walk
Are winding ♪
♪ And all the lights that lead us there
Are blinding ♪
♪ There are many things that I
Would like to say to you ♪
♪ But I don't know how ♪
♪ Because maybe ♪
♪ You're gonna be the one that saves me ♪
♪ And after all ♪
♪ You're my wonderwall ♪
♪ I said maybe ♪
♪ You're gonna be the one that saves me ♪
Fuck!
Kate Messner...
will you go out with me?
Oh, God.
Uh, camera two,
pan to camera one.
Kate?
- Yes.
- Ha!
Yes!
♪ She was using me ♪
♪ But I didn't care ♪
♪ Don't you leave me now ♪
♪ Just don't you dare ♪
♪ Can't you understand? ♪
♪ With the hold of my hand ♪
♪ Love is everywhere ♪
♪ Except where I stand ♪
♪ Boys of the world ♪
♪ Just listen to me ♪
♪ If you meet a girl ♪
♪ With looks to a tee ♪
♪ It might be okay ♪
♪ For a little while ♪
♪ But think seriously ♪
♪ Is that your style? ♪
♪ Can't you understand ♪
♪ With the hold of my hand ♪
♪ Love is everywhere ♪
♪ Except where I stand ♪