Hunger, a poet once said,
is the most important thing we know,
the first lesson we learn.
But hunger can be easily
quieted down, easily satiated.
There is another force, a
different type of hunger,
an unquenchable thirst
that cannot be extinguished.
It's very existence is what
defines us, what makes us human.
That force is love.
Folks, this is your
captain up in the flight deck.
We are on our final descent into
New York for an on-time arrival.
We want to thank you for flying Regis Air
and encourage that you ask us
any connecting gate
information you may need.
We're looking at partly cloudy skies
and we may hit a little
turbulence on our approach.
Not again.
Yes?
Rose get back here now.
I need your help.
We're landing, whatever it is can wait.
Now. Come now!
All right, relax.
Sir, we're landing.
Would you power off your device?
You call this a device?
You have to turn it off.
It's like when a cop
calls a car a "vehicle".
Or when he calls you sir
when he means "asshole".
Having a little gig in New York coming up.
You give me three or four
of those little baby vodkas
I'll get you a front-row seat.
Turn it off, put your seat up.
We're landing, sir.
Ma'am.
Seat backs in the upright position.
Finally.
Flight attendants,
prepare for landing.
_
- _
On behalf of the cabin crew,
I want to take a moment to say...
Peter, you haven't done anything back here!
This place is a mess!
There's something in the plane.
-What do you mean?
Something alive in the cargo hold!
-Shh-shh!
We'd like to
extend a special thank you
to any Black Platinum Award
mbers flying with us tonight
and encourage all our passengers...
What the hell do you mean, like a dog?
No, it's something really, really big.
I heard it move.
A thumping underneath the floor.
I heard it...
No, Peter, there are no
animals on the manifest.
It tried to open the latch.
I heard a noise.
Then it moved away.
But you can feel it moving.
Flight crew prepare for arrival.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Did you see it?
Nothing. I just think that you were...
Oh my God!
Go tell Captain Redfern!
Tell him to warn the landing crew!
And get emergency services!
There's someone down there!
It's gonna give!
Private Delta 3-4-7,
you're clear for taxiway Foxtrot.
clear for taxiway Foxtrot.
Regis Air 7-5-3, this
is Kennedy ground.
Regis Air 7-5-3, Kennedy ground.
Regis 7-5-3, Kennedy ground, over.
What the...?
Bishop...
a Regis Air flight out of Berlin,
the 767 widebody,
stopped on the service apron.
What's it doing there?
Apron's dead.
That's a blind spot.
I don't know.
The plane just went dark,
shut down, flat-out quit.
No lights, no radio, no nothing.
Regis 7-5-3, Kennedy ground, over.
Regis 7-5-3- Kennedy
ground, please respond, over.
Okay, shut down Foxtrot.
Clear all the gates and advise reroute.
How many aboard?
Almost full flight, sir.
Passengers, crew, about 210 souls.
Holy Jesus.
Shouldn't we wait for
first responders, sir?
Bishop?
Bishop, wait!
Engines are shut down.
No lights.
Whoa, it's cold.
It's like a dead animal.
There's something really wrong here.
It's like it never moved.
This looks so much bigger
from the ground than on the screen.
I mean, they're like buildings with wings.
All the window shades are shut, see that?
Bishop!
Hey, fellas.
Bishop...
Not all of them...
Scramble all emergency
vehicles to taxiway Foxtrot.
SWAT, Homeland Security?
Port Authority, FBI, TSA, CDC.
Robbie, no one on the tower calls home.
No one shares the news.
This is bad, real bad.
We've got ourselves a dead airplane.
Sync and corrected by caioalbanezi
www.addic7ed.com
_
Hey, buddy, you can't park there.
There's a fire hydrant.
It's a medical emergency.
Oh, is it really?
It will be if I can't
get this tie on right.
You know how to tie this?
I don't know, man, I wear a clip-on.
You're on your own.
You waiting for somebody?
Yeah, why?
Here's what I need you to do.
The meter maid comes by,
you tell them it's
official CDC business, okay?
Yeah, sure thing.
Zach.
Hey, man.
Hey, dude.
You're late.
Five minutes. It can't be helped.
Ten, Dad.
Ten? Okay.
That's wrong.
Maybe... maybe ten.
I got a good feeling about this.
Wish us luck.
Good luck.
Five minutes.
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
Ten.
I texted you five times.
I wouldn't have gotten that
'cause I don't text when I drive.
It's not safe.
Dr. Goodweather...
Eph, please.
She gets Kelly, my son gets Zach,
so Ephraim or Eph, please.
Dr. Goodweather, this is the last of six
court-appointed custody
counselling sessions.
You've been late for four of them.
Are you gonna say that I'm late
because I don't want to be here?
You might be onto something
but I have a really good reason.
There was this outbreak of Hantavirus
in this alphabet city pre-school.
Which is extremely rare
this far north and east.
Dr. Goodweather, every time you come in
you take over the session.
Because I have control issues, I know.
But I have to defend myself here.
Because this might be my last chance.
And I've thought long and hard about this.
And it seems like you two
have created this narrative
wherein I'm the bad guy.
But why?
Because I don't want out of my marriage.
'Cause I want things
back the way they were.
But this isn't just about you, Eph,
what you want, not anymore.
I'm an epidemiologist.
You know, if I take time off,
if I go fly-fishing, people die.
I get that you have an
important job, Ephraim.
And you're great at your job.
You get straight 'A's at your job.
But I'm flunking our marriage, is that it?
What are you writing? Please stop writing.
How horrible am I?
You're not horrible.
You're just barely present.
I've done everything you've asked me to
in order to get us back together again.
I quit drinking.
You wanted time alone so I moved out,
against my own wishes.
I've jumped through every hoop.
Tell me what you need.
Our time apart has only
clarified things for me.
It's allowed me to make
room in my life for Matt.
We're going to be living
together now and...
Matt, the Sears guy you were
talking about, at my house?
Matt is an operational manager.
At Sears.
Yeah, and you know what,
he gets straight 'A's at his job, too.
But at home, he's present.
Unlike you, he's always
here for both of us.
Does he drive a green Prius?
You want me to quit my job, I'll do it.
I'll quit my job.
I don't want you to quit for me.
I wouldn't be quitting for you.
I'd be quitting because of you for Zach,
so he isn't driving around Queens
in a green goddamn Prius.
Dr. Goodweather.
It's too late, Eph.
I love you but...
How can you love me and it be too late?
You want a guy who's crazy about Zach?
Check.
A guy who's crazy about you?
Decent, employed.
Check, check.
Can't you see that this
is the problem, Eph?
This is who you are.
Go.
Nora, how bad is it?
It's crazy.
I have like 12 different agency officials
about to have a
dick-measuring contest here.
No.
It's an international
flight docking out of Berlin.
CDC gets the first call.
I can be there in 20 minutes.
Can you keep the measuring
contest going that long?
Don't worry, I'll show them mine.
It might just work.
Sorry.
I guess the meter reader didn't
see it as much of an emergency.
Matt, huh?
Yeah, that's me.
Interesting.
You know, it's too bad
I'm such a rush, Matt.
But I'm sure I'll see
you again in my house.
You drive safe now, you hear?
_
Hey, boss.
Got my milk?
Uh, yeah, here.
Homeland Security is just desperate
to push the button on a terror alert.
They're ready to get
on that plane right now.
Jim, terrorists usually crash planes,
not land them and shut them down.
So what are the 911 calls saying?
There haven't been any.
None?
Uh uh.
Dr. Goodweather!
When we flew to Chicago last week
we sat on the tarmac for half an hour.
People were freaking out, texting, calling.
There've been 200 people
sitting there silently for...
over an hour now.
Pilots?
Absolutely no movement.
Have you done heat readings?
Surface of the plane's too cold.
Blocks it all like a screen.
We got Delsar mics attached
to the surface of the plane,
picked up mostly silence.
Mostly?
Well, cooling pings
from the sheet metal contracting.
Oh, and there's this.
What do you think that is?
Rustling of some sort.
Our experts think it's
the engine shutting down
or liquids settling.
How long between landing and shutdown?
Six minutes.
It's too short a window
for a contagious event.
So I think CDC should take
a back seat on this one.
I agree.
Do you?
Absolutely, I do.
How often do you touch your face?
What?
In a day, how often?
I don't know, once an hour?
Every three minutes.
You have mouth/hand
contact every five minutes.
You touch somebody else every 20 minutes.
That's how contagion works.
You don't like terrorists?
Try negotiating with a virus.
A virus exists only to find
a carrier and reproduce.
That's all it does and it does it quickly.
It has no political views,
it has no religious beliefs,
it has no cultural hang-ups.
And it has no respect for a badge.
It has no concept of time or geography.
It might as well be the Middle Ages,
except for the convenience
of hitching a ride
on a metal tube flying
from meal to meal to meal.
That's how a plague begins.
So you still want to be the
first one through the door?
_
So we heard you buy silver
without a receipt, man.
Is that right?
I'm always in need of good silver, yes.
Okay, well...
Can I get, uh, 50 for this?
It's a very nice timepiece, indeed.
I see that the band links have snapped.
You must have been in
a hurry taking it off.
Can I... can I get 50 for it?
I can offer you maybe 25...
if the test is good.
Unfortunately, this is
merely silver-plated brass.
A cheap Eastern European knock-off.
Agh!
Listen very carefully, son!
I know your little friend has a gun
and the hammer is cocked but I don't care.
I can control your entire body
weight from this pressure point
and this knife is pointing
straight at your radial artery.
By the time he clears his coat pocket,
your artery will be
punctured and sliced wide open
from top to bottom.
You fall down bleeding,
I go under the counter
and your friend starts
shooting at an empty space.
I can guarantee you this...
you will bleed out before the
911 operator answers the phone.
That is option one!
Option two is, you release the bills,
your friend gives me the gun,
he can keep the bullets, I don't care,
and you leave this store.
Now, son, you have a choice.
Is there anything else I can do
for you gentlemen this evening?
We have more
now on the developing story
out of JFK Airport tonight.
You're looking at live video
of the airplane identified
as a Regis Air widebody jet.
It originated in Berlin
and it shut down just
moments after landing.
We are told there has been no
communication from the pilot.
All attempts to contact the flight crew...
Berlin...
He's back.
I, uh...
I don't know if I have the strength
to do it all over again.
This time...
I cannot fail.
Feeling hungry?
Enjoy, dear.
_
I'm not looking forward to
what we'll see out there.
You with me?
Mysterious dead plane on the
tarmac not exciting enough?
Sorry, just another court-mandated,
happy family therapy day.
I noticed, you cut your hair.
You cleaned up nicely.
Did you break out a tie?
It's in my jacket pocket.
Did it help?
Uh, no, in fact, it didn't.
She wants to take Zack away from me.
And there's a... man-child
living in my house with my son.
Careful.
Stay focused.
You and Kelly have been
separated for a year,
and things happen.
It happened to us.
Oh, that's different.
How is it different?
It just is.
I don't think Kelly would agree.
She doesn't know. I never told her.
You didn't?
No, she...
she filed so I didn't tell her.
She doesn't know.
You really know nothing
about women, do you?
Okay, boss...
ready to go through the looking glass?
Ready, Jim.
I got your milk.
Keep it cold 'til I come back.
Oh my God...
Jim, do you see this?
It's every passenger.
Everyone on the plane.
Yeah.
We're seeing it.
They're all dead.
What is it, Eph? What killed them?
No signs of struggle.
No signs of blistering or chemical agents.
No bruising.
Not seeing discoloration...
no markings.
Shit, what is it?
Something sudden, painless.
All the window shades are
closed except for this one.
Is it a gas leak? Is it chemical?
The Hazmat Cat's picking
up high levels of ammonia.
Nothing deadly, though.
There shouldn't be any
ammonia in the plane systems.
Jim, check the cargo manifest.
Got it.
I need a cargo manifest.
What about the Geiger?
It's negative, Jim.
No visible signs of trauma.
No bloating.
Tongue and soft palate
appear pale, almost white.
Eyes are clear.
The skin is dry, it's inelastic.
There's no frothing or nosebleeds.
There's no signs of struggle.
Almost peaceful.
Let's try the UV lights.
My God, what is this?
Are you getting this?
These patterns are everywhere.
All over the cabin.
They're only visible under UV light.
The pattern is biological.
Probably where the ammonia is coming from.
I'm taking samples.
You take the front
galley, I'll take the rear.
Jimbo...
what is this?
No, "Jimbo, please"?
Um, that's the cargo compartment.
Have it emptied.
Take each piece of luggage
and check it for biological
agents and ammonia spectrum.
Got it.
Jim...
the cockpit door just opened.
It should be locked.
Nora, that door's not supposed to be open.
Just going to take a quick look.
Alright, I want you back
out of there right now, okay?
That door is supposed to be locked.
You shouldn't be in there alone.
Nora, can you hear me?
Eph!
The door to the cockpit is open.
Nora is inside.
Nora? Eph?
Come on, guys, somebody talk to me!
Nora, I'm coming!
Help me!
Lady, get the light outta my face.
I'm sending in SWAT!
No, Jim, send paramedics!
We've got survivors!
_
Mr. Palmer...
Shh! It's his dialysis session.
He's asleep.
Well, then wake him up.
When he's ready.
Now.
In time.
Dialysis complete.
How long have you worked for
Stoneheart, Mr. Fitzwilliam?
All my life, sir.
Mr. Palmer aided me and my brothers
after my father passed.
Gratitude, what an effective leash.
Herr Eichhorst...
Mr. Palmer, Herr Eichhorst
is here to pay his respects.
I'll be outside if you need me.
You may notice how chilly it
has gotten in here, Eichhorst.
Twenty full degrees cooler
than the rest of the building.
But not too cold for you, I trust.
Of course, it can't be
too cold for you, can it?
The cargo has arrived safely
and all four survivors have been found.
Throughout my life
I've learned what it feels to cross a line,
to do things.
Things that cannot be undone.
That line...
it has been crossed now, hasn't it?
Your breath...
I'll never get used to...
Yes, even I miss breathing sometimes.
Here we go.
Leave it to me, it won't be long.
Everett.
Eph.
How bad is it?
The NTSB has taken over a
refrigerated chemical warehouse
in the Bronx.
They've turned it into a fully
contained mass casualty morgue.
That's not necessary, Everett.
These bags are triple-sealed.
I'm handing a dozen bodies over to the CME
four from each section of the plane
for autopsies.
And the four survivors?
I've secured the isolation
rooms at a local hospital.
We need to move them there right away.
Of course. I'm sure they'll comply.
Comply? I'm not asking them.
Invoking the Health Powers
Act, those four survivors stay.
Quarantine?
It's within the powers of the
CDC, Everett, you know that.
Look, if you quarantine
I need you to meet with the next of kin.
Reassure them the CDC's on the case.
Fine.
We're trying to figure out what happened,
what caused this.
Isn't that what's most important?
-Yes, of course.
But it's also important we
don't have full-tilt panic.
These people need to hear
from someone in the field.
We don't know anything yet.
You two figure this out. I
don't have time for this shit.
Jim?
-Yeah.
When he talks to the families,
I want no press, Everett.
No press, I promise.
Okay, you're telling me only four people
survived this plane crash?
Ms. Luss...
It Mrs. Luss.
Mrs. Luss, there was no crash.
An unidentified agent
killed all of the remaining passengers.
Any information you can give
us would be of great help.
Of great help to who?
To us, ma'am, the CDC.
Okay, well, I'm no ordinary passenger.
I'm Joan Luss.
I'm an attorney... of
Matloff, Luss and Hayum.
So all that information
that you're collecting
you're going to need to get to me.
Personally...
What are you doing?
Don't seal me in, I'm talking to you.
Excuse me, little miss.
Don't you walk away from me.
I am Joan Luss.
Captain Redfern, this is
my colleague, Dr. Martinez.
What happened on my plane?
That's what we came to ask you.
Now, I want you to try to
recall, as best you can...
fresh cut grass, garlic, green apple...
do you remember smelling any of these odors
before you passed out?
What? Grass? Apples?
Mnemonic odors, the way
our brain reads chemicals.
Phosphine gas, colorless,
smells like garlic.
Or phosgene very toxic,
smells like freshly cut grass.
I remember landing the plane
and turning onto the taxiway.
And then...
I don't remember anything else.
Eph, can I get you for a sec?
Oh, thank God, you're here.
I was just telling him
I have this noise in my head
like a hum.
Could you have someone
look at my ears again?
We'll have somebody perform
a full battery of tests.
But for now you need to stay
inside this tent, Mr. Barbour.
You don't understand.
My wife is gonna panic
if I don't call soon.
I need to call home.
Hey, you.
You're the guy I gotta talk to around here?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
How about some Demerol, Doc, huh?
And what time's that
refreshment cart swing by, uh?
Mr. Bolivar, what is the
last thing you can remember
before landing?
I don't know, uh...
flickering lights, maybe.
I blackout sometimes.
Those cuts on your arm?
Oh, these?
Yeah, I cut.
For the fans.
Tell me, these tattoos,
occult, satanic things
is this really part of your belief system?
You're kidding, Doc?
My father's a Baptist minister.
I'm in it for the pussy.
Eph.
There's something you have
to see in the cargo area,
right now.
Okay, let's go.
Who un-crated this thing?
No one.
This was how it came out.
No straps, no containment wrap.
Well, what is it?
What's inside of it?
No one's opened it yet.
But, what does it say in the manifest?
It's not on the manifest.
You got golf clubs, kayaks, machine parts
40 generators, 10.000 condoms
10 plasma TVs, but no box.
Looks like a coffin, doesn't it?
Coffin? It's nine feet tall.
It's old.
It's hand carved, it's not machined.
Hey, guys, over here.
Guys, look, we swabbed
it, we ran the Geiger,
we did samples of the air
and everything is fine.
But the NTSB was crystal clear
they didn't want us to touch anything.
Help me open it.
Okay.
Soil.
Why would someone ship a box of soil?
What are the chances
of someone loading this
unchecked and unlisted?
Something this size in a
flight bound for the US?
Impossible.
Not in today's world.
Jim, get samples from the top, mid, bottom
plastic seal it.
No one goes near this,
not Customs, not Homeland Security, nobody.
Eph, look.
It's a latch.
Why would anyone put a latch on the inside?
Call Berlin.
There's gotta be a record of this.
Somebody put this on the plane.
We just have to find out who.
A lot of
confusion here tonight
at JFK International Airport, Nestor.
Officials with the Centers
for Disease Control...
Any man who doesn't put your mom first
is out-of-his-mind crazy. Right, Z?
... multiple casualties,
I repeat, multiple casualties
aboard the stalled airliner,
Regis Air flight 753.
Tonight was a big step for you.
Shh!
... what caused the fatalities.
As you can see, behind me
officials with the CDC are on the scene.
But whether this is any indication
of a biological contamination...
Terrorists, it has to be.
What do you think, Z?
Whatever it is, my Dad will handle it.
Good night.
Good night, sweetheart.
... what
caused the fatalities...
_
And I need the master list of passengers
with their points of embarkation.
Also every place where that plane landed.
_
Eph...
the families are waiting.
You know this is all about him
covering his own ass, right?
Just talk to them like
you'd like to be talked to.
Tell them what you'd like to hear.
Whatever happens I'll be there.
_
Hey, you hear that?
No. Sorry, nothing.
What the...?
Agghh!
Gun hands won't work.
Knocking boys out every
day when I was locked up.
Raised all the time like Mayweather.
When I go a pro
and I get rich rich,
I'll let you wash my car.
I'll let him be my driver.
Wooo!
That was it, you gonna sleep for a week.
Greatest of all time,
baby, greatest of all time.
You are avoiding me, Gus.
This guy...
Just like that?
Just appear out of nowhere?
Reminds me of my ex, huh?
Now I'm gonna tell you like I told her,
how you find me, bitch?
I'll catch up to you in a little bit, man.
We good.
Wassup?
As we agreed
you will pick up the
vehicle at the airport.
The airport?
The whole place is on lock.
You don't watch the news, white boy?
You will enter through a service staircase
get the vehicle.
When you get to a barricade
you will be let through.
It's all arranged.
It's all arranged?
Calm down, double oh seven.
I never let you down before.
This is different.
I need to make sure
you follow my instructions precisely.
Your brother's criminal record
and your mother's immigration status.
If this is a threat
you just made a mistake, puto.
It is not a threat. It is more a reward.
The rest of your fee is in the glove box.
Destination is pre-programmed
on the GPS in the vehicle.
I get picked up driving a
stolen van, that's it, bro.
They gonna send me back to the bull pen.
I can't go back.
Can't do it, man.
It is not stolen.
You will be let through
and at the end of it
your mother's immigration
status will be fixed.
Your brother's criminal record erased.
I do this for you, that's it, I'm done.
Lose my number and my address.
I'm trying to do the right
thing by my mother now.
'Cause if anything happens to her
I mean, anything...
I'll kill your waxy ass.
Three rules...
you will not examine the cargo.
You will not make any stops.
And you will cross the bridge
back into Manhattan before daybreak.
Do you understand?
In English then, the three rules.
Screw you.
Suck my dick.
I'll get it done.
_
urgent chatter)
My
daughter was on that flight!
Bolivar! Bolivar! Bolivar!
Sir, this area of the airport is closed.
You have to wait back
there with everybody else.
Hey, settle down, will ya!
Bolivar! Bolivar! Bolivar!
Hey, sir! Sir!
Sir!
It's alright, sorry,
just go get a wheelchair.
He's a medical.
You all right?
Sir, what do you have here?
You have... Coumadin.
You got a heart condition?
Are you all right?
Are you in charge?
What?
I need to talk to someone about that plane.
I recognize some of these
names in First Class.
That never helps.
Look, Eph, just introduce yourself
and tell them we're on it.
You'll do great.
Go on.
When you said no press,
I almost believed you.
I'm Ephraim Goodweather.
I'm the Chief Medical Officer
for the Centers for Disease
Control here in New York.
I have been asked to introduce myself
and to give you a preliminary update on...
How many survivors?
Please...
Please, please, please...
I think I'm supposed to stand
here and somehow reassure you.
I can't do that.
Two hundred and six passengers
on Regis Air flight 753 are dead.
And we don't know why.
Four passengers survived,
and we don't know why.
What I can tell you
having been the first to board the plane
is that they all appeared
to have died peacefully
without distress.
That's the only comfort I
can give you at this time.
You want answers
real answers to what happened
on that plane and so do I.
And I won't quite until
we're all satisfied.
I don't care about your promises!
I want my daughter back!
All you do is talk and
talk! That's all you do!
This is my daughter.
My daughter, Emma!
And I want to see her again, dead, alive.
I'm her father!
Don't you have children of your own?
Don't you have a heart?
Forty-eight hours, I'll get your answers.
It's the best I can do.
No!
Jesus! Goodweather, what
are you doing to me here?
Just tell me what you have.
I'm just getting into it now.
I haven't finished cutting all of them yet.
Just give me anything you can.
Okay, top of the charts...
is here.
Can you see this here?
Yeah, what is that?
It's an incision.
Deep enough to puncture one
wall of the carotid artery
without rupturing it.
Razor sharp, clean cut,
no bruising, no trauma.
There's no instrument that can do that.
Not that I'm aware of, anyway,
not with this precision.
Anything else?
Gets way more interesting.
A spot check of six other
corpses revealed the same thing.
The exact same wound,
in the exact same place.
Are you telling me
that the other passengers
have the same incision?
Or puncture.
Yes, all the ones I've looked at so far.
There is one more intriguing abnormality.
I don't... what
the hell am I looking at?
On our screen that looks white.
Because it is white and opalescent.
Blood proteins are separating.
No, in fact, there's a
complete absence of hypostasis.
No blood pooling anywhere.
And an absolute absence of erythrocytes.
I'll know more once I cut into
the liver and kidneys but...
I'm sorry to do this to you
but you're gonna have to
do the preliminary alone.
I don't want any of this
leaking to the press.
Okay, buddy, but you'll owe me.
For the rest of my life.
Shit.
Eph! I'm sorry but I think
you're gonna want to talk to this man.
Dr. Goodweather, my name
is Abraham Setrakian.
It's very nice to meet you.
I can't talk right now.
Eph, he says he has some
insight into the outbreak here.
Great.
Mr. Kent, here, can take
down your information...
Time is of the essence, Doctor.
It certainly is. Jim...
Eph...
You have to listen to me.
I have seen this disease before.
I have faced it before.
You... you must contain it.
You've seen it before?
I assure you we're taking
every available precaution.
You're not. You can't.
And he is counting on that.
"He?"
It is too much to say all at once here
without sounding crazy.
No, of course not.
Uh, Jim, we're going to the cargo hold
please take care of this gentleman for me.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Just come with me.
The bodies!
They're not decomposing normally, yes?!
The tissues are still pliable.
How do you know that?
-Nora, Nora...
Listen to me now.
What I am about to say
I do not say lightly.
All the passengers on that plane
dead and alive...
they must be destroyed.
Destroyed? Okay.
Here you go, fellas.
Feel better.
The heads must be severed!
The bodies burned, destroyed!
Doctor, did you find the coffin?
If you have the coffin
then you still have him!
It is not too late!
Destroy the coffin!
Do not allow it across the river!
_
As advised by Doctor Goodweather
I will examine the doby under UV light.
How did that old
man know about the coffin?
You mean the cabinet?
He called it a coffin.
I know what he called it.
He also told us to destroy 206 bodies.
And he had a sword.
Nora.
What?
What the hell is that?
Looks like a horsehair worm
or a Dirofilaria immitis.
Body is simple. It's just collagen.
Degenerate non-functional
digestive system.
Look at that.
It's beautiful.
It's looking for a host, it's desperate.
So it's not airborne.
That's the carrier.
Eph, look.
Soil.
Hey!
Where's that cabinet?
What cabinet?
There, right there.
Rewind.
Can you go slower, frame by frame?
There must be a gap or a cut.
No, there's not cut.
Watch the time code.
Two seconds. Go back.
Start there.
Wait, wait.
There.
What's that distortion?
I don't know.
It grabs the box and lifts it off...
up...
That box was 500 pounds.
Nothing could lift it up like that.
The old man said, "If you have
the coffin, you still have him."
Him.
This footage is only seven minutes old.
The box is still in the airport.
_
Uh huh.
What the hell is that?
Crazy ass white boy.
Come on, come on, pick up.
Jim, where are you right now?
At the main garage door
funnelling traffic out.
Stop it, stop it! Stop everyone.
This is an emergency.
You need to seal off the
perimeter of the airport.
That box...
Remember the box with the markings on it?
Yeah, yeah, the Berlin cargo omit.
That's the one.
Now listen carefully, Jim.
We need to stop all vehicles
big enough to hold it.
No vans, no trucks, nothing.
No big vehicles. No exceptions.
Okay, no big vehicles in or out
of the security zone. Got it.
Right, everybody listen up.
I want none of these trucks
big-sized vehicles released
without my authorization.
C'mon...
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Pull up there, sir, I'll be right with you.
Shit! Shit, shit!
ID and permit.
Oh, yeah, man.
Crazy what's happening, huh?
What do you want me to do with this?
Step out of the vehicle,
open the cargo area, sir.
Step out of the vehicle...
Get the light out of my face!
-Step out of the vehicle.
Can I get my seatbelt?
Hey. What's going on here?
I asked for ID, he gave me this.
Oh, well, this is one of our vehicles.
You can let him through.
-Sir?
I said, let him through.
You tell those sons of bitches I'm done.
I came through for them but now I am done.
You got it?
Okay, go.
I have now removed the
chest plate of one of the subjects
and found...
abnormal neoplasms in the heart, liver...
and kidneys.
The growths do not seem
like oncological aberrations
but almost like new,
fully functional organs.
What?!
No!
Ah!
Agh!
Sorry, Eph. Nothing.
You got anything here?
Just trying to figure out
how a 500-pound, 9-foot tall
coffin got up and walked away.
You called it a coffin.
We'll get a break.
We always do.
We just gotta find some place to start.
This is where we start.
What the hell are those?
Something new.
S-E-T-R-A-K-I-A-N?
Setrakian?
What is... what is that?
Armenian.
Is that where you're from?
At one time...
How soon may I leave?
Well, nothing happens 'til Monday.
The charges are filed then.
It's almost dawn now.
_
Are you the librarian?
Oh...
That's some ancient ink
you got there, old man.
What is it, numbers?
Yeah, numbers.
Mean anything?
Only to me.
Everything went as planned.
Love is going
to guide them all back
to their homes, to their loved ones.
Curious detail...
an old man with a sword
was arrested at the airport.
The Jew.
He's still at it.
After all these years.
You must admire him for that.
I'll take care of him.
I look out upon this island
and I savour what is to come...
purity.
Mr. Fitzwilliam...
a sentimental man
would venture out into the city tonight
to walk these streets one last time...
before the fall.
Do you require anything else, sir?
No.
For the first time in my life
I have everything I need.
Hello?
_
Huh? No, mommy, no.
I'm not smoking. You kidding me or what?
I'm working.
Just called to check in
to see what you're up to.
Is Crispin home?
He is.
_
Mama, one beer left.
Why do you do this to me?
How many times do I gotta tell you?
I'm making his breakfast.
I'm getting on the bridge now.
I'll be home in an hour.
_
I don't know what you are but
you're bringing me good luck.
Love, you see, is the
one force that cannot be explained
cannot be broken down
into a chemical process.
It is the beacon that guides us back home
when no one is there
and the light that illuminates our loss.
Its absence robs us of all pleasure
of our capacity for joy.
It makes our nights darker
and our days gloomier.
But when we find love
no matter how wrong,
how sad or how terrible
we cling to it.
It gives us our strength.
It holds us upright.
It feeds on us and we feed on it.
_
Emma... Emma...
Emma...
Oh, baby...
_
Love is our grace.
Love is our downfall.
Sync and corrected by caioalbanezi
www.addic7ed.com
Watch free HD Movies and TV Shows at
StreamingSites.com