-= www.OpenSubtitles.org =-
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(lock rattling)
(jackhammer pounding
in the distance)
(siren wailing in the distance)
(door squeaks)
(engine turning over)
Automated Voice: Turn right.
You will reach
your destination in four days.
(turn signal clicking)
(sighs)
(indistinct chatter)
(whirring swells)
(car horns honking)
Sorry.
(uneasy string music playing)
(music swells)
Radio Presenter: The next storm
is already developing...
(continues indistinctly)
(Man on radio
speaking indistinctly)
(music stops)
(wind whistling)
Radio Presenter:
The lucky winners
of this past weekend's
Super Lottery draw.
(continues indistinctly)
Male Voice Through Phone:
...hungry to know the meaning
and origin
of every new word she heard.
Fascinated by old buildings
and dying towns,
her wit was...
...as there were
necessary obstacles
to her ideal life of animals,
and plants, and perhaps...
...not been an easy journey,
not since she was 12
and had fled
from her adoptive parents.
She would turn 42
that autumn...
...a whole lifetime to explore.
Sometimes the details didn't
seem to jive, of course.
Sometimes names
were changed,
chronologies
were inconsistent.
As a freelance
graphic designer...
(engine revving)
(truck horn honking)
Move!
Shit.
(screams)
(panting)
Holy fuck.
What the fuck?
(engine revving)
(audiobook continues playing)
(car horn honking)
(eerie music playing)
What the fuck?
(audiobook continues playing)
(sighs)
- (exhales deeply)
- ...Fiona flings her body
against the horizontal
metal bar...
(gas pump beeping)
- Man: Hi, sweetheart.
- Hi.
Why don't you call the home
number and speak to Mom?
(sighs)
Because I wanted to talk
to you and not Mom.
Oh, um...
well, any... any progress
with the bank?
Yeah.
Hey, look,
signal's kind of bad.
Are you at home?
Actually, I... I left already.
I just wanted you to know.
What? When?
This morning.
Oh, we were supposed to come
over and help you tomorrow.
I know, I know.
I just wanted to avoid Mom
and the ensuing drama.
She's just worried about you.
- (sighs)
- So am I.
I know. I'll be fine.
We just wanted to make...
Oh, never mind.
So how far are you?
I'm sorry.
What'd you say, Dad?
I... How far are you?
About 300 miles
from the house.
Boy, you must have been
moving along, yeah?
Yeah, I... I guess.
(eerie tones)
(tires squeal)
Oh, I... I just wanted
to let you know.
Okay.
Well, thanks for calling.
Maybe we can come
and visit you
when you've settled in a bit?
Of course, and...
say hi to Mom for me.
(insects chirping)
(cell phone buzzing)
(sobs)
(sniffles)
(car engine revving)
(cell phone alarm ringing)
(sighs)
- (gasps, panting)
- (whispering) Sorry.
- S... scared you?
- Yeah.
(clears throat)
It's okay, no worries.
- Sure?
- Yeah.
(stammers)
Uh, do you recognize me?
No, not really.
I'm driving that.
Right.
Yeah, I... I just wanted
to apologize for yesterday.
I was texting.
I didn't see you trying to pass.
Well, it was a close call.
Nah, I put my phone down, and...
realized I was in a hurry,
and so I had to repass you.
It was just one
of those days, you know?
It's okay.
What's done is done.
But I scared you
a little bit.
I... Look, I gotta go, sorry.
- Do you live, uh, nearby?
- Uh, no, no, not really.
Where are you, um...
where are you going?
- I'm headed north.
- I'm always in the area, so...
Do you...
uh, do you have a name?
- Jessica.
I apologize again,
and...
I'll see you around.
Yeah, yeah, it was...
it was nice meeting you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I hope you have a good trip.
(taps car)
Thanks.
(Man whistling)
(keys jingle)
(engine turning over)
(solemn music playing)
(cell phone ringing)
(exhales deeply)
Do you mind to open up?
(gear shifter clacks)
Hey, there.
Hey, what's... what's going on?
No idea.
The engine just died on me.
It's a piece of shit.
What can I say?
Yeah, that's... that's too bad.
Yeah, I know.
Tell me about it.
You want me to call you a...
a tow truck?
No, if... if you could just
give me a ride
to the next town,
I can go to a gas station.
But first, I need some help
to get the car out of the road.
Look, I'm...
I'm just in a bit of a hurry.
Yeah, I mean, me too.
I... it'll just take a minute.
I'll push.
You can steer.
Come on.
I can check the GPS.
- Excuse me?
- I can search on GPS.
Why?
I'll... I'll find
the next gas station.
- I... I'll just give them a call.
- I know where it is.
It's just up the road
about 15 minutes.
Well, then I'll just go
up there,
and I'll tell them
to come back and get you.
Well, I do need help getting
the car out of the road first.
It's a bit hard with this thing.
I'm sorry, I've got to go...
It's just gonna take a minute.
I've got to go.
I'm late for a meeting.
- I'm sorry.
- I just need a...
(breathes deeply)
Male Voice Reading Audiobook:
One night, when her eyes
looked about the neighborhood
of the Palais-Royal
doubtful to what amusement we
should next partake ourselves
my friend proposed a visit
to Visconti,
- but his suggestion was not...
- (sniffles)
...I knew Visconti,
and what I'm saying is...
(sniffles)
(ringing tone)
- (exhales deeply)
- Hello?
Jess?
Hi.
Sweetie, why'd you leave
without telling us?
I don't understand.
Well, I woke up early,
and I thought I might
as well get going.
Sweetie, I... I tried you
a few times,
and I wasn't able
to get through.
(clicks tongue)
I'm busy.
So...
(sighs)
Are... are you there yet?
No...
I'd say sometime tomorrow.
Are you smoking again?
Nope.
(Mom scoffs)
(Mom sighs deeply)
So, um...
Jess, have you called
the therapist yet?
Like I said, I've been busy.
I just don't understand
why you're leaving right now.
After all that's happened,
wouldn't it be better...
Mom, we've been through this.
(Mom sighs)
Why don't you want
to talk about it?
Because I don't need to.
I'm fine.
- (door slams)
- Really?
Jess, come on.
- Sweetie.
- Really.
- Well...
- (truck door opens)
...we just think it's
a really bad idea.
You have friends and family
who will support you
down here, sweetheart...
- Well, I'm going anyway.
- (truck door closes)
(Mom sighs)
I just think
you should've stayed home
until you felt
a little bit better.
It's been six months...
it's time to move on.
Okay, but promise me
you'll talk to someone
when you get there.
(eerie tone)
I got to go.
Promise me. Please, Jess,
you need to promise me...
Mom, um, I got to go.
I... I'll talk
to you later, okay?
Okay, but call me
when you get there.
Okay, bye.
(truck engine revving)
(shallow breathing)
(keys jingling)
- (Man whistling)
- (engine sputters, turns over)
Hey, I just...
(whispers) All right.
(shallow breathing)
- Fuck!
- (tires screeching)
- (horn honks)
- Come on!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
(horn honking)
- (pounds on window)
- Hey!
I was just trying
to go to the bathroom,
and you almost hit me.
- What the hell's your problem?
- (gear shifter clacks)
- Hello? Hey!
- (tires squealing)
(shallow breathing)
(phone keyboard beeps)
Pick up, pick up.
(ringing tone)
Phone Operator:
911, what's your emergency?
Hi, my name is
Jessica Swanson.
I think I'm being followed.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Can you repeat that?
We seem to have
a bad connection.
My name is Jessica Swanson.
I'm being followed.
- Who's following you?
- I... I don't know.
There's this guy, I've seen him
a couple of times.
I don't know what he wants.
He's right behind me!
What is your location, ma'am?
I'm in my car!
Can you hear me?
Ma'am, please,
tell me your location.
Fuck, I don't know!
(car engine revving)
I can't, I don't know!
(car engine roaring)
Phone Operator: Ma'am?
(whispering) Oh, shit.
(panting)
I'm sorry, that's...
- That was a false alarm.
- It wasn't him?
No.
I'll tell you what.
I'll connect you
to one of the officers,
and you can tell him a bit
more about your situation.
(whispering) Okay.
(wheels rattling and squealing)
What the fuck is...
(eerie music playing)
(grunts)
(shallow breathing)
Shit!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
(panting)
Fuck.
(crickets chirping)
(grunting)
(suspenseful music playing)
(panting)
(grunting)
Come on, come on.
(screaming)
(whimpering)
Man: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
(Jess whimpering)
- Man: Oh, no, no, stop.
- (Jess grunting)
Jess: Get the fuck off me!
Get off me!
No! Ah, fuck!
- Man: Come here.
- (Jess grunts)
- (tense music playing)
- (Man groans)
(metal slides)
(heartbeat thudding)
(groans)
(shallow breathing)
(birds tweeting)
(doorknob rattling)
(footsteps thudding overhead)
(door opens, closes)
(screams) Hey!
(knocks on window)
Let me out!
Help!
Help me!
Let me the fuck out of here!
Let me out, please, please.
Please, I'm begging you.
Please. Please!
(knocking on window)
(panting)
(floorboards creaking)
(footsteps thudding overhead)
(Man whistling)
(footsteps down stairs)
(lock rattles)
(continues whistling)
(Jess whimpering)
(footsteps approaching)
(whispering)
What do you want from me?
What do you want?
Is it money?
I can... I can get you money, I...
Just tell me how much.
I can pay you.
I promise.
Just tell me how much.
(Jess breathing shakily)
Jess: You can let me go.
I won't tell anybody.
I... I promise.
Jess: (whispering) I promise.
Do you think you're
the first one to say that?
Take your clothes off.
Go on.
You want some help?
I just...
need to use the bathroom first.
Go right ahead.
- (thud)
- (Jess grunts)
(Jess grunts)
(key turning in lock)
(footsteps)
(Jess screams)
(Jess groaning)
(Jess whimpering)
(Man shushing)
Man: (whispering) It's okay.
There you go.
(normal voice)
I didn't even have time
to cut all the way through
at the rest stop.
Jess: Please just let me go.
Man: (whispering)
Almost gave up.
Jess: Please. (sniffles)
Man: (normal voice)
Let's see what we have here.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen,
I am finally learning
how to do this trick.
This is the only reason
- I married this man...
- Yeah.
Because he impressed me
with this trick.
- Yeah, the only reason.
- (laughs) The only reason.
All right, can you take this?
(laughs)
Husband: Pick a card.
Jess: Um...
Don't look, don't look.
(sniffles)
- Jess: Okay.
- Husband: Okay.
Jess: Ooh-hoo.
What was that move?
- Jess: What was that move?
- Husband: You just saw.
(Jess laughing in video)
- Jess: I'm watching you. I know.
- Husband: Uh...
- Jess: I know what's happening.
- Husband: Abracadabra!
You're cute together.
(Jess and husband
laughing on video)
- Jess: Where's my card?
- Husband: Oh, shit.
- Husband: Where is your card?
- Jess: Where's my card?
My card's supposed to be
in the middle.
Wait, did I mess it?
Wait, no, there's your card.
- (Husband laughing)
- Jess: What!
You think he's worried
about you?
(laughter on video)
Husband: I fucked it up.
(chuckles)
Man: Hey...
I asked you a question.
(Jess whimpering)
(Jess sniffles)
(necklace jingling)
(both grunt)
(uneasy music playing)
He left you.
- Man: Huh?
- He died.
How?
How did he die?
He... (sobs)
He killed himself.
(whimpering)
Man: In what way?
Jess: (stammers) A gun.
Man: And you found him?
(sobbing)
Man: That's tough.
- Man: That's tough.
- (Jess sniffles)
(Jess sobbing)
Man: (tuts)
Aw, it's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
(Jess sniffles, cries)
- (footsteps receding)
- (keys jingle)
(door unlocks, opens)
(door slams, lock clicks)
(shallow breathing)
(quietly whimpers)
(car engine rumbling)
(doorknob rattling)
(grunts) Come on!
(whispers) Ah, shit.
(grunts softly)
Come on.
(grunting)
(car engine revving)
(groans)
(laundry machine whirring)
(dramatic musical sting)
(car door closes)
(sighs)
(thump)
(shallow breathing)
(gulps)
(cell phone ringing)
(Man grunts)
Hey.
No, no, I'm not
doing much right now.
Just at the hotel.
About to go get some lunch here
in a little bit.
Oh, gosh.
It is...
absolutely beautiful here.
It's... it's so gorgeous.
Looks out over the water.
Mm-hmm.
You and I should come here
some time.
Yeah.
Nah, the deal's just taking
longer than... than I expected.
Um, I don't know.
It looks like
it may be Wednesday.
It just depends on when they
can make their mind up, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
No, we're just down
to some little detail on it.
I think it's gonna be fine.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
(clicks tongue)
And how's Mina?
Yeah.
Yeah, just...
I guess just make sure
she doesn't have any more milk
until we know for sure.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let me talk to her.
(chuckles)
Hey, little bug.
Aw, I miss you, too,
sweetheart.
Yeah, how's the stomach?
Yeah, Mom told me,
but you are gonna be
just fine real soon.
I promise.
Uh-huh.
I think that I'm gonna see you
in a couple of days,
but you're probably gonna be
asleep when I get home.
I love you, too.
All right, bye.
And let me talk to Mom first.
Bye.
(chuckles)
Yeah.
No, I know.
All right, let me, uh, let me
give you a call tomorrow,
and I'll let you know
how it's looking.
Okay.
Love you, babe.
All right, bye.
(clears throat)
(chair scrapes on floor)
(Man whistling)
(shallow breathing)
(eerie tones)
(suspenseful music playing)
(Jess panting)
(panting)
(grunts)
Jess: Help me!
Oh, God.
(screams)
(whimpering)
(grunts)
(Jess screams)
(Jess grunts)
(water rushing)
(gasping, grunting)
(hopeful music playing)
(groans)
(eerie creaking)
(flies buzzing)
(grunts)
(grunting)
(grunting in pain)
Mm.
(grunting)
(rustling)
(shallow breathing)
(groans)
(leaves crunching)
(eerie tone swells)
(shouts)
- Jess: No!
- Hunter: Back off!
Hunter:
Get down on your knees.
Jess: Please. I'm sorry.
You have to help me.
(sobbing) Please, I need you
to help me right now.
Fuck! What the hell is going on?
We have to get out of here.
- Let's go...
- You stay right where you are.
No, someone is trying
to kill me.
- What?
- He's crazy.
He's completely fucking crazy.
Please, do you have a phone?
Anything, please?
- (sighs)
- Anything?
Hang on.
Oh, shit.
I got to get out of here.
Please get me out of here.
What'd you do to your foot?
I stepped on a root.
I have some...
extra boots in the car.
Back that way.
Don't try anything with that.
I won't.
Hunter: Now come on.
Jess: Okay.
(dramatic music playing)
(car beeping)
(Hunter clears throat)
(Hunter grunts)
These are my wife's.
They're probably too big,
but better that than too small.
- Right?
- Thank you.
(car beeping)
Well, let's get out of here.
(car door closes)
(car door opens)
(engine revving, door closes)
(eerie creaking)
You okay?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
When was the last time
you had anything to eat?
I don't remember.
There's some sandwiches
in the backpack.
You can help yourself.
Goat cheese and honey,
if that's all right.
My wife makes
a killer sandwich.
(Jess grunts in satisfaction)
There should be some water
in there.
(Jess clears throat)
You think he's still out there?
Jess: Maybe.
I think he's long gone.
He's probably somewhere
(chuckles)
trying to think up an alibi.
Oh, God.
What's this?
No, no, no!
- Jessica, Jessica, calm down!
- No, this is him!
- (car door closes)
- No, no, no.
Jess: You have to help me.
Jessica, you're never
gonna be able to move that.
Jess: Come on. Come on.
One, two, three.
(both groan)
Oh, come on.
This is not gonna go anywhere.
Jess: Push! (grunts)
Ah, fuck.
Is there any other way
out of here?
How do I know?
(car engine revving)
That's him.
Hunter: No, no!
You let me handle this.
- He will kill me.
- Hunter: I'll handle this.
You get back over there.
Back up against the tree.
No, no.
Thank God, no.
Man: No, she's...
she's standing here.
Okay, yeah.
No, she's with somebody.
Okay, thank you so much,
and I'm so sorry that we had
to bother you with this again.
Okay, I will.
All right, bye.
Jess, for God's sake.
- Get the fuck away from me!
- Man: Jess, please.
Hunter: Look, what is...
what is going on here?
Sir, you're gonna have
to excuse my sister.
She's not feeling well.
I am not your sister,
you fucking psycho!
I found her
about a half hour ago.
- She says you kidnapped her.
- Man: Oh, God, no.
She had one of her episodes,
and before I knew it,
she was out of the house, and
she had jumped in the river.
Don't you believe him.
- Look, all right, um...
- Jess, that's enough.
Obviously, we...
we have a situation here.
Man: Oh, God.
W... what else did she say?
She said you locked her
in a basement?
Jesus.
Jess...
Listen.
We've had a...
a tragedy
in our family recently,
and her...
her husband killed himself.
Shut up, you sick fuck.
Man: Now she's developed
these triggers,
and one second, she's fine, and
then the next, she goes off.
- (thunder rumbles)
- Is she seeing a doctor?
E... every Tuesday.
He's lying.
He's fucking lying.
Listen, I just got off
the phone with the police
and called off the search.
This is not the first time
that this has happened...
- He's crazy.
- Get back.
Get back.
Over there.
Man: I'm sorry, sir.
W... what's your name?
Robert.
I can't begin to thank you
for what you've done.
Jess: Now that he's seen you,
he's never gonna let you
out of here alive, never.
Jessica, that is
enough for today.
Come on.
If you could just help me
get her in the car first.
- No, no! No!
- (Man shushing)
Jess: No! Help me!
It's gonna be okay, sweetheart.
- Jess: Help me!
- Man: You're okay.
- (Jess grunting)
- Man: Can you give me a hand?
- Ask for his phone!
- Robert: What?
- Stop.
- Ask for his fucking phone!
- Man: Let me just...
- Jess: No!
Ask for his phone
and call the police!
- (Man shushing)
- Jess: No, no!
- Excuse me.
- Man: What?
Can I borrow
your phone, please?
- (Jess grunts)
- Man: Fuck! Ouch!
Robert: You stop!
- Could you grab her, please?
- Robert: No, she's right.
I need to call the police
and make sure
everything checks out.
It's... it's gonna make me
feel a lot better.
Okay, but could you
please just help me
get her in the car first?
Phone.
- You want to see my phone?
- Robert: Yes.
Sure, if that's gonna
make you feel better.
Here you go.
- Watch out!
- (thunderclap)
- (Men grunting)
- Stop!
(gunshot)
(thunder echoing)
(solemn music playing)
(Jess panting)
(thunder rumbling)
(rain falling heavily)
(dramatic musical sting)
(shivering)
(panting)
(suspenseful music playing)
(Man whistling)
(thunderclap)
(gunshot)
(Jess groaning)
(thunderclap)
(Jess grunting)
(thunder rumbles)
(Jess gasps)
(thunderclap)
Man: I know you're close.
I know I hit you.
I give you about two hours...
before you bleed to death.
Soon the cramps will set in...
spreading through your body...
and then the rot will start.
Why don't you come out
and fight while you still can?
Yeah, I'll play fair.
It's loaded.
You have one minute...
to try and grab it...
starting...
now.
Are you too scared?
You know the one thing
I can't stand?
Cowards!
Just like that husband
of yours.
Why did he kill himself anyway?
Was he too weak?
You know...
people who are thinking
about killing themselves...
They usually cry out for help.
They send these subtle signals
to their family and friends.
That must just really
tear you apart.
Knowing...
that he...
probably tried to tell you.
That guilt must be
something else.
He was supposed to be
the father of your children,
and now...
he's rotting
in some grave somewhere.
(slowly exhales)
All that sorrow...
all that guilt...
would drive me nuts
if I were you.
Completely fucking nuts.
He was a coward.
I know fear when I see it.
It's all in the eyes!
It's all in the fucking eyes!
(light rustling)
Man:
People think they can hide it,
but they can't!
Not from me!
(thunderclap)
Man: Prove to me that I'm wrong!
Show me some fucking guts!
Show me you're just
a little bit better
than that shitbag husband
of yours!
Do you hear me?
Do you fucking hear me?
I'm gonna get you,
you delicious fucking bitch!
(thunder rumbling softly)
I'm coming for you.
I am coming for you.
(footsteps departing)
(rain pouring)
(Jess whimpering)
(exhales deeply)
(animals chirping)
(gasps)
(gentle music playing)
(groaning)
(eerie creaking)
(car engine revving)
(music stops)
(brakes squeak)
(car door opens)
(grunts)
(Man grunting)
Come on.
(dramatic musical sting)
(grunting)
(door softly closes)
(rummaging)
(panting)
(faint creak)
(engine starting)
(ringing tone)
Phone Operator:
911, what's your emergency?
Jess: (whispering) Help me.
Hello?
Jess: Help me.
You need to speak up.
Jess: There's a man in glasses.
I've been kidnapped.
I'm sorry.
Can you repeat that?
Jess: He's going to kill me.
He's gonna kill me.
- Who's trying to...
- Jess: Just trace this call.
Hello? I can't hear you.
Trace this call.
(brakes squeal)
(dramatic musical sting)
- (Jess screams)
- (Man grunts)
(Man grunting)
Man: Bitch!
(both scream)
(Jess grunts)
(wheels skidding)
(both grunting)
(dramatic musical sting)
(Man screams in pain)
(softly grunting)
(panting)
(whimpers)
(eerie creaking)
(helicopter propellers
whirring)
- (heartbeat pumping rapidly)
- Hey.
(grunts)
(eerie music playing)
(grunting)
(grunting in pain)
(grunts)
(panting)
(shallow breathing)
(ringing tone)
- Girl: Hi, Daddy.
- Can I talk to your mom?
Who is this?
Please let me talk
to your mom.
Mom, someone wants
to talk to you.
This is Catherine Dillon.
Jess: This is
your husband's phone, right?
- Catherine: I'm sorry?
- Right?
Yeah, but who are you?
Do you know
where he is right now?
I don't know
what you're talking about...
I asked you
a fucking question.
Do you know
where he is right now?
My husband is in California
on a business trip...
- Jess: No, he's not.
- I'm...
He's a kidnapper...
and a murderer.
Is this some kind of joke?
If it is...
No, it's not a fucking joke!
- Sam, are you there?
- You want to talk to him?
Here, hold on a second.
I'll put him on.
You have a phone call.
Sam, are you there?
Sam...
what the hell is going on?
Sam?
Talk to me.
My name is Jessica Swanson...
and if this is the last time
you hear from me,
it's because your husband
killed me,
just like he killed a man
named Robert.
People are probably looking
for him, too.
Sam!
Go on. Go on!
Talk to your wife!
Sam, are you there?
What the fuck are you doing?
I just need
to take care of something.
Are you there? Sam!
Sam, are you there?
Sam!
Bye.
(bird cawing)
(suspenseful music playing)
(Sam grunts)
(Jess screaming)
(spits)
(groaning)
(heartbeat pumping)
(heartbeat pumping rapidly)
(gentle music playing)
(helicopter propellers whirring)
(dramatic musical sting)
(eerie creaking)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
- (birds chirping)
- (eerie creaking continues)
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN