-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
Go away.
What should we do?
Begin the next game.
Sir, let me help.
Thanks so much.
You look great, sir.
Attention.
The fourth game is about to begin.
Please follow the staff's instructions
and swiftly make your way
towards the game hall.
Let me repeat the instructions.
The fourth game is about to begin.
Please follow the staff's instructions
and swiftly make your way
towards the game hall.
Players,
what you witness before you
is what remains of those who broke
the rules for their own benefit.
They tainted the pure and fair ideology
everything here has been built upon.
Each and every one of you
is considered an equal
within the walls of this facility.
You must be guaranteed
the same opportunities
without being disadvantaged
or facing any kind of discrimination.
We truly apologize for allowing
such an unacceptable incident to occur.
EPISODE 6
GGANBU
ROUND 6
LIST OF WINNERS
NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT
Front Man speaking.
Yes. A minor disturbance took place.
But it's being addressed.
No need to worry.
We'll make sure
there's no trace of the disturbance
by the time the VIPs arrive.
Yes, sir. The game will begin on time,
in line with the schedule.
What's wrong? Are you sad?
Why? Is your connection dead?
I'll kill that little slut.
Players,
welcome to the fourth game.
For this game, you will be playing
in teams of two.
Please look around and find someone
you wish to play with.
When two people agree to play together,
shake hands to show
you have become partners.
Let me repeat the instructions.
For this game, you will be playing
in teams of two.
Please look around and find someone
you wish to play with.
When two people agree to play together,
shake hands to show
you have become partners.
There can only be two players per team.
You will have ten minutes
to find your partner.
Hey, handsome.
Let's do this, huh?
I'm better than you think.
And I'm stronger than most guys too.
Guess what? I know how to con
just about anybody I see.
I'm not a genius,
but I still got it work out. Huh?
Hey, let me play with you.
Then I'll be your dream girl
all night long.
I'll do anything you tell me.
I'm not a regular girl.
Hmm?
You're pretending that you do not want me
on your team. Is that it?
Why? Can't decide?
Want me to choose instead, huh?
Stop embarrassing yourself.
No one will want to play
with you like this.
And you should all be honest.
You don't want a girl to team up with
or an old guy.
Of course we don't. We could die.
We already almost die
in the previous round.
This man is right.
And it was Adam's rib the Lord used
to make Eve after all.
And that's the reason
that we're choosing men.
- They played different roles than women.
- You idiot.
We're not playing in Eden right now.
Uh, hold on a second.
Why? You want a girl?
You're all idiots.
You two, you're making a big mistake,
and you're going to regret it.
- Sang-woo, let's...
- Ali, let's join forces.
Most of these games here,
you need to be strong or smart to win.
And I think if we're a team, we'll...
we'll beat a lot of the others out there.
Uh, uh, no, no, no, no, no.
Uh, it's okay, really, it's...
Uh, you two will make
a great team together.
I'll find someone to play with.
Let's make this work.
Sir...
Sorry, but, um...
You know it's just, um...
- Uh...
- You should go put this on.
Just in case people here...
Well, they might look down on you
for missing it.
You and me...
We'll be the best team.
Hey.
Wanna do this?
Why should I?
I can't picture you going around here
and begging these jerks.
Hmm? Embarrassing.
What matters is winning.
Embarrassing or not.
Then play with me.
I'll make sure that you win.
What will you do?
Whatever it takes.
What do you see in me?
Well, I wanted to ask you that.
You were someone who looked like
they would come with me.
That's how I feel.
I promise, okay?
There's no option left here.
I teach Math at a high school.
And I can run too. Soccer every day.
Everyone was asking,
but I held out so you and I could win.
'Cause you and me would be great together.
The... the thing is...
...we don't know which game
we're playing, so...
Hey, choose me so it can just be done.
At this rate, nobody will be left for you,
and you won't continue.
You know,
since the man who'd been cheating
is gone, there's an uneven number.
Once everyone is in pairs,
there'll be one person.
And what happens to that one?
What do you think?
They'll be out and they'll get killed.
I would guess that old man there.
Stop dragging this out.
Let's play together.
Hey, old man.
Wanna do this together?
The time for finding
a partner is now over.
You guys,
you're all making a big mistake.
Do you really think you can win
without me on your team?
It's me, Han Mi-nyeo!
I've made suckers out of everyone there is
from Dongducheon to Gangnam!
Guys...
What if you have to play Gonggi
or Elastics?
I'm an expert in those.
Babe, please, play with me.
Boys aren't very good at those.
- Hey. Get off.
- Come back!
- Hey, come on, be my partner.
- Oh.
Let's show everyone with a dick
they're wrong!
- Let her go.
- After us, we need to stick together.
- My gosh!
- I work well with women too!
- I'll be really good! I'll be...
- Stop it!
- Hey, don't trust this scumbag.
- Okay, okay.
He's a jerk. He's just gonna throw you
under the bus.
- Okay, sure.
- Look at me.
- That dead doctor and him worked together.
- Okay.
He played you.
He just wanted to save his own ass,
so he kept it secret from you all.
Tell me if I'm wrong, you jerk!
He was with him, guards!
- Hey.
- He deserves to die too!
Let... let go, bitch!
What? Hey, hold on a second.
Why is the room empty?
I still need a partner.
Hold on. Where did they go?
Who... who took my partner?
What's going on here? You can't do this!
Hey, I need a partner!
Let me go! Please!
Bring my partner here, you jerks!
Where's my partner?
I'm so sick of that whore.
It's nice to think
she won't be in my way again.
And, uh...
what she said about you in there,
you working with the doctor...
It's nothing.
That brat was so desperate,
she said whatever she could.
Attention.
All players, please follow the staff
to your designated positions for the game.
Ali.
Look at me. No one can stop us
if we work together.
I think you and I
could really win the money.
All right, let's do this and get out.
That money is ours
to give to both our families.
Let's do it.
You know, when I was a kid,
I live in a neighborhood just like this.
So did I.
And you know something?
- Our alleyway looked very similar.
- Really?
Players,
please take one bag each
from the staff member before you.
There should be a set of ten marbles
in each bag.
Please check to confirm the number.
It's marbles.
Old man, we're gonna be playing with this.
- Hmm.
- Are you familiar with it?
Ah, yes, very familiar.
Used to have a lot as a kid. Ah!
Oh, yes, back in the day.
And you know, I was pretty good.
Not too bad myself.
- Ah, that's good news.
- Yeah.
I'm glad it's not just about our strength.
That means you and I are...
gganbu now, pretty great.
Gganbu, huh?
I thought you said you played this before.
Gganbu, come on, you know.
It's a good friend.
One who you trust a lot.
You share things with them, you see?
- Ah!
- Your marbles, everything.
A gganbu. I remember now.
I had one in my town too.
Used to do everything with him.
Okay, we are gganbu.
Yes.
Should we do this to make it official?
Yeah, buddy. Like this.
- You and me, sir... Oh, no, gganbu, man.
- Yeah? Mm.
We'll go around this whole town,
and take all the marbles.
In this game,
using your set of ten marbles,
you will play the game of your choice
with your partner.
The player who manages to take
all ten marbles from their partner wins.
Let me repeat the instructions.
Using your set of ten marbles,
play the game of your choice
with your partner.
The player who manages to take
all ten marbles from their partner wins.
Oh, boy.
Shit, man.
Sang-woo.
How pretty.
Sir, excuse me.
You will have 30 minutes for this game.
Let the game begins.
Uh, sir, come back.
Let's start.
That means one of us ends up dead,
doesn't it?
So both of us should do nothing then?
So we should just die?
Or one of us dies so the other can go on.
You haven't played before, right?
Since the Korean War,
nothing has been this sad.
Tragic.
What should we play then?
Wow. You're so cold.
As cold as ice.
So you a spy from the North or what?
Hey, stop the dumbshit, girl.
What game are we gonna play?
You tell me.
These boomers know all these games.
Ten marbles,
then we can create our own game.
Hmm. I'll try to come up with one.
We must be close.
Yes, it was somewhere around here, huh.
Come on, let's play. Sir, we need to, huh?
Come, let's play this right now.
This is so strange.
It should be here. This is the alley.
Where... My house, where did it go?
Sir, come back.
So you guess if I'm holding even or odd.
Which one you think is in here.
That all makes sense to you?
Even or odd?
What's that?
Odd is like one, three, five.
And even is two, four, six.
Understand?
Just think it through.
Then you wager a few of your own.
Odd.
Open your hand.
Ah, shit.
I should have added another one.
Stop giggling, asshole.
Hey, old man,
who are you calling asshole, huh?
You really think I'm your minion
just 'cause I call you "boss" a few times?
- You wanna die, you bastard?
- You wanna show me?
Ooh! So, how are you gonna do it?
Hmm? You can't resort to violence,
you puny little idiot dog.
Sir, we have to play now.
We gotta start right now.
Play what?
With our marbles. Let's go.
Why should I?
Look around you. Everybody else is too.
We gotta do this.
No.
That game is for little children.
No. Sir, come back here.
So let's...
end the game in one round.
All or nothing. A simple bet.
Don't tell me that you would
rather do what they are?
Watch.
- Bullseye! Yes.
- Ah, damn it.
- My turn.
- Okay.
Playing what then?
Why are you in such a hurry?
You're just dying to kill me, huh?
We're just playing one round here.
And we got time left too.
Let's wait till the end.
What are we gonna do before then?
Talk.
About what, though?
Things we never told anybody about
I guess.
One of us is gonna die here, so...
doesn't matter what we tell each other.
No one can really embarrass
themselves anymore.
Okay?
Even.
What's your wager?
Two.
You're up now.
I don't want to do this with you, sir.
Can I stop?
I would like to play with someone else...
Shut up and keep playing with me. Come on.
Sir, he's not in his right mind, sir.
I think he's got dementia.
That does mean that he's out or...
He's not gonna play.
So that means he forfeited, right? Huh?
Ah, shit.
Just one little game, okay?
Here, it'll be...
It'll be so much fun, sir.
No. I'd better go home now.
I know my house is nearby.
It's somewhere down this alley.
Shit! Goddamn it!
Will you please just pull yourself
together, old man?
They'll kill us both
if we don't get started soon!
You got that thing in your head,
so I bet you don't care what happens here,
but I won't just sit here and die, okay?
Listen, I can't die!
I need to get out of here.
Don't yell at me.
All right, I will, but don't yell.
...12, 13, 14, 15. Bam, okay.
We're playing something else.
No way. I'm not gonna stop now.
We already did things how you suggested.
I should get a chance to choose.
No.
Goddamn it.
You people said we're equals.
What is this?
I think we should play
a new game here, huh?
Request accepted.
What do you wanna play then, huh?
Even.
Do it. Show me.
You asshole.
You gotta be cheating.
Uh, Sang-woo, why would I do that to you?
How are you winning like this every round?
You keep beating me. How's that?
The odds should be 50-50.
That means you're cheating!
I didn't. No!
Sir, I wouldn't do that to you.
You jerk! You pretended not to know
how this works!
You said you haven't done this before!
How did you do it, huh? Spill it!
Why did you come here from the North?
I thought things were good over here.
And so?
Were you right?
Your family, are they here with you?
Just my brother.
Your parents?
My father got shot trying to swim
across the border and drowned.
Our mother...
she was hiding in China and got sent back
once the immigration agents found her.
Where is your brother now then?
In a shelter.
Even.
Odd. Even. Odd. Even.
So did I win?
What's your wager?
Oh...
We take turns throwing marbles
till you make a shot that lands
in the hole I dug over there.
Then what happens?
What happens is that person
gets to take everything on the ground.
Ah...
You mean, you want a way
to turn this around, huh.
- What? You scared?
- Not a chance.
I'm not worried at all.
I'm pretty good
at getting things in the holes, huh.
You sure about this, hmm?
If you win the money and get out of here,
what's your plan then?
I did this to get a house
where I could be with my brother first.
Then I'll get our mother out of the North.
Hey, with a price that big,
you can do a whole lot more than that.
You gotta want something else too.
Is there anywhere you wanna go?
Jeju Island.
Jeju Island?
There was a thing about it on TV.
It looked exotic.
It didn't look like Korea at all.
Hey.
Don't you think
you should dream bigger, huh?
Do Hawaii. Hold on, go to the Maldives
for a while instead.
And have a mojito too.
Mojito?
Like the movie.
Lee Byung-hun's in it.
"Go to mojito
and have a glass of Maldives."
Really?
Oh, no, we gotta fix that then.
Well, once we're out of here,
we'll have a girls' night out
and make mojitos and everything, okay?
Oh.
We can't both get out of here.
God, I'm so sorry, Ali.
I know you won't cheat.
But I can't die this way, I beg you.
They'll kill my family
if I don't get out of here.
Sorry, Sang-woo. No.
I'm so sorry.
I have to think of my family.
Hey, Ali. Hey.
Hey, come on, if you help me,
then there's a way
that both of us could live.
You only got this far 'cause I was there.
Like when I gave the bus fare to you and...
I'm the one who got the team
through Tug-of-War,
we kept watch at night together.
And just before this begin,
you and I swore
that we leave here together, right, Ali?
Listen, Ali, please.
Trust me, help me
and I'll make sure we get out of here.
Huh?
Okay. What do we do?
What is it? It might be odd.
On the other hand, it could be even.
- That must be it.
- Come on, hurry up and go.
Odd.
Look at that. I won again.
How many are in yours?
Uh...
Oh, shit.
I, uh...
I still have one.
I still have one more.
Yeah!
Goddamn it.
Okay, here's what I think.
I think there are gonna be teams out there
who can't decide the winner either.
Mm. Why not?
Think about how you win.
Remember the rules. Thirty minutes
to determine who will win or lose.
So think about it.
Some teams aren't gonna have a winner
when time is finally up, right?
You win and you lose,
and things just keep going on like that.
That means not every team
will have a winner.
What will they do?
Eliminate all those teams?
Makes no sense.
They have to decide who won. Don't they?
Yeah.
We'll play again.
We'll be working together.
We're teammates.
So we'll just add up everything.
Our team will go play other teams
with all 20.
You and I can play as a team
just like we planned to from the start.
You and I will get out of here.
Player 414, eliminated.
Is that what you want?
You want them to do that to me?
Player 2, eliminated.
You ever have to see anyone die
before those?
Once, we have this plague
go through my town when I was a kid.
As time went on, more and more towns
got sick and died.
Soldiers started carrying the dead
into piles and lit them on fire.
That's how my grandpa, grandma
and older brother all died.
They burned together.
Damn. Your stories are
a bit too dark even for me.
And you?
What have you seen?
Player 130, eliminated.
First body I saw...
my mother's.
One day, I came back from school,
and my mom was lying there,
dead on the floor.
And next to her...
was my so-called dad with a knife.
The next body that I saw...
that was my dad's.
And the person standing there
holding the knife...
that was me.
He was a goddamn pastor too.
And when he hit her and...
did the things he did to me,
he would talk to God.
He'd always ask for forgiveness.
He didn't pray on that day
after he killed her.
I was too mad he even forgot, I guess.
Player 40, eliminated.
Even.
No, hold on. That's not what...
Wait a minute.
Just give me a second.
Odd.
Which one did you just say?
What?
Can you repeat...
what you said just now?
Even.
I said...
even.
Oh.
I lost this one.
We both can win this round? Are you sure?
Hmm.
You're positive?
Just hear me out first
and then turn me down if you like.
I mean it. Here.
Let me just give you this
to hold on to, okay?
So you won't have any guilt
around my death.
Your plan...
what is it?
Player 68, eliminated.
Well, it will depend
on who we're going against.
We need to know which teams will be here
after the round ends.
We better split up to get an idea
how all the other teams are doing
to be prepared.
Let's look for one
that seem too young or old,
and check only teams that are still
playing games at this point.
- Young or old?
- Yeah.
That's what we need.
Like someone who looks your same age
or someone who seems like
they're older than 50.
You go up a few blocks from here,
then meet up back up with me later, okay?
Okay, Sang-woo.
- Ali.
- Huh?
Your pouch there.
It's too dangerous to keep it out.
These people are bound to go crazy
before the end.
Who knows what'll happen then?
Lose it and we'll both die. You got that?
Here. I'll make sure that it's safe, okay?
What are you gonna do
if you win all that money and get out?
I don't know what I would do.
Someone was waiting
at the prison the day I got out.
I thought he was a creditor
who came to collect my dad's debt.
But he pulled out a card.
That weird card.
I had nowhere else to go, so I...
never thought about what I'd do
if I got the money.
Go with you to Jeju Island?
Sorry.
I forgot again.
Player 229, eliminated.
Oh, damn it.
Fuck.
Goddamn it.
I thought that was in. Damn it.
So you're all out?
Look at that.
One more right here.
Deok-su.
Nice knowing you.
That blue that went in,
that's mine, asshole!
Shit.
It was nice knowing you, you shithead.
Damn it!
Okay.
Oh. Oh.
You are all assholes!
Player 278, eliminated.
Done.
Here.
How's that?
It feels safer like that, doesn't it?
Yeah.
When the timer says three minutes,
come and meet up with me here.
Then I'll tell you what we do next.
Odd.
One, two, three.
We've got three each.
Yeah, but, um, what was your guess?
Huh?
Oh, yeah. But which one did I guess?
You said even was your guess.
Did I...
Did I say that?
Yeah.
That means...
that I lost again.
Player 43, eliminated.
- A team of older people.
- No, wait.
Player 85, eliminated.
No, no, no, no, no.
Three youngsters.
Oh, get out of the way.
Two old people.
Player 276, eliminated.
Come on. It's your turn.
Huh?
Oh. Right.
Here.
Odd.
Oh.
Hold on. What's today's date?
My son has his birthday soon.
What day is it? The 24th?
I was going to buy him a toy robot
for his birthday.
This year, I need to get him a gift.
I completely forgot last year.
I better do that soon.
I can't forget again.
Oh.
My hand.
What was your guess? A-Again?
Odd.
Oh.
I have 20 marbles.
The rule said we could play
whatever game to get our opponent
to give us theirs,
and the players cannot acquire them
using violence.
Well, I made absolutely sure
no harm was done.
You have three minutes
until the game is over.
Three minutes remaining.
Player 158, eliminated.
Let's do this.
Whoever throws one over there
and makes the shot that comes closest
to the wall, wins.
How's that?
It's Sae-byeok.
What is?
My name.
Kang Sae-byeok.
Sae-byeok.
Pretty.
And you?
Ji-yeong.
Your family name?
Don't have one. That's it.
Who should go first then?
It should be your turn.
Since your number is lower.
Let me see. Darn it.
I'm out of marbles.
Mm.
What should I do, huh?
I'd love to keep playing.
Hey. Would you let me
borrow one from you? Just for a while.
Sir, I'm sorry.
- Player 70, eliminated.
- Oh.
Look at that.
Forgot I had another one here.
Not out yet.
One more to go.
Two, four, six, eight.
Two, four, six, eight. Nineteen.
Nineteen.
Uh... Sir, wait. Hold on a second.
Sir, come back!
Hey, what are you doing?
I lost. You won.
Stop. Why the hell
would you try to do that?
Hey, butter fingers, what else can I say?
What you said
making sure that I won.
Is that what this is?
You think I'll be thankful
that you did this, huh?
Take another throw.
And I still wouldn't be able to win.
Ugh. Just let me lose
this thing in style, okay?
Ji-yeong, that's bullshit!
Stop acting cool and just do a real throw!
I have nothing.
What?
You got a reason to get out of this place,
but I don't.
I thought hard about what I'd do.
If I were the one who got out
since you asked me earlier.
No matter how hard I thought, though,
I got nothing.
The one who should have a reason
to get back out there...
that's what's right.
You can do it. Don't die in here, okay?
And go...
And go meet your mother.
Go get your brother too.
And go to Jeju Island.
Sang-woo.
Sang-woo, where are you?
Sang-woo? Sang-woo, hello?
I'm done with this side.
Sang-woo!
Player 199, eliminated.
Kang Sae-byeok!
I'm honored...
that we were partners.
Player 240, eliminated.
Sir, please. Let's just...
let's just play one more time, huh?
Come on, one more round.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
It's this one.
Yes, this is it.
My wife and I had this one here.
I raised my son right in here.
Yes. I even had a nice little pond
right here in the front yard.
Sir, please,
you have one marble left.
We're running out of time, sir.
And I, I would come home from work,
and see my son, his friends
were always here and they would all play,
and they wouldn't even know I was here.
You need to get it together!
Get it together and play with me again
right now, understood?
I would hide and I'd go
just behind the utility pole there
and take a peek at all of them playing
and just watching.
They would always have so much fun.
Sir, please.
Try to snap out of it, sir.
Oh, God. Sir, I'm begging you.
Why don't we do one more and bet it all?
What?
Everything that I still got,
and everything that you'd...
You can't possibly mean that.
You're gonna take yours and bet it all,
and I'll do the same
with everything that I still got here.
Okay? Keeps everything fair.
I'll wager all I got just to get your one?
What kind of nonsense is this?
There's no sense at all!
So then...
that's what you did this whole time.
Does tricking your friend like that
make sense to you?
Take it.
It's yours anyway.
We are...
gganbu, aren't we?
Don't you remember?
When you and I swore
that we were gganbu buddies.
Gganbu always share everything
with each other no matter what.
Thank you.
You made all this...
a good experience.
What a great way to go.
Really.
It's okay.
Hey.
Everything's okay.
Mm.
It will be okay.
Hey, I remember my name now.
My name is Il-nam.
Oh Il-nam.
Player 1, eliminated.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/8urjn
Help other users to choose the best subtitles