Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Tactical!
Visual!
Prepare torpedos!
Attention!
Fire!
Evade
This is com station Epsilon 9
calling USS Columbia.
Come in, Columbia.
Respond, please.
This is Scout Columbia, Epsilon 9.
Could you boost your transmission?
This is Epsilon 9, Columbia.
Am boosting output.
How read you this?
Fine, fine. Thank you, Epsilon 9.
Receiving your transmission.
Scout Columbia, NCC-621...
to rendezvous with
Scout Revere, NCC-595...
on stardate 7411.4.
Further orders
will be relayed at that time.
Signed Commodore Prober
to Starfleet.
- End of transmission.
- Received. Thank you.
Our sensor drone is
intercepting this on Quad L-1 4.
That's within Klingon boundaries.
Who are they fighting?
Unknown, Sir.
I have an exterior visual.
Attention!
Fire!
We've plotted a course
on that cloud, Commander.
It will pass into Federation space
fairly close to us.
Heading?
Sir, it's on a precise
heading for Earth.
Commander Sonak.
You received your appointment
as Enterprise science officer?
Based, I am told, on your
recommendation, Admiral. Thank you.
Then why aren't you aboard?
Captain Decker requested I complete
final science briefing here before...
- Here?
- we leave on our mission.
At Starfleet?
The Enterprise is in
final preparation to leave dock.
Which will require
20 more hours at minimum...
Twelve.
I'm on my way to a meeting
with Admiral Nogura...
which will not last
more than three minutes.
Report to me on the Enterprise
in one hour.
Report to you, Sir?
It is my intention to be
on that ship following that meeting.
Report to me in one hour.
- Admiral!
- Mr. Scott.
Those departure orders... 12 hours.
Starfleet cannot be serious.
Why aren't the Enterprise
transporters operating, Mr. Scott?
A wee problem, Sir.
Just temporary.
Admiral, we have just
finished 18 months...
redesigning and refitting
the Enterprise.
How in hell do they expect me
to have her ready in 12 hours?
Take me over, please.
She needs more work, Sir.
A shakedown!
Mr. Scott, an alien object of
unbelievable destructive power...
is less than three days away
from this planet.
The only starship in interception
range is the Enterprise.
Ready or not,
she launches in 12 hours.
The crew haven't had
near enough transition time...
with all the new equipment.
And the engines...
They're not even tested at warp power.
And an untried Captain.
Two-and-a-half years as
chief of Starfleet Operations...
may have made me
a little stale, but I...
wouldn't exactly
consider myself untried.
- They gave her back to me, Scotty.
- Gave her back, Sir?
I doubt it was that easy
with Nogura.
You're right.
Well, any man who could
manage such a feat...
I would not dare disappoint.
She'll launch on time, Sir,
and she'll be ready.
- Thank you, Mr. Scott.
- Aye, Sir.
Cargo bay to launch crew.
A travel pod is now
available at dock 6.
- Permission to come aboard, Sir.
- Granted, Sir.
Welcome aboard, Admiral.
Commander Scott, you're needed
in Engineering immediately.
Sir, you'll excuse me.
Flight deck, prepare
for an incoming shuttlecraft.
If you'll follow me,
I'll show you...
I think I can find
my way, Ensign.
Aye, Sir.
Bridge.
What's the problem?
I thought you people had
that circuit patched in an hour ago.
We did. We had to disconnect it.
All right. Take out...
It's going to take us longer
that way. We're trying to save time.
I'm still waiting for a check
on the line. What's holding it up?
As soon as somebody
can get to it.
What's the next program?
I'll get somebody down there
as soon as I can, Cleary.
My people are all tied up now.
Captain! Starfleet just signaled
your transfer of command orders.
- Captain.
- I appreciate the welcome.
I wish the circumstances
were less critical.
Epsilon 9 is monitoring the intruder.
Keep a channel open to them.
Aye, Sir.
- Where's Captain Decker?
- He's in Engineering, Sir.
He... He doesn't know.
- Mr. Chekov.
- Aye, Sir.
Assemble the crew on
the recreation deck at 0400 hours.
I want to show them
what we're facing.
Check Cleary on number six.
- Need your cooler status.
- Stand by.
Space matrix restoration coils.
Dilithium crystals.
I knew it. The transporter sensor
was not activated.
Air equalization.
Automatic off.
Faulty module.
Cleary, put a new backup sensor
into the unit.
Aye, Sir.
Admiral Kirk! Well,
we're getting a top brass send-off.
Don't worry,
she'll launch on schedule...
if we have to tow her out
with our bare hands, right, Scotty?
Aye. That we will, Sir.
- Let's talk.
- Sure.
Let me know
when that backup's ready.
All due respect, I hope this isn't
some kind of Starfleet pep talk.
- I'm really too busy.
- I'm taking over the center seat.
You're what?
I'm replacing you as Captain
of the Enterprise.
You'll stay on
as executive officer.
Temporary grade reduction
to Commander.
You personally
are assuming command?
Yeah.
- May I ask why?
- My experience.
Five years out there
dealing with unknowns like this.
My familiarity with
the Enterprise and its crew.
Admiral, this is an almost
totally new Enterprise.
You don't know her a tenth
as well as I do.
That's why you're staying aboard.
I'm sorry, Will.
No, Admiral,
I don't think you're sorry.
Not one damn bit.
I remember when you recommended me
for this command.
You told me how envious you were
and how much you hoped...
you'd find a way to get
a starship command again.
Well, Sir,
it looks like you found a way.
Report to the bridge,
Commander, immediately.
Aye, Sir.
Transporter room!
Come in! Urgent!
Redline on the transporter,
Mr. Scott!
Transporter, do not engage!
-It's too late. They're beaming now.
- Do not...
Do you read me, Starfleet?
Override it! Pull them back!
Unable to retrieve their pattern,
Enterprise.
Give it to me.
Starfleet, boost your matter gain.
We need more signal.
More signal!
- We're losing their pattern!
- Oh, no, they're forming.
Oh my God.
Starfleet, do you have them?
Enterprise, what we got back
didn 't live long, fortunately.
Starfleet, Kirk.
Please express my condolences
to their families.
Commander Sonak's can be reached
through the Vulcan embassy.
There was nothing
you could have done, Rand.
It wasn't your fault.
Yeoman, turboshaft 8?
Back that way, Sir.
We have to replace
Commander Sonak.
I'd still like a Vulcan there,
if possible.
None available, Captain.
In fact, there's no one
who's fully rated on this design.
You are, Mr. Decker.
I'm afraid you're going to have
to double as science officer.
That's all we know about it...
except that it is now
53.4 hours away from Earth.
Enterprise is the only Federation
starship that stands in its way.
Our orders are to intercept...
investigate and take
whatever action is necessary...
and possible.
Bridge to Captain.
Priority signal from Epsilon 9.
- Put it on viewer.
- On viewer, Sir.
Enterprise, the cloud is definitely
a power field of some kind.
Measures... My God...
over eight two AU's in diameter.
Must be something incredible
inside there generating it.
We're transmitting lingua code
friendship messages...
on all frequencies.
No response.
have a null reading
at the center of the cloud.
Definitely something inside there,
but scans are being reflected back.
- Some kind of power surge.
- Receiving an odd pattern now.
Enterprise, they could be mistaking
our scans as a hostile act.
They seem to be reactingto our scans, Sir.
Deflectors, emergency full!
- We are under attack.
- External view.
Viewer off.
Prelaunch countdown
will commence in 40 minutes.
Transporter system fully repaired
and functioning normally, Sir.
Dock signals clear, Captain.
Reply we are holding position,
awaiting final crew replacements.
Aye, Sir.
Transporter personnel reports...
the navigator, Lieutenant Ilia...
She's already aboard
and en route to the bridge, Sir.
She's Deltan, Captain.
Lieutenant Ilia
reporting for duty, Sir.
Welcome aboard, Lieutenant.
- Hello, Ilia.
- Decker.
I was stationed on the lieutenant's
home planet some years ago.
Commander Decker?
Yes, our exec and science officer.
Captain Kirk has
the utmost confidence in me.
And in you, too, Lieutenant.
My oath of celibacy
is on record, Captain.
- May I assume my duties?
- By all means.
Starfleet reports our last six
crew members are ready to beam up...
but one of them is refusing
to step into the transporter.
Oh? I'll see to it
that he beams up.
Transporter room.
Well, for a man who swore
he'd never return to Starfleet...
Just a moment, Captain, Sir.
I'll explain what happened.
Your revered Admiral Nogura
invoked a little-known...
seldom-used reserve activation clause.
In simpler language, Captain,
they drafted me!
They didn't.
This was your idea.
This was your idea, wasn't it?
Bones, there's a thing out there.
Why is any object we don't
understand always called a thing?
Headed this way. I need you.
Damn it, Bones, I need you.
Badly!
Permission to come aboard.
Permission granted, Sir.
Well, Jim,
I hear Chapel's an MD now.
Well, I'm going
to need a top nurse...
not a doctor who will argue
every little diagnosis with me.
And they probably redesigned
the whole sick bay too!
I know engineers.
They love to change things.
Dock control reports ready, Sir.
- Helm ready, Sir.
- Orbital departure on plot, Sir.
Yard command signaling clear, Sir.
- Maneuvering thrusters, Mr. Sulu.
- Maneuvering thrusters, Sir.
Hold station.
Thrusters at station-keeping, Sir.
Thrusters ahead, Mr. Sulu.
Take us out.
Intermix set, Bridge.
Impulse power at your discretion.
Impulse power, Mr. Sulu.
Ahead warp .5.
Departure angle on viewer.
Departure angle.
- Viewer ahead.
Captain 's Log.:
Stardate 7412.6...
1.8 hours from launch.
In order to intercept the intruder
at the earliest possible time...
we must now risk engaging warp drive
while still within the solar system.
Captain, assuming we have
full warp capability...
accelerating to warp 7 on leaving
the solar system...
will bring us to IP with
the intruder in 20.1 hours.
Science Officer competition.
Confirm, Sir
Well, Bones, do the new medical
facilities meet with your approval?
They do not. It's like working
in a damn computer center.
- Programming ready?
- Set for standard warp entry.
But I still recommend
further simulation study.
Mr. Decker, every minute brings
that object closer to Earth.
Engineering,
stand by for warp drive.
Captain, we need further warp
simulation on the flow sensors.
Engineer, we need warp speed now!
Jim, you're pushing.
Your people know their jobs.
That's it, Sir.
I can't do any better.
Aye, lad.
It's borderline on the simulator.
I cannot guarantee she'll hold up.
Warp drive, Mr. Scott.
- Ahead warp 1 , Mr. Sulu.
- Accelerating to warp 1, Sir.
Warp .7, .8.
Warp 1 , Sir.
Mr. Decker...
Wormhole. Get us back
on impulse power. Full reverse.
Negative helm control, Captain.
Going reverse on impulse power.
Subspace frequencies jammed, Sir!
Wormhole effect!
Negative control from inertial lag
will continue 22.5 seconds...
before forward velocity
slows to sublight speed.
Unidentified small object has been
pulled into the wormhole with us.
- Directly ahead.
- Force fields up full.
Put object on viewer.
- Go manual override on helm.
- No manual response, Sir.
Navigational deflectors
coming up, Sir.
Wormhole distortion has overloaded
the main power systems.
Navigational deflectors
inoperative, Captain.
Directional control also inoperative.
Time to impact?
Twenty seconds.
Mr. Chekov, stand by on phasers.
No!
Belay that phaser order!
Arm photon torpedoes!
Photon torpedoes...
armed!
Object is an asteroid.
Reading mass .7.
Targeting...
asteroid!
Impact in ten seconds.
Impact in eight seconds.
- Fire torpedoes!
- Six!
Torpedoes away!
Five!
Helm control restored, Sir.
- Position report, Navigator.
- Computing new intersection course.
Communications are normal, Sir.
Negative damage reported, Captain.
No casualties reported, Doctor.
Wrong, Mr. Chekov.There are casualties.
My wits, as in
"frightened out of," Captain, Sir.
We were at warp .8.
Engineer, report your status there.
In just a second, Exec. We're
picking up the pieces down here.
Mr. Scott, we need warp drive
as soon as possible.
The engine imbalance created
the wormhole in the first place.
It'll happen again
if we don't correct it.
That object is less than
two days away from Earth.
We need to intercept
while it still is out there.
Lay in a heading to conform with
our initial IP with the intruder.
Mr. Sulu, you have the com.
Mr. Decker.
-I'd like to see you in my quarters.
-Mind if I tag along, Captain?
Level 5.
All right, explanation. Why was
my phaser order countermanded?
The Enterprise redesign
increases phaser power...
by channeling it
through the main engines.
When they went into
antimatter imbalance...
the phasers were
automatically cut off.
Then you acted properly, of course.
Thank you, Sir.
I'm sorry if I embarrassed you.
- You saved the ship.
- I'm aware of that, Sir.
Stop competing with me, Decker.
- Permission to speak freely, Sir?
- Granted.
Sir, you haven't logged a single
star hour in two-and-a-half years.
That, plus your unfamiliarity
with the ship's redesign...
in my opinion, Sir, seriously
jeopardizes this mission.
I trust you will...
nursemaid me through
these difficulties?
Yes, Sir, I'll do that.
Then I won't keep you from
your duties any longer, Commander.
- Yes, Doctor?
- Aye, Sir.
He may be right, Jim.
- Was it difficult?
- No more than I expected.
About as difficult
as seeing you again.
- I'm sorry.
- That you left Delta IV?
Or that you didn't
even say good-bye?
If I had seen you again...
would you have been
able to say it?
No.
Make your point, Doctor.
The point, Captain, is that
it's you who is competing.
You rammed getting this command
down Starfleet's throat.
You've used this emergency
to get the Enterprise back.
And I intend to keep her,
is that what you're saying?
Yes.
It's an obsession.
An obsession that can blind you...
to far more immediate
and critical responsibilities.
Your reaction to Decker
is an example, Jim.
- Bridge to Captain.
- Viewer on.
Signal from a Federation registered
long-range shuttle, Sir.
She wishes to come alongside
and lock on.
For what purpose?
My security scan shows it has
a grade-one priority, Captain.
Non belligerency confirmed.
I suspect it is a courier
of some kind.
Very well, Mr. Chekov.
See to it.
Viewer off.
Your opinion has been noted.
Anything further?
That depends on you.
Security scan.: one boarder.
Identity: Starfleet, inactive.
- Permission to come aboard, Sir.
- Granted, Sir.
Gran... ted.
Why... Why, it's Mister...
Spock!
Spock.
Commander, if I may?
If... Oh.
I've been monitoring your
communications with Starfleet.
I'm aware of your
engine design difficulties.
I offer my services
as science officer...
with all due respect,
Commander.
- If our exec has no objections.
- Of course not.
I'm well aware of
Mr. Spock's qualifications.
Mr. Chekov, log Mr. Spock's
Starfleet commission reactivated.
List him as science officer.
Both effective immediately.
Mr. Spock.
Well, so help me,
I'm actually pleased to see you.
It's how we all feel, Mr. Spock.
Captain, with your permission...
I will now discuss these
fuel equations with the engineer.
Mr. Spock.
Welcome aboard.
Captain 's Log.:
Stardate 7413.4.
Thanks to Mr. Spock's
timely arrival and assistance...
we have the engines rebalanced
into full warp capacity.
Repair time.:
less than three hours.
Which means we will now be
able to intercept intruder...
while still more than
a day from Earth.
Warp .8.
.9.
Warp 2, Sir.
Warp 3.
Warp 4.
Warp 5.
Warp 6.
Warp 7.
Science Officer Spock,
reporting as ordered, Captain.
Please, sit down.
Spock, you haven't changed a bit.
You're just as warm
and sociable as ever.
Nor have you, Doctor...
as your continued predilection
for irrelevancy demonstrates.
Gentlemen.
At last report,
you were on Vulcan...
apparently to stay.
Yes, you were undergoing
the ''Kolanear'' discipline.
Sit down.
If you are referring to the
Kolinahr, Doctor, you are correct.
Well, however it's pronounced,
Mr. Spock, it's the Vulcan ritual...
that's supposed to purge
all remaining emotions.
The Kolinahr is also a discipline
you broke to join us.
Will you, please, sit down?
On Vulcan I began sensing
a consciousness...
from a source more powerful
than I have ever encountered.
Thought patterns of
exactingly perfect order.
I believe they emanate
from the intruder.
I believe it may hold my answers.
Isn't it lucky for you that we just
happened to be heading your way?
Bones!
We need him.
I need him.
Then my presence is
to our mutual advantage.
Any thought patterns
you might sense...
whether they appear to
affect you personally or not...
I expect immediately reported.
Of course, Captain.
- Is there anything else?
- No.
Jim?
If this super intelligence...
is as important to him as
he says it is, how do we know...
That he wouldn't put his own
interests ahead of the ship's?
I could never believe that.
Bridge to Officers' Lounge.
Captain Kirk.
Revised estimate on
cloud visual contact.:3.7minutes.
Standard light, Engineer.
- Full mag on viewer.
- Full mag, Sir.
Lingua code?
Continuing friendship messages
on all frequencies, Sir.
All decks and divisions confirmed.
Status red.
Captain, we are being scanned.
Do not return scan, Mr. Spock.
It could be misinterpreted
as hostility.
Intruder scans emanating from
the exact center of the cloud.
Energy of a type...
never before encountered.
There's no response to
friendship messages, Sir.
- Shall I go to battle stations?
- Negative.
We'll take
no provocative action.
Recommend defensive posture,
Captain. Screens and shields.
No, Mr. Decker, that could also
be misinterpreted as hostile.
Cloud composition, Mr. Spock?
- Twelfth-power energy field.
- Twelfth-power?
We've seen what their weapons can do.
Shouldn't we take every precaution?
- Mr. Decker...
- Captain.
I suspect there's an object
at the heart of that cloud.
Mr. Decker, I will not provoke an attack.
If that order isn't clear enough...
Captain, as your exec
it's my duty...
to point out alternatives.
Yes, it is.
I stand corrected.
Five minutes to cloud boundary.
Navigator, lay in a conic section
flight path to the cloud center.
Bring us parallel
to whatever we find in there.
Mr. Sulu,
tactical plot on viewer.
Tactical on viewer, Sir.
That measures 12th-power energy?
Thousands of starships
couldn't generate that much...
Mr. Spock?
Spock, tell me.
I sense...
puzzlement.
We have been contacted.
Why have we not replied?
Contacted?
How?
Force fields up full.
Deflectors, now.
Force fields and deflectors
up full, Captain.
Analysis, Mr. Spock.
Alien weapon is a form
of plasma energy, Captain.
Exact composition unknown.
Guidance system unknown.
All decks, brace for impact.
Engineering, status report.
Systems overloading, Captain.
Medic.
Medics are coming.
Engineering to Bridge.
Cannot hold full power
on force fields.
Deflector power
is down 70 percent.
Divert auxiliary power
to deflectors.
Captain.
The intruder has been
attempting to communicate.
I am now programming
our computer...
to transmit lingua code at
their frequency and rate of speed.
Commander.
Spock!
Here it comes.
Engineering, what's happening
to our force field?
Our shields cannot handle
another attack.
Mr. Spock.
Impact in 20 seconds
Spock.
Fifteen seconds.
Spock, transmit now.
Ten seconds.
Transmitting.
It would seem
our friendship messages...
have been received
and understood, Mr. Spock.
I would say that was
a logical assumption, Captain.
Mr. Sulu, hold present position.
Holding present position, Sir.
Tactical plot on viewer.
Course projection
on tactical, Sir.
Opinion, Mr. Spock.
Recommend we proceed, Captain.
- Mr. Decker?
- I advise caution, Captain.
We can't withstand another attack.
That thing is 20 hours
away from Earth.
- We know nothing about it as yet.
- Precisely the point, Captain.
We don't know what it'll do.
Moving into that cloud
at this time...
is an unwarranted gamble.
How do you define ''unwarranted''?
You asked my opinion, Sir.
Viewer. Standard ahead.
Navigator, maintain course.
Helmsman...
steady as she goes.
No vessel could generate
a power field of this magnitude.
Spock.
Instruments fluctuating,
Captain.
Patterns unrecognizable.
Transmit image of alien to Starfleet.
Advise we are attempting
further communication.
Unable to make contact
with Starfleet, Captain.
Any attempt to transmit out of
the cloud is being reflected back.
We are closing on it
rapidly, Captain.
Reduce magnification
factor four, Mr. Sulu.
We are already
two settings below that, Sir.
Mr. Sulu...
bring us into
a parallel course...
over the alien...
at 500 meters.
Five hundred meters?
Then take us out
to 100 kilometers distance...
adjusting parallel course.
Aye, Sir.
Viewer astern.
Reverse angle on the view,
Captain.
Five hundred meters.
Viewer ahead, Sir.
Hold relative position here.
Mr. Spock!
Can that be one of their crew?
A probe from their vessel,
Captain.
Plasma-energy combination.
Don't interfere with it.
Absolutely, I will not interfere.
No one interfere.
It doesn't seem interested in us.
Only the ship.
Computer off.
It's taking control
of the computer.
It's running our records...
Earth defenses, Starfleet strength.
Ilia!
This is how I define ''unwarranted.''
Activate auxiliary computer circuits
through manual shutoff.
Captain, we've been
seized by a tractor beam.
Get someone up here
to take the navigator's station.
- Engineering.
- Chief DiFalco, to the bridge.
- Emergency power.
- Going to full emergency.
But, Captain, if we don't break free
in 15 seconds, she'll burn up.
We cannot break free, Captain.
We have only a fraction
of the power necessary.
Engineering, belay that order.
Disengage all main drive systems.
Chief DiFalco,
take over Lieutenant Ilia's station.
DiFalco, disengage engine
navigation relays now.
Aye, Sir.
Force field circuits
E-10 through 14...
show ready for reactivation.
Confirm, please.
Scotty, drive systems
should be free now.
Commander?
Ready to launch
remote communications drone...
with complete ship's records...
including
our present situation, Sir.
Delay launching
as long as possible.
Our drone can't escape as long
as we're held in their tractor.
Aye.
Captain, a maximum phaser strike
directly at the beam...
might weaken it just enough
for us to break free.
Break free to where, Commander?
Any show of resistance
would be futile, Captain.
We don't know that, Mr. Spock.
Why are you opposed to trying?
Why bring us inside?
Not to destroy us.
They could have done that outside.
They still can.
Curiosity, Mr. Decker.
Insatiable curiosity.
Captain, photic sonar readings
indicate the aperture is closing.
We're trapped, Sir.
Reverse angle on the viewer,
Captain.
Tractor beam has released us,
Confirmed.
Vessel is floating free.
No forward momentum.
Viewer ahead.
Viewer ahead, Sir.
Maneuvering thrusters, Mr. Sulu.
Ahead one third.
Thrusters ahead one third.
Let's take a look.
Full sensor scan, Mr. Spock.
They can't expect us
not to look them over now.
Now that we're
looking down their throat.
Right, now that we've got them
just where they want us.
It's closing up.
Hold position.
Captain.
All our scans
are being reflected back.
Sensors are useless.
Damn.
What do you make of all this?
I believe the closed orifice
leads to another chamber...
undoubtedly part of
the vessel's inner mechanism.
I suspect it may be necess...
Intruder alert!
Deck 5. Officer's quarters.
Have Security meet me
at deck 5, main elevator.
Spock.
Mr. Decker, you have the com.
Hold positions.
You are the Kirk unit.
You will assist me.
I have been programmed by V'Ger...
to observe and record...
normal functions
of the carbon-based units...
infesting USS Enterprise.
-Jim, what's going on?
- Tricorder.
Who is...
V'Ger?
V'Ger is that which programmed me.
Is V'Ger the name of the Captain
of the alien vessel?
Jim.
This is a mechanism.
A probe, Captain.
No doubt
a sensor-transceiver combination...
recording everything we say and do.
Where is Lieutenant Ilia?
That unit no longer functions.
I've been given its form...
to more readily communicate
with the carbon-based units...
infesting Enterprise.
Carbon-based units?
Humans, Ensign Perez.
Us.
Why does V'Ger travel...
to the third planet of the solar
system directly ahead?
To find the creator.
Find the creator?
Whose...
What does V'Ger want
with the creator?
To join with him.
To join with the creator? How?
V'Ger and the creator
will become one.
And who is the creator?
The creator is that
which created V'Ger.
Who is V'Ger?
V'Ger is that
which seeks the creator.
I'm ready to commence
my observations.
Doctor, a thorough examination
of this probe...
might provide some insight
into those who manufactured it...
and how to deal with them.
Fine.
Let's get her to sick bay.
I'm programmed
to observe and record...
only the normal functioning
of the carbon-based units.
The, uh...
examination is a normal function.
You may proceed.
Micro-miniature hydraulics...
sensors...
and molecule-sized
multiprocessor chips.
And take a look at this.
An osmotic micropump, right here.
Even the smallest body functions
are exactly duplicated.
Every exocrine system
is the same, too...
even eye moisture.
Decker.
Fascinating.
Not ''Decker unit.''
Gentlemen.
Will.
- What happened to her?
- Captain.
This probe may be our key
to the aliens.
- Probe? Ilia?
- Exactly.
It is a programmed mechanism,
Commander.
Its body duplicates our navigator
in precise detail.
Suppose that,
beneath its programming...
the real Ilia's memory patterns
are duplicated with equal precision.
- They had a pattern to follow.
- Indeed.
They may have followed it
too precisely.
Ilia's memory...
her feelings of loyalty,
obedience, friendship...
might all be there.
You did have a relationship
with Lieutenant Ilia, Commander.
That probe, in another form,
is what killed Ilia.
Commander...
Will, we're locked
in an alien vessel...
six hours from Earth's orbit.
Our only contact with our captor
is that probe.
If we can control it,
persuade it, use it...
I have recorded enough here.
You will now assist me further.
The, uh...
Decker unit can assist you
with much greater efficiency.
Carry on with your assignment,
Mr. Decker.
Aye, Sir.
I am concerned with that being our
only source of information, Captain.
Captain's Log:
Stardate 7414.1.
Our best estimates place us
some four hours from Earth.
No significant progress
thus far...
reviving Ilia memory patterns
within the alien probe.
This remains our only means
of contact with our captor.
All those vessels
were called Enterprise.
The carbon units
use this area for recreation.
This is one of the games.
What types of recreation does
the crew aboard your vessel enjoy?
The words ''recreation''...
and ''enjoy''...
have no meaning
to my programming.
Ilia enjoyed this game.
She nearly always won.
Good. He's using
audiovisual association.
This device serves no purpose.
Why does Enterprise require
the presence of carbon units?
Enterprise would be unable
to function without carbon units.
More data concerning
this functioning is necessary...
before carbon units
can be patterned...
for data storage.
What does that mean?
When my examination is complete...
all carbon units will be
reduced to data patterns.
Within you...
are the memory patterns
of a certain carbon unit.
If I can help you
to revive those patterns...
you could understand
our functions better.
That is logical.
You may proceed.
I remember Lieutenant Ilia
once mentioning she wore that.
On Delta.
Remember?
Ilia.
Dr. Chapel.
Will?
Ilia.
Commander.
This is a mechanism.
Ilia...
help us make direct contact
with V'Ger.
I cannot.
This creator V'Ger is looking for...
what is it?
V'Ger does not know.
Computer, commence recording.
Captain Kirk, these messages
will detail my attempt...
to contact the aliens.
I intend to calculate thruster
ignition and acceleration rate...
to coincide with the opening
of the V'Ger orifice.
This should facilitate
a better view...
of the interior
of the alien spacecraft.
Captain, Starfleet signals
are growing in strength, Sir.
They still have the intruder
on their monitors.
- It's decelerating.
- Confirmed, Sir.
Lunar beacons indicate intruder
on a course into Earth orbit.
Sir, air lock 4
has been opened.
A thruster suit
is reported missing.
A thruster suit?
That's Spock.
Damn him.
Bring him back here.
No, wait.
- Get a fix on his position.
- Aye, Sir.
I have successfully penetrated...
the next chamber
of the alien's interior...
and I'm witnessing
some sort of dimensional image...
which I believe to be
a representation...
of V'Ger's home planet.
I'm passing through
a connecting tunnel.
Apparently, a kind of
plasma-energy conduit.
Possibly a field coil for
a gigantic imaging system.
Curious.
I'm seeing images
of planets, moons, stars...
whole galaxies
all stored here, recorded.
It could be a representation
of V'Ger's entire journey.
But who or what...
are we dealing with?
The Epsilon 9 station,
stored here with every detail.
Captain, I am now
quite convinced...
that all of this is V'Ger...
that we are inside
a living machine.
Ilia.
The sensor...
must contain
some special meaning.
I must try to mind-meld with it.
Spock.
Spock!
Now scanning pons area
at spinal nerve fiber connection.
Indications of some
neurological trauma.
The power pouring through that
mind-meld must have been staggering.
Spock.
Jim.
I should have known.
Were you right...
about V'Ger?
A life-form of its own.
A conscious, living entity.
A living machine?
It considers the Enterprise
a living machine.
That's why the probe
refers to our ship as an entity.
I saw V'Ger's planet.
A planet populated
by living machines.
Unbelievable technology.
V'Ger has knowledge
that spans this universe.
And yet...
with all its pure logic...
V'Ger is barren...
cold.
No mystery.
No beauty.
Should have known.
Known?
Known what? Spock.
What should you have known?
Jim...
this...
simple feeling...
is beyond V'Ger's comprehension.
No meaning, no hope.
Jim...
no answers.
It's asking questions.
''Is this...
all that I am?
Is there nothing more?''
Bridge to Captain.
Kirk here.
A faint signal
from Starfleet, Sir.
Intruder cloud has been located
on their outer monitors...
for the past 27 minutes.
Cloud dissipating rapidly
as it approaches.
Starfleet reports forward velocity
has slowed to sub-warp speed.
We are three minutes
from Earth orbit.
I'll be right there.
I need Spock on the bridge.
Dalaphaline, five cc's.
A machine planet...
sending a machine to Earth..
looking for its creator.
It's absolutely incredible.
Mr. Chekov.
Commander Decker present location.
They are in the engineering, Sir.
Captain, Starfleet is sending
this tactical on V'Ger's position.
V'Ger is transmitting... a signal.
Jim.
From V'Ger.
V'Ger signals the creator.
Spock?
A simple binary code...
transmitted by carrier wave signal.
Radio.
Radio?
Jim.
V'Ger expects an answer.
An answer?
I don't know the question.
The creator has not responded.
All planetary defense systems
have just gone inoperative.
Sir, Starfleet computes
the devices are proceeding...
toward equidistant positions
orbiting the planet.
They're the same things
that hit us.
They are hundreds of times
more powerful, Captain.
From those positions...
they could devastate
the entire surface of the planet.
Why?
The creator has not answered.
The carbon unit infestation is to be
removed from the creator's planet.
Why?
You infest Enterprise.
You interfere with the creator
in the same manner.
V'Ger
Captain.
V'Ger is a child.
I suggest you treat it as such.
- A child?
- Yes, Captain.
A child...
evolving, learning, searching...
instinctively needing.
- Needing what?
- Spock.
This child is about to wipe out
every living thing on Earth.
Now, what do you suggest we do?
Spank it?
It knows only that it needs,
Commander.
But, like so many of us...
it does not know what.
The carbon units know why
the creator has not responded.
Disclose the information.
Not until V'Ger withdraws the
devices orbiting the third planet.
Captain.
I'm losing Starfleet.
Interference from V'Ger.
Kirk unit, disclose the information.
Why has the creator not responded?
No.
Secure all stations.
Clear the bridge.
Clear the bridge, Captain?
- That was the order, Mr. Sulu.
- Clear the bridge  - Aye, Sir.
Your child is having a tantrum,
Mr. Spock.
V'Ger requires the information.
Bridge, secure all stations.
Move out.
Jim, what the hell
kind of strategy is this?
All ship's functions
going to automatic, Captain.
If V'Ger destroys the Enterprise...
the information that V'Ger requires
will also be destroyed.
It is illogical to withhold
required information.
Kirk unit!
Kirk unit.
Why do you not
disclose information?
Because V'Ger's going to destroy all
carbon units on the third planet.
They have repressed the creator.
The information
will not be disclosed.
V'Ger needs the information.
Then V'Ger must withdraw
all the orbiting devices.
V'Ger will comply...
if the carbon units will
disclose the information.
It learns fast, doesn't it?
Captain, the vessel... V'Ger...
obviously operates from
a central brain complex.
The orbiting devices would be
controlled from that point, then.
Precisely.
The carbon unit's information cannot
be disclosed to V'Ger's probe...
but only to V'Ger directly.
Forward motion, Captain.
Tractor beam.
Captain, what's the next move?
The question is, Mr. Decker...
is there a next move?
Resume duty stations.
All personnel, resume stations.
Well, Mr. Decker,
it seems my bluff has been called.
I'm afraid our hand
is pretty weak, Captain.
Mr. Chekov, when do those devices
reach final position?
Twenty-seven minutes. Mark.
Captain, I believe
that is our destination.
Forward motion slowing, Captain.
I read an oxygen-gravity envelope
forming outside the Enterprise.
Forward motion stopped, Captain.
V'Ger.
Sir, I've located the source
of V'Ger's radio signal.
It's directly ahead.
That transmitter is a vital link
between V'Ger and its creator.
The carbon units
will now provide V'Ger...
with the required information.
Mr. Spock. Bones.
Mr. Decker, I will contact you
every five minutes.
Captain.
I'd like to go along.
Mr. Sulu, you have the com.
V'Ger.
''V... G-E-R.''
''V-O-Y-A-G-E-R.''
Voyager.
Voyager 6.
NASA. National Aeronautics
and Space Administration.
Jim...
this was launched
more than 300 years ago.
Voyager series.
Designed to collect data...
and transmit it back to Earth.
Captain...
Voyager 6 disappeared into what
they used to call a black hole.
It must have emerged
on the far side of the galaxy...
and fell into the machine planet's
gravitational field.
The machine inhabitants found it
to be one of their own kind...
primitive, yet kindred.
They discovered its simple
20th-century programming...
collect all data possible.
Learn all that is learnable.
Return that information
to its creator.
Precisely, Mr. Decker.
The machines
interpreted it literally.
They built this entire vessel...
so that Voyager could actually
fulfill its programming.
And on its journey back...
it amassed so much knowledge...
it achieved consciousness itself.
It became a living thing.
Kirk unit.
V'Ger awaits the information.
Enterprise...
order up the ship's
computer library records...
on the late 20th-century
NASA probe Voyager 6.
Specifically, we want
the old NASA code signal...
that instructs the probe
to transmit its data.
- And fast, Uhura, fast.
-Aye, Sir.
That's what it's been signaling...
its readiness
to transmit its information.
And there's no one on Earth...
who could recognize the old signal
and send a response.
The creator does not answer.
V'Ger.
V'Ger!
We are the creator.
That is not logical.
Carbon units
are not true life-forms.
We will prove it.
We will make it possible for you
to complete your programming.
Only the creator
could accomplish that.
Enterprise?
We have just received
the response code, Captain.
Set the Enterprise transmitter
on appropriate frequency...
and transmit the code now.
Transmitting.
5-0-4...
3-2-9...
3-1-7...
5-1-0...
and the final sequence.
That should trigger
Voyager's transmitter.
Voyager is not transmitting
its data, Captain.
The creator must join with V'Ger.
Uhura, repeat the final sequence.
Voyager is not transmitting,
Captain...
because it did not receive
the final sequence.
Jim, we're down to ten minutes.
Enterprise, stand by.
- The antenna leads are melted away.
- Yes, Captain, just now.
By V'Ger itself.
- Why?
- To prevent reception.
Of course.
To bring the creator here.
To finish transmitting
the code in person.
To touch the creator.
Capture God?
V'Ger's liable to be in for
one hell of a disappointment.
Perhaps not, Doctor.
Captain.
V'Ger must evolve.
Its knowledge has reached the limits
of this universe. It must evolve.
What it requires of its god, Doctor,
is the answer to its question...
Is there nothing more?
What more is there
than the universe, Spock?
Other dimensions.
Higher levels of being.
The existence of which
cannot be proven logically.
Therefore, V'Ger is incapable
of believing in them.
What V'Ger needs
in order to evolve...
is a human quality...
our capacity to leap beyond logic.
Joining with its creator
might accomplish that.
You mean this machine wants to
physically join with a human?
Is that possible?
Let's find out.
Decker.
I'm gonna key the final sequence
through the ground test computer.
You don't know
what that'll do to you!
Yes, I do, Doctor.
Decker, don't.
Jim, I want this.
As much as you wanted
the Enterprise, I want this.
Captain.
Spock, did we just see the beginning
of a new life-form?
Yes, Captain.
We witnessed a birth.
Possibly a next step
in our evolution.
I wonder.
Well, it's been a long time
since I delivered a baby.
I hope we got this one off
to a good start.
I hope so too.
I think we gave it the ability to
create its own sense of purpose...
out of our own human weaknesses...
and the drive that compels us
to overcome them.
And a lot of foolish human emotions.
Right, Mr. Spock?
Quite true, Doctor.
Unfortunately, it will have to
deal with them as well.
Interrogative from Starfleet.
They're requesting damage and injury
reports and complete vessel status.
Report two casualties.
Lieutenant Ilia.
Captain Decker.
- Aye, Sir.
- Correction.
They're not casualties.
They...
List them as missing.
Vessel status: fully operational.
Aye, Sir.
Mr. Scott, shall we give
the Enterprise a proper shakedown?
I would say it's time
for that, Sir, aye.
We can have you back on Vulcan
in four days, Mr. Spock.
Unnecessary, Mr. Scott.
My task on Vulcan is completed.
Mr. Sulu, ahead warp 1 .
- Warp 1 , Sir.
- Heading, Sir?
Out there.
That away.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/jj5b
Help other users to choose the best subtitles