Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Sweetheart, remember that
you're doing pickup today
and you need to call the face
painter for the party.
Oh, and Henry needs more Lactaid.
All right. Got it.
Pick up the kids, call the face
painter, get Lactaid. I got it.
Also, I'm going to drop by the new house
and see how the work's coming.
Oh, okay, awesome.
Can you make sure that you measure
the backyard for the bouncy castle?
We're going to have
a bouncy castle at our birthday party?
- Do you want a bouncy castle?
- Yeah.
Then, yes, we'll have the best
bouncy castle in the whole world!
Bouncy castle! Bouncy castle!
Bouncy castle...
And an Ultimate Fighting Octagon?
Uh... I don't know about that.
But, hey, you talked to me!
I was talking to Mommy.
Okay, but just now, you talked
to me by saying that.
Why does she have such a problem?
It's just a phase. Don't push it.
Hey, sweetheart,
it hurts Daddy's feelings
when you give him the silent treatment.
I'm ready for school, I'm ready for
school! Pick me up, pick me up!
All right. Hey, Henry,
you know you can't bring Arthur to school.
But he's my best friend.
Honey, he's your best lizard friend.
You've got lots of non-lizard friends.
Not really.
Really?
Nope.
Oh. All right, have a good day.
I love you.
You're kidding me!
You can't take that to school, monkey.
Go put that in your room.
Sam, I will see you.
I love you.
- Sam.
- Hey.
What? Yeah, oh, golly, okay.
See you.
Thanks. Love you.
There he is!
Hey, Randy. How you doing?
Gregory Focker!
How's it going?
- Wonderful to see you.
- Great to see you.
Listen, I just came by to check
out the backyard and measure
Because we want to do a bouncy
castle for the kids birthday party.
Aw.
That's terrific, Gregory.
Okay, you're about five minutes late.
Yeah, I know.
A Miss Denslow from the
administrative board called.
She wants to get a list of the budget cuts.
You have a meeting in 20
minutes with John Raider
and some drug rep
from Pfosten Pharmaceuticals
is waiting in your office.
Andi something.
There's a drug rep in there?
Mmm-hmm.
Okay, look, in three minutes,
pop your head in and tell me
I have to go to my next meeting.
Okay. All right?
Sorry, I got to make this really quick.
I got a very busy morning.
I understand, Nurse Focker.
I'm Andi Garcia.
Oh, hi.
You have a lot less stubble in person.
I'm... There's an actor
named Andy Garcia.
Who?
Widow's peak. Sort of tough guy.
I was just kidding. Of course,
I know who Andy Garcia is.
I get that all the time.
Yeah. You must get it all the time
Because you're named Andi Garcia.
I loved the article you
wrote in the AMA Journal,
"Putting Patients First."
- You read that?
- I loved it.
It was so cool getting a nurse's
perspective on the health care crisis.
Yeah, that was the idea.
I actually started out
as a nurse, myself.
Really? Oh, well, nowadays,
I do less nursing and more...
Annoying meetings with drug
reps you'd rather not deal with?
Hey, Greg, it's time for your next meeting.
That's okay, I'm fine, Kristen.
Thank you.
Yeah, but he doesn't like to wait.
You know how he is, you know.
Well, it's John Raider?
Yeah, he's really picky...
He always runs late.
Always runs late. Thanks.
- You're swamped.
- No, I'm good. You want to have a seat?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll make this quick.
So we are launching a
killer new product at Pfosten
and, while we usually hire
doctors to lead our presentations,
I have a feeling about you.
I think you have the potential
to be a medical superstar.
And you'd be perfect to
represent our new drug, Sustengo.
Ah. Sustengo. All right.
It's an erectile dysfunction medicine.
It's not just any erectile
dysfunction medicine.
It's the first ED pill on the
market safe for heart patients.
Because, in addition to increasing
the penile blood flow...
See that penis?
It acts as a beta blocker
to keep the heart rate
down during intercourse.
I mean, how dope is that?
That's pretty dope.
Nurse Focker needed in room 220 B, stat.
I'm sorry, hang on one second.
Nurse Focker, room 220 B.
Will you get out of my ass?
If you would stop squirming around...
But you don't know what you're doing.
It could have been over, sir.
Hey, hey, hey,
how you doing there, Mr. Androvsky?
Everything okay?
Well, this nurse is a barbarian.
Okay, I'm not a barbarian.
He keeps clenching and
I can't make an insertion.
Louis, it's...
It's a natural response
to protect that cavity.
You're right, it is a natural response.
I would protect my cavity, too.
And we just got to do
it a little bit gentler.
May I suggest something?
Sir, why don't you extend your left leg
and put your right knee right up to your chest.
It'll help relax things down there.
She's right.
You just do that and you just grab
the side of the bed there, like that,
and exhale... There you go.
Nurse, did you sufficiently
lubricate the nozzle?
- I did do that.
- Great.
- Good, good, okay.
- You got this?
Yep.
All right. Take a nice deep breath.
And focus on relaxing your anus.
Right. That's right.
You just want to let it dilate,
sort of like a flower opening up.
Blossoming lotus.
Sort of like a desert cactus.
Maturing.
It's okay.
Just a little, friendly
visitor just saying hello.
All right, I'm just going to
stick it in a little further.
Oh!
Good smooth insertion.
Thank you.
I'm going to release the clamp.
And let it flow.
Better.
How's that?
That was great.
Nice technique.
That was so fun.
Yeah, yeah.
I was thinking about it and, honestly,
I just don't have time to
moonlight pitching a drug right now.
Shot down.
No, it's not you. It's just...
No, I get it, you know.
Running nursing
in med-surge is a big job.
Yeah, yeah, so big,
I'm making less than I did
when I was in the ER.
Look, we are sponsoring
a convention at the Hilton.
Mmm-hmm.
You can make tons of dough
for, like, one speech.
Think about it.
Okay. I will, I'll think about it.
Okay.
Knuckles?
Knuckles.
That was bad-ass, by the way.
Yeah. Literally.
Dr. Bob.
Scumbag.
Jack, my taxi's here.
Oh, honey, I just got off with Deb.
They are officially separated.
Dr. Bob finished moving out.
That lowlife.
Yeah. You can say that again.
You sure you don't want me
to come with you?
No, you know, I think Deb needs
a little mother-daughter time, honey.
All right?
Having an affair with a nurse.
I can't believe I didn't
see the warning signs.
He was very discreet.
She didn't even know until
she saw those text messages.
Whatever you call them.
Yeah, but I'm trained to detect
that sort of behavior, honey,
and the truth is I was so busy
putting Focker through the wringer,
Dr. Bob slipped right under my radar.
Oh, don't be so hard on yourself.
Well, I'll never let that happen again.
Are you having one of your
little heart palpies again, Jack?
My muscles are a little tight!
Yeah, yeah. From stress.
I can see that. Okay, will you
just, please, just relax, okay?
Everything is going to be all right. Honest.
- Oh, I got to go.
- Okay.
I'm going to miss you.
Hey, Mom.
Hello, my precious prince,
how are you, darling?
Good. How's the TV show going?
Oh, great. You know what this
week's episode is about?
Using the latest sexual toys
to spice up your love life.
- Really?
- Yeah.
As an early Hanukkah present,
I'm going to send you and Pam
a box of these musical condoms.
Don't do that.
You got to hear this, honey.
There's a little speaker inside.
And the faster you go,
the louder it gets.
You know what? Mom, Pam and I are fine.
We don't need musical condoms.
Honey, every couple can use
a little stimulation.
Oh, by the way,
interesting episode last week.
Which one? "Masturbation Through The Ages"?
I thought we agreed you weren't going to
talk about me on the air anymore.
Please, it was just a little
anecdote about carpal tunnel syndrome
from excessive self-pleasuring.
I have to connect your father now, okay?
We need to tell you something.
Ooh.
Hi! Gay? Roz?
- Hello?
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Gaylord?
- Dad?
- Can you hear me?
- Where are you?
You won't believe it. I'm in Seville, Spain.
Where... What are you doing in Spain?
I'm studying.
Sweetheart, your father decided that
he's not going to make
it to the twins' party.
- What?
- Let me explain?
Gay, you remember
when your mother's show
hit number one in the ratings
and she signed on for a second year?
I looked in the mirror
and I said, "Who am I?"
Then I see this clip on the YouTube
and there is a Spanish guy
and he's dancing the flamenco.
And the sweat is pouring off of his face
and there is such passion in his eyes
- ...and I said, "That's it!"
- That's what?
That's me. I am flamenco!
I will master this art.
Dad, this is crazy. What are
you doing? You're in Spain?
You're going to miss the party?
You picked a hell of a time
to go through man-opause.
Roz, I am not going through man-opause,
I'm just trying to find my true north.
True north, huh?
What are you, a compass or something?
No, but let's face it.
I'm a stay-at-home dad
whose kid hasn't lived
at home in 25 years.
There's an Arthur Murray studio
right here in Miami Beach.
Why schlep all the way to Spain?
I can't believe you, Roz.
Why can't you support my dreams
the way I have always supported yours?
- Guys, guys...
- When you wanted to try
...new sex positions for your
research, I was your guinea pig!
You volunteered.
- I pulled my hamstring...
- Hey! Hey!
...doing a reverse cowgirl!
That's because you did it backwards.
I never went soft on you.
Bernie, do you hear
how you're upsetting your son?
- Let me talk.
- Listen, will you?
That son of a bitch.
Oh, shit.
- Hello?
- 911, what's your emergency?
Yeah, my name is Jack Byrnes.
I live at 28 Cherry Blossom Lane.
I'm going into cardiac arrest.
I need an ambulance right away.
I'm guessing your average
response time at this hour
is between 12 and 17 minutes.
I need you to do better than
that. Thank you, goodbye.
Stay calm, Mr. Jinx. I'm going
to defibrillate myself.
Clear!
Seriously, though, my dad,
he always sounds a little crazy,
but this was like a whole different level.
- No, I mean they were really going at it.
- Really?
She accused him of going through man-opause.
Is that a real thing?
Your parents have the best
marriage of anyone I know.
They will be fine.
Yeah, I guess so.
You were talking about the kids.
Really, their teacher
suggested private school?
Yeah, she said she was concerned
about them "getting lost"
in the public school system or something.
What's the name of this place?
The Early Human School.
I have absolutely heard of that place.
Sounds like a school for Neanderthals.
No, it's actually considered
the Harvard of kindergartens.
Mmm. Well, I think Harvard's cheaper.
I'll go see who that is.
Hey, greetings from the Black Sea.
You look terrific.
Hi, stranger, thanks.
What are you doing there?
Listen, Pam. Is there any way
I could speak to Greg?
I want to get his advice
on something, believe it or not.
Sure, absolutely. Hey, Greg?
Yeah.
Greg, honey, it's your buddy, Kevin.
Hold on. Thank you.
- Hey.
How you doing, man?
I was just doing a little sailing
and living the dream, G-Diggity-Dog.
- Cheers!
- Kevin.
- Hey.
- You need a refill on that
goji berry smoothie?
You read my mind. Fill her up, Pak-Man.
Greg, you know Deepak Chopra, right?
I know of him.
- Hi, Greg.
- Hi, Mr. Chopra.
Dr. Chopra.
Get out of here, you rascal.
So, listen, the reason why
I'm calling is because next week...
Kevin, who do you Skype with?
I am just talking to my friend, Greg Focker.
- Hey.
- Come here.
Hey, honey, what'd you
do with Henry's Lactaid?
Oh, crap, I forgot. Sorry.
Well, okay.
But did you call the face-paint lady?
No, I'm sorry.
I had, like, 97 things to do, so...
Honey, I asked you to do
two things, that's all I asked.
I know. Sorry, babe.
Okay, so here's the dealio.
I'm going to propose to Svetlana.
You're going to propose? That's incredible.
I'm going to have three Russian
MiG fighter jets fly by
and skywrite "Marry me, Svetlana."
And then I'm going to hide a 50-carat
super-tasteful diamond ring
in this tin of extremely rare beluga.
Then we will finish the night
with a special performance
that I choreographed
with members of the Bolshoi
Ballet, dedicated to our love.
Thoughts?
Honestly, I'm thinking maybe
it's a little too involved.
Yeah?
I mean, with Pam, my whole thing was just
keep it simple, speak from the heart.
Keep it simple and speak from
the heart. I like it, hombre.
You know what? I'd better call
off some Russian MiG fighter jets.
And, hey, by the time I get to Chi-town,
this old dog here
could be an engaged man.
Hey, Kevin? Yeah.
The jet skis are ready!
The jet skis are ready?
Well, fire them up for me.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
Jet-skiing monks.
Wow, I cannot believe that Kevin
is finally settling down.
Well, I think he's found a soul mate.
Yeah?
Hey, you're going to eat some of this.
She seemed nice.
Yeah. I am very happy for Kevin.
I love him, especially when he's
not obsessed with you.
Oh, come on. You're being ridiculous.
Oh, you got it?
Hey, sweetheart, will you please
take a bite of the lasagna, honey?
- No.
- Uh-uh. Do you not like it?
Hey, what's the good word, Grandpa Jack?
Yay!
Greg.
This is Jack Byrnes.
Yeah, I know. I could tell
from the caller ID.
How are you doing?
Greg, excuse yourself from the table
by saying these exact words,
"I don't know if I still have it,
but let me check my files."
What? If Pam asks you what I want,
tell her that I asked you to locate
your birth certificate
for my genealogical work.
Just do it.
I don't know if I have that,
Jack, but let me check my files.
Files? You have files?
Yes, yeah, I do. I keep files.
He wants me to get my birth certificate
for that family tree thing he's doing.
Jack? Everything okay?
Everything is fine, Greg, I suffered
a minor heart attack,
but I was able to defibrillate myself
before going into fatal cardiac arrest.
Jesus! You defibrillated yourself?
The doctor said I was a lucky man
and I've just got to watch my diet
and keep my stress level down.
Wow, okay, so I guess
you guys aren't going to be able to
come to the twins' birthday party.
No, Dina and I will be there
as planned, Greg.
And I was able to keep this
on a need-to-know basis.
And right now, you're the only
person who needs to know.
Well, come on, Jack. I mean, I think
Dina needs to know.
Greg, stop talking and listen.
Okay.
Now, my genealogical research has
allowed me to track the Byrnes family
as far back as 1643.
1643?
Now, I wouldn't be able to do
that, say, to your family,
what with all the wandering
peddlers and nameless peasants.
Mmm-hmm.
But, as long as there have been Byrneses,
there's always been a patriarch
to lead our family through
good times and bad.
And I've finally come to the realization
that the next in line to the throne, Greg,
is you.
Me.
Yes, you, Greg.
Well... So my question is this,
in the event of my demise, are you
prepared to lead this family?
You know, Jack, we're right
in the middle of dinner.
Maybe we could talk about this,
you know, when you come into town.
If I go down, Greg, I need to
know someone will be responsible
for the whole Byrnes clan.
So I ask you, Greg, are you prepared to be
the Godfocker?
The Godfocker?
The Godfocker.
Well, that is a very powerful
turn of phrase, Jack.
And when you say Godfocker,
I mean...
I mean, I think I know what
you mean, but I'm just...
What exactly does that mean?
It's an attitude, Greg.
It's a confidence.
It's the way you carry yourself
that lets the world know that
the buck stops with you.
Yeah, I hear you. Mmm-hmm.
None of this can be achieved
without the basics.
A secure home for your family,
a top-notch education for your children...
Okay.
...and last but not least, having
your financial house in order, Greg.
Is that it?
Are you laughing?
Yeah, no, I'm just...
I was making... No.
Because this is no laughing matter, Greg.
Good, because I'm not laughing. Okay?
Are you saying you have what
it takes to be the Godfocker?
Greg?
Yes, Jack. I have what it takes
to be the Godfocker.
I feel like a great weight has
been lifted off my shoulders.
And an equally great weight put onto yours.
I like it. I like the weight. I want it.
All right. Need-to-know.
Need-to-know. Just you and me.
See you in two weeks.
Okay. Bye.
Hey, did you find it?
Find what?
Your birth certificate?
Yes. It was in my files.
Mmm.
You know, I was thinking, maybe we should
take a look at that Early Human School.
Great. I'll make some phone
calls and set up a tour.
- Good.
Samantha.
Henry.
You going to have your lasagna?
No, thank you.
You know, your mother worked very
hard making that lasagna for you.
No. It tastes funny.
He said he was feeling
kind of queasy, so...
It's okay.
Henry,
I'm your father and I'm requesting
of you to eat the lasagna.
Fine.
Good.
- Hello.
- Hello?
Greg? This is Jack Byrnes.
Jack Byrnes, this is Greg Focker.
I know, Greg. I called you.
Dina and I will be there
in approximately 18 seconds.
Eighteen seconds, got it.
Oh, no, that's yours, honey.
Welcome, in-laws!
Oh, Gregor. My goodness.
Dina, Dina Bobina, Banana Fana Fofina.
I'm so happy to see you.
Lovely Dina.
You, too, Gregor.
Hello, Jack.
Greg.
Everything okay, Greg?
Everything's great.
Good.
Unfortunately, renovations on the house,
not quite where I'd like them to be.
Well, those things happen.
They do. I mean, never to me before.
And Sam here has done very, very
well with her tae kwon do lessons.
She's a... What are you?
A yellow belt now?
Yep.
Yellow belt.
Wow, sweetheart. Very impressive.
She's lethal. She is a ninja.
Proud of her.
Now, Henry, you're going to
drink your milk, aren't you?
You want to hit the same
growth spurt as your sister.
Jack.
I'm just saying, you know,
it's hard to believe
that they're three minutes apart.
Shh.
Henry, do what your grandpa says.
Aw, man. For real.
Good man.
Okay. Who wants some turkey?
I do, right here! Right here!
Sweetheart, you didn't have to
make a whole turkey just for us.
Why not?
Actually, Greg did it.
Greg.
Well, I remember
at last year's Thanksgiving,
Jack said he liked roast turkey so much
and he couldn't understand why people
only had it once a year.
Excellent memory, Greg.
Plus, it's a wonderfully lean meat.
Healthy. Good for your heart.
Such a sweetheart.
Grandpa Jack, can I ask you a question?
You surely can.
How come you're afraid of lizards?
Henry, that's a very good question.
And I'll tell you why.
When I was stationed in the Mekong
Delta during the Vietnam War,
a tiny gecko crawled into my ear one
night and laid its eggs.
And I had to endure the torturous
probing of our unit's medic
to remove the lizard larvae
from my ear canal
before they hatched into my brain.
Jack.
Cool.
Yuck.
Yes, thanks for sharing that, Dad.
All right, gobble, gobble, everybody!
It's turkey time!
That looks good.
That's a work of art.
Thank you very much.
Looks great, Greg.
Thank you, Jack. And to carve it,
I thought we might use the beautiful
Irish hunting knife
emblazoned with the Byrnes family crest
that Jack so thoughtfully
brought back for us
from his ancestral homeland.
- Look at that, kids.
- Great.
Wow. Look at that.
See that crest?
That was used by your ancestors
long time ago, back in the olden days,
to identify their family.
Daddy, can I ask you a question?
Absolutely. He loves history.
Just soaks it up.
Can a girl poop from her vagina?
No, she cannot.
They're a little young for genealogy.
Yes.
Just a little off topic there.
Jack. Here you go!
Greg. You're the turkey carver now.
Thank you. I'm honored.
All right. Let's carve the roast beast!
Mmm.
Let's see. I think I'll start right side.
Nice and tender.
So, Greg, how are you liking your new job?
Well, I'll tell you, Dina,
it's a lot of responsibility on my plate.
But that's kind of what I love about it.
I mean, the opportunity
to manage an entire unit,
in a way, it's kind of like...
Christ! Shit!
Why couldn't you just get him
a warm-blooded animal?
- Pressure.
- Mom!
Honey. It's okay, it's okay, honey.
- Hello.
- Where is he going? Are you okay?
Hey, Kevin!
It's Kevin, everybody.
What? Okay.
You're in Chicago?
Hey. Hey.
- Hey, everybody. Hello.
- Kevin.
J.B.
Oh! Good to see you.
There he is! The engaged guy!
How you doing, man?
Oh! What happened to your pointer?
I had a little incident with the business
end of a turkey. It's cool.
- Where's Svetlana?
- Yeah!
Or should I say, the future
Mrs. Kevin Rawley?
She broke up with me.
- No.
- Oh.
You're kidding.
I'm so sorry.
Thanks, Pam.
You always know exactly
the right thing to say to me.
"I'm so sorry"?
My anchor.
What happened?
- What?
- What happened?
I don't know. I'm still trying to
make sense of it myself.
We were having some street food
outside a government building in Bulgaria
and I said, "Hey, you want to get married?"
And I took out a little piece of string
and I tied the twine around her finger,
and she just... She threw it on
the ground and said no.
Or nyet, because she's Russian.
She caught the next plane out of there.
Adios, Kevin.
Your proposal seems way out of character.
Why did you put so little effort into it?
Greg told me to.
What are you...
Kevin, no, no.
- What are you talking about? I didn't...
- Daddy?
I can't sleep.
Still in diapers.
No, Jack, they're pull-ups.
We're weaning him off diapers.
What's up, man?
I can't stop thinking about all that blood.
Really? All right, well,
how about I read you a story?
Uncle Kevin!
How you doing, tiger?
- Good.
- Oh!
Wow.
Are you having a hard time sleeping?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
There we go.
Jesus. Henry?
- Are you...
- Shh. He's sleeping.
He's sleeping. I put him in a still-point.
It's a massage technique
that relaxes the body by gently
easing the flow of cerebrospinal fluid.
Yeah. Look at him.
He's going to wake up feeling so refreshed.
I've been studying a lot of Eastern
medicine in my down time.
Well, listen, I just came by
to say my hellos,
so I will head on out.
- Good.
- Okay.
Hey, Kev, listen,
do you need a place to stay?
No, he doesn't.
You got a place to stay, right?
- And we're pretty full up.
- Not a problem.
I volunteer at a South Side
homeless shelter.
So, I'll probably stay there
and just work the soup kitchen
line in the morning.
That is so wonderful, Kevin.
Yeah, it's funny, I feed them food,
but those vagrants
and drifters feed my soul,
so it works out pretty good for all of us.
Perfect. We always need extra hands,
if you guys want to come on down tomorrow...
Actually, Greg and I are taking a tour
of this place called
the Early Human School tomorrow.
But maybe after...
You're kidding me,
the Early Human School?
Right.
My investment group
handles their endowment fund.
In fact, the director, Prudence,
is a dear friend and ex-lover of mine.
I'm going to put in a good word for you.
That would be great, wouldn't it?
Oh, of course.
Or not. I mean, you know, she's an
ex-lover, I think that'd be awkward.
No, nonsense. I'm on great terms with
all my ex-lovers.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Okay. All right,
well, you know, whatever feels right.
After the tour, Greg, I was hoping
you'd show us your new house.
And, Kevin,
when you're done feeding the bums,
why don't you meet us there?
Okay. I'll be there.
You know what, Jack? I still have
some items on the punch list
to go through with the contractors,
so I'm thinking maybe we should
put it off for a few days.
Ah, no, let's do it tomorrow.
Well, I think...
We'll meet you there at noon, Kevin.
I don't know.
- At noon?
- Yeah, all right. Okay.
And we're going to get you through this.
Anything you need, you come to me.
Okay. Thanks, J.B.
Yeah. Or me.
Okay.
Well, you can come to either of us.
Yeah, we're here for you.
Thanks.
Careful, yeah.
- I feel like crap.
- Yeah.
You're burning up.
Yeah, I must have gotten the flu the
kids had last week.
Oh, my God, the school tour is today.
Yeah, I know.
Honey, what am I going to do?
I'll do it. Okay? I'll handle it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, and your mom
can take the kids to school.
But what about my dad?
I got it, all right?
I really appreciate your including
me on the school tour, Greg.
Oh, Jack, you are a trusted advisor.
I mean, your words hit home about a
top-notch education,
getting your financial house in order.
That's it. That's it.
It's all about the kids, right?
The next generation.
I'm glad to hear you say that.
Makes me feel that I've chosen wisely.
Of course, children change everything
in a marriage,
and that was the issue with Debbie and Bob.
They stopped finding time for each
other once LJ came into their lives,
so Bob sought sexual fulfillment
outside the marriage.
Mmm.
- Dr. Bob.
He really disappointed me.
I'll tell you something. I'd like to
really teach that bastard a lesson.
I happen to have his new address.
Perhaps you and I should
sneak in there one night
and plant a tiny explosive device in
the stove.
Make it look like a gas leak.
Yeah. Yeah.
Or we could, you know, maybe
find some less criminal way
of teaching him a lesson.
You know, still get him.
I'm only joking, Greg.
Okay.
But it would be fun.
Yeah, oh, it would be great.
I'm hoping that you and Pam are still
finding time for each other.
Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, are you kidding?
- Yeah, no, no, we're great, we're...
Good.
I mean, you know, it's not easy.
You got to work at it, but...
Are you still physically attracted
to my daughter, Greg?
To Pam? Are you kidding? Yes. Jack,
there's never been a problem with that.
Even after her body's endured the
hellish ordeal of birthing twins?
Yes. Even after that. It's still... It's
all good. It's all good under the hood.
That's disgusting.
Welcome, parents.
I'm Prudence Simmons, director of the
Early Human School.
And at E.H.S., we know.
We know that no two early humans are alike.
So why should their educational
experiences be identical? Right?
Makes sense.
It's not about the 99.8% of graduates
that go on to the best secondary schools.
Wow, impressive.
Yeah.
That guy's really been
hitting the Bow flex, huh?
What?
It's not the overwhelming number
of Early Human alumni
that become civic leaders, CEOs of
Fortune 500 companies. No.
What's important to us is that they
become themselves.
Please welcome the Early Human Tumblers!
Whoo!
Kids are really good.
I like what I'm seeing from this place.
Yeah. And I'm sure it doesn't come cheap.
Mmm-mmm.
You think you can swing it?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah. Yeah, I got it covered.
And, you know,
if it's not covered right now, it
will be covered.
It's one of those things that you cover it.
Do you have the money or not, Greg?
New friends, hello!
Hi.
Hi, I'm Prudence. Greg?
Greg. How are you?
- Jack?
- Jack Byrnes.
So, Jack and Greg,
tell me what path you've chosen.
How do you make a "living"?
Oh, okay, well, I'm a nurse.
Oh.
He's being modest.
He's actually the department manager
of the medical-surgical unit
at Chicago Memorial
and I am a retired florist.
What a combination, a nurse and a florist?
How great.
May I ask how long you've been
in each other's lives?
Oh, I'd say... Well, it's about eight
years, hasn't it been?
Yeah, eight years.
- I'd say eight years.
- Really?
Yeah, yeah. Eight great years. Yeah.
Eight great years.
Well, it started out a little rocky.
We've had our moments.
Yes, but then we figured it out.
You seem like a wonderful couple.
- No, no, no. We're not homosexuals.
- Yeah, no.
No, no. No, no, no, no,
this is my son-in-law.
Yeah, yeah, no, no, no, no.
However, if you're looking to fill a
quota, we can be flexible.
Okay, that's an interesting joke,
but I appreciate levity in a moment
of misunderstanding,
so thank you, Greg.
I will say, Jack,
I hope I didn't offend you.
Oh. No, no.
Really?
No. I mean, I'm not gay myself,
but if I were gay,
I would certainly be proud to choose a
life partner like Gay Focker.
And that's his actual name.
Oh.
It is. Well, it's my, Gaylord was
my name when I was a kid and, yeah.
Well, I'll complete
the conversation with that.
Jack.
Prudence. Pleasure.
- Gay. Great.
- Greg.
Change that nametag.
You can call... It's Greg. Greg is fine.
Why don't we just stick with the truth?
An original American Foursquare,
Greg, very nice.
Yeah, yeah. It's got rock-solid bones
and, you know, it's...
Hey! There they are.
- Kev-O, that's quite a rental.
- Yeah.
Gustavo, my assistant, hooked it up.
I guess it's a Tesla Roadster or something.
Supposedly eco-friendly,
like that 2003 Prius, Greg.
Yeah, you got it.
Wow. It looks great.
Traditional American Foursquare.
Also known as a Prairie Box.
- Yeah.
- It's got really good bones.
Good eye, Kev.
Look out for your legs.
That's good.
Randy? Randy, what is this?
Gregory Focker!
Great to see you. How you doing, Dad?
Hey.
Randy, what is this? We're having
the party here in two days.
Um...
Refresh my memory, Gregory.
Are you kidding me? Randy, the twins
birthday party, remember?
Yes, of course!
The issue we're dealing with is
that we had to excavate 60 feet
of root-infested pipe back here!
So, of course, we ran into some
unexpected costs
along with an obvious delay.
Randy, is this yard gonna be done
or is it not gonna be done?
Jack, I got this. All right?
All Mr. Byrnes is suggesting is
that maybe inadvertently
you're taking advantage
of a gentle, trusting soul
who clearly is an amateur when
it comes to home construction.
- No, Kevin.
- Thank you, Swami Salami.
That's not true at all.
It is true, Greg. They're ripping you off.
No, Jack... Your plumbing excavators
have been on coffee break
for the past eight minutes,
this senior citizen over here
is unfit for active duty
and your backhoe driver's halfway
through a Sudoku puzzle.
- All right.
- Gregory,
who is this joker questioning my honor?
Nobody's questioning your honor, Randy.
I'm 34 years in the trade!
Thirty-four years, huh?
I got to pump, dump and hump to
get that backyard whole again!
Well, I got news for you.
You can pump, dump and hump all you want!
You're sandbagging this damn job
and you know it.
All right. You know what?
Jack, Jack, Jack!
Calm down!
You're leaving a big hole, you...
Hey, General! The Japanese surrendered!
The Japanese surrendered! That's it!
What are you talking about?
World War II.
I'll tell you what, Gregor.
I have a timeshare in town.
Why don't we have the party there?
Beautiful meadow. It'll be perfect.
No, no, Kevin, I promised the kids
they're going to have the party in the yard.
So, guess what? We're going to have the
party in the yard. Okay?
Soon as our dump truck driver's
back from lunch,
we'll get that out, bring the backhoe in,
lay down your base layer of sand.
Wait a minute. You're telling us
that you can't move that rig?
That's a union job, pops.
Screw it. I'm going to
move that truck myself.
- No, come on.
- No, you know what, Jack?
I'll do it, okay? You just help me
back it out into the street. I got it.
Here we go.
All right, start backing her up.
You're all clear.
Coming at you, Jack!
You're doing great, you're doing great.
Hey, look, I'm not in the union, Randy!
I'm backing up the truck!
Come on. Back, back, back. Doing
great. Doing great! Doing great!
Whoa! Whoa!
Brake it!
Oh!
You got it!
- We're good.
- Emergency brake!
Got it!
Jack! Holy shit!
Hang on, I'm with you!
Jack, I'm right here.
Jack, we're going to get you!
It's going to be all right, Jack!
Jack, we're coming! Hang on, Jack!
I got him!
I got you.
It's Kevin. I'm right here.
- Thank you, Kevin.
- Save your strength.
Upsy-daisy. Greg's right here. He's okay.
Yeah, I see him.
Hey, Jack.
Oh, here, it's starting.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's The Roz Focker Show!
And that means it's time
to sexpress yourself!
Hello, my audience!
Hello, my friends. Welcome.
Today, what do you think
we're going to talk about?
Sex! Sex. Sex.
Well, what else is she going to talk about?
Sex after children.
How do you find time to make love
with young children in the house?
What do you do if it's not working?
Do you have an affair?
No!
No, you say? But Roz Focker says yes!
Yes, you do have an affair!
You have an affair with your wife!
Oh, Roz!
Think about it, right?
You dress up a little nicer.
You meet at a hotel.
You role play.
There is absolutely no shame in playing
out a fantasy, but with each other!
All right?
Now, he's going to kill me,
but my own son, who is the father
of two adorable twins,
he has issues in this department.
He's busy at work. She's busy at home.
Their intimacy numbers are down.
They're not connecting.
And what do you do?
- It's called Sustengo.
- Sustengo?
I got to say, that sounds
pretty cheesy, Greg.
Yeah, well, I'm looking at these
Randy Weir bills, okay.
And we could definitely use the money.
And do me a favor. Don't tell
your dad about this, okay?
My dad? Why?
Just because he's been all into
me having my financial house
in order or whatever,
- ...and I just don't want to worry him.
- All right, fine.
I won't say anything because
he's already pretty upset
about you trying to bury him alive.
Honey, it was an accident.
Superstar!
Hey. Hey, can you hang on a second?
Okay.
I am so stoked you changed your mind.
You are going to rock
those urologists tonight.
Awesome. That's always been a goal of mine.
So, I'll see you at 8:00 at the Hilton?
Yes.
- And wear a suit.
- Wear a suit, got it.
- Knuckles?
- Knuckles.
Okay, bye.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Knuckles? Who was that?
That certainly didn't sound like Kristen.
No, no. That was the drug rep.
- Andi?
- Yeah, Andi.
What does she look like?
She's like a...
No, she's, like, an ex-nurse.
You wouldn't pick her out of a lineup.
Yeah, I know that you're doing this for us,
but the idea of you and
some woman named Andi
selling boner medicine at a hotel,
it really kind of icks me out.
Honey, there's nothing
to be icked out about.
Okay, fine.
- I love you.
- I love you, too, honey. Bye.
Okay, bye.
So, how come you're not talking to Daddy?
Because he said you were cuckoo.
He said I was cuckoo?
Mmm-hmm.
Well, we'll have to discuss that.
Yeah.
But what about Mommy and Daddy?
Is everything okay with them?
I guess they fight sometimes.
Mmm-hmm. And what do they fight about?
Um...
Like Mommy got mad at Daddy because he
was going to the hotel with Andi.
Andi?
Who's Andi?
I can't say because I'm not
supposed to be spying.
Like I always tell you, there's
nothing wrong with spying
as long as you suspect foul play.
So, who's Andi?
Andi gives Daddy his boners.
His what?
Uh-huh.
Hey, guys!
- Hey, Greg.
- How was your day?
Yeah. Great.
Hey.
How about you, Sam?
What? Come on, say something to me.
No! I won't!
Ah! You just did.
- Hey, Greg?
- Yeah.
I'm not so sure
using chicanery and
subterfuge on your daughter
is the best way to get her
to communicate with you.
No, no, no. That's not
chicanery and subterfuge.
For whatever it's worth.
Worth a lot. Thank you.
And I will see you later, okay?
I got roped into this hospital
administration dinner thing tonight, so...
- Work function?
- Yeah.
It's the price of being
in charge of the unit, so...
I see. That last minute, huh?
Yeah.
Department head called so I got to
do a little face time and...
- Have fun.
- Okay.
Hmm.
Jack?
Jack!
Is that you?
- Greg.
- What are you doing out here?
Just picking up some milk for the morning.
- You looking for a market?
- Yeah.
Okay, because there's one
right across from the house.
Oh, is there? I didn't know that.
Just take a left on Lincoln. Right there.
- Thanks, Greg.
- Okay.
- See you later.
Excuse me.
Hey!
Greg.
Hey, man. You following me?
Following you? Why would I be following you?
No, I'm just looking for milk.
Okay. Because, remember, I mentioned
out on the street there,
there's a store right in the neighborhood.
True, but Dina likes the organic stuff
and I heard there was a natural
food market downtown.
Amazing, you going all this way
just for a carton of milk.
You know what? You should get off here.
There's a really great natural foods market
about two blocks south of the station.
Oh.
Have a good night, Jack.
You, too, Greg.
Hey.
Oh! Hey.
Superstar!
Everything cool? You seem a little edgy.
No, I'm good. It's just my
in-laws are in town, so...
Anyway, I went over the drug info
and I think I got the science
down pretty well.
Oh, no, Greg. These doctors
don't care about that stuff.
If you want to sell a drug like
Sustengo, you have to make it personal.
Do you know any sexually frustrated
old dudes with a heart condition?
I didn't hear you come in.
What kept you so long?
I just got a little bit lost.
Everyone asleep?
Yeah.
We've got the house to ourselves.
I'm so happy that you
got away from your wife.
Excuse me?
She's been very suspicious lately.
Quick, quick, quick. We only have an hour.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Jack, come on. You've got to play along.
Roz Focker said we have to have
an affair with each other.
I'm role playing.
Right, right, right. I understand.
I just have a bit of a headache,
sweetheart, tonight.
I know. You've had that worried
look on your face all day.
I promise you, the Focker family
is going to be fine.
Now, come on.
Before my husband comes home.
Then, we'd better hurry, my illicit lover.
Let me just brush my teeth.
Ooh.
Your father-in-law did not really
put you in a lie detector machine.
No, that's true.
That's incredible!
Jesus Christ, I thought
my wife's father was bad.
That was a great speech, nurse.
Thank you.
And hey, "I'm staring at you."
It was "I'm watching you," but that's
what he did, yes. Thank you.
You killed it tonight.
Those stories about your
family were hilarious.
Thank you. So, I should be getting going.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. You're my fianc.
Hey, gorgeous.
Hello, Dr. Ballard. So nice to see you.
Hey, can I get you 200 cc's
of anything you want, stat?
Only if you can buy a drink
for my fianc as well.
Didn't know you were engaged.
Can you take a picture
for us for my scrapbook?
You know what? You don't...
He doesn't have to do that.
Yeah, it's for our scrapbook.
No, you know what, bro?
I'm cool like that. I'll do that.
You are such a doll.
Here we go.
One, two, three. Whoa!
Best picture ever.
You look great and you
have, like, a red-eye problem.
I'll see you later, babe.
I cannot believe I ever slept with that guy.
Yeah, right.
No, seriously, I did.
At a convention in Milwaukee last summer.
We were, like, drinking
tequila, doing rum chasers.
Always a bad idea, right?
Yeah.
Can you get me a margarita
on the rocks, no salt?
- You know what...
- I'm going to run to the restroom.
Gosh. You know what...
All right, cool. You're the best.
- All right? All right.
- All right, okay.
Hi. Can I get a club soda and a
margarita on the rocks with no salt?
Thanks.
Night out on the town, Focker?
- Dr. Bob.
- Hey, man!
What are you doing here?
I'm here for the convention. What about you?
Doing some work for Pfosten
as a medical expert.
But you're a nurse.
You know what? I don't really
have anything to say to you.
Okay, I get it, Greg. I screwed up.
But the pressure of being in that
family finally got to me.
What are you talking about?
You were his golden boy.
More like his golden bitch.
He wanted Deb and me to get
married in Oyster Bay. Done.
Can we name our baby after him?
"You got it, Jack."
And he gives me this whole spiel, right,
about how I'm next in line to his throne.
He came up with this name
for me, the Bobfather.
Really? He said that to you?
He pulled the same shit on you, didn't he?
In that family, we're all just hamsters
on Jack Byrnes' little wheel.
His Circus of Trust,
or whatever he calls it.
Circle of Trust.
I had no idea how deep I was in
until I stepped away.
And I'll tell you something,
once I got off the treadmill,
I've never been happier.
Yeah, well, I think I got it under control.
Hello, Greg.
Hey.
Hey, Jack.
You mind explaining this?
What is that? Oh.
Sustengo. Yeah, that's... You know.
These drug companies, they give
me all these free samples.
Is that it?
Or do you need to use this
because you're no longer
sexually attracted to Pam?
You know what, Jack? That's ridiculous.
Really. You know what?
I'm not even going to go there with you.
This is...
Have a good night, all right?
I'm going to go sleep.
Don't walk away from me, Focker.
Jack, is everything okay down there?
Everything's fine.
Okay. All right.
Because you seem to have a little, I mean...
I know what I have, Greg, and I'm
not concerned about that right now.
Right now, what I want
from you is the truth.
Jack, did you take one of those pills?
Well, I was highly preoccupied
and Dina wanted to make love,
and the label clearly states
that it's safe for heart patients.
Yes, but you need a prescription
after you've had a thorough examination.
How long have you had that...
The situation for?
Stop avoiding the question.
I'm not avoiding the question.
If you've had that
for more than four hours,
you could bust a capillary and have
serious permanent damage.
How long have you had it?
Been a little longer than four hours.
How long?
Maybe about five and a half.
Jack, you got to get to an ER right now
and get a shot of adrenaline
to counteract that drug.
You're a nurse. Don't you have
that kind of stuff in the house?
Yeah, I have an Epi kit,
but I'm not going to give you
a shot there, okay?
Focker, there is no way I'm going
to an ER room with this thing.
Now you need to stick me
and you need to stick me now!
I'm having a dick attack!
Stick me!
Shh. Just relax. Okay.
I'll get the needle.
All right. I need you to drop your pants.
What kind of sick drug are you
dealing to your patients?
Jack, I told you,
I took home some samples.
- All right?
- Maybe read the label
before you just pick up a drug and eat it.
Let's just do it.
I'm going to administer the shot
on the count of three.
Just... All right?
Okay. Just...
It's...
Your hands are cold.
I'm sorry. It's a bit...
Okay.
One,
two,
three.
Focker!
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
Wait, what's going on? What happened?
Everything's fine.
Henry had a little nightmare,
but Greg's got him settled down, okay.
No, no, Jack,
I thought I heard you screaming, too.
No, you didn't. It was all Henry.
- Well, let me go check on him...
- Oh, no, no, no.
- ...and make sure he's okay.
- You guys go to sleep.
Everything's under control.
Could you and Dad keep it down, please?
Here's Sirius Black.
Here's Orange Ninja, okay?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- Greg?
- How's he doing?
- He's all right.
You know, he's a little shaken up, but...
Greg, I was involved in some
covert CIA-sponsored
mind-altering techniques back in the '70s.
I'd like a few minutes alone with him
just to erase what he saw from his memory.
You're not going to erase my son's memory.
Greg, he saw his father inject a needle
into his grandfather's penis.
He already has issues. That's something
he might never recover from.
- I'll handle it, okay?
- All right?
Okay, thank you.
Hey, buddy.
So, you know how sometimes
you need help when you...
When you make a wee-wee? Yeah.
Well, when you get to be Grandpa Jack's age,
sometimes you need help
making a wee-wee, too.
So that's what you saw me doing.
I was helping Grandpa Jack because he's old.
Well, why did he scream so loud?
He wasn't screaming. He was celebrating,
he was just so happy.
He was, like, "Oh, Focker. Thanks
for helping me make a wee-wee."
- He just... He was so happy.
- Right, right?
Right, Greg.
- Yeah.
- Understand?
- I think so.
- Good.
Don't think this incident
is distracting me, Focker.
I know you're up to something
and I'm watching you.
Well, guess what? I have eyes, too.
So, I'll be watching you, watching me.
- Okay.
- All right?
- Fair enough.
- Good.
So we just watch each other, all right?
Okay, okay.
I'm watching you right now.
Domsey's Bakery. How can I help you?
Hello, yes, do you still have the
pineapple upside-down cake?
Yes, we do. Would you like
chocolate or vanilla frosting?
Neither. I'm only interested in merengue.
Please give me your access code
and releasing ID.
This is Santa. Releasing ID 7726548.
I need all-source, derogatory only,
on a person named Andi Garcia.
Alpha, November, Delta, Indigo...
Santa, your clearances haven't
been active for 12 years.
Now, you listen to me, Young Turk.
I was bugging Ho Chi Minh's sock drawer
while you were still in diapers,
so don't tell me about clearances.
Sir, my hands are tied.
But, I mean, you could probably just
Google the subject
and find out everything you need to know.
Oh.
Then I'll do that. Santa out.
Hmm.
Oh, honey, I can't wait to see
Kevin's timeshare later today, huh?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
What you doing?
Oh, just checking the weather.
There's a cold front coming in.
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
Greg.
Hey, how you doing? Sorry, I'm late.
Hi, honey.
A little emergency at the hospital.
Kevin was showing us his magnificent estate.
It's really nice.
So this is where you rough it
when you're not at the homeless shelter?
Kind of split time between the two.
Maybe 60%-40% here.
- Really?
- Now that Greg's finally arrived,
why don't I take you over to see the meadow?
Yeah, this is perfect.
- Oh, this is impressive.
- Wow, nice backyard.
- Yeah, love it.
- Wow, it is.
Thank you.
Let's reserve that quadrant
over there, Kevin?
It's perfect for the three-legged race,
egg toss, capture-the-flag game.
Why don't we put up a ring of
bouncy castles right out there
and we have, like,
a relay race for the kids
kind of intertwined in between them.
Loving it, Kev-O.
Kevin, is that a tattoo on your back?
Oh, yes, it is, Dina.
It looks really elaborate.
Could we take a look at it?
- Oh, sure.
- Mom.
Well, it's a curiosity.
My gosh.
Hmm.
Wow.
Is that Pam?
Yeah, it is.
You know, after the whole Svetlana episode,
I went on a little bit of a drunken bender
and wound up in a tattoo shop in Moscow.
And I asked the artist to ink me
with the image of the one woman
who's always loved me unconditionally.
- Pam.
- My grandmother.
The point being, in my drunken stupor,
I must have handed him
a photo of Pam instead.
You carry a picture of Pam in your wallet.
I do. I carry pictures
of many treasured friends
and loved ones on my travels.
Got a picture of me?
Of course I got a picture of you.
You recognize this mensch right here?
- Ah. There I am. Kind of.
- There you are, yeah.
That's... Interesting.
This is actually a very flattering
portrait of you, Pam-cake.
- Excuse me.
- Dad.
Prudence? Yes! Hello!
Yeah, hold on, honey. I don't...
Terrific. Okay, yes, thanks, Pru.
That was Prudence and she says
if you get to E.H.S. by 3:00,
she can squeeze you in for an interview.
- All right, that's great!
- Way to go, Kev-O.
- Thank you, Kevin.
- Good job.
So great you two could join us.
Really wonderful when grandparents
play an integral role
in early humans' lives. We love them.
Early humans do need guidance.
Is that your role, Jack? To guide them?
Yes, I see myself
as something of a shepherd,
guiding our family through life's pastures.
Yes, I would say Jack is sort of
an honorary shepherd.
Kind of a shepherd emeritus, if you will.
Well, when my sheep wander, I use
my prod to keep my flock in line.
Oh, there are a lot of family dynamics
at play here.
Why don't we begin the interview process?
Okay, Henry, I just want you
to clear your mind
and draw a picture for me of the
first thing that comes to mind
when you hear the word "family."
Oh.
This is just like being at the eye doctor.
Start at the top and work your way down.
Why would she give her an eye test?
It's called a Heisenreich Experiment.
We used it at the agency to test
the aptitude of potential recruits.
All the letters are the same,
so it's not really an eye test.
Very impressive cognition, Samantha.
E... E...
E? I need to start over.
Okay, Henry, let's see what
you've chosen to draw.
What is it? What did he draw?
Dad stuck Grandpa Jack in the wee-wee
last night. Because he's old.
I'm sorry? What did he say?
I didn't hear him.
Something about Grandpa Jack having a cold.
So tell me about your parents, Samantha.
Tell me about your parents, Prudence.
That's my girl.
Want to tell me about your family?
My dad is a great guy.
Thank you, buddy.
But Grandpa Jack makes him
really, really scared.
So he acts all crazy when he's with him.
Like he tried to cut the turkey
with Grandpa's big knife
and he slipped and he cut his finger.
And he was like, "Oh, shit!"
Oh, he's blowing the interview.
She's setting him up to fail
with these questions.
I mean, Sam's a better tester, anyway, so...
Well, that's because she takes after...
Takes after who, Jack?
Let's just say I've done some
research on twins.
There's a theory that in certain cases,
one twin gets an extra
chromosome from the father,
while the other sibling
gets an extra chromosome
from the mother's side.
Hmm.
Sam might be three quarters Byrnes,
whereas Henry could very well have
a double dose of Focker in him.
And what if he does?
My Grandpa Bernie taught me this.
Pull my finger.
Oh.
Double dose.
Let's go out to the courtyard
for some free play.
I mean, what is "free-play test"?
How well they hang on the monkey bars?
I don't think you get it, Greg.
You know when prison guards learn the most
about their inmate population?
During rec time in the yard.
I'm sure Prudence is
in her office right now
watching every move these kids make.
- Dad?
- Yeah.
Can I please go climb that big rock wall?
- Yeah, okay.
- Just be careful, buddy, all right?
All right.
Do you think he can handle that?
What's the big deal?
I'm just not sure you've instilled
the physical confidence
for him to shear a face like that.
Jack, do me a favor. Just let
go of the reins a little, okay?
I'll let go, Greg,
when you show me, once and for all,
that you have what it takes to lead.
I am in control of my family, all right?
If I give Henry permission to climb
a wall, he can climb a wall.
If he says he wants to climb
the Empire State Building
and I say it's okay,
it's okay, because I'm in charge.
All right? I'm calling the plays now.
So you just got to step back
and accept the fact that I have got this.
Whoa!
Oh, he is such a brave boy, isn't he?
See, it's not so bad.
It's just a slight fracture.
Okay, thanks.
Hey, Henry, are you doing all right?
Hey, I came as soon as I heard.
Prudence told me there was a little
bit of a kerfuffle over at E.H.S.
Oh, that's an understatement.
Thanks to Greg,
we can wave goodbye
to their educational future.
Jack.
Oh, no, no. Pru's a forgiving soul.
I think I can patch things up.
In the meantime,
I got a little something
for Hank the Tank here.
Someone to keep you company until
you're reunited with Arthur.
- What is that?
- Thanks, Papa Kev.
Papa Kev?
Yeah, old fraternity nickname.
I told Hank the Tank here he
could call me by that handle.
You're not Hank the Tank. Nobody
calls him Hank the Tank.
You want to be Papa Greg?
- No, I am Papa... I'm Greg.
- I'm Greg, his papa.
So I don't need to be Papa Greg.
I don't need to put a little
thing in front of it.
Paging Nurse Focker.
Pam, we need to talk for a minute.
Oh, okay. Mom?
Hey, Louis, what's up?
What up, dawg? Hey, hottie at 2:00.
There's the superstar!
Hey, hi, hi.
- Hey!
- Oh. Hello.
I have the raddest news ever!
Really? Okay.
So our VP of marketing
heard how well you did
on your speech last night and guess what?
What?
He wants us to lead the Pfosten
convention in Maui next month.
Yeah, that sounds great.
Honestly, I'm sorry.
I'm just a little distracted right now
because my son just broke his arm and...
Oh, poor baby.
Yeah, so...
You're a super dad.
- No, I'm not a super dad.
- It is so cute
how involved you are with your kids.
No, no, no, that's just what dads do.
It's not like a super...
Louis! What are you doing?
Is this the book?
What is... No, go. Come on.
In the back, right? I got them.
Sorry, it's just...
Somebody's grumpy.
I'm going to make this brief, Pam-cake.
I'm not getting any younger.
Dad. No, I want to make sure
there's someone around besides me
who you can fully count on.
I couldn't help but notice
how you and Kevin
have reconnected these past few days.
He's financially secure.
He's great with the twins.
Got a heart of gold.
He's a little goofy,
maybe, in his dressing,
but if that body art is any indication,
I'd say he's certainly open to the idea.
What idea?
The idea of a simple course correction.
A course correction.
Greg, Kevin.
Come on, grumpy daddy!
Come to Hawaii.
Okay.
Okay, grumpy daddy will think about it.
- Yes!
- Okay, okay.
Oh! Hey, honey, hi!
Perfect. Pam, this is Andi.
Andi, this is Pam, my wife.
Hey.
Hi, it's a... It's a pleasure to meet you.
It's a pleasure to meet you, too.
Your husband is a freaking rock star,
but I'm sure you know how lucky you are.
- Yeah.
- I'm not. She's the rock star.
She's a rock star mom and just
full-on, rocking person.
Oh.
And I'm just a groupie
trying to, you know, carry her amps.
No, you're... You're... You're the man.
Everything all right here?
Yeah, Jack, everything's all right.
- Pam, do you want to...
- Oh, my God.
You must be the famous Jack Byrnes.
Wow. I have heard so much about you.
I've heard very little
about you, Miss Garcia.
But I do admire your
cheerleading photographs.
Henry's doing much better.
We were just singing
an ancient Yanomamo song
about a brave warrior who falls from a tree
while hunting for chimpanzee meat.
He's good. Yeah.
- Hi.
Andi Garcia. Pfosten Pharmaceuticals.
And you're Doctor...
No. He's not a doctor.
Not in the Western sense of the word.
Not in any sense of the word.
You're an investment banker.
Many hats. Kevin.
Hi.
Okay, cool.
Well, I'm going to mosey on out of here.
All right.
Wow, you told me she sold
boner medicine, Greg.
You didn't tell me she is boner medicine.
Pam, that's ridiculous.
You also said you wouldn't pick her out
of a lineup, too.
Wouldn't pick her out of a lineup?
Greg, that woman is stunning!
Oh, he's covering, Kevin,
Because he didn't want
Pam to get suspicious.
Dad. Did you see the way his carotid artery
throbbed when he looked at her?
- Dad.
- Give me a break, Jack. Come on.
Now this is what I'm talking about, Pam.
I'm sorry, but this man cannot be trusted.
Could you for once in your life
stay out of my marriage?
Greg, come on, don't get hysterical.
I'm not getting hysterical.
He's getting hysterical.
Look, it's natural
to get a little tempted.
Nobody's tempted, nobody's...
Look, even our dear friend, the Buddha,
had to pass through some sorrow
on his way to enlightenment.
Our dear friend, the Buddha?
How's he doing? It's been so long.
Do you ever listen to yourself?
I try not to.
I speak from the heart, off the cuff,
like my man, JC,
at the Sermon on the Mount.
I think that's what you've
always admired about me.
Well, I got news for you.
You're not Jesus.
Well, he may not be Jesus,
but he's a far better choice for
Pam than you are, Greg.
Dad!
- I'm sorry.
- Would you stop
- ...with the course-correction stuff?
- No, that's right...
- What's the course-correction stuff?
- It's nothing.
I want to hear all about it, Jack.
You're leading this family
onto rocky shoals, Focker,
and as captain of the ship,
I'm steering us away to safety.
Well, you know what?
You're not a ship's captain, Jack.
We're people. We're not on a boat,
we're in a hospital. Okay?
We're human beings in a hospital
and you're not the captain.
Well, I may not be the captain,
Gregory Focker,
but you're not the Godfocker!
Good. Because I don't want to
be the stupid Godfocker.
I'm the Greg Focker, Jack!
All right? I am Greg Focker!
And by the way, Dr. Bob told me you
offered him the job first.
Nice to know I was your sloppy seconds.
You spoke to Dr. Bob?
Yeah, I did, Jack.
Had beers with him last night.
He's in town for a convention.
That's it. You're done.
- You're done, it's over, that's it.
- You know what?
You can't tell me I'm done
because I already quit.
You're done. I'm getting off the wheel.
- What wheel?
- The wheel!
The little hamster wheel
that we're all running up
to get a little taste
of your little water thingy!
Just, please, approval! Approval!
What the hell are you doing?
Please! Give me some of the Jack... Yeah.
It's like a metaphor for your approval...
Thank you for clearing that up!
What are you even doing here, Kevin?
I'm trying to help. Why don't you get on
your stupid monster yacht
with your bubble-butt Russian girlfriend
and do Jell-O shots
off of Deepak Chopra's butt?
Greg, don't drag Deepak
into this. Please, Greg.
Hey, Dina. Jack had a heart attack two weeks ago.
- Adios, folks!
Going down.
Hey.
- Hey.
- You okay?
Yeah.
Need a ride?
Hey, it's Pam. Leave me a message.
Hey, I'm going to sleep over
at the new house tonight, all right?
I just can't deal with your dad right now.
Are you sure you're going to be okay?
Yeah, I think I just need to clear
my head. Thanks for the ride.
No problem.
Why am I the bad guy here? Greg was
the one who was being dishonest.
Oh, please. All Greg did was
downplay that woman's looks,
so Pam wouldn't be jealous, and you know it.
You know you did the same thing
with that gorgeous double agent in Helsinki
during the Cold War.
Oh, you're still bringing up
Aatukka Kokkonen.
I told you her beauty
was privileged information.
It was a matter of national security.
Oh, yes. Like your heart condition?
Listen, Jack.
Greg cares about his family
just as much as you care
about yours. All right?
Pam?
Don't be mad. I totally
don't want to harass you.
You just seemed so sad,
I had to bring you some treats.
Oh. Wow, thanks.
Some Chinese food. Little wine.
No offense,
but does Pam even realize how dope you are?
Oh, yeah, no.
I think she thinks I'm dope.
It's just, you know,
it just changes when you have kids,
you know, because everything becomes
focused around them.
Totally. And I'm sure you're like,
"Hello! Can I have some fun, too?"
Yeah, no. I mean, it's fun, but
it's just a different kind of fun.
More wine.
It's not like old single fun,
where you go out.
It's more like wake up in the morning
at 6:00, make the kids breakfast.
You know, that kind of fun.
I love it. I mean, they're so cute.
Like, the other day, Henry came in
and he had his little top hat on and said,
"I'm the mayor of the kitchen."
Oh, he's going to be the mayor?
Just out of nowhere he got this
idea he wanted to be the mayor.
And then he came in and he said,
"And here is a proclamation.
You cannot use the 'frigerator."
And he had a sash on.
I think I have a picture of it.
Yeah. I mean, I'm biased,
but he's very creative.
I'm going to step out for a bit
and get some milk for the morning.
Don't, Jack. We both know that's not true.
I don't know why I still think
I can get anything by you.
Mmm.
I'm going to find Greg.
I'm going to bring him home.
You know where he is?
I have an idea.
And for the record, nothing ever
happened with Aatukka Kokkonen.
Aw.
And this is the play that
she wrote called Tropical Seas.
They're so cute.
Yeah. They really are.
That's you!
Yes. I am an algae-seaweed-type plant.
You know, I got to go home.
Yeah, I totally get that.
Andi, Andi, no, no, no.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Andi, I think I gave you the wrong idea.
No...
Greg, ever since we tag-teamed
on that enema,
I've wanted you.
It was just an enema. Really, I think
you're idealizing the enema.
Andi, you know what, I think you might
have had a little too much wine.
Wine is fine, papi! I took a few Sustengo.
You took a Sustengo? Why would you do that?
That's crazy. I'm going to call a cab.
Can I see more pictures of your kids?
Definitely not. You can't...
You got to put your thing back on.
Don't be a grumpy daddy!
I'm not being a grumpy... You got to...
No, Andi! Andi, give me the phone!
- You want it?
- I do want it.
- Come and get it.
- I want... I...
Andi, it's not funny.
Let's go swimming!
Andi, no, it's not a pool.
Is it heated? Is there a grotto?
No, no, it's a pit! Andi, don't do this.
Come on!
Put your clothes back on. All right?
Andi, no! That's not nice!
You don't throw people's phones
in pits, okay?
You're mean!
Andi, put the clothes back on! Come on!
I hate you!
Belly flop!
You really don't know where Greg is?
Honey, I struck out.
I guess my skills just aren't
what they used to be.
Look who it is. There they are!
Hey, Kevin!
Kevin. Quite a shindig.
Well, you only turn five once.
Or twice, in this case.
- Now, I've got a surprise for you, Jack.
- Gustavo?
Is that who I think it is?
You'd better believe it.
Jinxy!
When I heard about your health
issues last night,
I knew I had to fly him out here.
Kevin, incredibly thoughtful of you.
Thank you.
How come Daddy's not here?
Is it because I was mean to him?
No, honey, absolutely not, sweetheart.
It's because Grandpa was mean to him.
- But he's coming! He's coming.
- He will be here, okay?
So, let's go have some more fun.
All right? Let's go.
Let's go see what else there is.
Just wait one sec!
Gay!
Gay?
- Dad.
- What's that hole?
Why are you so muddy? Where is everyone?
They're at Kevin's.
The party's over at Kevin's.
I got to get over there.
- The kids' party's at Kevin's?
- I thought you were in Spain.
I was, but I can't miss my
little gazugas turning five.
How are you?
Hey! Oh, man. I'm so sorry.
I was so messed up last night.
Who's that?
That is... Dad, that's Andi Garcia.
- Oh.
- She's a work colleague of mine.
Oh, hi, Dad!
Yeah. She took a few too many
prescription pills
and then she pushed me in the pit.
Total party foul. My bad on that one.
Garcia? Is that Spanish?
Okay, we got to go.
Yeah. My grandparents are from Seville.
Are you kidding? I was just in Seville,
mastering the flamenco!
- No way!
- Dad.
- What?
- But I got to show her a few moves.
Her grandparents are from Seville.
- Dad, no, no! Dad, I got to go!
- Okay.
Ole!
Your dad's really good.
The faster you go indicates
an increase in sexual prowess.
Andi, good luck.
It's a good thing you pulled me away.
I was starting to get a semi.
- Oh, Dad, please.
- It's involuntary.
It's the parasympathetic nervous
system. Flamenco's very sexual.
Well, just so you know,
nothing happened with her.
I know that. We're Fockers.
That's not the way we roll.
But I know something went down
with the family.You okay?
Yeah, just the usual Jack stuff. You okay?
Your mom was right.
Man-opause. Makes me act like a lunatic.
You know, I get a little nutty.
Grandma Roz! Grandma Roz!
My God.
There she is! My little scrunchie-munchie.
Let me look at you, baby.
Oh, you look so cute. Do you
mind if we sit down, honey?
Have a little chat.
Because Grandma's feet hurt.
So, I hear you're not speaking
to your father.
Is that true?
Well, let me tell you something
about men, Samantha.
They... They... They're told to
be tough and hard, you know?
But inside, they're quite soft and gooey.
Kind of like a cannoli.
A knish? It's not exactly that.
It's more like peanut butter
and jelly inside burnt toast.
And once you know that, you
can cut them a little slack.
Besides, you'll have plenty of time
to aggravate him in your teens.
Grandma!
Hi, honey! Look at you, how big you got!
Hi, sweetheart.
Come here and give me a Focker
sandwich. Okay, I'm the cheese.
- We're cheese!
- I'm the cheese.
No, I'm the cheese and you're the bread.
We're sourdough.
Attention! Attention!
Henry and Samantha! Today you are five!
- This way.
- Okay, thank you.
Dad.
- Yeah.
- You coming?
Yeah. I just want to practice the dance
I'm going to surprise your mother with.
Go ahead.
Okay. I'll see you down there.
Gay?
My two cents. The way to deal with Jack,
no matter what he does,
just smother that guy with kisses.
He'll be putty in your hands.
Good.
- Love, love, love.
- Good, putty, thank you.
- Oh, Gay.
- Yes.
You look good.
Thank you.
All right.
- Can you do me a favor?
- Okay.
Can you just put this leg down
slowly? It's an old sex injury.
- Like this?
- Yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
This performance is my gift to you!
You are the chosen ones!
Pam.
- Pam!
- Greg.
I pronounce this your day!
Oh, what happened to you?
Oh, it's... I...
I'll tell you about it later, okay?
Look, I'm really sorry about what happened.
- I just...
- I'm sorry, too.
I let everything get out of
control and I shouldn't have.
It's just... It's just your dad.
- You know, I...
- I know. He's insane.
Yes. Yes.
Listen to me.
We've got our own thing and it works.
It does, right?
Yeah, we actually kind of know
what we're doing.
- I love you.
- Hey, Sam!
- Happy birthday.
Look, I know you don't want to talk to me.
I just want you to know that's okay.
I love you anyway.
I know, Daddy.
Dad!
There he is!
Hey, happy birthday, man!
Hey, look,
I think you left something at home.
Arthur!
- Yeah.
- Thanks, Dad.
It's so beautiful.
Oh, my God.
Oh, gosh.
I'm all right.
Gustavo! Birthday cake! Birthday
cake! Try the birthday cake.
There's 36 different kinds!
Kevin?
Rosalind.
What a mitzvah that you could
make it to the party.
What's wrong, honey?
I wish I knew.
Come. Sit down.
Look over this way a little bit.
And a little up. Up.
Hey, Jack.
Wow, that's great.
That's a great likeness.
That's really...
It really captured the intensity
and looks just like you.
All right.
So, look, last night,
I think we both said some things we regret.
Maybe I shouldn't have said
anything about Dr. Bob.
But then you did that whole
course-correction thing. So...
Anyway, "peace" of cake offering.
What the hell?
Oh, shit.
Jack, you all right? Jack, I'm sorry.
Jack, you okay?
Okay, Focker. At least you're going
to make this a little fun.
Jack. Let's not do this. Come on.
We've had this date
since the beginning, Greg.
All right. Let's dance.
Come on, man.
Jack?
Where are you? Jack!
Get out of the ball pit! Get out of
the ball pit! Get out!
Let's go.
Get out! Get out of the ball pit!
Get out!
Jack?
I saw you last night with Andi Garcia!
Nothing happened!
I've been in the wild for so long,
that maybe it's time to come home.
But then where is home?
Honey, home is inside of you.
What you have been seeking out
there is right in here.
- In your heart?
- No, in your heart.
In my heart.
Yes, yes, Kevin.
Suck it!
Arthur? Arthur? Mom! Arthur's missing!
Jack! Nothing happened.
What'd you say? Jack, nothing happened.
I'm telling you the truth.
Oh, shit.
Jinxy! Jinxy! Bad cat! Bad cat!
Jinx! Bad cat!
Jinx!
Jinx! Jinx!
Oh, shit.
Kevin, you are a lovely young man
with a number of unusual
fixations and hobbies.
Thank you.
I know you're going to find your way.
Trust me, honey. Because you
have the strength of a lion
and the soul of a poet.
Roz?
Bernie? What are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
The guy has issues, honey.
Bernard, I swear this isn't
what it looks like.
Your wife was comforting me
in a moment of distress
and my soul just reached out to her.
Your soul or your tongue?
No. There was no tongue involved.
There was a little.
Thank you for your honesty.
I thought you were in Spain, honey.
What happened?
I went half way around the world
to master the flamenco,
but there was one thing missing,
my dance partner.
Oh, Bernie.
You're my true north.
I know as long as we're together,
I'll never get lost.
Oh, what a beautiful line.
Come here, baby.
That's beautiful. So raw, this electricity...
Will you get out of here
so I can shtup my wife?
Shtup her? Yeah, sure.
Jinx!
Grandpa! Grandpa! What's wrong?
Jack?
- Jack.
Jack.
Honey. Greg, do something.
Okay. Having some chest pain? Yeah.
All right. Just relax.
I'm going to check you out.
What's wrong with Grandpa?
He's going to be fine, honey.
Okay, I'm here. Okay.
Jack, you have your nitro tabs with you?
Greg, he's not responding to my treatment.
Really? To you waving your hands over
him? He's not a Ouija board, Kevin.
Pam? Call 911.
Okay.
Kevin, can you go up to the house,
see if you have some aspirin?
Aspirin.
It's all right.
Jinx!
Arthur! Wow.
Thanks, Dad.
Just relax, Jack. It's going to be okay.
Breathe, breathe.
I promise.
Is he taking any other medications?
Just the 324 milligrams of aspirin
I gave him about 15 minutes ago.
Thank you, nurse. You did good.
We'll take it from here.
By the way, how'd you guys come by
all these bruises and lacerations?
Oh, it's a long story.
We were in the bouncy castle,
and then he tripped, and...
I get it. My father-in-law tripped
through a plate glass window
at my wedding last year.
All right. Let's get him loaded up.
Don't worry.
We'll take care of your husband.
We're going to follow behind
you in the car. All right?
Greg.
I know you were telling the truth
about Andi, Greg.
- Really?
- Yeah.
The pulse on your carotid
artery remained steady
as you pleaded your innocence.
Right, of course.
- And, Greg.
- Yeah.
It was never going to be Dr. Bob.
It was you.
It was always you.
You just relax and stay quiet, Mr. Byrnes.
I'll see you over there. Okay?
...Focker.
Why is he cursing at us?
Hey, we are trying to help you, sir.
What? What?
You're the Greg Focker.
I'm sorry, what?
You're the... You're the Greg Focker.
I'm the Greg Focker.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Let's get him up.
One more. I need more. I need more.
One more, one more.
No, I need more.
- Another present.
- Here.
Best Chistmakkah ever.
This is a very special gift, guys.
One more, cool!
What is it, Grandpa Bernie?
I've had it with me my entire life.
It's my own original whoopee cushion.
- What does it do?
- Are you kidding me?
Jack, lift up your leg.
Jack, come on.
Disgusting!
It farts!
Jack, we have to laugh at the
stuff that makes us human, right?
Gas, burps. Picking noses?
You kids want to pick your nose and
flick your boogers, do it.
Hey, Bernie.
But do it only when it's dry.
Don't do a wet one.
I have something for Jack.
Take that to your room.
It's what makes life, life!
I know. I know. Here, Jack,
this is a little something
from Bernie and me to you.
Oh, how thoughtful. Thank you.
It is a very thoughtful gift.
It was your idea.
I know.
- What's this?
- What is that?
That is your own personal yarmulke!
Jack.
One of those little Jewish hats.
Cute.
We know that you're into
that genealogy stuff.
So, when I was nursing you back to health,
I took the opportunity,
when you were taking a nap,
of snipping a couple of your pubes
and I sent it to one of
those DNA testing sites.
You did what?
We thought it'd be fun to trace
your lineage all the way back.
- Yes.
- And it turns out, Jack T. Byrnes,
that you are one twenty-third Israelite!
Welcome to the tribe, Jack!
While I dispute the findings,
I appreciate the gesture.
Thank you, Bernard, Roz.
You're welcome, Ya'akov.
Your Hebrew name. Ya'akov.
- Ya'akov.
Two A's.
Well, listen, Greg, we're in your home
and you're in charge here,
so why don't you lead us in a toast?
Right.
Honestly, Jack, I have no desire
to try and sound like I am
in any way in charge of anything
in this house.
But I do love our family very, very much.
And I'm really happy that we can
all be here together for the weekend.
Then we'll part ways and you guys will
return to your homes
in your own respective states. Cheers.
- Cheers.
Actually, sweetheart,
your dad and I have a little...
Gaylord, we're moving to Chicago.
No, we're serious. We sold Focker Isle.
We just bought the house two
doors down. Isn't that great?
- No, that's not great.
- Oh, no, if they're moving here,
- then we're moving here.
- Good!
We'll live together, one big happy family.
We should discuss this.
No. No. No. Jack,
nobody's moving because
nobody's moving. Right?
How else are the kids going to
be Fockerized if we don't live here?
No. Nobody's going to be Fockerized.
- No.
- Why not?
This Google is a wonderful tool,
Jinxy cat.
Don't tell anyone, but I'm going
to do a search on myself.
Come on. Who needs something like this?
Who's the target demo
for a drug like Sustengo?
And I got to say it's somebody
like my father-in-law.
His name is Jack Byrnes. You
know, he had a heart attack
and he called me up, he said, "Greg,
I've had a heart attack."
Now, I said, "First of all, Jack,
"don't you have to have a heart
to get one of those?"
First weekend I ever met him,
he said to me, he said,
"Hey, listen, keep your snake in its
cage for the next 72 hours."
I didn't say it like that.
All right.
Maybe somebody's had their snake
in their cage for about 30 years! Okay.
Remix. What's a remix?
You know, the guy is definitely obsessed...
Byrnes, Jack Byrnes
My father-in-law My father-in-law
Candidate for the drug Obsessed with sex
Byrnes, Jack Byrnes
Not getting it up
Jack, Jack Byrnes
Talk about sexual frustration
Byrnes
Obsessed with boobs He can breast
feed his grandson
Jack Byrnes
Mannary gland Couple of tugs off
the thing himself
Hey, Focker
I never did that.
Hey, Focker, I got nipples Okay
Hey, Focker, I got nipples Wow
Can you milk me?
Circle of trust goes round and round
Jack Circle of trust goes round and round
Byrnes Circle of trust goes round and round
Jack
Hello!
Hot little number he's got named Jinxy
Now, he's talking about you.
Jinxy cat, Jinxy cat I love you
The Godfocker.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org