Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ Everyone knows I'm right
about one thing ♪
♪ You and I don't work out ♪
♪ You bring out the mean in me ♪
♪ I bring out your insecurities ♪
♪ You know what I am talking about ♪
What?
Nothing.
Alexa, play "Old MacDonald."
♪ Old MacDonald had a farm ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
- ♪ And on his farm he had some ducks ♪
- Trixie!
♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ With a quack quack here ♪
- ♪ And a quack quack there ♪
- Trixie, I'm not kidding.
♪ Here a quack, there a quack,
everywhere a quack quack ♪
- ♪ Old MacDonald had a farm ♪
- Hey. - Hey.
Turn it off.
♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ And on his farm he had some cows ♪
- I'm so, so sorry I'm late, Mr. Van Allen.
- ♪ With a moo moo here... ♪
It's okay. Melinda's…
It's okay, Melinda's still getting ready.
♪ Old MacDonald had a farm ♪
- ♪ E-I-E-I-O. ♪
- Alexa, stop!
Don't play that shit ever again, please.
Vic, can you come here?
What?
I need your help.
Alexa, play "Old MacDonald" again.
♪ Old MacDonald had a farm ♪
Trixie, you're going to drive
your mom crazy, you know that?
I know.
♪ And on his farm he had some ducks ♪
- ♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
- Have a seat.
- ♪ With a quack quack here ♪
- Hey, Trixie.
♪ And a quack quack there,
here a quack… ♪
Don't look at the mess. Look at me.
Yes.
I don't know, I just...
Should I wear this or this?
Um…
No? You don't like either?
No, I'm just thinking.
Hmm?
I think you look beautiful
in the dress you have on.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
With what shoe?
The black shoes I got you in New York.
Okay.
Go get them.
Please.
Sure.
Do you know I love you?
Come on.
Let's go.
♪ Sneakin' Sally through the alley ♪
- ♪ Trying to keep her out of sight ♪
- Enjoy.
♪ Sneakin' Sally through the alley... ♪
We asked her
and she chose public school.
- You let her choose?
- Mm-hmm.
- She's six.
- I was kicked out
of so many schools growing up,
I'm just grateful she wants an education.
- You aren't worried about competition for college?
- College?
The kid's brilliant. The worst thing
we could do is send her to college.
Joel.
So, uh, how you doing tonight?
Hmm?
No, I was just asking
how you're doing tonight.
I'll let you know
after a few more of these.
♪ Oh, when up pops the queen ♪
♪ Trying to double talk,
get myself in trouble talk ♪
♪ Catching myself in lies ♪
♪ Catch myself in lies ♪
♪ Mama just looked at me
as if I was, ah, crazy... ♪
♪ I woke up this mornin',
lookin' round for my shoes, yeah ♪
♪ You know that I have
them old walkin' blues... ♪
Whoo.
♪ He got Elgin movement
from his head down to his toes ♪
♪ I bet he can make himself a dollar
anywhere he goes ♪
♪ He got the Elgin movement... ♪
Yo.
Yo. How's it going?
I'm getting a lot
of cleavage action tonight.
Hmm. I see that.
Is that Joel with Melinda?
Yeah.
They've really hit it off
in a short amount of time, haven't they?
I guess they have.
Hello, Mr. Boring.
Why don't you dance?
I'd hate to ruin your evening.
You know he's only here because she asked
Jess and Grant to invite him here.
She can invite whoever she wants.
Vic...
they fucking?
- Should we ask them?
- Vic.
They're friends.
Aren't they just.
- I'm gonna just blurt it out, okay?
- Okay.
A few of us are concerned.
- You're concerned?
- Yes.
That they're fucking?
What if your concerns aren't my concerns?
Look, you adore her and everyone knows it.
- I love her.
- She loves you, too.
You're good, Vic.
We just don't want you out here
looking foolish.
I'll stay off the dance floor.
Vic. Hey.
I'm sorry to interrupt, Mary, my bad,
but, uh, Melinda's drunk
and she's standing on top of my piano.
- That concerns me.
- Yeah.
Whoo.
I like dancing though.
You could dance if you want.
Ya, ya, ya. Okay, okay.
I-I don't know how to give toasts,
so I'm going to climb down from this piano
and how about if I play a song.
Yeah?
My husband's good at giving toasts.
Yeah, Vic!
Okay.
Oh.
♪ It's wonderful, it's wonderful ♪
♪ It's wonderful ♪
♪ Good luck, my baby ♪
♪ It's wonderful, it's wonderful ♪
♪ It's wonderful ♪
♪ I dream of you ♪
♪ Chips, chips ♪
♪ Doo, doo, doo-doo-doo,
ci-boom, ci-boom, boom ♪
♪ Doo, doo, doo-doo-doo ♪
♪ Ci-boom, ci-boom, boom ♪
♪ Doo, doo, doo-doo-doo. ♪
♪ Chips, chips ♪
Whoo!
♪ Doo, doo, doo-doo-doo ♪
♪ Ci-boom, ci-boom, boom. ♪
Yes!
- Thanks so much.
- No problem.
Good to see you, Vic.
Hey, uh, two of those St-Germains
with the champagne drink things.
Got you right there, boss.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
How you doin', Vic?
I'm fine. How are you?
Eh, hangin' in there, bro.
I just want to tell you two things, okay?
Okay.
I really want to repay you
for your abundant hospitality,
you and your wife,
as, you know, a stranger to the area.
Sure.
You've both been really cool.
Really cool.
The second?
Huh?
- The second thing you wanted to...
- Oh, man.
I wanted to say, you're a brick
for how nice you are
about me seeing your wife.
Seeing my wife.
It's good to have a friend.
I mean, it's all innocent, of course,
you know,
but some guys, some husbands,
- they get a little…
- Yeah, jealous.
- Yeah.
Have you been around here long enough
where you've heard the name Martin McRae?
Uh, the guy…
yeah, the guy who's gone missing.
He saw a lot of my wife.
What does that mean?
He started seeing a lot of my wife.
You suggesting…?
They were friends.
You want me to believe
you did something to Martin McRae?
I killed him.
Does Melinda know?
Oh, God, no.
She'd be horrified.
All right, bro,
considering he was a friend of yours,
I don't think it's very funny
to joke about...
He wasn't a friend of mine.
A friend of your wife's.
Well...
that's obviously something different,
isn't it?
Are you, like, threatening me?
Do you feel threatened?
I don't believe you.
Then don't.
I'll be right back.
Joel?
I'm going home.
- What?
- I'll call you tomorrow.
What happened?
♪ But I'm not the guy you're taking home ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I keep dancing on my own ♪
♪ I keep dancing on... ♪
What did you say to Joel?
Nothing.
You must've said something.
No.
I didn't say anything.
Well, I saw you talking.
What were you talking about?
Bedbugs, maybe? No, that was Mary.
You're so weird.
Would you like to get in the car?
You must've said something...
'cause he was different
after he talked to you.
I promise you, I didn't.
I don't believe you.
So, uh...
- five hours, right?
- Yeah.
- That's a hundred.
- Mm-hmm.
- Venmo. I-I'll give you 200. How's that?
- Oh, sure.
Melinda, what are you doing?
- I'm gonna make coffee.
- I'll make you coffee.
Go to bed. You're drunk.
- I can do it.
- No, it's fine. I...
Melinda… you're naked.
What are you doing?
- What?
- The babysitter's standing right there.
The babysitter.
So what?
- It's not appropriate.
- Jesus Christ.
America is so suffocating.
Sorry about that.
- My wife's... a whole nother culture.
- Yeah, it's okay.
Thank you.
I wish you'd pick someone
with some more brains.
Is that what interests you in a woman?
Her intelligence?
That's one of the things, yes.
Is that why you picked me?
For my brains?
You're very smart, Melinda.
Yeah.
Not in a way you respect.
Joel might be dumb,
but me makes me enjoy who I am.
And that turns me on.
Vic.
Close the door on your way out.
Thank you.
Stick with it, Trix.
Did you know I had it on there wrong?
Were you going to tell me?
I didn't need to tell you, did I?
In no time, you'll be like your dad,
building bombs.
Hmm.
Dad doesn't build bombs.
He made a computer chip.
♪ You've got a cute way of talking ♪
♪ You've got the better of me ♪
♪ Just hold me tight ♪
♪ And leave on the light ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't wanna go home ♪
♪ You've put a spell on me ♪
♪ I'm right where you want me to be ♪
♪ You make me feel like dancing... ♪
So, you have music today, right?
Yes.
- Does that mean violin?
- Yes.
- Will that be fun?
Okay.
Have a good day. I love you!
Love you!
Your mom is gonna get you
after school, all right?
I'm coming!
Vic!
What?
You're running around murdering people
and you don't call me
to help cover up the crime scene?
- It was a joke.
- Yeah.
I should fucking hope so.
How'd you hear about it?
I've heard about it
from so many people now,
I honest to God don't remember
who told me first.
Jesus Christ.
But, boy, did it work.
- Thanks.
- I don't think I would
kill somebody for sleeping with my wife.
Who says they slept together?
Vic, I don't mean to be
the bearer of bad news, but...
it's pretty obvious.
Isn't that why you threatened him?
I didn't threaten anybody.
Okay, look, man, I-I don't know, man.
Look, coming from somebody
who loves and respects you,
you gotta reign Melinda in, man.
Like, this isn't the first time.
The fact she's comfortable, like,
flaunting all these relationships
around in front of us,
is fucked up.
Yes, she's a fucked up person.
I knew it. I knew it since the moment
I saw Joel leave
that you had done something disgusting
'cause you're a fucking snake.
It was stupid.
Fucking stupid.
And Martin was my friend...
and I miss him.
That is…
That's not something you joke about.
It was a bad idea and I knew it
right when it came out of my mouth.
- You...
- I'm really sorry.
You are not just going to apologize to me.
You're going to apologize to Joel.
I already spoke to him.
He's leaving on Saturday,
so I invited him over for dinner
on Friday.
Joel, good to see you.
Dinner's almost ready.
Melinda wanted to cook,
but, uh, Trixie banned her from the stove
for two weeks.
It's a long story.
Is Melinda here?
Melinda? No.
Just you and me.
Why, is that awkward?
I'm just fucking with you.
Yeah, come on in.
So, uh, come on in.
Get you a drink?
Vodka soda?
- Uh, yeah.
- Make yourself at home.
Have a seat.
Thanks.
Who's that?
That is Joel Dash.
He's a friend of your mom's.
Kind of like Martin McRae.
Remember him?
Dry your hands and take this out to Joel.
Thank you.
No lime, right?
Uh, no lime for me, thanks.
Thank you.
So, you're leaving tomorrow?
Uh, yeah.
You know, I got a job in New Mexico.
It's a good one.
Pays well.
Pretty exciting.
Sounds it.
Well, Last Supper it is.
Making an old family recipe,
lobster bisque.
Hint of tang, not too creamy.
I think you're gonna love it.
I'm actually allergic to shellfish.
What?
- Yeah, I can't eat it.
- You're kidding me.
All… any shellfish?
No.
I've always wanted to visit New Mexico.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm going to be working
in Albuquerque,
- which is a little bit different from Santa Fe.
- Hmm.
Santa Fe is probably
more charming, I think.
I definitely want to visit Santa Fe
'cause I heard the same thing,
it's beautiful.
Yeah.
Well, maybe we'll come visit.
Uh, yeah, I mean, I-I don't know
how big my place is going to be, so...
Joel, I think if we came and visited,
we'd probably stay in a hotel.
Oh, right, right.
How's the grilled cheese?
Actually, it's amazing.
- Oh, good.
- Can I have some?
- Yeah.
- A bite?
I don't like lobster bisque.
Oh, my God.
Right?
This is amazing.
Melinda kind of has the palate
of a 12-year-old.
Our first date, I took her
to the best restaurant in the city
- and she ordered mac and cheese.
- Yeah.
It's like he was ashamed to be with me.
No, I just realized you were ordering
off the children's menu
to save room for alcohol.
You see, Vic never drinks.
I drink sometimes.
Sometimes I think he's not normal.
'Cause normal people can let go.
You wish that I were normal, Melinda?
- My God, all the time.
- 'Cause if I were normal,
I don't think Joel would be over here
having dinner with us.
You don't have to be rude.
I'm not being rude.
I made lobster bisque.
Um...
If you guys don't mind,
I'm gonna run to the restroom.
Good call.
Trixie.
Baby, I think it's time for bed.
Okay.
Did you finish that, baby?
You know, your dad is gonna read you
a bunch of bedtime stories.
Wouldn't you like that?
Yeah.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Can you come give your mama a kiss?
Mmm.
Don't let him skip pages.
He can be sneaky like that.
Good night.
"Bedtime Olie is sleeping now
without a care.
The end. Zzz…"
Why is Mom so different
around other people?
You think Mom's different?
Yeah. Don't you?
I think that's just who she is.
But how can it be who she is
if she's different?
Mm, because people are strange
and grown-ups are complex.
I don't like Joel.
I know.
Go to sleep, baby shark, okay?
♪ That these feelings won't go away ♪
♪ They've been knockin' me sideways ♪
♪ They've been knockin' me out lately ♪
Come here.
♪ Whenever you come around me ♪
♪ These feelings won't go away ♪
♪ They've been knockin' me sideways ♪
♪ I keep thinking in a moment that ♪
♪ Time will take them away… ♪
Vic.
Um, you don't have to do the dishes now.
I know you're tired.
Actually, I'm wide awake.
It's okay.
I'll do them in the morning.
I'm going to get you another drink.
Uh, thanks.
♪ And flowers they bloom ♪
♪ And I'm telling you ♪
♪ I'm telling you ♪
Can you please give this to Joel?
I'm going to leave you two alone
for a bit, okay?
Ooh.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I understand why you were
acting like that.
I'm not trying to imasculine...
Re… remasculate you.
What?
I mean, don't you want to apologize?
Why would I do that?
Because you said you killed Martin McRae.
I can't apologize for that, Joel.
I did kill Martin McRae.
I hit him with a hammer.
Oh.
Look at that.
Your Uber's here.
I didn't order one.
I did.
Let's go.
♪ Oh, baby, what's that I hear? ♪
So, you're a writer. What do you write?
Uh, short stories mostly,
but, uh, screenplays as well.
- Oh.
- You write movies?
Well, I've sold a couple of scripts,
one that may actually get made.
Hollywood, you know,
they develop stuff for years and years.
What's it about?
Myself, mainly.
It's a movie about you?
Yeah, it's loosely based on me.
It's about a writer.
Uh, you know, a young guy,
uh, writes noir fiction
and, uh, he uncovers
a vast conspiracy in his town.
Uh, it… I think it's interesting.
It's got a fresh tone.
So, uh, what do you do?
Uh, not much.
A lot of, you know, small things.
I, uh, build web apps.
Thank you.
Publish a magazine of poetry
and photography,
and, you know.
Most of the time I just ride my mountain
bike and hang out with our daughter.
You get paid to ride around
on your mountain bike?
I wish.
I retired.
Oh, wow.
From what?
He built the chip for drones that
help them find the people they blow up.
Right?
Wow.
Drone warfare. That's…
That's kind of a moral gray area,
isn't it?
Well, not if you're just making the chip.
Don, let's not get into politics.
Yeah, but the-the chip is used
to kill people.
Eh, sometimes used
to kill innocent people.
Or used to find starving children
and drop food off to them.
Yeah.
But they don't.
No. They don't.
Look, but the moral of the story is,
Vic is a genius and he's rich as fuck.
Vic?
Vic Van Allen?
- Yeah.
- Oh. Okay.
- Yeah, I know exactly who you are.
- Oh.
You killed Martin McRae.
- Oh, my God. It's a joke.
- Oh, come on.
It was a joke.
Really?
Funny.
Your wife is so beautiful.
Do you like to dance?
I love to dance.
Really?
Let's dance.
Okay.
You ever seen Vic dance before? Ever?
No, I didn't know he can dance.
- Did you know he could dance?
- No.
- Is that Vic dancing?
- Seriously.
Um… yes.
I didn't know he could dance.
- Oh.
- Don't be mean. He loves...
He loves dancing.
- That's so surprising.
- Yeah.
Wow, they're just gonna get dizzy.
- Oh, oh, oh. Okay.
- Oh, oh. Oh, hey.
Oh, he even gave her a dip.
Oh, boy. Oh, damn.
- I hope his knee don't give out.
- I know...
You know he got a bad knee.
You looked like you were having fun
dancing with Kelly Wilson.
Yeah. It was fun.
She's very attractive, don't you think?
Yeah, I guess so.
You want to fuck her?
That wasn't the first thing
that crossed my mind, no.
But it did cross your mind.
I mean...
like, yes, at a certain point, you think,
well, I guess I could, you know,
fuck this person.
But...
Do you think she'd be a better fuck
than me?
Ow! What was that for?
'Cause the answer was yes.
No, it wasn't.
Ow! Fuck, Melinda.
You're gonna get us killed.
Well, if you think Kelly Wilson
is a better fuck than me,
then I don't mind killing us both.
I didn't say that.
But you thought it.
Don't touch me.
- You kiss my ass.
- Yeah.
Yes.
Do you want to fuck me?
Oh, come here.
Get in there, Trix.
Go, Trixie.
Go, go, go, go.
Shit.
I'm telling you, the other team's
at least 12 years old.
They don't look 12 years old.
They fucking look 12 years old.
Stop it.
Yay, Trixie!
Hello?
Hi. Is this Mr. Van Allen?
Yeah.
This is Rick from Whitmore Bank
calling about Melinda Van Allen's account.
Yes.
There were insufficient funds to cover
the check that was issued last Thursday.
How old are you?
Okay, who was it drawn to?
To a Mr. Charles De Lisle.
What was the amount?
It was $3,000.
Does it say what it was for?
The memo line says, "Piano lessons."
Right.
It makes perfect sense.
If you add additional funds
to the account,
we can waive the $50 overdraft fee.
Thank you. I would appreciate that.
No problem, sir.
Could you spell the recipient's
last name, please?
Hi. Yeah, I'm just wondering, uh,
do you guys have live music
in the evenings, by any chance?
You don't.
All right, that's a shame.
Hi. Yeah, I'm wondering, do you guys have
live music in the evenings?
Hey, is this the Oak Tree Lounge?
Yeah, I'm calling to see if you guys
have live music.
You do.
What's his name?
♪ That's why the lady is a tramp. ♪
No.
Dad!
Chelsea's teaching me how to play poker.
Good. That'll come in handy.
In national news,
Congress has voted to allocate more funds
to the military's drone program.
The motion aims to not only
expand the program
but also to include and refine
the current targeting system.
The vote comes in the wake
of a successful strike
on an ISIS weapons storehouse
just outside of Kabul this past Thursday.
Now, opponents of the bill warned this
news will only increase tensions overseas.
And in breaking news,
police have found the body
of Martin McRae,
the 33-year-old man who went missing
from his apartment last spring.
McRae's body was found in the woods
in La Bouche Parish.
He had been shot to death.
Stay tuned for your latest in weather
coming up after the break.
How was your night?
Magnificent.
Where'd you go?
To have dinner with a new friend.
I think you're going to like him.
And then...
I don't remember what we did,
but it was really awesome.
And I think I drank a lot,
so don't be angry.
I see.
Let me help you.
Come on.
Melinda…
Sweetie, I have to tell you something.
Ooh-ooh.
What did I do?
They found Martin McRae.
He's dead.
I'm sorry.
Are you?
- Dad?
- Mm-hmm?
Can we call him Roger?
You can try.
- Look after her.
- Oh.
Ready?
Careful.
You got him? Okay?
Huh?
Thanks a lot.
Dad, I think he smells like poop.
- Dad?
- Mm-hmm?
Do you think Mom's okay?
Yeah.
She may be a little sad about her friend,
but she's okay.
What about you?
Dad?
Yeah, baby, I'm fine.
♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ With a quack quack here
and a quack quack there ♪
♪ Here a quack, there a quack,
everywhere a quack quack ♪
♪ Old MacDonald had a farm ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ And on his farm he had some cows ♪
♪ With a moo moo… ♪
I'm glad the police caught that guy.
- Yeah.
- You know,
put to rest all the talk, you know.
What talk? I didn't hear any talk.
Oh, there's definitely been talk.
Thank you.
Hey, nice work. You sound great.
That dude can play the keys.
Yeah. He's been giving Melinda lessons.
Oh, he's been giving Melinda lessons.
Yeah.
Where's Trixie?
I took her to Janey's.
Is there any coffee?
You want to tell me
why you didn't come home last night?
Not really.
You want to tell me why you cut a check
for $3,000 to Charles De Lisle?
Not really.
Okay.
You want to tell me
what the fuck you're doing?
Finally some emotion.
You're drunk.
You have no idea how unattractive it is.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, I think you're jealous.
I think you're acting like a child.
Don't you find that appealing?
No, not at all.
Then why are you waiting up all night
like a parent?
Is that what I'm doing?
What do you want to know?
Where I was?
What I did?
Because I'll tell you everything.
I'm not interested in the details,
Melinda.
Well, now you're really full of shit.
Really?
You want to know if I'm fucking him?
Ask me.
You want to know if he makes me come?
Or you want to know how I make him come?
He left a bruise.
You want to see?
We have a child. We have a family.
That was your choice.
I want you to stop seeing him.
Or what?
What?
You gonna divorce me?
No, because you're gonna listen to me.
Look how assertive you've become.
If I didn't know you, I'd think you'd
throw me on the floor and you'd fuck me.
Huh?
Yeah?
No?
Yeah, you wouldn't do that.
That requires a certain amount of passion,
like you'd actually have to love me.
I do love you!
Are you in love with him?
If you were married to anyone else,
you'd be so fucking bored
you'd kill yourself.
♪ I turn the radio on,
but the music's all the same ♪
♪ Well, I just wanna hear
the trumpet play ♪
♪ Come on, y'all ♪
Hey, lady. Damn.
Come on, let's go!
♪ Mama's in the kitchen, baby,
making lemonade ♪
- Really?
- ♪ Daddy just got home from work ♪
♪ In a suit that's tailor-made ♪
- Oh!
- ♪ I turn the radio on ♪
♪ But the music's all the same... ♪
No!
Hey!
You're not...
You're not winning.
Go!
Oh, come on!
Ah!
Jen, can you turn the music off?
Hey, everyone, come here.
Come here. Come here.
Um, I want to introduce you
to a friend of mine, Charlie De Lisle,
- who's very happy to be here.
- Right on.
- And he'd like to play a song.
- Oh.
Right?
- I'm not playing a song. I'm not.
- Come on.
Come on.
Yeah, I promise, he's amazing.
And he's my teacher.
- I am.
- Okay.
Uh, ladies and gentlemen,
this is just a little something.
Charlie!
Jen!
Jesus.
- Stop.
- Shh.
Charlie's playing.
- Pardon me.
- Vic.
I want to introduce you
to my friend Charlie.
Hi. Yeah, I'm Charlie.
It's-it's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
- Thanks for giving my wife piano lessons.
- Yeah, no, of course.
I mean, she's a real natural, so it's, uh,
you know, it's my pleasure.
Have we met before?
I don't think so.
I think you'd both remember.
- Well, pleasure.
- Yeah.
Yeah, have a nice night, man.
Nice to meet you.
Vic. Hey.
Mary.
Have you seen Melinda?
I think she's upstairs.
Go, go.
Melinda!
Come in! It's raining!
I'm making cookies!
Can you come help me, please?
Sure.
Hey, Vic.
Is it raining?
Yeah.
I must be high as fuck
'cause it is raining.
I'm getting out.
♪ 25 pounds of tenderness ♪
♪ In each and every touch ♪
Time to pass the cookies.
♪ 25 pounds of understanding my man ♪
♪ And I don't want to worry too much... ♪
- Hello.
- How are you?
- You… hey.
- I'm sorry.
- You know I want this. Okay.
- Yeah, okay, okay.
♪ That I can't even name ♪
- ♪ And it all adds up ♪
- Salud.
Looks good. Can I have one?
Ow! Sh…!
Fucking dumbass.
I told you.
Dumbass. A hot cookie.
What happened?
He got greedy.
I'm fine.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm...
Look who it is. Hello.
Where have you two been?
Uh...
None of your business.
Ah, get away from me.
All right, it's time to change it up.
- Magic, action.
- Hold up. One, two.
Oh, come on, man.
♪ Hey, ho ♪
- ♪ Hey, ho ♪
- Yeah.
♪ Hey, ho ♪
♪ You drew a picture of my morning... ♪
I was so surprised to see you
dancing with Kelly.
Why?
I just didn't know you could.
I can't. I just like to.
Now… Oh, shit.
Fuck.
Man, what's wrong with you?
Maybe next time you get the itch,
you should ask me.
Get his head up!
- Here you go.
- I got him. - Get his legs.
Get his legs!
Call 911.
I know CPR.
- Okay, lay him flat on his back.
- Call 911, goddamn it.
- Who knows CPR?
- You gotta get him on the...
on the flat surface. Look out.
We gotta get him on the patio.
I'll lift him.
Okay. Get him up. One, two, three.
Fuck, he's heavy.
The fuck is the matter with you?
I know CPR.
Look out.
Please do something.
Please do something!
- What the fuck!
- Is somebody calling?
Oh, fuck, is he breathing?
I don't think he's breathing.
You gotta clear his airway.
Come on, guys.
Okay. You gotta clear his airway.
- Oh, fuck.
- You're not doing it right.
You're not doing it right.
- Vic!
- Here, let me do it.
Goddamn it, you're not even trying!
- Come on, Melinda.
- You're not! You're not even trying!
Melinda.
- Stop it, Melinda.
- Stop fucking telling me...
- Melinda, calm down!
- God… goddamn it!
Oh, oh.
Come on, let's get you
some Kleenex and some ice.
Come on inside.
Come on, let's go inside.
Fuck.
He have a lot to drink?
- Yeah, he was pretty drunk.
- Yeah.
Yeah?
Who saw him get in the pool?
Well, we were in the kitchen,
and there were people in...
- Yeah, yeah, we were the last two in the pool.
- Yeah.
About how long were you out of the pool?
- Uh…
- Not long.
Time it takes to make cookies.
Hmm.
Was there marijuana involved?
Yes, but I-I have a card.
That's not important.
We're just trying to figure out
what happened.
Vic killed him.
What?
- Ah, come on, man.
- Melinda, come on.
- Jesus.
- Huh?
You killed him.
- Melinda…
- Didn't you?
- Melinda. - Stop it.
- Okay, nah.
- Didn't you?
- Melinda, calm down.
You probably hit him over the head
and drowned him.
Okay, yeah, it's really...
My wife's upset.
I'm not fucking upset!
You fucking killed him!
- Whoa, oh.
- Mrs. Van Allen,
would you like to speak privately?
Get an account from the rest of them.
Goddamn it...
Who pulled him out?
- We all did. - We all did.
- We all pulled him out.
Vic and I did CPR.
But, um...
Charlie got banged
against the edge of the pool,
um, but Don was lifting him.
That didn't affect the death.
Didn't help.
And how long did you attempt
to revive him, Mr. Van Allen?
As long as we had any hope
he was still alive.
- We alternated.
- Hmm.
He was dead in the pool.
- Mr. Van Allen.
- Yeah.
- Would you follow me in here, please?
- Sure.
I'd like to talk to Chief Nichols, too,
please, privately.
Was your wife sleeping with Mr. De Lisle?
I don't know.
I don't ask her those type of questions.
Well, that's strange. Why is that?
'Cause I don't feel the need
to dictate her choices.
I accept her and love her for who she is.
Well, she's currently
accusing you of murder.
I didn't say she was always rational.
Hmm.
Did you kill Mr. De Lisle?
No.
When Grant and I went inside,
it was raining quite heavily.
Mr. De Lisle was clinging
to the deep end of the pool.
I didn't get the sense
he was a very strong swimmer.
Grant and I went in.
I tried to steal a cookie.
Good night.
Hey.
Listen, get some rest.
Call me if you need anything.
I will.
Don't let this get you down, all right?
Get him down?
He should be down.
He should be at the bottom
of that fucking pool.
Thank you so much.
You know what? Just keep this.
Okay? Thanks.
Watch out for the dog.
Thank you.
So, what now?
You want a divorce?
I can't stand that you think
you're this much smarter than me.
I don't think that.
If you think I killed Charlie...
...aren't you frightened of me?
No.
Why not?
'Cause I'm the thing you killed for.
Hmm.
You sure?
Okay.
I love you!
Love you, too!
Love you!
Hi.
I didn't know your kids went
to this school.
They don't.
I was actually hoping to talk to you
and I didn't want to come to the house,
and, uh, I didn't know where else
to find you.
Okay.
I just want you to know that I don't
approve of what my husband's doing.
What's he doing?
I don't think that talking about people
behind their backs is right.
- Neither do I.
- I mean, it's ridiculous
for Don to keep insisting
that you could've...
You know, with Mr. De Lisle's accident.
And I told Don, I said,
I don't think it's a good idea
to have Melinda over to the house,
but he keeps inviting her over
to talk about his crazy theories.
I see.
Look, hey.
This is not your fault.
We should have you and Don
over for dinner.
Uh...
Hi.
Come in.
Hey, come on in.
- I love them.
- Oh, thanks.
- Kelly, you look so beautiful, I can't stand it.
- Hi.
Oh, thank you, Vic.
- Don, thanks for coming. Come on in.
Thanks for having us.
This way.
Do you know anything about snails, Don?
I can't say I do.
A snail will climb a 12-foot wall
to find its mate.
- It's the smell.
- Huh.
Mind if I smoke?
Please don't... it'll kill 'em.
Oh, well, we don't want that.
Don, I need you to stop telling people
that I killed Charlie De Lisle.
Is that right?
Yes. I think it's hurting your reputation.
I think it's hurting Kelly's reputation.
Well, that's funny that you're not worried
it'll hurt yours.
You know, I was gonna ask you
what you think killed Charlie.
What killed him?
Well, just, who dies like that?
Accidentally in a swimming pool?
Thousands of people a year.
What do you think killed him?
- I think you drowned him.
- Yeah?
I heard I killed Martin McRae, too.
You said you killed him.
Did you believe me?
No.
Good for you.
I thought it was weird, though,
that you said you did,
that you seemed to take pleasure in it.
And that was enough for you
to share my wife's opinion?
It's my opinion.
Would you, uh, be willing to take
a lie detector test
saying you didn't kill him?
Sure. Get one.
You're a weird guy.
So I've been told.
Hey, hon.
Hi.
Um, we're having lunch.
Oh.
I was just going to get something to go,
but I can join you for a second.
- Hi.
This is my husband, Vic.
- Victor Van Allen.
- Oh.
- It's, uh, nice to meet you.
- You, too.
This is David Ricigliani.
He's opening a practice here.
Oh. What kind of practice?
Psychotherapy.
Well, this town definitely needs that.
- You think?
- First practice?
Uh, no, no.
I actually closed my practice
in Cheshire recently.
- Upgraded.
- Yeah.
I'm curious, do you think my wife
has schizophrenic tendencies?
- What?
- Well, he's a professional.
I thought I'd ask.
No.
- It's possible he may have some insight as to…
- You're such an asshole.
- No, I don't think so at all.
- Hmm.
Do you think my husband might be
psychopathic for asking you that?
Or maybe just an asshole?
Uh… how about, uh, couples therapy?
I was going to get something to go for the
guys, but maybe I'll just skip it, huh?
Hate to interrupt your lunch.
I'm used to this.
Nice to make your acquaintance, David.
You don't happen to have a card, do you?
'Cause I may need a psychotherapist.
Oh, uh...
No, no. I… I don't have any on me.
Mm-hmm.
Well, I know where to find you.
Hi.
- Oh.
- Oh, I'm sorry to interrupt.
I didn't know it was dinnertime, but...
No, no, no, no, sit down, please.
This will just take a second.
Hi.
I just have a question for Don.
You know a guy named David Ricigliani?
Um...
Who's David Ricigliani?
He's a man your husband hired.
Who did you hire?
A private investigator.
What for?
To follow me.
This is ridiculous.
- How could you do that, Don?
- I made him a week ago.
I ran into him at a diner with Melinda.
Go outside, I see a telephoto lens
in the back of his car.
Oh, my God.
Guy tried to tell me
he was a psychotherapist.
Where'd you find this guy?
You can't just walk into my house
and accuse me, in front of my family...
Apparently, anybody can accuse
anyone of anything.
Unlike you, however, Don, I have proof.
This is a bank record of a wire
from my wife
to your account for $743.50,
which is sort of an unusual amount,
so I assume you went splitsies
on the retainer.
- Your wife…
- Oh, my God.
Have you lost your mind?
What the fuck were you thinking, Don?
Goldie, go inside.
- Uh, this is, this is humiliating.
- At least tell me where you found him.
Your wife wired that money to me.
- Back of a newspaper?
- Goldie, I said inside.
It's from your wife.
- Sorry to interrupt your dinner.
- No, no, no.
Don't you apologize for anything.
I'm the one who's sorry.
What the hell are you apologizing
to him for?
Are you kidding me, Don?
- Don't apologize to this piece of shit.
- Will you stop, Don?
Goldie, I thought I told you to go inside.
She did tell you to go inside.
Go inside, Goldie.
Go inside, Goldie!
Goddamn it.
Who left the fucking gate open?
Hey.
- Daddy?
- Mm-hmm.
When Charlie drowned in the swimming pool,
did his feet touch the bottom?
I don't know. I wasn't there.
Sure, you were there.
Well, I was there when we were trying
to save him...
everyone was...
but everything happened very quickly.
But you still know what you did.
I didn't do it, honey.
I think you're kidding me.
I'm not.
I'm not, Trix.
Why won't you tell me how you did it?
Everyone keeps asking me how you did it.
Sweetheart...
...if I did kill someone...
...do you know what they would do to me?
They would put me in prison
for the rest of my life.
Do you understand?
I still think you drowned him.
You're just telling me you didn't.
Well, let's keep that between us.
Rita.
Kangaroo.
Bring sloth back in.
You, you?
Yes?
It's killing me.
What?
Brazil?
I've never been to Brazil.
Yes.
No, she would.
She'd love it.
She'll get used to it.
What'd you say?
Oh, we can talk.
Love you.
How was your night?
You don't want to tell me?
You just don't want to talk.
- You must be Vic.
- Yeah.
- Tony Cameron.
- Hi.
Old friend of Melinda's.
- Nice to meet you.
- Thank you for having me over.
- Sure.
- Nice space you got here.
- Thank you very much.
Yeah, it's like a science lab.
Kind of.
Are those snails?
Yeah. Check it out.
Wow.
How about that?
Huh.
Um, is Melinda here?
Yeah, she's upstairs.
All right.
All right, well,
I guess I'll see you up there.
- Great.
- Okay.
Yeah, so I've been working on,
uh, building LEED-certified housing.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
In both-both here in the States
and-and also in Brazil, actually.
That's where our new initiative is.
'Cause, you know, the point is, well,
if we can create sustainable living spaces
for people around the world, we can help
create a more sustainable planet.
You know, for-for… for Trixie.
You know, for the,
for the next generation.
Can I get you a drink?
I'll take a sparkling water,
if you got it.
Sure.
Thank you.
Hi.
- Hi.
- There you are.
- Tony.
- Hi.
- Hi. Wow, it's great to see you.
- Hola.
Hi.
¿Cómo estás?
I can't believe you're here.
- I know, it's been a while.
- It's just crazy.
I know.
How are you?
I'm great. I'm great. Great.
You hungry?
Yeah, actually, I'm starving.
I'm starving. Well, that's why
I came over, obviously.
- Starving's good.
- Yeah.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Can I help?
- No.
- No?
- All right.
Is he being nice?
He's very nice. Very nice.
I was just telling him how we reconnected.
I was, I was working in
the state legislature here
and we started just chatting on Facebook.
I think what you're doing
is very inspiring.
Well, thank you.
- If that counts.
- Thank you.
- Right?
- I'm just...
- Very admirable.
- Yeah.
Just, I'm happy it gives me a chance
to reconnect with old friends.
Fun fact: Tony was the first American
I fucked.
- What? You blushing?
- Just...
Well, it's just…
Are you okay?
It's just an unnecessary amount of detail,
Melinda.
Well, it's true. What?
Wha...? Don't worry about Vic.
- He couldn't care less.
- Oh.
He's doesn't want to control me
like a normal man.
Uh, no, I'm not normal.
As somebody who dated her, Vic,
I-I really sympathize with you.
She's-she's a very difficult person
- to control.
- Oh, yeah. Right?
But that's also what makes her special.
You know that.
And then you broke up with me.
- Did I?
- Yes, you did.
He broke my heart.
- It's not true.
- You did, too.
Smells great over here, by the way.
- Thank you, thank you, thank you.
- Yeah.
Mmm.
Vic, you know what we should do
is get some-some snails.
That sounds amazing.
Garlic and a little butter?
- Want me to get 'em? I can get 'em.
- Come on.
No, the snails aren't for eating.
Oh, sorry. They're not for eat...
What are they, what are they for?
They're not for anything.
Well, you won't miss
a dozen or so, will you?
The snails are not for eating.
No, he won't. Just go get them.
I mean, they're-they're not like
your pets, are they?
Fun fact:
You know you have to starve them, right?
What?
Before you eat them, you have to make
sure their intestines are empty.
Otherwise, you'll poison yourself
and you'll die.
I did not know that.
No snails.
Who knew?
Hey, Tony.
Oh, Vic. That's funny.
Melinda's been trying to get ahold of you.
She's got a building site
she wants to show you.
She keeps talking about it.
Oh, really? She didn't, uh, say anything.
Well, come on, jump in.
All right.
It's really a beautiful spot.
Melinda and I used to go hiking up there
back when we started dating.
Sounds nice.
So why'd you break up with her?
What?
You know, when you guys were young.
Oh.
You know, I really don't remember.
I…
It was such a long time ago.
Going a little fast, Vic, don't you think?
So you guys just, like, reconnected?
Uh, yeah. I mean, a couple months ago,
just casually.
You gonna be in town for a while?
This is the way, huh?
Yep.
Should I give Melinda a call?
Sure, go ahead.
There's no service.
Oh, that's right. I forgot.
Here we are.
Where's Melinda?
She and I used to go mountain biking
up here.
There's a gorge just across the way.
She said we should meet her there.
Ah, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Stop, stop.
Here?
You're gonna fall.
What are you guys doing?
How's Tony?
- Right here?
- Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
I like him. He's actually got brains.
I'm going to pour you just a glass,
'cause we're celebrating.
Now we toast.
May the boys of St. Vincent's
keep their hands off our pigtails.
What are you doing?
You getting her drunk?
We're celebrating.
What are you celebrating?
Oh, life.
Wine.
Have you seen him?
Who?
Tony.
- Tony.
- Tony Pony!
- Tony Pony?
- Tony Maloney!
Tony Baloney, I have not seen.
Daddy?
Yes.
We're going on a picnic.
Do you want to come with us?
I would love to. Where we going?
The gorge.
The gorge?
Why are you the only man
who wants to stay with me?
I don't know.
But you do?
I do.
You're not bored?
No.
Are you?
But I'm sad.
I got you something.
You didn't know I took that.
- I was three months pregnant.
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Roger!
- Hey, Trixie!
- Roger!
Trix!
- Hold on. Hold on.
- She's fine, she's fine.
- I'll be right back.
- Stay.
- Trix! Uh...
- Vic, stay.
Trixie, back up, honey.
Get away from the edge, sweet pea.
Back up, back up, back up.
Thank you. Okay.
We have to go back, okay?
This is too close to the edge.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Okay.
Oh, damn. I left my scarf up there.
I'm sorry.
We can't go back now.
Oh, I'll go back for it.
But like tomorrow.
- Would you?
- Yeah.
I'll go back and get it
first thing in the morning.
Okay.
Thank you.
No problem.
- Hey. Can I get you some tea?
- Hi.
No, I'm fine.
She went down so easy, but I told her
you'd come give her a kiss.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Hey, wh-who were you, uh,
on the phone with?
Tony?
No.
I haven't heard from Tony.
That was Don.
Can you sleep in my room tonight?
- Sure.
- Please.
I love you.
Vic?
Hey, there!
Hi.
What are you doing?
Uh, just, uh, went for a little ride.
Uh, Melinda forgot her scarf.
- Oh.
- Found it.
Found it. Great.
Thanks.
So, which...
How you doing? How's Kelly?
She's fine.
What are you doing down here?
Like I said, just, uh, looking
for that scarf, but...
you got it, so...
It was lying in the grass.
Oh.
What are you doing with that stick?
Nothing.
Oh, shit.
Fuck. Fuck.
Fuck you, you fucking psycho!
You're going to jail!
Come get me now, you piece of shit!
Are you gonna catch me on your bike?!
You motherfucker.
Where'd you go?
Did I lose ya?
I was right. I was right.
Kelly, you are not gonna believe this.
This is… this is it.
This is a book.
Trixie?
Fuck.
Trixie, what are you doing?
We're not going!
I was…
was...
Goddamn, fucking autocorrect.
Goddamn it.
Oh!
What?
Nothing.
I saw Tony.
♪ Everyone knows I'm right
about one thing ♪
♪ You are my only vice ♪
♪ And I got you addicted
to trying to be bulletproof ♪
♪ But you had too much to lose... ♪
♪ Hah ♪
♪ Hah, hah ♪
♪ You've got a cute way of talking ♪
♪ You've got the better of me ♪
♪ Just snap your fingers and I'm walking ♪
♪ Like a dog hanging on your lead ♪
♪ I'm in a spin, you know,
shaking on a string, you know ♪
♪ You make me feel like dancing ♪
♪ I'm gonna dance the night away ♪
- ♪ I feel like dancing ♪
- ♪ Whoo ♪
- ♪ Dancing ♪
♪ Dance the night away ♪
- ♪ I feel like dancing, dancing ♪
- ♪ Whoo ♪
- ♪ Ah, ah-ah, ah-ah ♪
- ♪ Ah ♪
- ♪ Doo, doo-doo-doo, doo, doo, doo-doo ♪
- ♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Doo, doo-doo-doo, doo, doo, doo-doo ♪
- ♪ Doo, doo-doo-doo, doo, doo, doo-doo ♪
- ♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ Doo, doo-doo-doo,
doo, doo, doo-doo ♪
♪ Doo, doo-doo-doo, doo, doo, doo-doo ♪
♪ You take me higher ♪
♪ I'm gonna catch on fire 'cause ♪
♪ You make me feel like dancing ♪
♪ I'm gonna dance the night away ♪
- ♪ I feel like dancing ♪
- ♪ Whoo ♪
- ♪ Dancing ♪
- ♪ Dance the night away ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ I feel like dancing ♪
- ♪ Whoo ♪
- ♪ Dancing ♪
♪ Dance the night away ♪
- ♪ I feel like dancing ♪
- ♪ Whoo ♪
- ♪ Dancing ♪
♪ Ah, ah-ah-ah, ah ♪
♪ Doo, doo-doo-doo, doo, doo, doo-doo ♪
- ♪ Doo, doo-doo-doo, doo, doo, doo-doo ♪
- ♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Doo, doo-doo-doo, doo, doo, doo-doo ♪
♪ Doo, doo-doo-doo,
doo, doo, doo-doo... ♪
♪ ...MacDonald had a farm ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ And on his farm he had some pigs ♪
♪ With an oink oink here ♪
♪ And an oink oink there ♪
♪ Here an oink, there an oink,
everywhere an oink oink ♪
♪ Old MacDonald had a farm ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ And on his farm he had some dogs ♪
♪ With a woof woof here ♪
♪ And a woof woof there ♪
♪ Here a woof, there a woof,
everywhere a woof woof ♪
♪ Old MacDonald had a farm ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-O. ♪
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/9r3x7
Help other users to choose the best subtitles