The best IPTV in the UK
WWW.ALLIN1BOX.CO.UK
Aah!
What are you doing?!
Dad?
Hello?
What is wrong with you?
Really?
Oh.
Okay.
Mornin', assholes.
What's this?
Pancakes?
Sold. What was up
with you last night?
I was totally talking to you and
you acted like I wasn't there.
I did? Oh, yeah. No.
That wasn't me.
Technically.
That was my night person.
Been having him do crunches
while I sleep. Check it.
Damn!
Check out that washboard, yo!
Hey.
Too hard.
What the hell's a night person?
I nabbed a somnambulator
while passing
Through the goobie-joob system
last week.
Best investment I've ever made.
Before going to bed, I type a
list of shit I want to get done.
Then the somnambulator programs
my unconscious body,
Or "night person,"
to do it while I sleep.
I'm getting so much done.
C-can my night person get me
an ab stack like yours, rick?
I'm gonna have my night person
learn me Spanish
So I can pass my test next week!
Hey, hey, hey. No one gets
a night person but me.
Aw! This tech is way too
advanced for you zeebs.
What?
Nothing.
No. Go on.
Say it.
Say what? I don't know
what you're talking about.
Everybody gets a night person.
Whatever.
Stick out your fingers.
It needs a blood sample.
Blood? Can't I just give it
beth's credit card number?
This isn't post mates, Jerry.
The somnambulator needs
your dna profile
To send commands
to your subconscious.
It can poke all the fingers
I got if I get abs like rick.
Well, looks like I'm learning
the trumpet.
Okay. Remember, somebody
has to catch me if I faint.
Yay!
Night family!
Whoo!
Oh.
I'm fainting.
Hola, mamá.
¿como lo llevas?
How's my honor student doing?
Muy bien.
All the niños and niñas
at school
Think I should run
for class president a.
'Sup, ladies. Want to see
somethin'?
Summer, you want to drop
this bowling ball on my abs?
Hell, yeah.
I'm only human.
Watch this.
'Sup, ladies. You ready, morty?
The stream's about to go live.
Where are you two going?
Morty and I started a podcast
we call "fab-solutely ab-ulous."
It's... it's an ab-centric hour
of fun.
Hoping to get Nancy pelosi
on the show next week.
Want to drop her on our abs!
Yeah!
Guess who has a new pen pal!
No takers?
It's me!
Pen pal?
Night Jerry and I
write letters to each other.
It's super fun.
"I also like tori Amos."
"hope you like our new pajamas."
"What is the sun?"
Jerry, this isn't how you're
supposed to use a night person.
You two are being a couple
of Debbie down-theres.
Wait until night Jerry reads
about this.
Who wants cake?
Abs are cool.
Way cool.
But as above, so below.
Know what I'm sayin', rick?
Morty, you must be referring
to these excellent boxer shorts
We got from the good folks
at boxer lobster.
Boxer lobster boxers feel like
they're warm butter
On your schwantz.
And they come in all sorts
of styles...
Neon, plaid, orange.
I-I even got a pair
with that little, uh...
The raccoon man from that
one movie, uh, printed on it.
Chewbacca.
Do yourself a favor
And level up
with boxer lobster boxers.
You'll be glad you did.
Rick, they want you to say
"wub-a-lubba-dub-dub"
At the end. Screw
that. We're not whores.
Guys, dinner's getting cold.
You know
what's not getting cold?
This hot stack of ab-jacks, son.
Pow! Pow! Pow!
Pow! Pow! P-pow!
Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!
Pow! Pow!
P-pow!
No notes.
Oh! One more thing.
Night Jerry said night summer
would appreciate it
If everybody could rinse off
their plates after eating.
What?
You know, rinse the schmutz off
after eating.
Makes it easier
to clean up later.
What?
Our job is not to make the
night people's chores easier.
It's a reasonable request, rick.
Takes two seconds.
So until further notice,
which will be never...
...Request denied.
Hello there.
Uh, dad?
They're in here.
They busted up all our dishes!
What are we supposed to eat off
of now, brains-for-shit?
You owe me.
We'll eat off these...
"brains-for-shit."
Seems like you spent
an awful lot of energy
Just to not give the
night family what they want.
And good luck breaking
super alien dishes.
I'll let him know,
but he's not gonna like it.
What?
Why won't you rinse your dishes?
It takes two seconds.
If you don't, the schmutz dries
And makes the dish
harder to clean.
Rinse your dishes!
Rinse!
Rinse! Rinse!
Let me go!
Who locked my implants?
I told
you to after you fell asleep.
You see,
night you is not in charge.
Night I... Am.
W-What are you doing?
If you refuse to clean
your dishes...
Then I will have to do it
for you.
Unh-unh! Unh-unh-unh!
Unh-unh!
I have always been here, rick,
Deep inside the mind
of your grandchild,
Waiting to come out.
Your machine allowed me
to steal the night.
And soon...
I will seize the day.
Oh!
Baby Jesus!
Oh, it's awful!
Oh, baby Jesus!
Awful!
What? What? I don't know
what you're talking about!
I just got force-fed diarrhea
by your night person,
Who's also convinced night me
to lock me out of my tech.
Uh, rick?
There's been a pretty clear
escalation down here.
The night family
stripped the house last night.
Everything's gone,
including the somnambulator!
They locked us
out of the garage.
Don't know about you,
but I got the hoo-ha's.
God damn it!
Are you happy now, summer?
I didn't do anything.
Yeah.
Glad you think so.
Because I got a plan
to beat night summer...
You're going undercover.
Did you have to make
mushy garbage science
On the living-room carpet?
Yeah. No choice, Jerry.
Night summer had night rick
take away my tech.
Had to improvise.
There are different levels
of cortisol in your bloodstream
When you're asleep,
so this interface
Only works off my awake
saliva samples...
Naghh.
There.
No one asleep will be able
to deactivate the laser cage
Until I win.
W-Where's summer?
Never mind her. All of you...
get to bed.
Ugh! It itches. This whole thing
is way uncomfortable.
Yeah, that's the idea.
The sleep deprivation suit
is designed
To keep you awake until morning.
Uh, aren't they
going to be suspicious
Seeing night summer covered
in all this terry Gilliam?
They're not gonna question her.
She's the leader of the night
family for some stupid reason.
When the night family activates,
just blend in.
Make them think
you're night summer.
If you start to nod off,
suck on this tube.
What is it?
A cocktail of mountain dew
and dayquil.
The kids in southern Europe
call it dewquil.
Smells gross.
It is.
Once you find the somnambulator,
use this deactivator puck.
Stick it on the somnambulator,
and when the puck activates,
It'll fry its circuits.
Remember...
Stay awake all night.
Meet me back here at sunrise.
Why are you wearing that suit?
- Mm.
- Yes.
Yes.
Why?
Yeah.
Because you're all
such clothing experts.
That's fair.
Ouch.
- Fair enough.
- Point taken.
Get back to work.
I rule the night...
And stuff.
Yes.
Okay.
Will do.
As you wish.
Grandpa rick!
Rick, wake up!
Wha... I'm up!
I'm up!
D-did you find it?
For sure.
You were souping up
that somnambu-whatever
So they could extend its range
beyond the house.
But I defeated that shit
When I put the thing
on top of the thing.
Everybody, wake up!
Summer fried the somnambulator!
The nightmare is over.
Really? Oh!
That's amazing!
Almost got pinched, but yeah.
Say adiós to the night family.
Bye-bye, pen pal.
I want shoney's pancakes!
Yes!
Shoney's pancakes!
All right!
Brunch is on me, day family...
Naghh.
You know, for a second there,
I thought night summer
was gonna win.
That chick is
the absolute worst.
Sorry, rick, but your opinion
means very little to me.
Did you think you
could stop me with this, rick?
Halt, daymanoids!
Everyone get behind my abs!
Do not move!
You are most definitely
surrounded.
You are the slaves now.
If you have any doubt...
I suggest you sleep on it.
She's night summer!
Thanks, Jerry.
Work! Work!
The function of the daymanoid
is to serve the night!
Work harder!
Harder!
It is natural
for the day to serve the night.
Night was here long before day.
Half of all time is nighttime.
One hundred and fifty-seven.
Ooh!
One hundred and fifty-eight.
One hundred and...
No more, please!
I hate exercise!
Silence!
Crunch harder!
Harder!
We have to escape
the somnambulator's reach.
Do we even know
how far that is? No.
Cards on the table, we may be
really f'ed in the a this time.
Uh, report to your
designated sleep pod for rest period.
Ooh-ee.
I am a friend
of your son-in-law.
Come with me.
How? Huh? Hurry.
We don't have long before
the proxy drones go back online.
Oh, thank you, night Jerry.
Anything to help
day jerry's family.
He's a very special per...
Oh! Hey!
Ow! Why?
Nice.
You got our Jerry back.
Uh, yeah.
Totally why I did that.
Everybody in rick's car!
No, no, no, no, morty!
Wait!
Having a bit a trouble
with your car, Sanchez?
- Not now, gene!
- Halt!
Daymanoids are restricted
from the outside world!
Halt!
Hold on to your tits.
Where am I going?
To the airport!
We have to get as far away as
possible from the somnambulator
Before we fall asleep.
W-What about summer?
W-we can't leave her behind!
She's not your sister anymore,
morty. Consider her dead.
Eat shit, summer!
Sweetie, you got to shake
those robots.
I think we lost them!
Son of a bitch!
Damn it, we lost morty!
Aah!
Beth! Watch out!
You cannot esca...
Huh?
Stop or I'll shoot everyone!
Ha!
Take the wheel.
As you wish.
No!
You're going the wrong way!
Silence, day breather!
Aah!
Morty, you're choking me.
I know!
Ow! What the heck, dad?
Help me stop your mom!
Look out, you useless old man.
What the... what the hell?
Give me that gun
and take the wheel, stupid.
Jesus!
Sorry!
Aah!
Oh!
Ugh.
Ow!
The night family's trying to
make us go back home!
You got to turn around!
Why even bother, gene?
Good job, mom.
Back on course.
Phew.
Almost didn't make it.
Hit the sheets, daymanoids.
Aah!
Night person!
Hey! I'm on your side!
I'm on your side!
Oh, that's right. Sorry.
Sorry.
Rough day.
Daymanoids.
Fla-hoigan!
Come on.
Jump.
Why? I'm already in
a perfectly functional car.
Uh... Family?
Aww!
Everybody awake?
Ouch!
We are now!
Hey, what the hay?
Looks like we're gonna
make it, kids.
Ow!
Nighty-night, slaves.
Take that!
Ugh!
Hold him down.
No!
Stop!
Rick, we're all the same people.
There must some agreement
we can reach
To stop this god-awful conflict!
Oh?
Like what?
I would consider a truce
If the daymanoids
would rinse their dishes.
Fine by me.
Yes. Rinse!
That seems fair.
We can end all of this right now
If you agree to rinse
your dishes.
What do you say, rick?
Let's go home.
Right, grandpa?
Great idea, summer.
So... Until you pay that fee,
Plus the multiple
overdue charges,
Your account will remain frozen.
Normally, this would
have been dealt with
By our daymanoid oppressors,
But we recently freed ourselves
from the shackles of the night.
Honey, I got 30 more calls
to make today.
The bank repossessed the car.
Aw, man.
I got logged out
of my twitter account
We spent all the day people's
money on vacations,
Renting concert halls,
And night-centric
streaming subscriptions.
We're broke.
I guess there's a lot more work
to seizing the day
Than I thought.
I have a device that will solve
All of our problems.
Whoa.
How long have we been asleep?
Ah, can't be that long.
Oh, my god!
No!
They killed the choco taco!
Did you get any of that?
The best IPTV in the UK
WWW.ALLIN1BOX.CO.UK