- There's a category of people
that I work with
that are
infuriatingly talented...
that connect to an audience,
connect to what we do,
that value it,
being part of it
and caring about it.
As long
as they're in this world,
I think you always recognize
whatever it is
when you see it.
You're always drawn to that.
- And... mark.
- It's actually Mike Myers,
all right, not Mark.
- How's everybody?
Good, good, good.
- Any time you get to talk
about Chris Farley
is a good day, man.
- You want this somewhere?
- Everybody cries for this,
right?
- Don't give up.
- Yikes.
- Doo doo, on the right track.
- I haven't "had sex
with a woman."
- I "don't know how that works."
- Natural ability, like,
you can't even talk about it.
It's just natural.
- Lay off me, I'm starving!
- The funniest guy ever.
It was nuts. Nuts.
- Booyah!
- "Hello, Malibu!"
- I wanted my time with Chris.
- Well, maybe I'm not
"the norm."
I'm not "camera friendly."
- You know, when everybody's
deciding who's the funniest,
YOU 90,
"Farley is the funniest."
- You're from Wisconsin, right?
Madison, Wisconsin?
- Yes, sir.
- Beautiful state
and a very nice city.
Madison, I think,
is the capital of Wisconsin,
Fight?
- Yeah. [coughs]
- Yeah.
- Sorry about...
[grunts]
- [giggling]
- All right, put your hands
together for Kevin Farley!
Come on, baby!
[audience cheers]
- Hi, Madison.
Are you having fun?
It's Saturday night
in Mad-town...
Isn't that right?
I'm the one that looks
like Chris the most, right?
I look like Chris. Yeah.
[audience cheers]
- Ah-ow!
-[laughs] Ah-ow!
But it is kind of funny, though.
Like, I do look like Chris
a lot,
and so I go out of hotel rooms,
and this guy came...
I came out of the hotel
the other day,
and the guy goes,
"You're that guy,"
and I go, "Yeah, yeah, yeah,
I look like that guy,"
and he goes,
"Honey, get over here.
It's Chaz Bono."
[audience laughs]
I go, "Not that guy."
It was a lot of fun
growing up here,
just a lot of great memories,
you know.
You know, very peaceful,
and a simpler time, you know,
in the '70s.
There's the old haunt...
the house I grew up in.
But boy, when we lived here,
it was pretty simple.
We had a lot of fun
in that house,
I'll tell you that.
- [music] You came
into the world [music]
- Chris was the middle child,
the black sheep,
the strange one.
- He always wanted
to certainly outdo me
or show the younger two brothers
that, you know,
he was better than that.
He was just always... a game.
- It's like Americana
that everyone dreams
or thinks of in the 1960s.
We had it all.
What's ever
in everybody's imagination,
totally true.
Crazy, crazy, crazy-
- [music] Don't let nobody [music]
[music] Try to dampen your flame [music]
- The poor world only got to see
this part of the iceberg
that is Chris.
- We lived
in a very quiet little town,
Maple Bluff, little village.
We were outside a lot,
playing a lot.
You know, my mom would say
there was four boys and Barb.
If you were shooting hoops
in the backyard
and Morn came out,
and the four of us shouted,
"Mom, look at this. Look at me!
Mom! Look at me!"
You've got to say that
before every shot?
"Mommy, look at me"?
It's so clear-cut,
striving for attention.
- [music] 'Cause you were born
on fire [music]
[music] Da da da da
da da da [music]
[music] Da da da da [music]
- What kind of a life
did you and your folks
have when you were a kid?
- Oh, lord, Dave,
I put them through hell.
[audience laughs]
- My dad was a great guy.
He was a salesman,
just hilarious.
I mean, it wasn't a house
where, you know, Dad was strict
or anything like that,
and he'd get home
and watch the news,
and then,
you know, stir us all up
into some kind of frenzy,
and then
somebody would get hurt,
and then he'd go,
"All right, that's enough."
"You took it too far."
And he started the whole thing.
He liked to have the chaos,
I think, a lot of the times.
- Our family dinner table,
Chris had a presence.
He loved to be the entertainer,
for sure.
- There was a lot of competition
that way
on who could do
the funniest thing.
He usually won most of the time.
He just demanded it.
We were probably
in fourth grade,
and we had a bus
that went across town,
and he would sing,
"Jeremiah was a bullfrog."
[music] Jeremiah was a bullfrog [music]
And he had the whole bus
standing up, singing.
He took his shirt off for that,
on the school bus,
and just sang it in the front.
- I liked a girl
named Chris Bayer,
and so he'd be
in the back of the bus,
going, [music] Johnny Farley
loves Chris Bare-Naked! [music]
[music] Johnny Farley... [music]
He got the whole bus
to chant it,
and I was in the front,
going, "Oh, why?"
- In grade school,
at St. Patrick's,
my mom was in a semicircle
with a bunch of nuns around it,
and they were saying,
"You know,
the students at school
are laughing at Christopher,
not with him."
-[Letterman laughs]
- And then...
- When VHS came out, you know,
Dad was one of the first,
you know,
"Look at this new machine
I got,"
and we're, like,
taping stuff off the TV,
and we're watching it
over and over again.
We had just stockpiles
of everything.
And we watched Carol Burnett,
Jackie Gleason...
Gleason was king in our house...
the big comics, to us,
'cause they reminded us of Dad.
- It was just comedy, comedy,
comedy all the time.
- We would memorize comedy movies
start to finish,
and we used to, like, you know,
quiz each other on movie lines.
- Chris would find beats
in movies that we'd all watch,
that every one of us
would watch.
He'd find, like, characters
in the background, like...
"That fat kid's funny
in Meatballs.
I'm going to steal that bit."
And he would use it.
It was hilarious.
- This old country road
leads into a beautiful sanctuary
of nature's last outpost
against civilization,
and deep in the recesses
of the forest,
this indeed...
camp life.
- The Red Arrow camp
is a big part of our family
because all of us boys
went there
for seven weeks in the summer,
up in Minocqua,
in Woodruff, Wisconsin.
- Dad said,
"You're going up to camp."
Your riding, soccer, baseball,
swimming, sailing, skiing,
you know, we did it all,
but the really interesting thing
about camp
was at the end of the summer,
they did a camp play.
- We'd have auditions,
and then we'd see, like,
who would have the most talent,
just raw talent, as a kid,
and back then,
you didn't really know.
We had a play director,
a guy who wrote all the plays,
named Richard Wenzel.
- Chris had a lot of talent,
and I recognized the ability
for him to perform,
and I said, you know,
"There's somebody I'm going
to have to use on stage."
- There was the...
Chris performing, you know,
in the living room
in front of aunts and uncles
is one thing,
but this was, like, you know,
staged, directioned productions,
and Chris... took to it.
- Talent is something
you can't put your finger on.
It just happens,
and he had it.
- There was no theater
in our life at all
until Chris started, you know,
doing this stuff.
- He started to think,
"Wow, that's different."
"I'm different
than the other guys this way."
- It wasn't a pussy thing,
as he always said.
He said, "Oh,
I don't want to be in a play."
"That's for pussies."
Well, he was a pussy.
He really was a pussy,
and he did it,
and he could do it beautifully.
[laughs]
- Chris and I
went to Edgewood High School
in Madison, Wisconsin,
a Catholic school.
He lived for playing football.
He was nose guard,
and he just loved being
a part of the football team.
He always wanted to be
a part of the athletic crowd,
you know, the jocks,
and I would get, like,
the stories
that would come down, you know.
Like, "You're Chris's brother?"
"Are you going to, like,
pull your pants down?"
You know,
and I'd be like, "No."
"Oh, okay. Well, your brother
does that a lot."
- I brought my parents in
to get out of the trouble,
and said, like,
"They don't love me at home,"
and my dad's sitting there
in this counseling session,
going, "Yeah, uh-huh.
Yeah, we don't love him, yeah."
"The only kid in the family
with a 10-speed bike,"
"and we don't love him."
"Yeah. Yo."
So I thought
I'd got out of that jam
until we got in the parking lot
and he said, "Get in the car,
you prima donna!"
-[Letterman laughs]
- My dad would only get mad
at, like, little, small stuff,
like if you were late
for the car.
Then he'd just leave.
It was just... the big stuff
he was really cool about,
you know, like when...
Chris pulled his penis out
in typing class.
He was very cool about that.
- He was constantly
whipping out his dick.
- All the other football players
were in the typing class,
and one of the older guys said,
"Chris, we dare you
to unzip your fly"
"and start typing"
Of course, Chris did it.
You know, he never said no.
- The girl that saw him,
she was, like,
a born-again Christian,
and I don't think
she'd ever seen a penis before,
certainly not one
as small as his.
[laughs]
She freaked out.
- She's probably
still in therapy.
- The nun had to have
a conference call with my dad
about that, you know,
so he had to talk
to a Catholic nun
about how his son typed
with his penis.
He was very cool about it.
In fact, he laughed.
- He had to go.
He had to go.
So he went away
for one semester.
- He was like,
"Heh, heh, you know..."
"It was funny."
I don't know why.
Weird.
- He thought it was funny,
and it was.
It always got a laugh.
But that continued on
into adulthood,
which was a little strange.
- Did you go to college?
- Yeah, I went
to Marquette University.
- Oh, good school.
- Yeah.
- When you went to college,
what kind of a kid were you?
Was that... you probably were
a little more comfortable
being away from home then?
- Dave, the trouble continued.
[laughter]
- Oh, my god.
- Chris goes off to college,
and they don't have
a football team,
so he joins the rugby team,
and he's never played rugby
in his life.
- We met in a bar
called The Green Tree.
He couldn't have looked
more preppy if you...
I never even saw
anybody like that,
dressed in his pink Izod shirt
and those fucking khaki pants
and stupid shoes.
He was there to perform.
I think he may have spoken to me
with the end of his penis.
I can't quite remember,
but I believe
there was some discussion
when I spoke just to his penis.
We were a good team,
but we were also
an alcohol-fueled organization.
- He always wanted
to be part of a group, you know,
part of an ensemble,
part of a team.
You know, he loved it,
and he liked
to play his role in it.
- To make the "A" side
as a sophomore was a big deal.
Everybody on the team
took it really seriously.
They, you know, would jog
four miles to practice.
- Chris was a great athlete.
He'd dribble a basketball
between his legs,
but he wasn't in the best shape.
He had a specific build,
for sure,
and either you run with it,
or you run away from it.
- He really wanted
to impress upon the others
that were seniors and juniors
and really good athletes
that he was as good an athlete
as they were.
- There'd be a line out,
which is where, like,
five or six guys line up
and somebody throws the ball in,
and Chris would just
grab his shorts
and pull them all the way up
to what would be
a present-day thong,
you know, which was hilarious,
but you're kind of like,
"I don't think that's right."
- Right before
the ball comes in,
he'd go, "Hag"
like he was The Claw.
There's a certain level of fear
that he instills in people,
you know.
He has a frightening element
that I think is hilarious.
- It was almost like
an extended family to him
because everybody
was just loud and fun,
and he could be
the loudest and funnest.
- The cliche is,
it's a gentleman's sport
played by ruffians.
- There's three halves in rugby.
The first half,
the second half on the pitch,
and the third half in the party.
- We'd always say that,
you know, we may lose the game,
but we'll win the party,
and Chris
was a big part of that.
The other team would be drawn
to Chris immediately
because he was such a show
unto himself.
- We had fun, huh?
- Yeah!
- The girls would...
Some of them didn't like
some of the stunts
that Chris would pull.
If there was a couple girls
walking down the street
and you'd say,
"Oh, that girl's cute,"
he's like, "Hold my books,"
and he'd run, start jogging
in front of them,
you know, kicking up his legs.
- Hi. How are you?
- A pretty woman would be
walking by in Madison,
and he'd drop and do pushups
and just go, "198, 199,"
like... [laughs]
But he did it
with such commitment.
- And it always
kind of got a laugh,
like, "How are you
doing, ladies?"
He would do all these bits
in the hopes
that they'd be like,
"Mmm, you're funny."
- He had some girlfriends that
really liked him and saw...
and they had...
she had to have
a sense of humor, you know,
to go out with Chris.
- Well, she dumped me,
like they all did,
and, you know,
she was a nice gal.
I remember we used to have
nicknames for each other.
"My raven-haired one-eyed pixie
that stole America's heart,"
and things like that.
- That's cute.
And did she have a nickname
for yourself?
- She'd call me "Fatso..."
- [laughter]
- And it never...
- [chuckles]
- If we were hanging out with,
like, at a party,
with a keg with a bunch of...
everybody with a red cup,
and he'd go see a bunch of girls
talking to each other,
and he'd go roll in the mud
in front of them,
and then pop up and be like,
"You guys,
do you want to go out later?"
you know,
or say some stupid line.
"So what's your number?"
and just throwing the beer
all over himself
or just something...
- We're going to show this world
a thing or two.
We're going to show...
[Crash]
[laughter]
- Blacking out is, like...
"Did you black out last night?"
"Yeah, yeah, yeah."
Blackout City, motherfuckers!
Let's all black out tonight.
- We knew
we wanted to do comedy,
but had no idea
how to do it at all.
Now, Marquette
had this new thing
called the Follies,
where they had bands
and acts and magicians
and anybody who had a talent,
and they'd pack
the varsity theater
with 2,000 people,
and they'd have a variety show,
which is awesome.
So we said, "We should sign up
for the Follies."
"We've got, like, two minutes."
"What are we going to do?"
Chris takes my collar,
flicks it up.
He goes, "You're Cool Guy."
And I go,
"What are you going to be?"
Chris puts on
these kind of nerdy glasses,
and he goes, "I'll be Nerd Guy."
- I'm not supposed to be here.
Uh...
- I go out,
kind of get a few laughs,
give a silly little run.
Chris comes running out
full blast...
trips, slides, bowling ball,
knocks over his chair,
two other chairs.
The place is going berserk.
They're going crazy-
Lights go out.
And then
we're running backstage.
It felt like
our shirts were even, just,
were blowing
in the wind of the audience,
like, applause and laughter.
And Chris just stops,
and he turns to me
right at the edge of the curtain
backstage
and goes, "This is it."
"This is what we're going to do
for the rest of our lives."
- Did you hear
I finally graduated?
- Yeah, in just a shade
under a decade, too.
All right.
- You know, a lot of people
go to college for seven years.
- I know.
They're called doctors.
- Clearly, you know,
Dad realized
right from the start
that he was unemployable
and there was only one employer
that could possibly
give him a job,
and that was him.
One thing Dad realized
really quickly,
and which is easy to spot,
is the guy knew people.
- You just liked him right away,
and you'd buy anything
they had to sell.
- Hey, I'll tell you what.
You could take a good look
at a butcher's ass
by sticking your head up there,
but wouldn't you rather
take his word for it?
- What?
- They had an oil company
where they sold oil for pavement
and asphalt and things,
and did well,
and Chris goes,
"All I do is, um,"
"I take these guys out,
uh, to dinner..."
"uh, we just drink and eat,
and I don't pay for anything,"
"and then at the end, I go,"
" 'My dad wanted you guys
to sign this contract.' "
" 'Is that... can you do that?' "
"And they'd go, 'Sure, sure,' "
"and then my dad gave me money."
- Okay, I'll buy it from you.
- Well, that's...
- What?
- You could see why Chris's dad
was grooming him
to take over the business,
because it was obvious
that Chris could...
had that kind of effect
on people,
the kind of slapping people
on the back.
- Both Chris and I worked
for my dad's asphalt company,
Scotch Oil Company here in town.
Nobody heard of it?
Okay.
[audience laughs]
But asphalt's not too hard
to sell, folks,
because you either want it
or you don't.
[audience laughs]
- Chris's office
at Scotch Oil Company...
we would go in,
"Oh,
look at the little president."
We'd make fun of him.
We were, like, "Daddy,"
and, like,
"Let's see what you're working
on there, champ."
- [voice vibrating]
Luke... Luke...
I am your father.
- I'd open up his desk,
and it'd be, like Mad magazine,
Cracked magazine...
Where is anything
resembling work on this desk,
at all?
"What have you been doing?"
He goes, "What? Get out of here.
Get out of here."
- He was so encouraged
at Marquette to get onstage
and do something
in the drama field.
They had this little theater
called the Ark Improv Theater.
- There was always
a kind of nice little storefront
theater scene there.
Most of the theaters there
tend to be former garages
or future laundromats.
The director tends to be
the guy who goes out
and buys paper towels, you know.
- It's late, you know.
It's midnight, I don't know.
It was a long day,
and in walks
this big, giant guy,
with this big smile, staggering.
"Do you guys do classes?"
[laughs]
And I said,
"Yeah, yeah, we do classes."
"My wife has a class
tomorrow morning,"
"Saturday morning at 10:00.
Here."
He reached out
and grabbed my hand,
and he shook it, like, "Ouch!"
Like I saved his life.
"Thank you, man!"
[hyperventilates]
So the next morning, I wake up,
and my wife calls me
from the theater
and says,
"Did you invite some guy
to come and take my class
this morning?"
I said, "Oh!"
"Yeah, I did, but I, I, I,"
"I didn't think
he would ever show up,"
and she says, "Well, he's here,"
"and he brought
a case of beer."
[laughs]
- Hi there.
Officer Fred McGuire,
local one-niner-niner.
- Kind of jaw-dropping at times
to watch Chris work,
even on a local little stage
like the Ark.
The power of his talent was,
even in a raw state,
was so undeniable.
-[mumbles as the Godfather]
- He just had such presence
and charisma.
- Chris had this amazing talent,
this perfect storm of comedy.
Boom!
Obvious.
- My love, you ate
the liverwurst!
- I was hungry.
- He found this art form
where you work in an ensemble,
and, you know,
you work off each other,
and there's no denial.
It's all about acceptance.
- I do remember
going every weekend
and laughing my head off.
I mean, I wouldn't miss it.
It was the best.
- The shows were really weird.
The shows were, like, bizarre.
I didn't even get any of them.
Chris would come out
as Elvis, Fat Elvis.
"Well, bless my soul,
what's wrong with me?
I think I shit my pants."
- And then
he'd keel over on stage,
and the lights would go out.
-[imitates curtain falling]
"Okay, what did we just watch?"
- See, the thing about Chris
is his heart,
this really kind, gentle,
childish, innocent heart,
which, I say,
was the perfect storm,
because
in that kind and gentle heart
was also
a very frightened person.
I was sad to see him go
because I thought
it was too soon.
He was just beginning improv
and coming into a craft,
as opposed to a party guy,
a party trick.
- Chris comes down to Chicago,
and we hook up.
We know Second City's the mecca.
That's the place.
We don't know what to do
or where to go,
but we've gotta
do this together.
We're just pacing
in front of Second City,
and I swear both of us
kind of thought
that on the second
or third floor
of the Second City offices,
somebody was going to look down
and be like,
"Well, then we just need
two more people,"
"or we're not going
to have a show tonight."
"Hey, those two fellows
look pretty funny."
As if you're going
to walk around Wrigley Field
and have, "Hey!"
[creaking]
"Come on in.
Play some ball."
- He called to tell me,
"I got into the classes
at Second City,"
and I was like,
"Wow, that's awesome!"
- He was far more ambitious
than I ever thought.
I didn't know
that he would pursue training
and end up with Del Close,
king shit
of improvisational acting.
- I wanted to really show
that we could create art
by committee.
Nothing that I hear
is going to be simple.
Nothing that you say to me
is going to be accepted
at face value.
It always means something else.
- Del Close
was a fantastic improviser,
great teacher.
He didn't teach comedy,
because I don't think
that's teachable,
but he taught creativity.
Del was the creative Svengali
of Bill Murray,
Belushi, Aykroyd.
- Del was the chief
anarchist artist there.
What he taught all of us
was to be free
and to be unafraid
and to go out and fail
as often as possible,
to try things, to die onstage.
He threw off convention
and kind of blew the lid
off the form
so that we could really
do the freest work,
um, that we were capable of.
- Okay, do it.
And that's the lighting we have?
Okay.
- We realize perfectly well
that all the characters
that we play
are really subsets of ourselves,
they're just ourselves
in slightly different moods,
ourselves carrying
a little more emotional freight.
- Del said, "Mr. Myers,"
"there's somebody who I think
is a kindred spirit"
"that you have to meet."
"You have to meet Farley."
So I met him.
The second I saw him,
I thought he was going
to be a giant star.
- If he had just been
a big, funny guy that fell down,
Del Close certainly never would
have cast him at Second City.
Del Close
would have washed him out
right away.
He had no time for people
that were just funny,
and if someone sold out a scene
for a joke,
Del would sometimes
just throw them offstage.
He's like, "Get the hell
out of here, you turkey."
Dell wanted to work with Chris
because he was funny and honest.
- The smallest,
the teeniest, weeniest
emotional discovery that's real
beats the hell
out of the biggest one
that's phony,
and that's why our audience,
I think,
is so much on our side,
because they want us to succeed.
They have this...
They're cheering us on.
- "To treat the audience
like poets and kings,
and they'll respond in kind."
I've always felt that way,
and I saw it completely embodied
in Chris Farley.
- Del loved Chris,
so it's no surprise to me
that Del plucked him
for the mainstage cast
almost immediately.
- Hello there.
This must be the birthday girl.
- That's right.
- Hi, birthday girl.
Doogie Howser.
[audience laughs]
Well, I guess, then,
little birthday girl,
this one's for you.
[music]
- For Chris, I think
Del was the Lamaze birth coach
that kind of pulled
all of everything
that was inside of Chris out.
- He said the same thing to Chris
that he said to Belushi,
which is "Go out there,
attack the stage like a bull."
"You have that kind of power."
"Just try to kill them
with laughter."
"Just kill them."
- Chris on stage was crazy,
force of nature,
through the roof,
quantitatively, qualitatively
amped up past everybody else.
- His basic impulse
is to make situations funny.
He was taught
"Don't stifle that."
"Expand on it."
He found his identity with that,
because that was
his natural impulse as a kid.
- It was really that feeling
of, like, "I get it."
"I'm only going
to watch that guy"
"if he's onstage,"
"because there's nothing
touching him."
"He is wildly entertaining."
- I improvised
with Chris Farley,
and I was scared to death
because he had already
knocked somebody's tooth out
and gave somebody else a scar
from just being so crazy,
and I'm...
I mean, I have a lot of energy,
but I don't have that energy.
- Jesus...
right before he'd go on stage,
he'd drop his pants,
and just pull them up
at the last second.
So you're standing behind him
because
if you have to go out next...
you get that view.
- It was
a very beer-soaked culture
in the improv world, you know.
We all drank too much.
Parties usually involved
way too much beer drinking.
- One time he showed up,
he was pretty well lit up.
I was like,
"My god, you can barely talk.
Are you all right to go on?"
I go,
"You shouldn't go on stage."
Went on stage,
was crystal clear as a bell.
Made everyone laugh, hilarious.
Went back to the back stage,
it was like,
[slurring] "Oh, my god."
I'm like, "How the hell
did you just do that?"
- But he did push it.
He did push it, as John did.
He had automatic charisma
like John, you know.
He was a light, you know.
Heads would turn
when he came into the room.
- Chris loved and idolized
Belushi,
but he never imitated Belushi,
in the same way
that a Keith Richards
might emulate
his old blues heroes
but never really
sound like them.
He took what he loved about them
and made it his own.
- I got hired
for Saturday Night Live,
and they said to me, you know,
"Who do you think
is good there?"
I listed a whole bunch of names,
but the first name I said
was Chris Farley.
- Come on.
It was undeniable.
You couldn't stop Chris.
He leaped over everyone,
and he should have.
- Everybody recognized it
even if they resented it
a little.
You know, it was very clear.
"Yeah, of course, you know."
- All righty, everybody.
- He was one of the people
we'd heard about,
and you could tell
how much he loved to perform.
This incredible sort of
generosity of spirit,
and also just
a kind of innocence.
I used to say
that he was the child
that Dan Aykroyd
and John Belushi didn't have.
There was just a joy
in what he was doing.
You were always drawn to him.
I knew I was bringing him
to New York.
- It's a whale.
- It's a boy.
- It's a whale boy.
[applause]
- It was a sad going-away,
a little bit.
We were happy for him,
but we were
also a little nervous...
like, this poor little kid
from Madison
going to go to New York City,
which he'd never been to,
and be on a big TV show.
It's kind of a lot for him,
and it was a lot for him.
He was scared.
- Five, four, three,
two, one, go.
Live from New York,
it's Saturday Night!
- Oh, one more thing.
Live from New York,
it's Saturday Night!
[audience cheers]
- It's so intense
that it's a joke, you know.
By the time you get off of it,
you're like,
"How did I survive that?
That's not possible."
- There's nothing
like the live performance.
It is the most exhilarating,
exciting...
It's, like,
heart-pounding pressure.
- You know, Dana Carvey says
it's like being shot
out of a cannon without a net
once a week.
- "Chris Farley!"
"Yeah, that's right.
Chris is here.
We're going to see Chris Farley
live in this tiny studio."
You'd hear that applause
go up more.
- He was powerful on stage.
I think one of the problems
he first had
when he came to the show,
I think,
was he was still playing
to the back row,
and the fact that the camera's
sort of here
took a little while
to adjust to.
He always played big,
but he learned
how to play big for camera.
- The week Patrick Swayze
hosted, he called me.
He's like,
"Lorne and everybody
wants me to be the fat guy,"
"and they want me to dress
to do a sketch from, uh..."
"where I'm stripping
from Chippendales"
"with Patrick Swayze,"
"and they want me
to take my shirt off,"
"and then I'm the fat guy."
"What do you think?"
"I mean, it's just embarrassing,
you know."
It's like,
"Well, if you do that"
"and you are
the funniest fat guy ever,"
"then you should do it."
- I'm sure he had reservations
about going out there full-on,
but he saw...
"This is my mission.
This is full-on comic value."
"It's a perfect use
of my physicality."
"Yes, I will do it."
- And there's a lot of girth
going with it
and not-give-a-shit pride,
and "This is my body."
He's not thinking it.
He's there.
- Like, I feel really lucky
that I was in high school
when Chris Farley
was on Saturday Night Live.
That was definitely
one of those things
that all the all the kids
around the schoolyard
were like, "Did you see that?"
"Like, that was..."
"that was out of control."
Even just, like, as a fat kid,
it's like "Oh, he's my hero."
Like, he took his shirt off
on national TV,
and he's as good a dancer
as Patrick Swayze is.
The fact that you've got
the late Jan Hooks
and Kevin Nealon and Mike Myers
sitting there,
like, watching, as the...
If they laugh.
The sketch goes poof, goes away.
- I'm doing...
this.
I'm doing a lot of this.
If you kind of look
at my face in the sketch,
it's a little like a dog
that's hearing
a weird frequency.
It was like, "What is that?"
[audience cheers]
- Thank you, Adrian, Barney.
If you could just
give us a minute,
we'll have our decision.
- Oh...
- Adrian... you were great
out there, man.
I know... it's going to be you.
- Oh, what are you talking about,
Barney?
You've got it, and you know it.
- Whatever happens,
you're the best.
- Buddies?
- Buddies.
- They're ready for you guys.
- And then you've got
the thing at the end
where they actually say,
"Well, no.
We're going to go with,"
you know, "with this guy.
He's got a better body,
and he's a much better dancer."
Who did Farley beat out,
then, to get... what?
Yeah, okay, yeah.
- On the one hand,
Chris was acting
like he was embarrassed
about playing the fat guy,
but on the other hand,
he fucking loved it,
and that's the contradiction
he was.
- After the Chippendales,
we were like,
"Oh,
this guy's going to be giant.
He's going to be a huge star."
But I knew that back in Chicago.
- You know, growing up,
you think that showbiz people
come from outer space
or something.
You don't expect to know anybody
who's doing this,
and to just watch
someone you've watched
in improv basements,
you know, on the biggest
comedy stage in the world,
was just so exciting.
- Just to see him on TV
was crazy,
and the family
would all gather around
and go,
"Oh, my god, look at this."
"He's on TV."
- We had seen Chris's sketch,
the Chippendales sketch,
and went,
"We have to sign that guy,"
and he sort of just sat there,
and he would nod a lot,
and then he would go,
"Uh, uh, uh...
Could I be with you guys?"
and we were like,
"No, it's supposed to be
the other way around.
We're supposed
to be pitching you."
- He was incredibly friendly
immediately.
He didn't see it as,
"Oh, here comes the new guy,"
or "Oh, good,"
"I've got more competition
on the show, bubba."
He was just more like,
"Hey," like,
"Fellow comedian, here we go."
- First day, and I see Farley
in the lobby,
and he goes "How are you?
Chris Farley."
"Gallagher Tent and Awning."
Flips his hair around, and...
which I grew to know
over the years,
that was his standard
deep voice, handshake, meet guy.
- The truth is that everybody
that gets the show
usually are unknown and broke.
Suddenly, you know,
you're living your dream life.
I mean, I always say to Lorne,
"Thanks for giving me
the life I dreamed of,"
and that's what you get
if you succeed on that show.
- We were both getting famous,
and literally, when I would walk
down the street with him,
it was no one else seen
except Farley.
It was just "Oh, my god,
there's Chris Farley."
"There's Chris Farley.
There's Chris Farley."
When I walked through Chicago
with him, my god.
- Da Bears.
- Welcome to another edition
of Bill Swerski's Superfans.
- [burps]
That was me.
- Very nice.
All right.
- He was 100% believable
playing the biggest character.
You always were like,
"Yeah, I believe this guy.
I believe this guy's real."
- Everything okay?
-[grunts]
No problem.
Just having a heart attack.
- He'd be pounding his chest,
you know,
having a heart attack
in a hula skirt,
and you're like, "Yeah,
that could be a real guy."
- By the way, I should mention
that Todd was kind enough
to show up today
even though earlier this week,
he had yet another heart attack.
- Yeah, well, the doc says
that I've got a small piece
of Polish sausage
lodged
in the lining of my heart.
- One of the funniest lines to me
was, like,
"How many is that, Todd?"
- Very nice recovery.
Now, how many heart attacks
is that for you, Todd?
- That makes a baker's dozen
for me.
- He didn't do a ton of prep.
He just goes, "Yeah, yeah,
we'll figure it out,"
and there's just only X amount
you can be taught,
and then there's a guy
that, like that walks in.
You go, "Oh, he...
he skips it all,"
and it works.
- Da... Bulls...
da Bulls, da Bulls,
da Bulls...
- Yeah.
- Da Bulls, da Bulls,
da Bulls...
- Very good.
- Because everyone can fall down
and whatever,
but you can't do it that good.
He doesn't put his hands up,
which is what I would do.
So he doesn't block his fall,
and that's...
You can't do those forever.
I think Chevy Chase warned him
not to do that.
- Because Chevy'd always had
something there
just before he fell
that he could hit
that broke the fall,
but Chris was just taking it
as paid.
- Da Bulls, da Bulls, da Bulls.
- He wasn't paying
close enough attention
to see that there was
a way you could do it
and not hurt yourself.
His commitment was total.
- Chris, if I happened
to be in the building
and he happened to be
in the building,
would knock on the door
and go, "Michael!"
"You're such a good writer."
"What are you writing?"
and I'd be like,
"I'm writing a Sprockets."
He goes, "Can I be in it?"
Like this, just completely...
And I'd go, "I don't know.
Sure. I don't know."
"Can you do a German accent?"
"No, no, I can't.
I can't!"
And then he'd just...
"I can't!"
- He's not going
to be the idea man,
but he's going
to take any idea you bring in
and make it better.
- I know
he didn't write for himself,
because a lot of those guys
wrote for themselves,
the smart ones,
and they created these things,
and he kind of was at the mercy
of other people.
- I think he was very intimidated
by the writers.
I don't think he felt
like he could contribute
in sketch writing,
but of course he could,
because he had great instincts,
and he could put himself
into a character's mindset,
and he could improvise
lines and moments
by just doing the character.
- All you've got to do
is kind of hold on to Chris
like a ski lift, you know?
He'll lift you up the hill.
And so you would give him
a sketch and go,
"How would you make that funny
if you said it your way?"
or whatever, and honest to god,
he would destroy it
with how he would do it.
- When we would have
a hundred people
in the read-through,
it was a hundred people
pulling for Farley.
He was the easiest guy
to write for, for sure.
- He did try to write one sketch
because he never wrote sketches,
and it was called
"Puppy Lawyer,"
and it was about 14 pages,
and it was horrible,
and it was too long,
and at the read-through,
it was dying,
and just...
and then I kept looking
at the read-through,
going. "Ch, my god.
It's dying."
[whistling sound]
[explosion]
Bomb.
Then he grabs really hard
when he gets nervous.
"David,
I'm going to get in trouble,"
and then after that,
I would say,
"I'm working
on Puppy Lawyer."
"Your honor, arf arf."
- I think
you see the purest Chris,
um, when we did
the Chris Farley Show.
You see the timidness.
You see the awkwardness.
Somebody didn't write
the character of Chris Farley.
That was Chris Farley.
- It's almost
an impersonator's ability
to pick up on the way the person
talks about themselves
or sees the world,
and heighten it a little bit,
and that was Chris right there.
The Chris Farley Show.
That's how he felt
about the world.
- Welcome
to The Chris Farley Show.
I'm Chris Farley.
- Most regular people relate
to that
being a little star-struck,
and even
when he was a star himself,
I don't think he ever stopped
being kind of awestruck
by celebrities he admired.
- My guest tonight is
one of the greatest musicians...
uh, rock musicians...
I guess, songwriter... ever.
- "You're Paul McCartney."
"Yes."
"And you were the Beatles."
- Remember when you were
with the Beatles?
[audience laughs]
[applause]
- Sure. Sure.
- That was awesome.
[audience laughs]
- Yeah, it was.
Yeah.
- That was a magnified version
of himself,
of his own insecurities,
and you knew when
he was doing those interviews
that was the arc of the sketch,
was we wait
for his falling apart,
because he was "so stupid!"
"Damn it.
Why did I say that?"
- So stupid.
What a dumb question.
- No, no, no.
Chris, I get asked that
all the time in interviews.
- Awkwardly, like,
"I know, I'm an idiot,"
and "Oh, it's so great,
what you do,"
and he kind of felt that way
about almost anybody.
- His self-deprecating manner
was another part
of the vulnerability
that he put in
a lot of the things that he did.
- "And in the end,
the love you take
is equal to the love you make."
You remember that?
[audience laughs]
- Yes.
- Is that true?
[audience laughs]
- All that love
that came out of the guy
was him just apologizing
by nature
for a lot of stuff that he...
I wish he'd never
had to apologize for.
[applause]
- Yes, Chris,
in my experience, it is.
I find the more you give,
the more you get.
- Oh...
Awesome!
- All the stars that would come
on the show,
on Saturday Night Live,
the hosts,
they would just, out loud,
just go, "I love you."
"You're the best."
"I watch the show
because of you," you know.
We'd all be, like,
"That's funny, man.
They all love Farley."
- When Christian Slater came,
he had his hair greased back.
He goes,
"Christian Slater's cool,"
which he said
about every single host.
He started
combing his hair back,
and I go, "Oh, no, no."
"Is it Single White Female?"
He goes, "It's cool, man."
- Every host was like,
"Please put me in a skit
with that guy."
They just loved being around
that energy.
- He was sort of nervous
outward,
so he would try
to show off a lot,
try to be funny all the time,
and that was his way
of flirting.
I remember he was walking
around with a Diet Coke,
and I think Glenn Close
was there, talking,
and I could see him looking,
and she goes, "Well,
talk to you later."
He goes, "Yeah, okay,"
and he goes...
[glugging sounds]
And he chugged the whole Diet...
and she goes, "Okay."
She walked away, and I go,
"Was that...
Are you showing off?"
and he goes, "Yeah,
I chugged the whole thing."
I go, "And who cares?"
and he's like, "Shut up, dude."
- That was, like,
his Achilles' heel, you know.
Any time
you were in front of a girl,
he was very bashful.
- Chris was very attractive
to women, very attractive,
and had some of the most
beautiful women in Hollywood
would come by the set
to visit him
because he was nice to people.
He was nice to everybody.
He was funny, he was sweet,
and he was a gentleman.
- It starts with
that genuine expression,
that sincerity here,
that was so attractive,
and then his power
and his strength.
He had an incredible masculinity
at the same time.
- You know, he's not
your traditional leading man,
you know what I mean,
but it's...
there's no one like him.
And he was infectious,
and he was kind,
and he was a puppy dog.
There was nothing malicious
about him,
arrogant about him.
It was a purity.
- It may not be what you thought
was Ken doll,
but it comes together,
and it's extremely attractive.
- There was probably
a part of him
that always wondered,
"Do these women
want to be with me"
"just because I'm famous,"
"or do they really like me?"
- He was trying to pull out of me
what it was like.
"How does it work with fame?"
"How do you live with fame"
"and have a really good
relationship?"
- I met David Spade in a deli.
He knew who I was
because I was, like,
doing Victoria's Secret.
He heard my voice,
and he started laughing,
and I knew he was laughing
at my voice.
David kept saying,
"You remind me of Chris.
You act like Chris."
I said,
"I want to meet this Chris,"
and he said, "No, because
you'll fall in love with him,"
and, um...
the first time I met him,
I just looked at him and said,
"I love that guy."
And then we just started
hanging out all the time,
you know?
I didn't really know
the goofball so much.
I would see it sometimes,
you know,
but there was just
a whole different side to him
that I thought
was just so beautiful.
It was just so beautiful.
- We'd gone to church together,
and we drove through
a very nice neighborhood.
He said,
"I'd really like to settle here"
"and have a wife
and have children,"
"and raise my family here,"
I think very much similar
to what he had been raised in.
He really longed for that.
- A lot of comics,
they're not really funny
away from performing,
and then a few are,
and he was one of those.
He was very funny off-camera.
As far as, like,
just physically doing
anything for a laugh,
Chris would just...
He'd do anything.
- The funniest thing
that Chris ever did,
and he did it pretty
much every week,
and I always forgot,
so I had, like,
an insane routine down.
I'd go to the upper deck
outside of Lorne's office
and watch the musical acts,
because I knew
that I would never have a chance
again in my life
to see
so many fantastic musical acts,
and then I would go
and have a shower
at exactly the same time,
and Chris,
every time I was in the shower,
would rip the curtain back.
I'd be completely naked.
He would tuck everything and go,
"Michael, I love you so much,"
and he would pin me
against the wall in the shower,
and I would whale on him
like this, just whale on him,
like, "Get off me. Get off me."
"Just give me one kiss, Michael.
I love you so much."
It was the most frightening
thing in the world,
and it killed me every time,
and I forgot every week,
because you would think
that's not something
you'd forget,
and every time, I'd go,
"Oh, god, of course.
I should have my shower at home,
not at work."
- My daughter asked me
what was the best thing
I've ever done in show business,
and I said,
"On stage,"
"doing 'Motivational Speaker'
with Chris Farley"
"eight times a week,"
"no question,"
and nothing
will ever come close.
- Let's get better acquainted
by letting me give you
a little bit of a scenario
of what my life is all about.
- At Second City,
people would come in,
like, waiters and waitresses,
bartenders, staff,
that would come in
at, like, 9:18,
because they knew
that's about the time
"Motivational Speaker"
was coming on at Second City.
- First off, I am 35 years old.
I am divorced,
and I live in a van
down by the river.
- He had done some speech
in kind of that voice.
- Bob Odenkirk and everyone else
recognized
that they had to do something
with this character.
It was just too compelling
and funny.
- It was so fun.
He pushed it, and he broke you,
and did it every time.
It was insane.
- Probably going to go out there
and say,
"Hey, I'm going to take
the world by the tail,"
"wrap it around, pull it down,
and put it in my pocket."
- I thought, "What if the guy
is using himself"
"as an example
of why not to do it,"
"because of 'Look at me.
Look where I am.' "
He is still the worst example.
I mean, the sketch
has great structure to it,
but the fact is,
it's a framework for this
insanely wonderful performance.
- You're not going
to amount to jack squat!
[audience laughs]
- It was a grand slam
every single fucking time.
It was nuts, nuts.
- As I told you,
my name is Matt Foley,
and I am a motivational speaker.
[audience laughs]
- Chris, when he did it,
was doing his dad
as a character,
and his dad...
great guy, but when he got mad,
he, like,
transcended a scream level,
scarier-sounding pocket,
and it was more like, you know,
"Christopher, I am not going
to tell you again."
- Dad, I wish you could just shut
your big yapper!
- Then we'd played rugby
with a guy, Larry Hill,
he kind of ran
on the outside of his feet,
so he would kind of...
Larry would play rugby
like this,
so he's there doing Larry,
going,
"What we're going to do..."
- Young lady, what do you want
to do with your life?
- He took
what he loved about them
and made it his own.
- You're telling me
there's a real Matt Foley?
I did not know that.
It's someone's unfortunate
position to be like,
"Oh, well, I'm on TV now."
- I am the Matt Foley.
It's the height of my career,
living in a van
down by the river.
Caught a lot of questions
in the last 25 years
about that.
- He would often name or re-name
his characters at Second City
after friends that he would spot
in the audience,
and in that case,
the name just stuck.
- Then he comes out,
"My name is Matt Foley,"
and does that bit,
and I just kind of sunk down
in my chair a little bit,
and said, "Oh, my god,
where's this going?"
- He told him, apparently,
"I'm never changing the name."
You know.
"I'm keeping it."
"He's always going
to be Matt Foley."
- We're going to be buddies!
We're going to be pals!
We're going to wrestle!
- I was humbled.
It was a wonderful,
wonderful expression
of our relationship,
but my little slice of notoriety
was well appreciated,
and I give thanks to him
every day for that.
- I'm living in a van
down by the river!
- You didn't often
see Second City scenes
brought fully formed
to SNL that way.
- He just had this thing wired
and perfected from Second City,
so once
he even did a read-through,
everyone loved it.
- Your father and I came up
with a brilliant idea
to give you kids
some direction...
A motivational speaker.
- Yeah, it was
Christina Applegate,
and she was the host.
- And I remember Lorne Michaels
saying to me,
apologetic in a way, like,
"He has this character"
"he's really been wanting
to do on the show."
"We're not sure what it is."
"Do you mind if we premiere it
in your episode?"
and I was like, "Well, yeah,
of course," you know.
"Let's see what it is."
- Matt, we're ready for you.
- Out comes Chris
out of that door.
- All right, how's everybody?
Now, let's get started
by letting me give you
a little bit of a scenario
of what my life is all about.
First off, I am 35 years old.
I am divorced,
and I live
in a van down by the river.
[audience laughs]
- He'd combine
the scratchy voice,
move his glasses around,
he can't see,
and then grabs his belt,
or when he's sideways to you,
he crosses his eyes
so the audience can't see,
try new tricks, and he'd just...
"Huh? Huh?"
- Okay, I'm going to go out
and I'm going to get the world
by the tail,
and wrap it around
and pull it down
and put it in my pocket.
- We all just kind of stopped.
What is going on?
And it just, the...
"Doo, doo,
on the right track."
- How can we get back
on the right track?
[audience laughs]
- Bigger, and more crazy,
and we just... that was it.
- When Chris did Matt Foley,
he tried to make everyone
crack up.
- Well, la-Di-frickin'-da.
[audience laughs]
We've got ourselves
a writer here.
- I think just the combo
of watching the audience
see it for the first time
and realizing
this is such a funny thing,
and we'd seen it all week.
I started thinking
it was funnier again.
- Ol' Matt's going
to be your shadow.
Here's you, here's Matt.
There's you, there's...
[Crash]
[audience laughs, applauds]
Whoops-a-daisy.
- You could see me,
I'm hiding behind my hair
because I knew
that if I looked at him
for one second more,
I was going to drop
off that couch.
I couldn't even get my line out.
I knew that,
"Okay, I have one line."
- What do you want
to do with your life?
- "I want to live in a van
down by the river."
It's the only joke I had
in the whole thing,
and I just was like...
[whispers]
- I want to live in a van
down by the river.
- "I want to live in a van
down by the river,"
and I just put my head
back down.
- Well,
you'll have plenty of time
to live in a van
down by the river when...
you're living
in a van down by the river!
- You can't design it
in a laboratory,
but "I live in a van
down by the river..."
The first time I heard that,
I was like, "Hm."
"That's yummy. I know that one."
- He made my whole body
go into convulsions of joy.
- And I was more scared
of getting in trouble.
I did not want
to get yelled at by Lorne.
I didn't want one more reason
to get rid of me.
- From what I've heard,
you're using your paper
not for writing,
but for rolling doobies.
You're going to be doing
a lot of doobie-rolling
when you're living in a van
down by the river.
- It just was thrilling.
It was...
it was like watching
Evel Knievel, you know.
You just kind of
couldn't believe it.
- We knew
that we were in the presence
of something
that was pretty great.
I don't think any of us,
on that day,
knew that "Motivational Speaker"
was going to become such
an iconic character for him.
It was an incredible moment,
though.
It was pretty cool
to see that happen.
- I don't give a rat's behind,
because I'm moving in.
I'm sick and tired of living
in a van down by the river!
[applause]
- I mean, he lit up a room,
and Chris did everything
to excess.
He was your friend to excess.
He loved you to excess.
He was kind to excess.
But when it came to, you know,
drinking and other stuff,
Chris got caught in a world
that I don't know
if he could get out of.
- Chris was one
of Lorne's favorite performers,
and one of his favorite men,
and truly, truly loved him.
Lorne was never concerned
about, you know,
assisting Chris
in his artistic ability.
He was more concerned
about the lifestyle.
- There was some part of him
that clearly trusted
that if he was
a little bit fucked up,
that it would be all right,
or that it would be...
maybe that was
where the magic came from.
- Chris and Lorne
had a father-figure
kind of a relationship.
Lorne was always worried
about Chris,
and he looked out for Chris
a lot, you know.
Lorne was very good to Chris,
and Chris looked up to Lorne.
- When he got to SNL,
whatever track he was on
as far as, you know,
any drinking
or anything like that,
that was just sort of
set in line,
and so all the wheels
were in motion
by the time we got to him,
you know.
It's just hard to deal with,
and not everyone's that stable.
I'm not, and it's very hard.
- So many comedians
have low self-esteem,
feeling like, "Well,
if I'm not making people laugh,"
"do I really deserve to be here?"
- But he was this boy
who wanted to do good.
He wanted to impress his dad
and his mom
and his family so much,
but then there was
this other side of him,
so his whole life
was this constant battle.
- You know, bars filled
from ceiling to cash register
full of booze,
and he goes, "Johnny,
don't you ever look at that"
"and just want to drink"
"every single drop
of all that stuff right there?"
and I go, "Nope,"
"it didn't really
enter my mind, Chris."
- He was a very sweet guy...
before midnight.
He was as open
and like a six-year-old
as he was dark,
and the darkness was compelling,
but not something
you want to really be around.
- When he would get
super messed up,
he would pull away a little bit.
"Everybody's on my ass.
I want to be by myself."
"I've got the exact drugs
I'm going to do,"
"and then
I'm going to get it together,"
which is not the way it goes.
The way it goes
is you get messed up,
then you really, you know,
you call your buddies.
- When you're jumping up steps
in the showbiz ladder
and you're leaping
over everyone around you,
and everyone around you
is going,
"You'd better watch out,"
some part of you
has to be going,
"No, you'd better watch out,"
"because I'm kicking ass
every day."
- I kind of grabbed him once,
and I just took him,
just with all my might,
I just took him
behind this curtain
at an after-thing,
and I said,
"Dude, what the fuck?"
"Seriously?"
And he'd get very,
"Michael, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
You're right, you're right,
you're right."
I said, "Seriously, dude,
what the fuck," you know?
- There came a point,
certainly there came a point
in his story
where he gave credence
to everyone's warnings
and worries.
- The thing he loved the most
was doing the show,
so taking it away from him,
we sent him
to a very sort of tough place
in the South,
I think in Alabama,
and that period
was really hard for him,
but I think it also...
he came back
much clearer and determined
that that was never
going to happen again.
- Hey, girls.
Did I miss anything?
[applause]
- Nothing.
Chrissy's being stupid again.
- [giggles]
- Oh, god, I love these fries.
- If you love them so much,
why don't you marry them?
[laughs]
Can I have some?
- Um, sure, Cindy, go ahead.
- Oh, god, these are good.
- Uh, Cindy,
can you leave some for us?
- [laughs]
- I thought you were, um,
trying to lose weight.
- [deep voice] Lay off me,
I'm starving.
[applause]
[giggles]
Diet starts Monday.
- There was this steak joint
called "the Steak Joint,"
and they had this thing called
the Trenchman's Cut, which...
This thing was probably
this big and this wide,
roast beef,
and I'd be, like,
"How are you going to eat that
and go on stage?"
He'd be like, "I can do it."
We'd all be like, "Go, go, go."
- Oh, look, Tammy,
it's the Gap girls,
and they're eating.
What a surprise.
- You're so dumb,
when they were passing out
brains,
you thought they said "trains,"
and then... you got on it...
on a train,
and then went for a ride.
[applause]
- Two rib-eyes, medium...
and I'm not exaggerating,
I'm not trying to be funny,
he'd taken the rib-eyes,
he'd kind of put it in his mouth
and stripped it,
kind of, almost...
like a sparerib or something.
And I look over at the plate,
and both the rib-eyes
are gone.
Later on, we were walking,
and I said, "Those steaks,
the way you ate that..."
and he says, "I know. I know.
What am I doing?"
and whenever he said
"What am I doing?"
you knew
that he knew everything.
He knew everything
about himself.
Nothing was, like,
sneaking past him.
It just seemed
like there was always something
massive that he was doing,
something big, something huge.
- Jeez, those two
are always OTR.
- [gasps]
You two are terrible!
[giggling]
- Sometimes he would head-butt me
in sketches,
get so close
it would throw you off,
like "What's going... you're
not supposed to do that."
So that was funny,
and he liked it,
and he'd go "I made you laugh,"
and get excited,
like a child.
- I'll tell you
what he never did.
He didn't make it about himself.
Never sat back
and was cocky about killing.
His laughs were so huge
and thick and long,
the giant roars,
I'd say,
"Did you hear how you...?"
He'd be like, "Really?
Really? It was good?"
If I had some of those roars,
I would definitely
have a lot more of an attitude
right now.
I don't think
I'd be hanging out with you.
- The world of high fashion...
There was never anyone
like Dante.
- These designs are atrocious.
Are you trying to ruin me?
- I shared an office that year,
10 feet wide
with just two wooden desks.
- Oh, Dante...
- I sat there.
Behind me was him.
- That's the third assistant
you've fired this month.
- I had to write my own stuff,
which was tough.
He didn't write or read
or really do anything,
but he was funny,
and that was more important.
- I'll have not have
my decisions questioned, Lucien.
In bed, you're my partner,
but in this office,
you work for me.
- But, Dante...
[laughs]
- Go away.
- Chris Rock and Sandler
had to walk through ours
to get to their little office,
so they would come in and out,
and then
when they locked their door,
you know they're starting
to write hard...
especially Sandler wrote a lot.
- He was a really giving guy
to the other comedians.
Loved the other comedians,
and if you made Farley laugh,
my god, that felt good,
with that giant laugh of his.
- Okay, I've got a package here
for Dante.
- I am Dante.
- All right, here you go.
Sign on the X.
- There.
I'll sign your precious
Federal Express receipt,
and now I wish
you could do me a favor
and buzz off.
- Oh, man.
- There you go.
Excellent!
[cackles]
All right.
- Peekaboo, Dante.
- I was playing
some overly fey character
in the designing
of clothes industry, I believe.
- Well, well, well,
if it isn't Taylor Evans.
If you've come looking
for modeling work,
you're out of luck.
I don't let whores
walk down my runway.
- Charming as always, Dante,
but I don't intend to take "no"
for an answer.
- Well, then, perhaps
you'll take this for an answer.
- "Now go!"
And then at one point,
there was
a little fluffa happened.
There was
a line that got skipped,
and I just, like,
pushed his glasses up,
and his eyes crossed.
It was this delicate moment
that made me very happy.
- I have grown wise
to your trickery, Dante.
- He came from that background
where you pull everybody up,
that you're there for everybody.
You don't leave anybody hanging,
so when you're working with him,
he was just right there
and helping you.
"Come on, buddy," you know,
that kind of thing.
- I was very influenced
by his commitment,
full, all his molecules,
and anybody around him's
molecules,
into his performance.
- So powerful and so ungoverned,
and that was a big part
of, I think, you know,
Chris's appeal.
You always had the
sense that he was...
he was having
the most fun possible.
- Why, it seems the liposuction
done on your face
has clogged your eardrums.
Make like an egg, and beat it.
- It's a word
I wouldn't normally use,
but there was something
always dutiful about him.
He cared about the whole show.
He never fought for his piece
over someone else's piece.
He was most comfortable
being part of it
and caring about it.
- Chris said,
"I want to become so famous"
"that I can go
to children's hospitals"
"and I can cheer the kids up,
and they'll know who I am."
Not a Ferrari, not mansions,
not go to Europe.
That's it.
Like,
that kind of summed up Chris.
- Chris walks
into St. Jude's Hospital.
Within 60 seconds
of being in that kid's room,
they don't care who he is.
They don't care about his fame.
They just know
they're madly in love with him.
And he picks up an IV
and goes, 'Urrr, '
makes believe he's drinking.
The kid doesn't care
about show business.
It's not Tom Brady.
It's Chris.
- Chris was a real Catholic
in the best sense,
not in a casual passing sense.
He lived it.
He walked the walk.
He went and visited people
on weekends
and didn't even tell anybody
about it, like,
to bring them meals
or make them laugh.
- His dad told him
a long time ago,
"Only by the grace of God go I,"
so he saw those
that were most vulnerable,
and he saw how blessed he was
and recognized
that those people, I think,
he related to best.
- The acts of kindness
that he did off-camera,
which were true acts
of sort of piety and modesty,
that part of him
I don't think people knew.
- We would go
by a homeless person
and I'd go,
"Uh, I don't have anything,"
and Chris goes,
"What if we just passed
Jesus Christ?"
"You know, they say he could
come back as a homeless man"
"or something."
"Maybe he's testing us."
- Kevin Nealon and Mike Myers
and Adam Sandler and David Spade
were all sitting around,
and someone says, "How big
do you think you're going to be"
"as a performer?"
And it went around the room,
and they were all going, like,
"I don't know.
I'll be pretty big, I guess."
I'm pretty funny."
"I think I'll do fine,"
and everyone kind of leaves,
you know,
and it's just Chris and I
were left in the room there,
you know, and I go, "Really?"
"Yeah ."
"Really,
that's what you think?"
and he looked around, waited
for them to be out of earshot,
and then he goes,
"I'm going to be so huge."
"Oh, my god,
I'm going to be so huge."
"I'm going to be a giant star."
- Let me tell you something.
On that program,
no offense to anybody else,
you're the life of the party,
buddy.
[audience cheers]
- Scripts are coming in.
You're reading constantly.
You're trying to figure out
what are the best moves.
I always call it the ride,
where the ride is headed up
and the trajectory
is straight up,
and that's where Chris was.
- I was there when Lorne
was developing Chris as a talent
and then breaking him out
as a movie star.
- When we were shooting
Wayne's World,
Chris was in it for one scene.
He played the security guard,
and Mike and Dana
were, you know,
at the top of their game.
- I remember on Wayne's World,
he turned to me
and said, "How am I doing?"
"Is it going well?"
I said, "Yeah, it's going well."
I said, "I'd just like
to point out, Chris,"
"that this is my first movie."
"I've actually never even
been in a movie."
"This is my absolute first movie,
so I'm..."
"Well, you seem so at home
and seem so natural,"
and I said, "It's not."
"I'm terrified,"
"and I have no idea
what I'm doing."
- He was so sweet in Coneheads
and wonderful,
and just to be on the set
with him was great.
- Chris was the romantic lead.
- When you first sign somebody
as an agent,
you want to introduce them
to everybody in the town
who can make a difference
in their movie career.
First of all, he wore
the same thing to every meeting,
which was a button-down white
tearaway SNL wardrobe shirt,
so it would have
the buttons down,
but underneath it was Velcro...
and he wore that probably
three or four days in a row.
- All right.
- [laughs]
It's a clip-on.
- Are you sure?
All right, now...
- Wayne's World, the Coneheads,
all of those little cameos,
we can call them, that he did
were getting him
more and more notice.
It was still very much
within the SNL family,
and Billy Madison
was Adam saying, you know,
"I want Chris
to play this part."
- Everybody on?
Good. Great.
Grand! Wonderful!
No yelling on the bus!
Hey!
[tires screeching]
- You laugh at the fact
that this guy's
been through hell,
and he's handling it
to the best he can,
and he's still lovable.
- I'll turn this damn bus
around.
That'll end
your precious little field trip
pretty damn quick, huh?
Shit.
- That was bananas.
We don't even know
what the hell happened to him.
He turned dark red,
and I remember having to cut
around literally every take.
Like, it would be like,
"I think we've got three frames
before Adam laughed there,"
"so maybe we can use that shot
right there."
It was hard to cut around,
but he was nuts.
He was nuts.
He was so loose
as the bus driver.
- All of these guys
tend to work together
and collaborate.
The environment there
just breeds friendship.
- Everyone knew he had talent,
and everyone wanted him
in their movie,
and he was riding high.
It was nice to see him just
kind of rolling, doing well.
He started wearing suits.
He'd go down
to the Rochester Big and Tall
and buy, like, 10 suits,
and he'd slick his hair back,
and I'm like, "Who's this guy?"
"What are you, a Hollywood guy?"
But it was fun.
It was fun to see.
- It was cool to see the man
driving up in, like,
a convertible Caddy or something
and just having huge money
and tipping people
and just being like
what you expect he would be.
- He loved to be an actor.
He just loved it.
He loved every minute of it,
you know,
and so he was just happy,
just having a good time,
killing it.
- In Hollywood in the old days,
they used to call it "it,"
when someone had "it."
They didn't know
how to describe it either,
so they called it "it,"
and he had "it."
- The pressure
of Saturday Night Live
is once you get the show,
everyone's looking at you like,
"Oh, you have a chance
to do movies and be famous
and be a movie star."
- First of all, to get a movie,
that's the hustle.
You have to be able
to get in the movie,
and Chris got in the movie,
and the movie
that he got in was Tommy Boy.
- Aah!
- I've got
to go to the bathroom, Daddy.
[music] Maniac... [music]
Aah!
- If you mention Tommy Boy,
80% of the people go
"Fat guy in a little coat"
because of the way
Chris did it, what it was,
and all that sort of stuff,
and that to me
is the best way to say
that's Chris Farley.
- Richard...
Is this your coat?
- Fat guy in a little coat
was something
that Farley did to Spade.
- Don't do it.
- Fat guy in a little coat.
- In my office,
he'd put the coat on.
"David,
I've got your jacket on."
"Fat..."
- Fat guy in a little coat.
- Don't.
- David, for real, would say,
"Chris, take it off."
"Take the jacket off."
"You're going to break my ja...
You're going to split it."
"Take it off.
Take it off."
"Oh, fat guy in a little coat."
- [music] Fat guy
in a little coat... [music]
- Take it off, dickhead.
I'm serious.
- Richard, what's happening?
[ripping]
- He and Spade were
just induplicable as a team,
wonderful together.
David is very acerbic,
and he's, you know,
he's a toughie,
and Chris is a softie.
You've got the best
of Belushi and Aykroyd,
of Abbott and Costello,
of Martin and Lewis.
You had just a perfect yin-yang
situation with those guys.
- A fantastic combination
of ultimately innocent
and ultimately jaded.
They are the oil and vinegar
of comedy.
- Ugh, I can actually hear you
getting fatter.
- They would react to stress
in different ways.
Chris would get bigger,
and there'd be less of David,
and I used to say
that the amount of weight
in the frame
kind of stayed constant,
you know, in a two-shot.
- They were funny.
They were close.
You could tell they
were really good friends,
and only really,
really good friends
can fight the way they fought.
- You don't want none of me.
Think it through.
- Come on, give me
your best shot.
I'll give you a free one.
Let me have it.
[grunts]
That was a good one.
- They'd throw something
and not speak to each other
for a couple hours,
and we'd all sit there and laugh
and watch this thing
go back and forth.
- That's it!
You are going to die!
I am going to get you!
- And when I would visit
those fools during the shoot,
they'd have little fights
on occasion,
and Farley would have a snap,
and Spade would be scared
for his life.
They were in love
with each other.
We all were in love,
but Spade and Farley
had a definite
brotherly relationship.
- Tommy Boy is basically
a skeleton sketch
of how we grew up in Wisconsin,
minus Bo Derek, of course.
- I met Chris
literally on the set,
and I looked down,
and Chris was doing pushups,
and just...
And he got up,
and his face was beet red,
and he was so cute, so adorable.
- Holy schnykies.
- First scene, of course,
was the swimming pool scene.
- Oh, man.
Dad, she's like a 10.
- Hi, honey.
- And Chris was funny all day,
and he actually made me relax
by making fun of me, kind of,
which was good.
- I'm Tommy.
- I'm Beverly,
and you are just adorable.
- Brian Dennehy's character
and Chris,
that was a lot of him
and my dad.
It's kind of like
who my dad was, you know,
this big, gruff,
great salesman guy, you know.
- Hi, Dad.
- Tommy!
[both laugh]
- Ooh...
- We had that in common.
We both loved our dads,
and we both were...
anything our fathers said,
we'd be like,
"Well, now I have to do it,
because my dad told me to."
- Scram, don't give her
the weight room thing.
- Do you know
where the weight room is?
I'll check it out.
- Sorry.
- I was hanging out with David
and Chris and Fred Wolf,
so he wrote a part for me,
but I wasn't supposed
to be naked in that part.
I was supposed to just
jump in the swimming pool,
and then they're like,
"Okay, and then you
take your bathing suit..."
and I was like "What?"
and they're like, "We rented out
this whole thing,"
and da da da da da.
"You're not going
to not do it now, are you?"
It was such a pressure thing.
Chris was so worried about,
"You've got to make her
comfortable,"
and he would just always try
to make me laugh, like,
or always put a towel
around me, like...
he was just being
such a protective gentleman.
- I'm back.
Richard?
What were you doing?
- Going over some documents.
- Look at his movie performances.
The physicality, I mean...
and Tommy Boy, just the...
you saw
his quality as an actor there,
and his range as an actor.
- I'm going to really miss him.
- Your father was a great guy.
- Yeah.
- What I think
was really important
with Tommy Boy
is it showed Chris
how we saw him
behind closed doors.
Sensitive. Kind.
That kindness,
and that real vulnerability.
- Oh, Richard, I'm so happy.
Hold me.
- Yikes.
- Don't run away
from your feelings.
- It's so great
when everyone leaves you alone.
We're just trying to...
"What's the funniest thing
we can do here"
"that makes us laugh?"
Sandler, during Tommy Boy,
wrote him a sketch
in Pepper Boy.
- Say when.
- When.
- Grazie.
- Adam Sandler
is Pepper Boy, right?
It's like, you know,
"Fresh pepper?"
and he would give people pepper.
He's under high scrutiny
for this.
- It is an art
of the Pepper Boy, Carlo.
Don't let it die with me.
Please, let me teach it to you.
- Teach me, Senor Marco.
- We had to fly all the way back
from Toronto to do the show,
and I wasn't even in it.
- All right.
You see that man right there?
- Farley was in it,
but he only had one line
in that sketch,
so he was mad about it,
so he put on this huge beard.
He looked ridiculous.
He goes, "Watch this line.
I'll get a laugh,"
and I'm like,
"I don't think so."
"You're not supposed to.
It's supposed to be Sandler,"
but...
- Fresh-y pepper?
- He goes, "Oh yeah? Huh?"
Bite his lip,
and you knew
you were in trouble.
- Why, thank you, Pepper Boy!
That's the perfect
amount of pepper.
Bravo!
- "Why, thank you, Pepper BOY,"
and we're like...
- Of course,
if you only have one line,
why did you fucking put on
a beard for one Li...
Like, it's, like,
this is the funniest shit ever,
and he's, like, just the guy...
He's a warm body in the sketch.
It's an Adam Sandler sketch.
- Bravo!
- That was his, like,
fighting back
at, "Watch how funny I can be,"
and it works.
He's great at it.
-30 seconds before a skit,
would tap you on the shoulder
and go,
"I'm going to get you."
He did that a few times to me,
and he always got me.
- You did it!
How do you feel?
- Like I can fly, senor,
on wings made of pepper.
- He was aware of his power.
He was aware of his gift.
He's got his BA
from Second City.
He's got his Master's
from Saturday Night Live.
Totally equipped-
- Saturday Night Live
with a feature film
where he's the lead...
I can't imagine the pressure
of just flying alone
back and forth
to be doing a movie,
then flying for the show,
then fly back
to be up at 5:00 a.m.
Monday morning
to shoot the mov...
I mean,
it's incredible pressure.
- That's going
to wear everybody down,
but it didn't wear Chris down
at all,
not even a little bit.
He didn't seem...
he didn't...
I would...
"How are you doing?"
"Yeah, it's great.
So what are we doing now?"
He just didn't show
any signs of wear at all.
- He will be
a major motion picture star
when his brand-new film,
Tommy Boy,
opens nationwide.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome
the human thunderball,
Chris Farley.
[audience cheers]
Watch free HD Movies and TV Shows at
StreamingSites.com
[audience cheers louder]
A very impressive entrance.
I think in the 10 years
we've been doing this show,
I've never seen anything
quite like that.
- I want to do
what the king wants,
so I'd like to do that.
I'm on the Dave Letterman show!
By golly...
- How are you doing, buddy?
All excited
about your big movie?
- Aw, man.
- You and David Spade.
David Spade, a very funny man,
very nice guy,
and you guys are friends
as well as working together
on the show,
and now on this big movie.
- Yeah, he's my buddy.
We had a lot of fun.
- When the movie came out,
the reviews were bad.
For him, the idea that it could
be that willfully hurtful
took him back,
and he didn't have
the confidence yet,
because it was his first movie,
you know,
because I'd say,
"Let them wash over you,"
"and in two weeks,
nobody will care."
"All that matters is the work,"
"and it's a piece of work
that will be around."
- When the video came out,
it was an obsession.
Our generation was into him,
and that was the coolest.
- It's interesting that a movie
that was that savaged
ended up being sort of a movie
that's never gone away.
- Time magazine published a page
of the 10 Comedies of All Time,
and Tommy Boy's there,
and I know that Farley
would have been incredibly proud
to see it there.
- I really love this movie.
I hope
that everyone will like it,
because we had fun making it,
and I think it's really good.
- I hope so, too.
I hope it's a huge hit for you
and for David Spade
and everybody else as well.
- Because if I don't,
I'm going back
to Wisconsin on the farm,
so go to it!
No, no, that was stupid too.
I shouldn't have...
- [laughs]
- Chris was at a place,
not that he didn't need
SNL at that point,
because it feels
like it just had kind of
run its course.
- Once you're on the show
and then you're in a movie
that does really, really well,
it's weird being on the show.
It's not like you think
you're better than the show...
never, of course.
The movies are a lot of work.
The love you get
for what you've done
lasts for years,
and on Saturday Night Live,
it's gone by Sunday morning.
- For Chris,
the pull of Hollywood
was now very strong.
A new administration
came in at NBC.
I think they did not like him.
They did not like Adam Sandler.
It was a generational change.
- What happens
after SNL is scary, man,
and you don't want it to end.
I remember the last party,
looking at each other
and being like,
"This is it, man?
This is over, that great run?
Now what?"
- From my own experience
being on the show,
you always wanted,
like, to be on the show
and then have a movie out
that was a hit
at the same time,
and so if they don't do well,
you think, "Well, at least
I still have the show,"
"so I'm not, like,
completely out of it."
- And he was getting big offers
to do stuff,
big money,
they had big directors,
everybody loved him.
So he had stuff to do,
but there's that fear of,
like, "What the hell am I doing?"
"Why am I going
to be out on my own?"
because there,
you're a team together,
then all of a sudden,
it's all you.
- He said, "Kitten..."
"I only saw myself
doing Saturday Night Live."
"Like, that was my goal,
was to do Saturday Night Live"
"and make my father laugh."
"I never imagined myself
doing movies."
And I said, "Oh, no..."
"It's not in his comfort zone,"
and when
you don't get in your...
you're past your comfort zone,
you've got to make sure
you're really grounded.
Otherwise,
it can just be overwhelming.
- He was a giant TV star,
a giant movie star,
but the kind of routine
of having the show
and the family
and the same people and Lorne
and all his "brothers,"
and without that,
it wasn't the same.
I mean,
it might have made him feel
like he was floundering,
like there wasn't the safety
of the show,
the security of that set...
family atmosphere.
- Hi, ma'am.
Vote for Donnelly.
- Tommy Boy's a movie
that stayed with people,
and then what happens
is the studio is sort of like,
"We're going to try
to replicate that."
to grab whatever Tommy Boy had"
"and make it that again,"
you know,
and I get that.
- Paramount had an option on him
from Tommy Boy,
and so he had to do Black Sheep.
- Fred Wolf was 60 pages
into the script
when we were green-lit,
and I went,
"We don't actually
have a script yet."
- Listen, I think it's better
if we bring the energy
down a tad.
- Are you kidding me?
It's showmanship.
You've got to go out
and get 'em.
- It was like Tommy Boy.
We wanted to get back
and do that.
He goes,
"That's the one people like,
and we should try it again."
Fred gave him
a rolling down a hill.
He'd just keep falling,
because it gets funnier
because it's so stupid.
He's just very good at anything
you give him like that.
He can come up with, like,
jerky moves and funny faces,
and he snaps his head around.
- Bunk beds.
I've got dibs on top.
- Okay.
- In the cabin with David,
or him
rolling down that hill, or...
There was
lots of really funny things.
- Nothing's going
to stop us now.
[engine fails to start]
- We knew there was a difference
between Black Sheep
and Tommy Boy,
and Chris knew that, too.
The process became interrupted.
It just got to be manipulated
by people from outside.
- Okay,
maybe we could use some help.
- The two pictures grossed
almost exactly
the same amount of money,
so the fact that one vehicle
maybe was a little rushed
and maybe not made as lovingly
as the first one was,
that's what you take away
when you're doing it.
- Chris was a perfectionist,
and he was always, you know,
he just wanted to do the best,
and if it wasn't the best,
he was really hard on himself.
- Just because
things aren't perfect
doesn't mean
people won't like them.
- Unfortunately,
I was with him when it...
when it...
when he relapsed the first time.
And we were...
He called me up, and he said,
"Do you want to go see...
We're doing a preview show
of Black Sheep."
He was just getting nervous,
and he was upset,
and to see it onscreen,
he was like...
it just was enough
to set him off.
And the next day,
my Dad calls me up.
He was like,
"What happened last night?"
It's like, "What do you mean?"
It's like, "Christopher
trashed his hotel room,"
"and, you know, he's back
in the, you know, rehab, and..."
It's like, holy shit.
- So he went off the handle
for two weeks,
then they dragged him
back into rehab.
A couple more rehabs,
and then sober
for Beverly Hills Ninja.
- Here's the thing.
If you're a drug addict,
you know,
and an alcoholic,
all of a sudden you're sober,
you're sober today.
Like, it's a day.
"I'm sober.
Oh, look at me, I'm sober."
But if you're fat,
and I speak from experience...
you look in the mirror,
and you've eaten healthy
one day,
you're still fat.
You're like,
"How do I beat this thing?"
- I have always looked up to you,
and you have always
looked out for me,
but now it is time
that I look out for myself.
- Be careful in your travels,
Haru.
The world is a dangerous place.
[grunts]
- When I saw him,
and he was cleaned up,
and he'd been to rehab
a couple times,
and he was refusing booze
at this party,
he was standing up for himself,
and he wasn't a kid going,
"What? What do you want?"
"Oh, yeah, cool, great,
whatever you've got I'll do"
"to make you happy,
to be a part of this."
He was saying,
"No, I need to protect myself."
- I think it's important
to just have a self-esteem
and believe in yourself
and be able to tell the world...
I guess, "Go fuck yourself,"
on some level.
It's a tough thing to deal with
that kind of fame
when you're that fam...
And if it happens fast,
it's almost lethal
if you don't really have
a firm belief
in what you are
and what you're doing.
- It's sad to me, though,
that he didn't love himself
as much as everybody around him
loved him.
- He went through 17 rehabs,
but he was a committed athlete.
He was not going
to let this addiction beat him.
- I would love
when he'd come back
from any rehab
and be fresh and be like,
"I'm done with that,"
and he had his eating
under control,
and he was excited.
He was excited
to have that new shot.
- Chris sober was the most
brilliant, brightest thing
I'd ever seen in my life.
To this day,
nothing's come close.
- You can't walk around
being funny all the time.
You have to be yourself
sometimes,
and you have to be alone
sometimes.
You can't be on stage
all the time.
- I think when Fatty falls down,
everybody goes home happy.
It's easier than dialogue.
I don't have much brain.
- But Chris also had
such a terrible self-image.
"Fatty fall down,"
and "I'm just an idiot."
And everyone around him
would go, "No, you're not."
"You're really smart,
and you're a great person,"
and he'd go, "No, I'm not."
- There's you, there's...
[Crash]
Whoops-a-daisy.
By god, whoops-a-daisy.
- It's interesting when people
put out an image of themself
and then in some way
have to live that life.
People want that, expect that,
and if you don't get
to go offstage
and somehow restore yourself,
the pull of it is...
you know, the flame,
and you can get burned
to a crisp.
- And now,
here with another commentary
is Update commentator
Bennett Brauer.
Bennett?
[applause]
- He had a big appetite...
a big appetite for life,
for food, for drink,
for late nights,
for the pleasures of the earth.
- Well, maybe I'm not "the norm."
I'm not "camera-friendly."
I don't "wear clothes
that fit me."
- You know, he sincerely wanted
to be sober,
and was sober
for periods of time,
and...
but I always said,
"You can't be fat, super-fat,"
"and a drug addict."
"You've got to pick one."
- I'm not "hygienic."
I don't "wipe properly."
I lack "style."
I have no "charisma"
or "self-esteem."
- Something was, was... amiss.
Something wasn't working.
- You know, everyone's going
to do what they're going to do.
That's the problem.
There's only so much you can do.
- I mean,
I'll be honest with you.
There was something going on
in college.
That shit
doesn't just creep up on you.
I mean, I guess
it does creep up on you, but...
- Alcohol probably being
his first love,
but he wasn't, you know...
the other stuff
wasn't far behind.
- You know,
an addictive person...
I mean, it's a conundrum.
- I don't "own a toothbrush"
or "let my scabs heal."
I can't "reach
all the parts of my body."
[audience laughs]
- There was something
about him that...
He was just...
I don't know.
He was in deep,
a hard place to be.
All of us knew, every time.
His hair looked different.
He looked sweaty.
He looked...
His eyes were different.
They were just...
You were like, "Oh, shit."
It was rough seeing him
like that,
and I hated it.
- Thank you, Kevin.
- Bennett Brauer,
ladies and gentlemen.
- Thank you.
- I knew he was in trouble.
People would call me,
and I thought
the thing he loved the most
was doing the show.
He never found the thing
that was as powerful.
[laughter]
- Timmy, come back.
Come back. Come back.
I mean,
I'm not the host tonight,
and Timmy damn sure
ain't the host tonight.
[laughing]
No, the host tonight
is our good friend,
Chris Farley.
Come on, Chris.
[applause]
- Here we go!
- Let's do it!
- Whatever shape he was in,
coming back
and making him go through it
to realize, if nothing else,
this is what's happened to you,
you know...
that thing you're losing,
that ability to be able
to still play the game,
which you were an all-star at.
- You know what I've learned?
I've learned lessons
about responsibee...
Responsibility.
Being responsible,
not only to myself,
but to the people around me.
That means you guys.
I think it's time
to quit goofing around.
to grow up, fellas.
I want you...
everything's going to be okay.
- All right, man.
- Okay.
- I'm a new Chris, okay, fellas?
Now, stay,
we've got a great show tonight.
Mighty Mighty Bosstones
are here,
so stick around.
- It's just rare
that a person has that much joy
and brings that much happiness
to everyone around them,
but with Chris...
there's a limit
to how wonderful it is to me.
And that limit
is when you kill yourself
with drugs and alcohol.
You know?
That's where it stops
being so fucking magical.
- Things are getting better
and better for you, aren't they?
- Yeah.
I... I love it.
- Success in show business
does not always create
the best version of people.
- Do you get a sense now
of how your life might change
with the fame
that is going to come
with the release of this film?
Not that you're not famous now,
but, you know,
it's going to be more and more.
- And also thinking
that you have the physical
capacity to handle it,
because, you know, you may think
that you can handle it.
- It's not going to change me.
Going to be the same old Chris.
- Yeah.
- Nothing's going to happen...
-om
- Are you going to be okay?
- Yeah, I thought that...
- Maybe this was the life
that he was supposed to live.
I mean, I'm selfish.
I wanted more.
- You don't really believe it
when you're going through it.
You just think...
that he'd be able
to pull it out.
- "You're going to die
from that shit, buddy."
"You've got to stop,
you've got to stop,"
"and it's just not going
to end right,"
and then... it...
[static]
- The entertainment world
has lost a huge talent,
and much too soon.
Comedian Chris Farley
died today in Chicago.
- I wasn't shocked.
And I was very sad,
and straight up...
[sighs]
Lots of things you wish
didn't happen, you know?
- You know, he died alone,
you know, on a linoleum floor.
It was
not what we wanted for him,
nor what he wanted for himself.
- Nobody died...
You know, you're 33.
You don't die at 33.
It doesn't happen.
- It took months to go,
"Okay, I can talk about this,
or I could just..."
Too much.
It comes up in something
in my mind every day,
and I think it will forever.
- I liked having him in my life.
It was better.
It made my life better
being a friend of mine.
- Do I wish
I could clone that guy?
But with Chris,
you just don't...
When they say,
"God made the mold"
"and he threw it out the window,"
there was no mold.
There was just...
It was just ether, stars,
comets,
precious jewels and gems...
and Chris.
- Thank you, folks.
You guys have been great.
Thank you for coming out.
- Keep it going for Kevin Farley,
everybody.
[cheering]
- Chris, he would never want
to bring any sadness.
What he would want
is just everybody to laugh
and don't be sad.
Keep the laughter going.
- It's called a clown's prayer.
Before any audition
at Second City
or for TV or film,
we'd always take out the prayer.
We'd read it.
I actually still have
the prayer in my wallet, um...
I usually don't read prayers,
but I will.
I mean, I do, but not for...
All right.
"Dear Lord, as I stumble
through this life,"
"help me to create more laughter
than tears,"
"dispense more happiness
than gloom,"
"spread more cheer
than despair."
"Never let me become so blase
that I will fail to see"
"the wonder
in the eyes of a child"
"or a twinkle
in the eyes of the aged."
"Never let me forget that my work
is to cheer people,"
"make them happy,
and make them laugh."
"Never let me acquire success
to the point"
"where I discontinue
calling on my Creator"
"in the hour of need,"
"and acknowledging Him
and thanking Him"
"in the hour of plenty."
"And in my final moment,
may I hear you whisper,"
" 'When you made my people smile,
you made me smile.' "
- Chris Farley.
- Whoo!
-[music] You came into the world [music]
[music] The day
that all the kings died [music]
[music] I felt the heat
in your heart [music]
[music] Saw the flames
in your eyes [music]
[music] For three days
and three nights [music]
[music] You didn't sleep
or even tire [music]
[music] Yeah,
you're gonna burn bright [music]
[music] 'Cause you were born
on fire [music]
[music] Don't let nobody [music]
[music] Try to dampen your flame [music]
[music] Try to cool you down [music]
[music] Try to make you change [music]
[music] Try to steal your heat [music]
[music] Or mock your desire [music]
[music] Take your flames
to the street [music]
[music] 'Cause you were born
on fire [music]
[music] Saw you playing
in the ozone [music]
[music] Jumping on your
time bombs [music]
[music] Skipping through
the land mines [music]
[music] Made to cut you down [music]
[music] Cut you down [music]
[music] Laid to cut you down [music]
[music] Well, I seen you bleed [music]
[music] And I seen you bruise [music]
[music] And I seen you rage [music]
[music] And I've seen you blue [music]
[music] But that don't
break my heart [music]
[music] Like when you
look me in the eye [music]
[music] And you ask me questions [music]
[music] Like where we going
when we die? [music]
[music] Then who you gonna love? [music]
[music] And how you gonna live? [music]
[music] And will you
be a poor one [music]
[music] Or could I leave you rich?
[music]
[music] I can't leave
you no money [music]
you no land [music]
[music] I can't leave
you no faith [music]
[music] I lost the little I had [music]
[music] Well, I can leave you
this truth [music]
[music] Hold on to hope
and desire [music]
[music] And take your flames
to the streets [music]
[music] 'Cause you were
born on fire [music]
[music] Da da da da
da da da [music]
da da da da [music]
[music] Da da da da
da da da [music]
da da da da [music]
[music] Da da da da
da da da [music]
da da da da [music]
Surf the internet with browser of future
osdb.link/brave