Previously on "the 100"...
This is how my people
show they're ready
to go to war.
Do the rest of you
agree with echo?
Octavia: free us,
And we'll fight
your war.
Anders: training
starts tomorrow.
I'll make disciples
of your yet.
How does it work?
Well, you killed
my best friend,
So I'm not sure
I want to help you.
-I'll do anything.
-Our other friends--
Bring them here.
Cadogan:
send in their friends.
Murphy: indra,
what are you doing?
Indra: killing a demon.
This is what he wanted.
Open the door!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Emori: we've got
another live one!
I need you to
stay still, ok?
Ok. We're gonna
get you out of here.
Oh, no! Ohh!
Take care of my son.
You take care of him
yourself, all right?
I'm not letting
you die.
Indra: sheidheda--
where is he?
Emori: we rushed in
to help the faithful.
Before we knew it,
he was gone.
Indra: he escaped
through the secret passage.
We need to find him
before he can reach wonkru.
Well, might be
a little late for that.
Your buddy knight's
gone, too.
Sangedakru will
follow him.
He's one of their own.
The other clans will
take more convincing,
But with
no alternative--
Emori: there is
an alternative.
Madi!
Man: let's leave.
Go, go, go.
Come on.
Madi kom louwoda
kliron kru.
Russell?
I--i didn't know you
you spoke--
Sheidheda.
In the flesh...again.
You betrayed me,
madi.
I offered you
the world,
And you chose
weakness,
Love.
I'd like to see
you bleed.
Unfortunately for me,
Indra's reign
has changed things.
Yeah. Yes.
They follow her.
Despite the redness
of her blood. Hmm?
This free rein
won't do at all.
I'm in a quandary,
madi.
As a fellow
former commander,
You have a claim
to the throne,
And while killing you
solves that problem,
It makes my indra
problem worse.
She may be an imposter,
but she does have
followers,
Trikru fools mostly,
But grounders
just the same,
My people
just the same.
I'll give them
a chance to kneel
Just like I'm
giving it to you.
Kneel for me
right now, madi,
And I'll let you live.
Refuse to kneel...
And I'll slice open
the chests
Of every person
you love
And feed their hearts
to your dog.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Good girl.
I'm so glad we've come
to this understanding.
Let them go.
They're not
my prisoners, clarke.
Great. Then
here's the deal.
I'll use the key
to help you
But only after you
let my people return
to sanctum,
All of them.
You're free to go
with her.
Echo: we're not
going anywhere.
We have a war
to fight.
We're staying,
too, sir.
What did you
do to them?
Anders: we didn't
do anything.
They're simply committed
to the cause,
Ready to serve mankind
in the last war.
A moment that will
soon be upon us
Now that you're here
With the help
of the key.
So here's
the new deal.
We talk to our
friends alone.
I don't even want
to see your men
in the halls.
You want my help?
Earn it.
First disciple anders,
have all nonessential
personnel
Return to livsec.
Sir, I'm not sure
if that's--
Yes, my shepherd.
Good.
Your shepherd
stays here.
The rest of you out.
Now!
Miller: in other words,
Get the flock
out of here.
Go. I'll be fine.
Clarke: miller, put him
against the wall.
Miller: let's go.
Jordan:
I have questions.
Yeah. Get in line.
Echo, octavia,
and diyoza are
with them now?
Clarke: why the hell
do they think I have
the flame in my head?
That was for one day
over 100 years ago.
M-cap,
memory capture,
A device that's
able to pull
select memories
From one's mind.
They put octavia
in it.
And saw the flame
going into her head
in polis.
Amazing.
Wait. If they still think
it's in clark's head,
Then echo, octavia,
and diyoza never told
them it isn't, meaning--
Niylah: they're not
with them.
Ok. Niylah, gabriel,
jordan, you stay here,
Watch cadogan,
and hold this room.
If things go south,
we're gonna need
a way out.
Let's go find out
what the 3 most
dangerous women
On this or any
planet are up to.
Woman: moving day.
On your feet.
You're really gonna
let them send me
to penance?
Err! Aah!
Aah!
Seeker diyoza,
you will never commit
To the cause if
you continue to--
Unh!
What? You didn't really
think I believe this garbage.
We're gonna kill them,
all of them.
You have a plan.
Took some convincing
to get our friend levitt
to help me,
But, yes,
I have a plan.
What can I do?
There's been
a complication.
Our people are here--
Clarke, raven, miller,
niylah, jordan.
The watches
are synched.
Put on the guard's
uniform and take this.
I'll give you exactly
one hour to get everyone
We care about
off this planet.
One hour, hope.
What if I can't?
Can't isn't an option.
You tell them if
they're still here
Then they die, too.
They'll want to know
how I'm doing this.
That's why I haven't
told you.
One hour.
Ok.
Madi!
Madi, are you here?
Are we sure this
is where she went?
It's the last place
she was seen.
Go search the perimeters.
I'll take the kitchen.
Emori, the basement.
Murphy.
I got upstairs.
Oh, god. Hey.
Madi, madi, madi,
stop.
It's ok. It's ok.
It's me.
Murphy?
Thank god.
Hey. Hey.
You're ok.
Guys, I got her!
Sheidheda--he--he's
alive. He's here.
Hey. Look at me.
You are safe now, ok?
Just sit down,
sit down, sit down.
Look at me, look at me
And breathe in through
your nose, all right,
with me like this.
One more time.
There you go.
Emori: madi.
See? We won't let
anything happen to you.
He's broadcasting
from the palace.
Murphy:
madi, come with us.
Indra: let's move.
We know where he is.
I gave you an order!
Keep madi safe.
Go get the bastard.
She must have been
important,
My callie, for her
language to survive
all this time.
Kalliope pramfleimkepa.
They say she was
brave, strong.
Legend has it
when she died, even
her enemies wept.
What does pram...
You know what?
It doesn't matter.
Gabriel: funny.
I remember you
differently.
How are you
still alive?
Cryogenics.
Plus a well-balanced diet.
Ah.
Yes.
Gabriel, right?
Anders said you
were like me--
Immortal, from earth,
worshipped by his people.
Uh, no. No.
Not like you.
I lost my way
for a time,
But I never actually
believed I was a god.
We're all gods, doctor,
and we're all
On a journey
to transcendence
Even if we took
different paths.
Now that sounds
like you.
I must say...
It is nice to talk
to someone from that time,
And, yes, I was
different then,
But a man learns a lot
as the centuries tick past,
Wouldn't you agree,
doctor?
Hmm. So what
have you learned?
Ah.
We found these logs
When we arrived,
Remnants from
the civilization
That lived here
before--the bardoans.
It took centuries.
We finally translated
the characters.
It's a story
not unlike our own,
But this is the part
I find most intriguing.
"The orb becomes
like a star,
"Challenging all
we have done
And all that we are."
Beautiful,
don't you think?
"Only then will
the last war begin.
"Make it past and cease
to be fallible.
"Transcend into greatness.
Evolve into more."
I like the rhyming part
better.
Gabriel: the bardoans
didn't record the code?
Oh, I wish it
were that easy.
That's why
you need clarke.
Yes. The ai
knows the code.
We enter it,
And our last war
begins.
Jordan: ridiculous.
We evolve to a higher level
through our lowest behavior?
The answer to all
this violence isn't
Just more violence.
Cadogan: the end
of violence,
The last war.
Every war seems like
the last one until the next.
You don't believe me?
Have at it.
It's all there.
In the meantime,
I'm famished.
Niylah: stop.
What are you doing?
Having lunch.
You're all welcome
to join me.
Gabriel: no, no, no.
If we shoot him, we
lose our leverage.
What do we do?
We can't leave here.
I'll bring him back
after lunch.
What the hell
is she thinking?
Oh, I get playing
good, little soldier
to stay alive,
But when somebody
hands you a one-way
ticket out of here,
You take it.
Will you
stop pacing?
We'll get to hope
before they take her
to penance.
How?
Octavia: whoa.
I'm so sorry,
octavia.
I know.
So am i.
No guards?
Raven: clarke
threatened not to help
With the flame if they
got in her way.
Thanks for playing
that one cards down,
by the way.
I thought it was
good leverage,
Knowing you would
eventually show up.
We're glad you did.
Just hug me back, miller.
Diyoza: wait!
She's not one
of them.
Clarke.
Raven.
Miller.
You described
them well.
Diyoza: this is hope,
my daughter.
Time dilation's
a bitch.
How'd you get out?
Doesn't matter.
Right now, we need to
Get ourselves
to the stone room
And get out of bardo.
We can get
acquainted later.
Let's go.
Hey. Where's echo?
She'll catch up.
Diyoza: she will, huh?
What's going on?
Hope.
She's getting revenge
for bellamy.
Talk now.
All I know is
that we have...
45 Minutes to get
you off this planet.
What happens
in 45 minutes?
I don't know.
Really. Levitt
helped her with something,
And she didn't tell me
what it was
Because she knew you'd
get it out of me
And try and stop her.
Octavia: levitt
wouldn't help her.
What did she
do to him?
-He's alive, ok?
-Let's move.
Aunty o.,
Where are you going?
To find levitt.
-Hope.
-Shh.
Someone could hear us.
How could you let
her do this?
Because I want her to.
They took everything
from me.
I know what it's like
to kill innocent people
for a cause,
And I promise you, it's
not gonna fill that hole
in your heart.
Only we can do that.
There are no
innocent people here.
Woman: liar.
Look at their eyes.
They hate us.
At least they're
alive to hate us.
Yeah. Sure. At least until
sheidheda and his army
Come back to finish
what he started.
No. Indra won't
let that happen.
No? Look. You saw
the faces of her guards
When he was speaking.
They were trikru,
loyal to her,
And he was still
getting to them.
Well, john, even if
he does take control,
These people aren't
a threat to him.
They will be.
When we were playing
chess, he made sure
To take my pawns
so they couldn't move
Across the board
to get promoted.
Taking out the faithful
before they can get
revenge will be
Right below madi
on his list
Of priorities,
all right?
I'm telling you,
these people
are in danger.
If you're right
and we help them,
Then so are we.
Yeah. I'm aware.
Come. Sit. I think
you'll enjoy this.
It's some things
from our time.
Not my time.
My, uh--my
mother's maybe.
Ho ho ho!
That was just mean.
It's hard to make me
feel older than I am,
But, uh, go ahead.
Just take a sip.
Heh. Kombucha.
It's wonderful,
isn't it?
It's good
for the gut, too.
It reminds you
of something.
Yeah. My grandmother
in colombia.
She made her own
Right before they cut
off her drinking water
So the rich could
water their lawns.
Then you
are self-made.
Hmm.
Me, too.
My first job was
flipping burgers,
Dreaming of the day
I'd escape.
Well, you certainly
did that.
That I did. I knew there
had to be something more
Than politics,
the dying ecosystem,
The memes.
Earth was
pretty terrible.
It got worse
after you left.
Good for the cult
business, though,
am I right?
Hmm. Heh.
We weren't a cult...
But being right is
always good for business.
Look. I don't mean
to be rude,
But, uh, as I said,
I have some experience
with people
Claiming to be gods.
Hmm. I don't claim that.
In fact, I don't
even believe in god.
I do, however, believe
that I was chosen
Mm-hmm.
By whom if not god?
We'll find out
when we win the war.
What if you lose?
We...won't.
"For all mankind."
Is that it?
Damn right.
You can thank me
when we save you,
Or you can join us.
Join your war to
save the human race
By renouncing everything
that makes me human?
Love, family--
those are the things
that connect us.
We're not just dna.
We're emotion.
Without that, what
are you fighting for?
Let me ask you
something, doctor.
Have you ever done
anything you regret
In the name of love?
I'll take that
as a yes.
The point is,
we all have.
We all fight
for our families,
our countries.
We do whatever
we have to
So that our side
can survive,
And when someone
you love...
Betrays you...
Well, that is
the worst pain there is.
We have none
of that here.
With all--ahem--
due respect,
You can't fight
a war for the soul
Of the human race
with an inhuman army.
Who says we can't?
I mean, this life,
It doesn't matter,
Even lives
as long as ours.
What matters is...
What comes next.
We're about to find out
what that is.
The answers that we've
both been seeking
for so long,
They're finally
within our grasp.
Isn't that worth
a little sacrifice?
Anders: sir,
I need a moment.
Thank you
for your company.
Please escort dr. Santiago
back to his friends.
What is it?
We have a problem.
Levitt.
-Hey.
-Ohh!
What happened?
I failed.
She killed two people
in front of me,
And...i broke.
Wait. Not yet.
We need to find out
what echo's planning.
The key has landed.
Octavia: what did
echo make you do?
I helped her get it.
Gem9.
Miller: gem9?
Diyoza: a bioweapon.
It's the reason
the species that was
Here before they arrived
isn't here now.
How's she
deploying it?
Central humidification
system, the machine level.
I told her how.
I'm so sorry.
Raven: so I'm guessing
it spreads through water.
Humidification would
make it airborne.
Raven reyes.
Of course you'd know that.
Clarke: airborne means
it's a suicide mission.
No, no, not
necessarily.
It will take time
for the compound
To go from its entry point
to the vents.
Echo will make a run
for the stone room.
Which is what
we should do.
She gave me an hour
to get you all out.
We still got time.
That means we can
still stop her.
Untie me, please,
so I can get help.
Hope: aunty o.,
They will kill her.
She'll kill us all.
-No.
-I'm sorry.
octavia! Octavia!
Help!
Niylah: what are the odds
everything works out
And we just walk
out of here?
That's what I thought.
Oh, my god.
-What?
-Maybe it's structured
Like korean.
What?
My dad's father
was korean.
He taught me
the language,
What he knew of it,
anyway.
I didn't want to learn
it at first.
It looked like there
would be thousands
of characters to study.
But there weren't?
No. That's not
how korean works.
It uses an alphabet,
same as english,
Just with the letters
stacked into blocks
of syllables,
Blocks that are
easy to mistake
as characters.
You think cadogan didn't
decode the text right?
I think it's
possible. Look.
What if each
of these strokes
Is just a letter?
They could have
the whole language
completely wrong.
Well, maybe not
the whole thing
But multiple word phrases
like "last war."
Now it just sounds like
you're trying to find proof
To support what you
want to believe.
How is that any different
than what they're doing?
We all see what
we want to see.
If you're looking
for the wrong answer,
It's easy to miss
the right one.
Come on. Look at what's
written about unlocking
the stone.
There's no mention
about violence or pain,
Just...preparation,
judgment.
-Like a test.
-Exactly. Like a test.
It would make sense.
Niylah: where's
cadogan or the gun
you took?
Yeah. The look on anders' face
made it clear
That neither would be
coming back with me.
What did I miss?
Not much. Just...
That I'm a genius.
Jordan has a theory.
That they got it wrong.
The last war isn't
a war at all.
-If I'm right...
-And that's a big if.
Then it's a test.
Now, I'm just
guessing here
But probably to be
taken by whoever
enters the code.
One individual representing
a whole species.
No pressure there.
You got to admit
it makes more sense
than a war.
Should we tell them?
No. No, no, no. No way.
If there is a test
to decide the fate
Of the human race,
bill cadogan should not be
The one to take it.
Come.
Show me what you--
what you mean.
Ok. My father's side
of the family was korean.
Now, if you look at these...
He's not here, either.
We should enlist the help
of the other clans.
We can't trust
the other clans.
Now move out.
There are other
rooms to--
He's reciting
the lineage.
Now that that's out of the way,
I--malachi kom sangedakru,
the last true commander--
Vow to honor and defend
our traditions
And my people,
But first, you must prove
that you are my people
By bending the knee.
It's quite simple, really.
If you don't kneel,
You die.
Your path
to the throne
Leads through me.
You say you honor
our traditions,
So honor this one.
I was hoping
you'd say that.
New look for me.
I'm flattered.
Mine's nice, too,
don't you think?
Raah!
Thank you, indra,
for giving me
Exactly
what I wanted--
A chance to return
to the old ways,
My ways.
we'll see.
Huh!
Agh!
Hyah!
Yah!
Arr, aah, arr!
You looking for this?
Hyah!
Indra: get out
of the way!
Get out of the way!
Aah! Aah!
-Agh!
-Hyah!
Unh!
Kneel or die.
I won't let you
take my people.
Unh.
Die it is.
Raah!
Aah!
Ohh!
Stop!
Spare her life.
I will kneel.
Ahh. Ahh.
Uh-huh.
Ohh.
Err.
Ahh.
-No, heda.
-Ahh.
You were right, then.
Sheidheda won.
We're safe in here,
all right?
The reactor door
is sealed.
No one can get to us.
So, what now?
That's tomorrow's
problem.
Today, we survive,
all of us.
Don't look now, john,
But I think you just
might be someone
worth believing in.
Raven: echo, no!
Stop!
You were supposed
to get them out.
Octavia: it's not her fault.
We wouldn't leave
Without you, echo.
You don't
have to do this.
I get it. Everything
they took from you
They took
from me, too,
But there are
good people here.
Who? Levitt?
The man who stole
your memories
And gave them
to the enemy?
All of this happened
because of him.
Way to honor
your brother's memory.
Echo, this is
not who you are.
I know you think
this is the right
thing to do,
But--trust me--
it's not.
There's always
another way.
Grief is something
we can learn
to live with,
But once you make
a choice like this,
It stays with you.
This is nothing like
the choices you make, clarke.
You take lives
to save the people you love.
This is vengeance
pure and simple.
Clarke: echo, stop.
This is not what
bellamy would
have wanted.
Echo: you have no idea
what bellamy wanted!
If they killed me or you
or you, octavia,
He would be standing
right where I am.
Raven: I don't
think so.
Stay back!
The bellamy who helped
massacre a sleeping army
That was sent
to protect us
Maybe he might
be there,
But not the man we spent
6 years on the ring with,
Not the man you
fell in love with.
Echo, you're my sister,
And my sister
wouldn't do this.
You're wrong.
I'm not leaving, echo.
If you drop that,
I am staying right here.
You will have
to kill me, too.
Aah!
Hey, hey, hey.
It's ok.
It's ok. It's ok.
We're here now.
Come on.
Let's take you home, ok?
We're gonna go home.
Anders: good choice.
Clarke: we had a deal.
I told cadogan
If I saw any of you,
I wouldn't help him.
Anders: that was before
we knew that one of you
Killed 3 more of us,
torturing another
Just to get him
to give you a weapon
With which
to commit genocide.
The man makes
a good point.
Let's call it even.
Even? I just told you
3 disciples are dead.
You people disgust me.
Look at yourselves.
Raised in the wild.
You're nothing
but primal beasts
Utterly in thrall
to your feelings,
Prioritizing
the want of self
Over the need
of all others.
You don't deserve
the shepherd's mercy.
Miller: brave words
coming from a man
Standing alone
in front of a pack
of armed beasts.
Diyoza: he's not alone.
Anders: smart girl.
Diyoza: probably
not a good idea
to fire lasers
In a room
with a wmd.
Let's get back to
the shepherd's mercy.
Echo will be sent
to penance for 20 years,
But she'll be back
before you know it
Unless by then the code
hasn't been entered
To begin the last war
In which case,
she dies there.
Hope: I have a better idea.
You die here.
Hope, no!
Unh!
Hope: no, mom!
Diyoza: get her out of here!
Hope: no! No!
Octavia: hope, it's too late!
Hope: no. No, mom! No!
Go!
What are you all
waiting for?
Move! Go!
Mom, I'm sorry!
Hope, we have
no choice.
I cannot lose her,
not--not again!
Don't waste this,
little one!
Be better than me.
Octavia: get the door!
Mom! Mom!
Aah! No!
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN