Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Previously on Ghost...
Stansfield is having
a publicity problem.
What better place
to dig up dirt on Sweeney?
You know he's friends
with the Westons.
My old college roommate,
Congressman Rick Sweeney.
I'm blessed to announce
that I will be entering
the NBA draft this year.
They found their suspect.
- Who is it?
- Carrie Milgram.
But she's not a murderer.
Where were you on the night
of Jabari Reynolds' murder?
Zeke was here.
Ezekiel Cross.
I'm recording you.
Take you downtown
for some questions.
I'ma need you to handle
the product alone.
You trust me to do that?
Yo, what happened to him?
He got caught
with fake product... ours.
We need a new connect.
Might be able
to help out with that.
If Cane's offering product,
you need to take it.
Yeah, I didn't think it was
gonna be like this, Renzo.
I need more.
- I needed to see you again.
- It's too late.
Just in case
you change your mind.
Yas, what's going on?
I should be allowed
to have a drink or two.
She's going
to a really good home.
Tariq!
You're going to need someone
with a lot of influence.
You wouldn't happen
to know any Westons, do you?
You don't have to be
so modest.
This is a big thing, man.
Look, just because I'm going
to be an investigator
in the DA's office does not
mean that I'm not gon' miss
my brothers
and sisters in blue.
Stop lying, bro.
You know damn well
these sad motherfuckers
are dead to you after tonight.
Just between you and me,
Rashad.
All right, everybody,
let's raise our glasses
to Detective Investigator
Kamaal Tate.
- Thank you very much.
- Cheers.
Hey, think you got
the wrong event, kid.
Oh, no, I'm-I'm here
to see my, um... my uncle,
Councilman Tate.
You're related
to Councilman Tate?
Chief Bozeman, I really
appreciate your diligence.
I know this young man.
- Councilman.
- Mm-hmm.
Tariq, what the fuck
are you doing here?
- Uh, we need to talk.
- Talk?
Nigga, this ain't
the Breakfast Club.
You know
where you are right now?
Look, I need
some of your connections.
Child Services got my sister,
and I need you
to get someone over there
to speak to me.
Yeah, I can.
But what will you do
for me, Tariq?
Hmm?
I'm gonna need a little quid
from you before I can quo.
Talk to me.
You mentioned that you know
one of the Westons, right?
Yes.
Brayden Weston is my roommate.
How well does he know
Rick Sweeney?
That fuckin' cocksucker.
Ah, I love when we're on
the same side of a question.
Can you use your relationship
with this Brayden
to get me some information
on Sweeney?
He has something
that belongs to me.
What's that?
A congressional seat.
Now, if you get
something for me
that cancels him out of office,
then I can get you your sister.
How the fuck do you
expect me to do that?
Don't sell yourself
so short, young brother.
We both know
what you're capable of.
A'ight.
Just give me a little time
to figure that shit out.
But I need my sister now.
I can help you now, on credit.
But you gotta get me back
with interest.
Are we clear?
Yeah, I got you.
All right. I'll make the call.
Go down to CPS in the morning.
I'll make sure
that they see you.
Now get the hell outta here
before these boys
sober up enough
to arrest your Black ass.
Mm.
Go on, kick rocks,
little nigga.
Ah, thanks
for coming by, nephew.
Love you.
Hey, where's my drink?
He ain't here yet?
He's late.
- Does Papi know I'm back yet?
- Yeah.
And he's gonna know
if you fuck it up too.
Hey, you late, nigga.
What's he doing here?
He belongs here.
Cane found a new connect.
So we all back
in business together.
Now, whatever beef
y'all still got going,
y'all need to squash
that shit right now.
Y'all hear me?
So you trust him again?
I need product, and so do you.
This is what's best
for all of us.
The greater good.
You get that, don't you?
- Yeah.
- Good.
And, Cane,
don't be fuckin' with him
and the way
he does business, period.
- Yes, ma'am.
- A'ight.
Whoa, hold up, hold up.
I need the money up front.
Oh, you don't trust me
all of a sudden?
New connect, new rules.
Fucking mess.
Make sure
you run me my shit back.
I got you.
You frame
that teacher bitch yet?
I didn't even have to do
all that shit.
- We good.
- Yeah, we better be.
'Cause if them bodies
come back on me,
I come down on you,
no matter what Monet says
about no greater good.
Listen, nigga,
you stay outta jail
and I stay outta jail,
all right?
We in this shit together,
that's the greater good.
Yeah, whatever.
I'll have the shit tomorrow.
Make sure you have
Monet's money.
I heard what she said
before she left, nigga.
All this shit I be doing
for this family,
and the niggas can't even
offer me a ride.
- My man.
- Yo, Mecca.
- You made it.
- I did.
- All right.
- We up and running.
All right.
Anybody wanna help
the nigga out?
Mec!
Fuck, man!
To the left, man.
Another step forward. Bam.
Party favours.
Feliz cumpleaños, Nuff.
Yo, let's go!
Let's fucking go!
Cane, get over here, man.
- What up? What up?
- This is my boy Nuff.
I told you about him, right?
Nuff, this is Cane.
He's helping us expand
into more territory.
- What's happening, playboy?
- What up? What up?
So this how you throw
a damn party, huh?
Man, you better pace yourself.
Hey, I gotta take this,
but, uh, Cane,
fix yourself a plate, man.
My place is your place.
My family.
Fire, Chef. For real.
Close your mouth when you chew.
Cane, how you know Mec?
I met him through my boy Guap.
Mec used to run the hood
same time as his dad.
So he knew him
before he went to Kuwait.
Hey, girls. Come over here.
This the birthday boy.
What's up? You ready?
Open wide.
Mecca, you getting in
on this shit?
Don't worry about that nigga.
Man been a lost cause
since we got to New York.
What you mean?
He's had a hard-on
for some bitch.
Don't you know
that there's a difference
between my business
and family business?
Huh?
Sorry about that, Janae.
He'll be back online
in a minute.
For now,
why don't you help, uh,
Zindzi out with my boy Cane?
It's a party, y'all.
Feel the love.
Detective Whitman, uh,
you know,
I got practice in the morning.
so whatever you need to ask me,
can you just ask me
so I can go?
You didn't seem
so worried about practice
when I grabbed you.
Looked like you were putting
your work in already.
Yeah, uh,
Coach is expecting me, so...
What sport do you play?
Basketball.
I mean, I'm Zeke Cross.
I just declared for the draft
a couple of days ago.
I don't really
follow basketball,
but, uh, that's great for you.
So, what, do you just do
a few laps in college
before you're off
to your new life, right?
I mean, it's not like that.
No? You like school?
Uh, what do you like about it?
You like your friends?
Like your girlfriend?
Yeah, I like school.
Did you know Jabari Reynolds?
The professor? Nah.
Uh, he wasn't my advisor.
Oh, okay. Who was your advisor?
Carrie... I mean
Professor Caridad Milgram.
Can you describe
your relationship with her?
That's it. She's my advisor.
Can I get a phone call?
I need to call my aunt.
Like, what's going on?
Like, I've been here for hours.
Hey, hey, you're not-you're not
under arrest, okay?
I don't want you to go
worrying your auntie.
We'll be done soon.
Hey, you-you declared
for the draft, right? Whoo.
I mean, can you imagine
if the press found out
you were in here for hours?
What kind of rumours
might that start?
That could hurt
your draft prospects.
But I didn't do anything.
And that's what
I'm gonna tell 'em
if you cooperate.
Let's just finish up,
get you back to Stansfield.
I'm cooperating.
Good.
Just a few more questions.
About you and, uh,
about Carrie.
Yeah.
Damn, you already up at it?
Play hard, work harder.
I had Nuff take the product
to your car.
You sure your family
can move all that?
Yeah, Monet can handle that.
And she paid you up front.
Yeah, well...
Guap said Monet took
your product off the street.
So where you gonna sell
my shit?
Fucking Guap.
Man, you know Guap
got radio mouth.
Monet ain't like that shit.
She wanted the business
to stay under the radar.
So she runs it to this
Steve Urkel-ass nigga
up at Stansfield.
Uh-huh.
Right.
And what's your problem
with him?
I mean, Monet's right.
His system keeps us invisible.
But she don't know
what he's doing up there.
So you don't like it
'cause you don't have control.
Mm.
- You don't trust him?
- Nope.
So what's his name?
You don't trust me either.
Well, I don't work with people
who don't trust me, Cane.
I just showed you
my whole fucking life, man.
All my peoples.
You know what? It's cool.
You don't wanna give me
the name, there's the door.
I'll see you around.
Tariq St. Patrick.
Uh-huh.
And you need to be able to
control this Tariq St. Patrick.
- Yeah, I guess so.
- Okay.
Well, maybe I can help.
I am offering you a hand.
I know you're too smart
to turn your back on that.
Right?
Tate made me
give you 15 minutes.
That's all you got. Go.
Okay. Yas belongs with me.
Your sister needs
to be in a grounded,
safe, stable environment.
And I can provide that.
In a college dorm?
Look,
she's with a great family.
One of my favourites,
the Royces.
She'll stay there
'til we see what happens
with your grandmother.
But my grandmother's
the problem.
She-she's unstable.
Maybe if I get an apartment,
then can Yas will stay with me?
An apartment?
You'll also need a stable job,
proof of income,
a clean drug
and criminal record.
Yeah, I can do all of that.
You couldn't even
get this meeting on your own.
Trust me, money and influence
can buy a lot of things.
But it can't buy
what's good for a child.
I told you.
I barely know Carrie Milgram,
and I don't know anything.
I need to go to practice.
I-I can't help you.
You're free to go at any time.
You keep saying that,
but you have my wallet
and my phone.
Just gotta say the word.
I mean, this fucker's
been ringing off the hook.
It's probably my auntie.
Now she's looking for me.
Oh, uh, your auntie?
Does she know about
your relationship with Carrie?
- Should I pick up and ask her?
- No, there is no relationship.
Look.
I understand
why you'd hesitate to admit it.
If your school finds out,
she loses her job.
But in the eyes of the law,
nobody fucking cares.
You're both adults.
It's not a crime.
You know what is a crime?
Lying to the police during
a criminal investigation.
I need you
to tell me the truth.
Today we'll be discussing
Jeremy Bentham's theories
on utilitarianism.
- I was thinking we could...
- I'd like to take this one
if you'll allow me,
Professor Milgram.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Is there
an objective greater good?
It's a question that's played
a vital role in my dedication
to a career in public service.
You see, Rashad Tate is
and will always be
for the people.
And that includes all of you.
Be it better education,
cancellation of student debt,
creating...
The act
that's purely in service
of your voting base...
or potential voting base...
negates its subjectivity.
Go off,
Professor Milgram, okay?
But he has a point.
Bentham argues that
an act's utility determines
whether it's good or bad.
What keeps the many happy
is objectively
the greatest act.
Ugh. A colonizer
would say that shit.
Excuse me?
Slavery was promoted
as being in the interest
of the many.
Sure did make your
colonizing ancestors happy too.
Okay, but Bentham
acknowledges that utility
and its outcome
is always changing.
We have to leave room
for moral evolution.
Mm, that sounds like
a slight justification
- for slavery to me, Luis.
- Mm. Slight.
And that's assuming
we all operate off
the same moral code.
I've been to some of
your frat brothers' parties.
I'd speak to them on that one.
- Ooh! Shh!
- Had fun, huh?
So, Lauren, you don't think
that there's a basic moral code
which we adhere to that informs
the overall greater good?
No.
Well, what if you knew
that BruShaundria
would one day be
a serial killer?
Why me?
Would that justify
murdering her now?
Try that shit.
I think that any act
that infringes
upon someone's way of being
or happiness is wrong.
It's stripped of the mantle of
being the greater good, period.
I wouldn't kill BruShaundria.
You mean you don't
wanna get merc'd
in self-defense.
Well, let's find out, shall we?
Don't play with me.
So there are
fundamental truths,
virtues that lift mankind
in which we can measure
objectivity of an action
in service of a greater good.
Do you see Jackie's point,
Lauren?
- I mean...
- In leaving room for virtue,
you often risk missing an
objectively greater good act.
Sometimes
if you don't eliminate
the concept of morality,
you risk everybody
taking a loss.
How's that in the interest
of the greater good?
Young man has a point.
I mean, are you really saying
there's not a single
good outcome
you'd rather not risk
just to preserve
your virtue, Professor?
We can fucking
do this all day!
I think they went
to school together
or college or something.
- That's all I know.
- You know what I think?
I think that he found out
about you two.
She had him killed
to shut him up.
There's nothing
to find out about.
Look, I don't mean to be rude,
but like you said,
she's way older than me.
She's hot and very available.
You know I used
to work with her, right?
Very, very, very generous.
She enjoys it too.
You know what I mean?
Nah, I don't know
what you mean.
Oh, I mean that just...
I mean, Carrie
was never one
to focus on one guy, right?
Wasn't her style.
That's not true.
She's not the type.
Oh, she was
Jabari Reynolds' type.
Back in the day, but sure.
You know, he wrote
a book about her or something.
You don't know.
No, he got back in.
Oh yeah, it's been
a couple of months,
I mean,
up until he died, of course.
That's not true.
Apparently, he was very jealous
over someone else
she was seeing.
You sure you don't know
anything about that?
No.
So you weren't with her
the night he was killed?
That's gotta be
my auntie or-or my coach.
You made me miss practice.
This is not your auntie.
Were you in a sexual
relationship with her?
Hmm?
Is she calling
to get you to lie for her?
Were you with Carrie Milgram
at her apartment
the night Jabari Reynolds
was killed?
No.
I wasn't with Carrie the night
Jabari Reynolds was killed.
Can I go, please?
No.
You need to hang tight
for a little longer.
I'm gonna check something out.
In the meantime,
I'll have an officer come in.
Help you call your auntie.
So how did the meeting go?
She basically told me
to fuck off.
You're 19
and your sister needs a home.
- It's a big ask.
- I mean, I understand,
but I need to see
my sister, man.
I need to see Yasmine.
I gave her my word, and...
it might not mean a lot to you,
but that's my little sister.
You know...
I like that it means
something to you, Tariq.
Since you gave me your word
that you'll help me out
with Sweeney.
Now, I know that he and Weston
have been friends
since their college days here.
There's gotta be
something on 'em.
I-I know it.
I don't know.
He looks like a closet freak.
But I need proof.
I'm thinking Eliot Spitzer,
Anthony Weiner.
Real creepy type shit.
That's the kind of dirt
I need, Tariq.
A'ight, look, I'll get it.
But I need you
to find my sister.
An address or something.
Then I'll get you
whatever you want, okay?
Well, young brother...
...that's my kind of deal.
All right.
- Hey.
- What's up?
Um, thanks for helping me out
in there.
Of course.
Listen, uh, last night,
sorry I bolted on you.
I'm just... I feel like
you're always preoccupied.
No, it's-it's just, I got a lot
of things going on, and...
I gotta-I gotta take this.
You always do.
Fuck.
Bash.
Tariq, what can I do
for my favourite
minority partner?
I need a legitimate paycheck.
No problem,
we'll form a new LLC
and run you a paycheck
through it.
A'ight,
it'll look legit, right?
You're questioning
my business acumen.
- I'm insulted.
- No, I mean, you know.
I'll have my lawyers
draw up the papers.
All you'll need
is someone to sign on
as president of the corporation
and a 30K down payment.
Bash, what?
You gotta be kidding me,
bro, 30 bands?
There are strict
transaction fees
at the bank of Stern and Stern.
A'ight, you'll get your money.
Why can't I be the president?
You want an IRS audit?
I don't.
We need to make this
look clean, even if it's not.
- A'ight.
- Find someone you trust.
I'll call you
when the papers are ready.
Niggas really think
they in The Fast and Furious
and shit.
You ain't tell me you was
bringin' white boy with you.
I brought him.
Man, we spent
a whole evening together,
which was your choice,
not mine.
I'm still white boy to you?
That's fucked up, Cane.
Is that the product?
Come to Daddy.
Yo, you buggin' if you think
I'm givin' your stomped-out ass
any of my fuckin' product.
Fuck you mean, nigga?
Just give him the bags.
Look, you of all people know
I can move weight, Cane.
What the fuck?
You know what?
You and Machine Gun Kelly
over here
fuck up Monet's business,
I'ma just take it back
to the streets.
Whoa, the streets,
that's an option?
Nah, we're staying
right where we are, B.
I really can't wait
for y'all to fuck this up.
Continue to wait.
Thank you.
Yo, don't listen
to that nigga, man.
We can't keep switchin' up
how we doin' shit
now that I gotta get
my sister, bro.
Well, how much
do we need to get her back?
I ain't gonna lie, a lot.
Fucker Bash is asking
for 30 bands.
Gotta make some bread.
Say no more.
You know I got you, fam.
You know that spot
that you showed me?
I did a little redecorating.
You're gonna love this.
Scan that, right there.
- What?
- Yeah. The brick, right there.
What the fuck?
This what you been working on?
One of our tutors did some
sick shit with a 3D printer.
She took out a few old bricks,
replaced 'em with retrofitted
3D lockers.
Both columns,
fully functional storage.
So, what, every tutor got
their own code or some shit?
Exactly.
Product in, cash out.
You and I are the only ones
with the master QR.
No more running around
and handing shit out,
no more storing shit
in my parents' garage.
One location for everything.
When we want to expand,
anybody, anywhere.
And the best part,
no one will know it's us.
We'll be like
some fucking ghosts.
This shit is fire, man.
We'll get some money
with this bitch.
That white boy,
he's your way in.
I watched your meeting.
Tariq's partner,
you know who he is?
Yeah, he's some kind
of rich kid.
That nigga is the rich kid,
and he's known Tariq
for years now.
He's hype, easy to control.
Perfect for us.
So you want me to get at Tariq
through Brayden?
You wanna run Tariq,
you need to cut him
at his soft spot,
and that rich kid is it.
You need to get Brayden
in your pocket.
Does Daddy know Cane's back?
You know what, Diana?
I'm tired of y'all
running around here
asking me "Daddy this"
and "Daddy that."
You wanna know about Cane,
ask your father yourself.
You want more responsibility?
You wanna be the one
askin' all the questions?
Here.
You go deal with your father.
Fine.
Hey.
Um, what's the Wi-Fi passcode
again?
It's on your wall, Councilman.
In your office.
Is there something I've done
to offend you, Professor?
I certainly hope not, because
I would love for us
to be friends.
Oh, I think you've done nothing
but be yourself, Rashad.
You know, I think if you and I
spent some time together alone,
you'd really warm up
to my charm.
Detective Whitman.
I didn't think we had
a meeting scheduled.
We don't, but we need to talk.
Councilman,
may we have a minute?
Ah, of course, Detective.
You know, it's been a while
since I wore the uniform,
but if there's anything
I can do
to help the department,
please don't hesitate to ask.
- Appreciate that.
- Mm-hmm.
I have Zeke Cross
at the precinct.
What? Why?
Is he under arrest?
He's saying you have a totally
professional relationship
and that you two
were not together
the night Jabari was murdered.
Your alibi is up in smoke.
You must have confused him.
Did you put that kid up
to kill Jabari?
Or he just figure it out
on his own?
Kevin, we both know
this is personal.
I know you wanna
pin this on me,
but neither Zeke nor I
had anything to do
with Jabari's murder.
Really?
Then why lie about your alibi?
Or is Zeke lying?
I'm not lying to you, Kevin.
I know what you're capable of,
Carrie.
I know the things
you can get a man to do.
Just know that I won't rest
until I put cuffs
on both of you
and you pay
for what you've done.
Open five.
Prisoner coming through.
Thank you.
I'm happy you finally called,
Nae-Nae.
Don't call me that.
And that wasn't my mom's house
where you turned over
those cans.
I got kids, Dante.
Yes, and a husband, right?
In prison?
What else you think you know?
You run a bar.
Not the life
I remember you wanting.
Look, it's been 24 years,
and not a word.
Why now?
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Monet.
You know, you always had me,
but when I nearly had you,
I-I got roped up.
Wasn't supposed
to go down like that.
Now I'm finally the man
you said I could be,
and I guess I couldn't
come back until then.
Shit, I can't believe
you bought the place out.
That import-export business
must be good, huh?
I see you did your research.
You did yours, finding me
under my married name and shit.
I had to, Mrs. Tejada.
Nae-Nae Stewart
wasn't bringing up anything.
That's because she's gone.
- Look, I gotta get outta here.
- Monet.
Look, I get it.
Your life is different now.
You know, I would really love
to take you somewhere.
I don't know
if that's a good idea.
Why?
Old friends
can't go places together?
I don't know
that we're old friends.
Okay.
Then what are we?
You really knew
I would call, huh?
I hoped that you would.
I can't tell you which,
but a major sports outlet
is gonna pay me
stupid money for this shit.
Don't worry about it.
Just get your shit together.
- Come on.
- You can't sell that.
How do we know if Zeke's okay?
Girl, calm down.
Zeke ain't no fucking
Aaron Hernandez.
He ain't do shit.
He'll be fine.
But I'm more curious as to why
Sierra and her goodies
were in Zeke's room
in the first place.
Uh, yeah, since when did you
start sleeping
with people for stories?
Okay, since when did you
start slut-shaming, Lauren?
I'm not, I'm just saying,
I think it's foul
that you let him hit
for a story.
Lauren, calm down.
Your feelings about Tariq
clearly got you on edge, girl.
I'm not tripping off Tariq.
I gotta get over that.
I just wish he would tell me
how he really feels.
See, that's why I don't fuck
with none of these
undergrad niggas.
They don't know a real woman
when they see one.
Mm-hmm.
But you know what you need?
Up here worrying about
that nigga's bag,
but you need to get up
into this.
Oh!
Is that weed?
- Yes, bitch. We smoking Lizzos.
- Okay, no.
I have internship interviews,
and if they drug test me...
it's a wrap.
When you ready to forget
that nigga's name,
don't worry, I got you.
Hmm.
That bitch is gonna need
more than that to relax.
Oh, yeah. A whole lot.
Look, um, I know Monet,
she had fronted me some money
with Cane, and...
I don't got that shit yet.
I ain't hit you about that.
I wanna talk to you
about the lawyer
that got your mom off.
- Davis?
- Yeah.
I tried to get
an appointment with him,
but the lady at the desk said
I need a referral.
Look, 'Riq, I held you down
with Monet
over that sugared coke.
You owe me.
'Riq, I need you.
I got you, D. I got you.
Okay.
Don't worry about it.
Yo. You find her?
I'm a man of my word,
young brother.
A'ight, so when can I see her?
Six p.m. sharp today.
- Hey.
- What's up?
That's in a hour.
Better hop to it.
Can you text me the address?
I gotta go. Text me.
Yo, you dead ass, Tariq?
I bring you up here,
and then you bring her?
Look, Lauren, it's not
like that, a'ight? I...
It's so much shit
going on right now.
Everything's so complicated
'cause of my mom, and...
Okay, then tell me,
what is it like, Tariq?
What's it even like
between me and you?
I'm just asking you
to be up front with me.
You know what? Never mind.
Lauren.
Lauren, wait!
Come with me, please.
Look, I wanna show you
what I've been doing
this whole time.
Please?
Man, this is something else.
Never done anything
like this before.
We can do so much together
if you just let me.
Hey, Auntie, it's Zeke.
I'm at the 21st Precinct.
I need your help.
Tariq, what's this about?
'Riq, 'Riq.
Yas, what's up? You good?
Look, I got you something.
Yas, this is my friend Lauren.
Lauren, this
is my baby sister, Yas.
Hi.
She's pretty.
She is, right?
Thank you. So are you.
Hey, come on. Talk to me.
How's school?
Who been bothering you?
Who I gotta beat up?
I think you're
beating me at this.
I kinda am.
What? I am.
An honest woman.
I respect that.
Are you Tariq's girlfriend?
- Um...
- Whoa, Yas.
Um... Tariq?
I'm the one
that's supposed to be
asking you the questions.
A'ight? So talk to me.
You hanging in there, right?
You'll be home soon. Okay?
I don't wanna go home,
not with Big Mama.
When you come back,
you won't have to go
with Big Mama.
You can come stay with me.
You really mean that, 'Riq?
Yeah, of course I do.
I can be with you all the time,
and Lauren can visit.
- I hope so.
- Yeah.
And so can Mom.
Um, I don't know
about Ma yet, Yas.
You know, I'm still
working on that.
It might take a little minute.
But look, I got this
so I'm with you
anywhere and everywhere you go.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Um, where's your bathroom?
Down the hall to the left.
Okay, but is that,
like, your left or my left?
Hey, look, so you can call me
at any time you need me, okay?
My number's right here.
Go like this, this, and boom.
Just make sure nobody
sees this phone.
- Okay.
- Nobody, okay?
Okay, time's up.
I-I could have sworn
we just got here.
I bent over backwards
to make this happen,
Mr. St. Patrick.
Yasmine, let's go.
See you soon, okay, Yas?
Thank you
for bringing me today.
Watching you and your sister,
I get it now.
- You're all she has.
- Yeah.
You know,
I wanted to show you that.
I just didn't want you
to think
I'm just bullshitting you,
you know?
I got a lot of shit going on,
and I hope that's okay for you.
You sure?
Hey, Auntie, it's Zeke.
I am at the 21st Precinct.
I need your help.
Oh, shit. I gotta go.
What is it? Can I help?
Nah, I gotta do this alone.
I told you she would
text you back.
What, you a psychic now?
- Mr. Cross.
- Excuse me. Rude.
You can shut the fuck up.
- Put your pants on.
- What the fuck?
What-what's wrong?
Fucking cops
just grabbed up Zeke.
I know.
What do you mean you know?
Sierra was there.
She was the one who shot it.
She-she showed me.
Fuck, are you serious, Lauren?
Look, with everything going on
with your sister today,
- I just forgot.
- Oh man.
Lauren, if anything happens
to Zeke, I'm outta here.
A'ight, half of my acceptance
was based on me helping him.
Wait, what?
This doesn't-that doesn't
make any sense.
There's a lot of shit
that's not gonna make sense
to you right now, Lauren.
Fuck.
Tariq, I'm so sorry.
Is there anything I can do?
No, it-it's fine.
I, um... I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
I gotta go handle this, okay?
I'll hit you later.
Yo, Davis, I need you to handle
something for me ASAP.
She ain't comin'.
I need to call somebody else.
Zeke, you need to trust me,
'cause there's no one else
who can help you.
Wait.
Check out my PBA card.
It's in my wallet.
Of course you have a PBA card.
He'll help me.
Detective Ramirez?
Where's Zeke Cross?
I'm his guardian.
You can't hold him.
- You need to calm down.
- Don't tell me to calm down.
And don't you
fuckin' touch me either.
Now, where is my nephew?
Where'd you get this card?
I don't remember.
Call him. Ask him.
When was the last time
you saw Detective Ramirez?
He's a fan.
I met him at a game.
He told me to show the card
in case I-in case
I got jammed up.
- Zeke!
- Hold on, ma'am.
- Ma'am!
- Zeke.
Ramirez gave you
this card himself?
- Zeke!
- I just... I don't...
- Huh?
- Uh-uh, get up, Zeke.
Who the fuck are you?
You need to watch
how you talk to me.
Now, are you chargin' him?
I'm asking him some questions.
He's here voluntarily.
Well, now he's
voluntarily leaving, asshole.
Give me a fuckin' break.
Where's my client
Ezekiel Cross?
I wanna see him now.
Your client?
Who the fuck hired you?
Ah, I'm Davis McLean,
criminal defense attorney.
- A mutual friend.
- Yeah, yeah.
I know who you are.
And we don't need
a criminal lawyer.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Listen.
I-I just ran a gauntlet
of reporters outside
to get in here.
It's a zoo.
Now, you go out there,
they'll eat this kid alive.
Yeah, use the back door.
I'll handle the press for you.
Hold up. Just let me ask him...
You wanna lose
your motherfuckin' badge?
Get the fuck outta my face.
Ezekiel Cross
voluntarily presented himself
to detectives to assist
in an investigation.
He was never a suspect,
just a good citizen
looking to help the police.
Detectives will tell you
he was not charged
with anything and in fact,
they were more than happy
to have this help.
Look at me. Did they hurt you?
What happened?
Professor Reynolds.
They think me and Carrie
had something to do
with his murder.
The fuckin' professor bitch
I told you to stop fuckin'.
Zeke, you need to end
this shit now.
I did.
Obviously not soon enough.
Why they tryin' to pin
this shit you?
What are you not telling me?
She was with Jabari.
So your girlfriend was fuckin'
the dead professor nigga.
Zeke, you on your way
to the NBA,
and you out here
getting caught up
in some community pussy?
Come on, man.
Look, I-I didn't say anything.
I-I didn't know what to do.
I called you.
You didn't answer.
And then I gave them
Ramirez's PBA card.
Wait, you did what?
Fuck!
You fuckin' gave them
Ramirez's PBA card?
That's what you told me to do.
Isn't it?
Monet.
Is there something wrong
with Ramirez?
Shit!
You always talk about having
my best interest at heart,
but don't tell me shit
to protect myself!
This is my life, my career.
What the fuck did you
just get me into?
Damn, I'm sorry, Zeke.
I should have took that card
away from you.
Look, I'ma make this right.
I promise.
I promise, baby.
As promised.
Business is poppin'.
Oh, so you
the new delivery boy now?
Tell your boss nice work.
Boss?
Nah, me and Tariq are partners.
You think I'd be
running this shit down here
if I was just a delivery boy?
Nah, we split our shit 50-50.
Uh-huh.
You good?
Yeah, this isn't all
I need to pull down tonight,
if you know what I mean.
How much you need?
At least eight bands.
Y'all pressed over eight bands?
You know that's not even
lunch money, right?
Listen, I keep telling you,
if you wanna make
some real money,
might as well
run the streets with me.
Make that stack
look like change.
Nah, we're not
diversifying right now.
Ah, right.
Them your boss' orders.
I told you, Cane,
I handle my own shit.
You ain't a real hot nigga.
Look, we're working together,
so put some respect on my shit.
Okay, big man, you got drip,
come get into it
with me tonight.
See how a real operation runs.
I'm not working
the corner again, fuck that.
I'm not trying
to pimp you out, bro.
You coming or not?
Look you can either
get in the car and trust me
or come up short for your
boss... your business partner.
Fuck it.
What are we gonna do?
Shit, I know a couple Guaps
we can run this through.
A'ight, bet.
Oh, shit, I gotta dip.
Wait, what?
I gotta go, nigga.
Get the fuck out.
- You just said that we were...
- I got shit to handle.
Okay, leave the bag.
And once I figure out what the
fuck is going on, I'll turn it.
Leave the bag?
No, I don't know
if I can do that, Cane.
You wanna
make the money or not?
Yeah, figure out your broke-ass
Tariq daddy issues
outside on the curb.
Fuck.
Cane, wait, wait!
I need it tomorrow by ten a.m.,
not a second later.
Say less.
Just send me the addy
and I'll pull up.
Don't fuck me on this, bro.
Nigga, please.
Fuck.
Zeke is upstairs resting
right now,
but I'm telling you, Cane,
if he goes down for this shit,
Lorenzo won't be able
to save your ass.
God couldn't walk through
that door and save you.
You understand me?
We gotta fix this.
We? Nah, nigga, me.
All you ever do is
fuck things up for this family.
Y'all so smart.
Y'all ain't tell him
not to use the card?
That's why she's mad.
She gave him the card.
But when you shot the nigga,
she never asked for it back.
Oh, so she blamin' me for it.
Shit, man, if something
happens to Zeke...
She I'll never get over it.
I should've known
something was up
when Ev told me
Zeke missed practice.
Dru, Monet got the call
while you were here.
What happened?
Monet wasn't here.
She left a few minutes
after you.
Where did she go?
Yo, what the fuck?
That's your fuckin' plan, huh?
Lettin' Zeke
go down for your murder
'cause you knew he was
fuckin' his professor?
- What professor?
- Nigga, Carrie something.
Listen, how the fuck
I'm supposed to know
he's fuckin' his professor?
I sent my lawyer up there
to handle that shit.
You need to chill the fuck out.
Chill the fuck out?
Nigga, they had Zeke down there
all fuckin' night
askin' him questions.
They're fishin'.
That's what they do.
I told you
Davis'll handle the shit.
It's gonna be harder
than you think, Tariq.
Zeke dropped Ramirez's PBA card
on them
before Monet could get him out.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Why the fuck would he do that?
'Cause he don't know
fuckin' Ramirez is dead.
Monet never told him
what I did.
Now Zeke's caught out there.
Now, if the cops find out
Ramirez is dead,
Zeke can get jammed
for both bodies,
since it was your fuckin' idea
to link them together.
Yeah, but you so fuckin' sure
that the body
ain't comin' back, right?
Yeah, I'm sure of it.
But when it comes down to it,
you gonna take the weight
for all that shit.
Ramirez, the professor,
all that shit is gonna be
on your fuckin' ass.
Listen, it ain't gonna
come down to shit, a'ight?
Like I said, Davis'll fix this.
Zeke'll be safe.
You'll be safe. I'll be safe.
We'll all be safe, a'ight?
Ain't nobody safe, nigga,
especially you.
Fuck outta here.
Fuck!
Your family hired
some of the best
appellate lawyers
in the state.
Yeah, but my father
thinks they robbed us.
Unhappy clients always
believed they've been robbed.
But the truth is,
sometimes there is no way out.
Which sadly is the case here.
Are you sure?
Oh, yes. We're sure.
Uh, Ms. Tejada,
obviously we
will remain vigilant.
If there is indeed a way
in which we can be of service,
we'll absolutely reach out
to you and your mother.
No, she doesn't need to know,
but thank you for your time.
Could you try to look
a little less gleeful
when you're sending
our paychecks out the door?
So what?
I don't wanna represent
a psychotic,
murderous drug dealer.
It was a lose-lose situation.
If we had lost, he'd kill us.
If we'd won,
then Lorenzo Tejada
would go back to just...
Sounds like
a repeat customer to me.
What's in our best interest?
Remember that.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
Shit, shit.
Come on, fuck.
Thank you, God.
You're a real one for this.
Cane, where have you...
been all my life? Damn.
Listen, I had a few
pickups of my own to make.
- You what I mean?
- Yeah. No, I can see that.
Bro, I didn't think you were
gonna show, to be honest.
Nah, man, listen,
we business partners.
You trust me,
I trust you, remember?
Facts.
Hand me that bag.
Oh! Fuck!
Bro, this is way more
than we needed.
Man, you are right,
the streets are where it's at.
You had me for real.
Nah, I gotta link Tariq, but...
Aw, "I gotta link Tariq"?
You sure
you wanna get your boy?
Come on, you don't wanna join?
Come on, let's have some fun.
Come on, baby. Let's have fun.
Nope, I gotta go. I gotta go.
I gotta go.
Fuckin' Tariq.
Why don't you buy yourself
something nice, on me?
My name's Brayden.
And I think I'm in love
with you already.
"My name's Brayden.
I'm in love."
- Bye, Brayden.
- God damn it, Tariq!
I know I'm gonna regret asking,
but what's, uh...
what's going on, Cooper?
There is this case
I turned down,
but it's the high-profile,
big-fish shit
that uh, Davis likes, so...
What was it?
Lorenzo Tejada, appeal.
I remember him.
Manslaughter?
Uh, and multiple drug offences.
Uh-huh.
Well, if Walter Griffith
was good at one thing,
it was prosecuting
those types of cases.
Wait. Wait, that was
Walt Griffith's case?
I heard he got fired
for-for, uh,
tampering with evidence
or stealing drugs from...
From the evidence locker, yeah.
But he did a fantastic job
of putting monsters
like that Tejada guy away.
Cooper, you coming?
Yeah, yeah. One sec.
My bad, bro.
Parking was a bitch.
Listen, man, you can't be late
to shit like this.
A'ight, I gotta know you
serious.
You got the money from
the dead drop, though, right?
- It was enough?
- Yeah.
I'm in this, Tariq. 30K.
Know I got you bro.
You don't gotta worry.
Speaking of business,
I know you said no
about diversifying
to the streets, but I...
How many fucking times
I gotta tell you
we're not fuckin' with Cane, B?
- I know.
- Listen, we pick up
the product from him
like we've been doing
and continue business
like usual.
Be fine.
Gentlemen, I'm interrupting
my massage for this.
See you found someone
you can trust.
Yes, I did.
All Mr. Weston
has to do is sign here
and you'll have a president
and a legitimate paycheck,
provided you have my cut,
of course.
I have your cut.
You ready, Mr. President?
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/9btw3
Help other users to choose the best subtitles