Enjoy Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
I really like him.
I just...
I don't know,
sometimes he just...
he just makes these jokes
that are kind of...
cutting.
Like...
kind of like he's
making fun of me.
He makes jokes at your expense.
Um... well, I think
he's just trying to be funny.
But, um, yeah, I don't know
if I'm supposed to...
joke back or just...
Have you asked him to stop?
Yeah. Sort of.
And what did he say?
Um...
well, he said that I was
being overly sensitive
and that they're just jokes.
So he continues even
though he knows it hurts you.
Well, nobody else
seems to mind, I guess.
But if he cares
about you, he would stop.
You should tell him to stop.
I think he'd just say that...
it's my problem
and I should just get over it.
Well, then tell him to fuck off.
This guy's a sadist,
he likes to cut people down.
You can tell him that.
He'd just say
I'm not getting the joke.
A sadist never understands
why others
aren't enjoying his sadism
as much as he is.
You should find someone
who makes you feel good.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
Okay, yeah.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
- Um, Margaret.
- Hmm?
Can you just promise not to...
to say anything about this
to anyone?
Of course not.
Fort Knox.
- Good night.
Abbie is out for the night.
How's the wife?
Fair.
I'm gonna go with "fair."
Mm-hmm. Could be worse.
Yeah, that's our motto.
We had that inscribed
in our wedding bands.
Hmm.
Peter.
Mm-hmm.
Do you ever draw?
- Do I draw?
- Yeah.
You know, drawing.
I mean, yeah.
Uh... Chloe likes me
to draw with her sometimes.
Yeah?
The other day, she made me
draw Peppa Pig, 47 times.
Yeah. I...
I made a drawing the other day.
A nude? Of me? A nude of me?
No, it was abstract,
a geometric thing.
Can I see it?
No.
I hadn't drawn anything
in 22 years.
I used to do it all the time.
Constantly, hours and hours.
Forget to eat,
forget where I was.
Never told me that.
Well, it's not really
very important.
So, what do you think,
further sex,
or you got to get home?
Hey, wakey, wakey.
Time to get up.
If you get up,
I'll make you breakfast.
Hell no.
Oh, thank you.
Steamroller?
No.
Hmm.
No! Mom, please stop!
Mom!
Good morning.
Through cell membrane
reorganization,
1037 can play a significant part
in inhibiting metastasis
and tumor cell proliferation,
so, in short, it's potentially
pretty fucking great.
Interns, you guys
didn't hear that.
Hi, smidgen.
Seriously, Abbie?
Are you hungry?
I was gonna cook.
No need.
Well, you should eat something.
Are you having cereal?
Maybe.
Yeah, well, it's not a meal.
It's fine, I'm going to Lucy's
in a little bit anyway.
You are?
Were you planning on telling me
that you're going out?
I'm telling you now.
Yeah, but it would have been
nice to know in advance.
You know,
just a one-sentence text.
Is that too much of an ask?
I'll take it into serious
consideration for next time.
- Come on, let me make you something.
- Mom! It's fine!
I'll just get something
with Lucy.
They always have...
snack bars at these orgies,
anyway.
Wanna see something?
Um... I don't know.
Do I?
What the...? Oh, my God.
Abbie, is that your tooth?
No, it is, in fact,
not my tooth.
What on Earth is it?
I don't know,
I found it in my wallet.
You found it...
What are you talking about?
Seriously, just like appeared
in the change pouch today.
Look, it's got like...
tartar on it and shit.
Well, where the hell
did it come from?
Smidge.
Promise me that you'll be
careful on your own at school.
Gonna be reckless, ma.
Some frat guy hands me a pill,
I'm just gonna take it.
No questions asked.
That's not funny.
Sorry it's not funny.
Now, let's
get busy. Come on, Jean-Louis.
Come along. Oh, that's fine.
- Who gets your vote?
- Scobie.
- He's the one who objected.
- Hello.
I'll take Tex's room
here and Gideon's.
You take Jean-Louis with you...
Oh, really?
Well, my friend, you're in luck.
They've got these, uh...
rustic individual bungalows
in the middle of the woods.
I'll send you a link.
What, in New Hampshire?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
It's quaint,
it's maximum quaintness.
I'm listening.
I figure we can go up on...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...uh...
on Friday night.
Hi, Mom.
Oh, smidge.
Hey. Hey.
Honey.
It's no big deal.
Yeah. How'd it happen?
Riding bikes with Lucy.
You don't know how
to ride a bike.
Yeah, you never let me.
I let you. It's just...
it's dangerous, that's all.
Evidently.
Had you been drinking?
A little bit.
Okay.
All done.
Mom, can you please stop
tucking me in?
You have nothing,
nothing to be scared of.
- I'm not scared.
- No, I know.
It's just, everything
is going to be all right.
I know.
Look, I'm...
I'm sorry that I didn't
respond to your text sooner.
I was at work and my phone
was in the other room.
I know. It's fine.
No, it's not fine.
It's stupid, it's just stupid.
Jesus, Mom, if you're gonna
eat shit about this,
can you please do it
in the other room?
I'm kind of sleepy
from bleeding all evening.
Abbie, what the hell?
Sorry.
Don't curse, please.
So I said, "Can't you just
do this one thing for me?"
And, uh, he asked
what he'd get in return.
And then what happened?
I said he'd be happier
knowing that I'm happy.
Was that enough?
No.
He wanted me to...
to do something for him.
Things for him.
What did you say?
I told him
that he's a piece of shit.
And I told him
that he didn't deserve me.
And I left.
- You said that?
- Yeah.
You did good, hear me?
You're tougher than leather.
Just don't tell anyone I...
Of course I won't.
I would never.
I promise.
It's gonna be
a happy ending for you.
...typically
with replacement therapies,
such as different types
of therapeutic enzymes.
We have also benefited
from novel biologic platforms,
such as gene therapies,
which have proven successful
as part of
our development pipeline.
The overall goal is to develop
a robust manufacturing process
that aligns
with our recent focus
on product attributes
and is critical in generating
quality target product profiles
for novel candidate compounds
in development.
Of course this requires
a tremendous effort...
Sorry, sorry.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Abbie!
What the fuck?
It's okay. It's okay.
Um...
Are you okay?
Yeah, are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
I just...
I just thought something
might have, um...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, honey, it's fine.
- What happened?
- Nothing.
I just feel a bit off.
I'm going to go take a shower.
Don't go anywhere, okay?
I love you.
- Hey.
Are you sure you're all right?
I threw up.
Must have been something I ate.
I'm feeling much better now.
Do you wanna, like,
lie down or something?
Hmm-mm. What do you want
for dinner?
Don't wanna cook.
I was gonna go to Lucy's.
I'm gonna need you to stay here.
I'm not gonna go biking. Okay?
You go out too much.
I go to Lucy's.
We play Elder Scrolls.
No, you get drunk
and then you carve up...
- Mom, I am 18 years old.
- In two weeks.
Stay home.
This used to be quite a place.
It's been deserted
for a long time now.
- Will you take me in?
- Goodness no.
It isn't safe out there anymore.
That's why they put up
this barrier.
It would be very easy
to step around it.
What attraction could
there be for you out there?
I'm not sure.
I'm a reasonable person,
I don't know.
Maybe I wanna satisfy myself...
- Margaret?
- Yes.
Um, I was just wondering
if you could sign off
on my hours...
It's not a good time. I'm not
available every second, okay?
Okay.
What are you doing?
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
That's fine, keep going,
keep going. Keep going.
- Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
- What is it?
Just, just, just...
Here, here, here.
Come on, come on.
- No, no, stop, stop, stop!
- What?
Okay, just stop.
I'm just not...
into this whole... thing.
- Okay?
- It happens.
No, no, no, it's not that.
It's not that.
I mean, you know me.
It's just...
Since when do we fuck
in the bathroom?
What's with the urgency?
I just felt like it.
Well...
it's not my thing.
If it's not your thing, you
shouldn't have agreed to do it.
Do you wanna go for a crawl
and get some loot?
I'm low.
You wouldn't.
What the fuck?
Hold on.
Okay, now you're just
being creepy.
It's not creepy
to want to look at your child.
No, but you're doing it
in a creepy way.
Sorry.
Mom, what is going on?
You're being like... even more
suffocating than usual.
Just gonna miss you.
I'm... only gonna be
like two hours away.
I know, but...
who's going to protect you?
I don't need protection.
No. You're very strong.
But know that if anyone
so much as touches
a hair on your head,
I will find them
and I will hurt them.
Mom, when you say things
like that,
I mean...
that's for you, not me.
I don't need to hear that.
But you seem to need
to say it an awful lot.
Yeah, well, I'm...
I'm just trying
to tell you that I love you.
Then just say "I love you."
I love you.
There you go.
It's that easy.
Hey, hey, hey.
What?
You wanna drink whiskey?
I figure if you're gonna drink,
I better show you how.
There.
Ready?
Wait, wait. Wait, wait.
What the hell is that?
Nothing.
1, 2, 3...
Come on, I raised you
tougher than that.
Again.
Nope. No.
- Nnn... no.
- Abbie, I haven't even picked out anything yet.
- Can you stop, please?
- It doesn't matter. I'm not gonna wear it.
Yeah, well, you can't wear
a sweat shirt every single day.
- Apparently I can.
- No, you can't.
If you go to school dressed like
that, people will think you're weak,
and that is not something
that you want to project.
Oh, is it not
something I want to project, huh, Mom?
Well, then maybe a cracking new
jumper would do just the trick.
It would be just my ticket.
What?
Stay here.
- Abbie.
- Are you okay?
- Come on, let's go.
- Why?
Mom!
You're hurting me, stop!
What are you... Why?
What's going on?
Why are you being weird?
Come on. Just come with me.
Come on, hurry up. Quick!
- No.
- Move it, Abbie, now!
- You're being fucking crazy.
- Abbie, just... just trust me.
Just get in the fucking car.
Ow!
Abbie!
Stop being fucking crazy!
Go away!
Abbie.
Look... this is just a...
it's a challenging time
for me right now.
There are factors
creating stress in me.
Your going away,
and work, and...
Don't be scared.
I'm on top of it.
Can you hear me?
...a clean data profile
showing anti-amnesic properties
and some neuroprotection
in some models.
I'll kick it to Margaret to
break down the trials for you.
Margaret?
- Margaret?
- Hmm?
The trials.
Right. Right.
It's, um...
Uh, if the phase, the phase...
a phase-one single
ascending dose, um...
phase...
It's, um, it's in the packet.
It's, uh...
It's, uh, it's in the packet.
Margaret, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
- Fuck!
- Oh!
I'm sorry. Sorry.
I mean, I... I apologize.
I should go.
I...
So sorry for that, everybody.
Andrew, could you please get someone
to help us clean this up? Thanks so much.
Go away.
Please, David.
You heard me.
Are you speaking to me?
Of course I'm speaking to you.
Why are you here?
What, in the park?
Stay away from me and my kid.
Well...
you approached me, madam.
I don't know who you are.
Don't play fucking games.
Why are you here? Why now?
Okay, you are mistaking me
for someone else.
You piece of shit.
You mother fucking
goddamn piece of shit.
Ben is with me.
Right now, here.
That is a lie!
Madam, if you're
going to raise your voice,
we're going to go...
we're going to go
back to the Boulevard.
Don't walk away from me.
What do you intend to do?
I intend to go home, Margaret.
So you do know who I am.
You introduced yourself to me.
You came up to me,
you shook my hand.
You told me about Abbie.
Don't you remember?
Stay away from my daughter!
"You introduced yourself to me."
"You told me about Abbie."
"We shook hands."
"Shook hands."
Do you know this man?
Yes.
We were...
involved once.
Uh, when did you split up?
Twenty-two years ago.
- Twenty-two years?
- Mm-hmm.
I haven't seen him
since I was 19,
and then about a week ago,
he just, uh, he just appeared.
At your home?
Or a place...?
No, at a conference,
and then in a store,
and then again in a park.
Public places.
Yes, but places
where I happened to be.
- It's not a coincidence.
- I understand.
I'm just trying
to get the facts.
Has this man accosted you,
harassed you?
Not exactly, no.
Okay, has he
initiated contact at all?
No.
But I know him.
I know what he's capable of.
Well, um...
what would you like us to do?
I want you to issue
a protection order.
At the very least,
I want you to contact him
so that he knows
that the police...
Those aren't really
options at the moment.
You're free to file a complaint,
and I can provide you guidelines
on how to deal
with a potential stalker,
but unless you have something concrete
to show this man's harassing you...
Officer, I can't do nothing. I can't
just sit around and wait for him to...
There's nothing we can do.
So just...
be smart, be careful,
and don't hesitate to contact us
if the situation
escalates, okay?
Hey.
It's dark in here.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's only nine days left.
It all went so fast.
Um... I was wondering
if you're going to be doing
my recommendation
or maybe somebody else?
- Me.
- Okay. Cool.
Um... good night.
Gwyn.
Yeah?
Do you think you could
kill someone?
Um...
I mean if you had to.
Them or you?
Uh...
No, I don't think I could.
Why?
- It's nothing.
- Are you okay?
You know, if you need
to talk to somebody, I'm...
I'm actually,
I'm a really good listener.
Have you ever done anything bad?
Like... like bad?
Yeah.
I have.
Why?
I did something bad.
When I was young.
Unforgiveable.
Well, what was it?
I won't tell anyone.
I promise.
Fort Knox.
I was 18.
And I, well...
...my parents,
they were biologists.
They're dead now.
But after school,
I took a gap year
and traveled with them
from London
to a research facility
on the Queen Charlotte Islands,
off the western coast of Canada.
I drew a lot back then.
I wanted to be an artist.
Thought that being in nature
would inspire me creatively.
It didn't.
It was cold and boring
and there was hardly
anybody there.
But there was this...
man.
Another biologist
from some university up north.
David was his name.
And he was handsome
and charismatic.
And he noticed me.
Of course he noticed me,
an 18-year-old
in that remote place.
And he went about it right.
Charmed mom and dad first.
Oh, they just fell
in love with him.
Before you knew it, it was
the four of us all the time.
He'd entertain us,
tell us stories.
Give me wine.
Pills.
After a few weeks,
I moved in with him.
My parents, they were...
they were hippies.
Naive, stupid.
I told them I was grown up,
and they believed me.
At first it was wonderful.
I was his muse, I inspired him.
He said he was on the verge
of a breakthrough.
I didn't question it.
All I knew was
that for the first time,
I felt important
and appreciated.
So I didn't object
when he started asking me
to do things.
"Kindnesses," he called them.
They were little things
at first.
Cooking, cleaning.
He told me not to draw.
Told me not to wear shoes.
Even outside.
But the kindnesses,
they evolved.
Became tests.
Endurance tests.
Meditation for hours.
Fasting for days.
Poses.
Stress positions.
After a kindness,
he would shower me
with praise and affection.
The more I did,
the more inspired he became.
Said he could see the future.
Said he could hear God
whispering his name.
And I believed him.
I believed every
goddamn thing he said.
And whatever he requested,
I could hack it.
And if I couldn't,
he'd tell me to burn myself
with cigarettes.
But I could hack that, too.
Winter came and my parents left.
But I stayed.
I was so stupid and fucked up.
It was five months before I even
realized that I was pregnant.
David told me
not to tell anyone.
He forbade me from giving birth.
I tried to stop it.
It kept growing.
And whatever I did,
no matter how much
I could take...
David wasn't inspired anymore.
I gave birth on the bed.
No drugs.
No doctors.
I looked at my baby and...
immediately I realized
why I'd been put on this Earth.
I named him Benjamin.
For a few weeks
it was all right.
David didn't pay much attention,
but I cared for him.
I didn't think I could love
anything more than I loved David.
But Ben proved me wrong.
David, David knew that.
One day he asked me
to go into town for supplies.
I'd never let my baby
out of my sight until then.
When I came back, two of Ben's
fingers were on the counter.
That's all that was left.
I begged David to tell me
what he'd done with him, but...
all he'd say was
that he'd eaten him up.
"He's in my belly now, Maggie."
That's what he'd say.
Over and over.
So I went to bed
and stayed there.
I stopped eating,
my baby was dead.
But David, David just kept
saying he wasn't.
He was...
inside.
Said he could feel him moving,
said he could hear him crying.
Crying out for me.
And after a while...
I could hear him, too.
Suffering.
Trapped.
But alive.
It went on for weeks.
David wouldn't let me
come near him unless...
The kindnesses,
they became very hard.
And I did my best.
But I guess I wasn't
as tough as we thought.
So I ran.
Stole some money,
the truck, and ran east,
to America, where I thought
he'd never find me.
I've never told anyone that
in my whole life.
You should be honored.
I don't understand.
I let it happen.
I let him hurt me.
I let him poison
my brain with lies
and then I let him
kill my child,
and then I ran.
I don't get it.
Is this...
Is this some kind of joke,
or is this a test for me?
Because that's horrible.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I...
I shouldn't have said anything.
Just go home
and forget it ever happened.
Okay.
Feel better.
"We shook hands."
"Shook hands."
"Then we went to..."
"I went to the Boulevard."
Boulevard.
- Thanks, hon.
- You're welcome.
Good morning, Maggie.
Take a seat, darling.
You're beautiful.
Still beautiful.
You look like shit.
I know.
Distinguished shit, all right?
Get out of town. Now.
If you don't go, I will do
whatever I have to do.
I will.
Relax.
We'll be fine.
All of us.
Me, you...
Abbie.
Are you threatening my daughter?
Threaten? God no.
I don't make threats.
Seems to me, you're the one
making threats at this table.
You're goddamn right I am.
So where's the father?
She doesn't have one.
Oh.
Well, that's quite a trick.
No, it's not.
I went to bars, I met men.
It was easy.
Does she have your magic?
Your gifts?
She's certainly not
a gifted cyclist, right?
I went to the police. I can
have you arrested at any time.
Arrested? For what?
Drinking tea in a diner
or sitting in a park?
- What?
- Why are you here?
Because he's still inside me.
Here.
- Suffering.
- Don't.
- Every day he cries...
- Just stop it now.
...he screams,
"Where is Mother?"
- "Why did she abandon me?"
- Shut up.
I tell him to let go,
I say, "Your mother ran."
- "She ran from her baby."
- No, lies!
But he refuses,
he just hangs on.
- He should hate you...
- You lying...
- ...but he yearns for you.
- ...insane, fucking pig!
You protest too much.
I know you know.
He's alive.
I've kept him so.
I took good care.
He's here, thanks to my charity.
Any minute,
I could change my mind.
I could purge the boy,
put him out
of his fucking misery.
Thought you didn't make threats.
Well, if the boy's dead,
where is the threat?
What do you want?
I want...
a kindness.
It would be, I think,
right if, from now on,
you didn't drive to work.
Instead you walk.
Barefoot, no shoes, no socks,
you know, every day.
And then what, hmm? Then what?
I'm giving you a gift.
You see that, right?
Do this simple thing
and life goes on undisturbed.
Till the next thing, and then
the next. I know how this works.
No, no, no, no, no.
I promise.
You just do as I ask.
You don't follow me,
you don't meddle in my affairs.
You just do this and I vanish.
You arrogant, fucking...
I don't do what you say anymore,
you understand?
I don't negotiate.
I don't take orders,
I don't look away.
So whatever you think
that you're doing,
it'll fail,
because I'll be there ready.
Come after me,
come after my child,
I swear to God,
I will kill you.
You kill me, you kill him.
There is no him.
I just want you to be happy.
That's why I'm here.
Barefoot, every morning.
We wouldn't want
any more accidents.
Oh, fuck.
Happy now, you piece of shit?!
Now, you disappear.
Now, you fucking disappear!
Naan?
I think you need
to see somebody.
Oh?
I think you're having
an episode.
What? Oh, no.
Everything's fine.
You've got nothing
to worry about, I promise.
There.
There you go.
That said...
I'm gonna need you
to help me out
by being extra careful
for a little bit.
Okay?
If anyone approaches you
that you don't know,
tries to talk to you,
you don't engage,
you go away immediately.
Why?
Because someone is
behaving erratically.
Who?
Someone from work.
Okay? Someone I had to let go.
Is making trouble.
What's his name?
This guy?
David Moore.
David Moore?
Yeah. British guy.
About 60.
You never mentioned
any other British people
at your work.
I did, I'm sure I did.
Okay, then I'll...
stay away
from old Brit David Moore.
Stay away from anyone
you don't know
until I say "all clear."
Here. That's chicken.
...who was killed
in an invasion of his own home
by a high-powered rifle shot
from some distance away.
Seems to have come to some
sort of a conclusion here.
The fugitive, wanted
for two and a half years,
James Cobb,
in part wanted because...
Why are you here?
I'm visiting a friend.
Come here.
What friend?
His name is, uh, David Moore.
No David.
No, there is.
No David here.
I know that he's staying here.
Rent room or get out.
Rent room or get out!
How much?
Get out! Get out!
Now! Now, now, now, now, now!
Text me, on the hour,
every hour.
Just to let me know
that you're okay.
Just, just write "okay."
Can you do that?
How about I, uh,
I'll make it worth your while?
$20 a text, hmm?
That's a pretty good way
to make some pocket money.
Don't you think, smidge?
Smidgen?
Pow.
What is this?
What the hell
are you doing here?
- Margaret.
- What is he doing here?
Relax. Why don't you
take a seat?
Can you answer
the question, Abbie?
- I called him.
- You did... did what?
She's concerned.
All right, I'm concerned.
You haven't been to work in a
week, and Abbie says you're out...
- You let a total stranger into our house.
- ...every night, all night.
- He's your boyfriend, isn't he?
- I don't have a boyfriend.
Don't treat me like I'm a fucking
infant, I know what you two do.
- Don't cuss.
- The point is, we're here to help.
I'm fine.
You are not fine!
I need to talk to you
on our own.
Abbie, can you give us a minute?
- I'm just trying to help you.
- Can you go to your room now?
- Please!
- Now.
- Please?
- Abbie.
Go to your fucking room.
How dare you come
to my house uninvited?
It's important that I know
that you're all right.
Well, I am all right. As far as
you're concerned, I'm always all right.
Look, we're friends.
Okay, no, we are friends,
and when I see a friend
that's in trouble...
I am handling it, okay?
I'm doing what I have to do
to protect myself
and my daughter from harm!
What harm? Margaret?
It's none of your business.
Look...
I, uh...
I have a number here.
It's for a good woman, okay?
- A psychiatrist.
- What the fuck?
No, just stop.
You are overstepping.
I owe you nothing!
If I don't return your calls,
you suck it up.
You don't pop in and you
certainly don't discuss me
or anything else
with my goddamn daughter.
- What harm, Margaret?
- If you think that I would let anything
happen to her, you are mistaken!
I would do anything,
sacrifice anything
for my children.
For them, I'm unstoppable.
I'm a goddamn champion!
Children?
When was the last time
you slept?
You need to get out.
Oh, come on.
- Get out.
- All right.
All right.
- This is the person I was talking about.
- Get the fuck out!
If that buzzer rings,
you don't answer for anyone.
Do not open that door.
Do not leave this apartment,
ever, for anything,
unless I'm with you,
do you understand?
You can't keep me as a prisoner,
I'm an adult.
No, you're a child, and you'll
do what I fucking say!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to yell.
Hey, I'm sorry.
Mommy, you lied to me.
I called your office.
Nobody named David Moore
ever worked there.
Yeah.
He's not from work.
He's from when I was young,
and he wants to hurt us.
But I won't let that happen.
And I'm sorry
that I couldn't tell you.
You're lying to me again.
I'm not.
Mom, there's no guy.
You're just...
You're just saying all this.
You're just making this up
to keep me here,
to control me.
No, no, I'm not.
Mom, I'm... I'm all grown up,
and I'm gonna go away
and you can't take it.
No, smidge, that's...
that's not right.
You have to stop.
It'll all be over soon...
Whatever this is, Mom...
you have to stop,
it has to stop.
I can't take it.
It'll all be over,
it'll all be over soon.
It has to be over now.
Or I'm gonna leave.
I'll go.
I will.
And you won't be able
to stop me.
No, no.
Shh! It's all right.
You're safe here.
I don't feel safe with you.
Come here. Come here.
Come here.
It'll all be over.
Tomorrow.
I promise.
You kill me, you kill him.
Don't move.
I have a gun.
You know he's here?
He's right here.
That's why you couldn't fire.
He's dead,
and you fucking killed him.
You know, he's very upset
that we're arguing.
Listen.
You hear him cry?
Shh!
Listen.
Can you hear?
Get the fuck off me, you fuck!
Listen. Listen!
Listen.
He's dead, he's dead, he's dead.
- Shh-shh-shh-shh!
- He's dead.
Listen to your son.
He can't understand why
you allowed this to happen,
why you let him get hurt,
why you ran.
What kind of a mother
abandons her child
when he needs her most?
Are you going to fail him,
Maggie, again?
Is Ben inside me?
Stay away from my daughter.
She's just a substitute.
I held up my end.
But you, you followed me,
you tried to kill me,
in breach of our deal.
I think...
I think this calls
for a kindness.
Assume the position.
In the park, Washington Park,
two o'clock till dawn,
every night
until further notice.
Right?
Go near her, I'll kill you.
If you want to keep her safe,
then you do as I ask.
It's that simple.
I hold up my end, Maggie,
always have.
This is not the time
for recklessness.
I'll kill you.
I'll fucking kill you...
Mom.
Happy birthday.
Don't come after me.
Don't call me.
Baby, I fucked up.
I just left him there...
with that man.
I should burn in hell
for what I did.
Go to the doctor.
You'll be okay.
What?
Abbie.
Abbie, no!
No!
Abbie! Abbie, talk to me.
Come on, please don't do this.
Just talk to me!
Abbie? Abbie!
Abbie, stop!
He wants to hurt you!
Abbie, don't!
Abbie! Abbie, open the door.
- Drive! Now, please! Drive the car!
- You Abigail?
- Yes, I'm Abigail. Start the car!
- Please!
- Look at me! Abbie, don't go!
- Drive! Drive!
Abbie, don't go!
Abbie!
Motherfucker.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
You fucking piece of shit.
- Margaret? Hey!
- Shit!
Were you fucking spying on me?
- Huh?
- Stop it!
- Were you fucking spying on me?
- Fuck! Margaret!
Goddamn it.
- Why are you here?
- I was worried about you.
What did I tell you? Huh?
What did I tell you? Stay away
from me. My children are in danger.
I don't have time
for your bullshit.
You are sick, all right?
You're sick
and you need help and...
And what?
And I am in love with you.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Didn't you know?
Fucking men.
You can't stick your dick
in anything
without deciding that you
love it or you hate it.
You don't love me,
you just annoy me.
Impede my mission once more and
I'll beat you till you're dead.
Okay.
Fuck.
Don't worry!
They're coming.
They're coming for you.
They're...
No, no, no.
No.
Abbie? Abbie, it's nearly 1:30,
and I don't know where you are.
Will you call me?
Please, call me.
Just, when you get this,
just call.
Just, please, just...
just let me know
that you're okay.
Shh! I can protect you.
I will keep you safe.
I will not fail you again.
Yes?
Uh, there's
a man here to see you.
All right.
Ballion.
The girl at the desk
said your name was Ballion.
Ballion. What is that,
French or something?
I mean, what's wrong
with "Walsh"?
Maggie Mary Walsh.
It's a fine name.
So tell me,
how was it last night?
They still work, don't they,
the kindnesses?
Ease the pain, quiet the noise.
Make you proud.
Look at them.
They have no idea.
You do realize that I'm
the only person
that can see you,
who really knows who you are.
These people, they don't
have the first inkling
of what you're capable of.
You're a warrior.
You're a champion.
Well...
I'm the only one that knows.
I'm the only one that can
see the hole right there
in the center of your heart.
This... life,
this...
character that you've created,
Ballion, did you think
that she would fill it?
Did you... did you think
that this job would fill it?
You made a daughter
to fill the hole,
but even that didn't work,
because nothing will heal you.
Nothing except him.
Come to this room tonight.
Ten o'clock.
It's been 22 years.
Maggie.
Be with your son.
Fine.
Hey, boss.
Hey.
I... I just wanted
to say, I'm...
I'm glad you're feeling better.
Thank you.
Tomorrow's my last day.
You haven't seen
that guy again, have you?
What?
You know, the asshole.
Oh.
- No.
- Good. You're very strong.
Thanks.
All right, see you tomorrow.
I helped.
Excuse me?
I helped, right?
I helped you with...
with things.
Yeah.
Of course.
A lot of things.
Good.
I'll make sure
your letter is glowing.
Abbie, if you're watching this,
it means...
Abbie, smidge.
If you're watching this,
it means that
something went wrong.
I... I wrote everything down
in a letter a long time ago.
I hoped I'd never have
to give it to you.
It is what happened to me.
Every word is true.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I thought that I
could make it all okay, but...
I was unlucky in what happened.
But, Abbie, I was...
I was so lucky,
so, so, so very lucky
to have you.
A million deaths
would be worth the 18 years
that I spent with you.
I love you.
I admire you.
I hope that you understand
why I needed to do what I did.
And if you don't...
I'm sorry.
But I know that when you have
children of your own...
you'll understand.
When you become a mother,
your own life doesn't mean
so much anymore.
You become disposable.
Gloriously disposable.
Maggie.
So glad you could come.
You look wonderful.
I tried to find
something elegant,
but, you know...
there's a view.
And I got some wine.
Do you want a glass?
- Where is it?
- Hmm?
The gun, show it to me.
It's in the river.
No more of that now.
I got you a little something.
Here.
I saved it for you.
I remember you drawing it
when I first laid eyes on you,
on the beach.
Every morning,
there you'd be on that beach
with your pad,
no matter the weather,
working for hours
on that same drawing.
You didn't know
but I was watching you.
I knew.
I always knew.
Of course, you always
saw right through me.
You just watched and watched.
Never said anything.
And then there you were
at our place,
getting my parents shit-faced
on that disgusting
homemade wine.
- Oh, yeah.
- It was very clever what you did.
You knew exactly
what you wanted.
Yeah. But so did you.
I was a child.
A stupid child.
And you just kept coming
over and over.
But then one night,
there you were, at my door,
and within minutes,
a world that had seemed
so cruel, so disordered,
became...
immaculate.
Do you remember
how stunned we were
when the sun came up
and we realized
it had all been real?
Of course I remember.
That time, the life we made was
holy.
It was perfect.
God, Maggie,
I've missed you so much.
It's too bright.
We both missed you, Maggie.
Yeah.
He's awake.
He's moving.
Would you like to feel?
Come here.
It's okay.
There.
Feel the little hand
reaching out for you?
Hmm?
You wanna talk to him?
Talk to him.
He can hear you.
It's all right.
Nothing will happen, I promise.
Ben?
Whoa, whoa.
It's okay. It's okay.
Yeah?
He says hello.
Put your hand right here.
He needs you, Maggie.
It's okay.
Do you want to say hello?
To your son?
Hmm?
Say hello to your boy.
Hi...
baby.
My baby.
Tell him how you feel.
An-an-anything you want,
he's here.
Ben.
Ben, I...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for...
for being a bad mom.
It's all right.
He forgives you.
Maggie.
No, no, no.
You're forgiven.
He loves you.
No, no...
No, no!
Oh, David.
David, he's alive?
My son is alive.
He is, yes. He's...
He's inside you?
Yes.
- Suffering.
- No, no, no.
He's happy now.
He's happy now. You're here.
He knows that you love him.
- He needs to be fed.
- No.
- He needs to be held.
- He needs his mother.
- He has his mother.
You're right here with him.
You just... you need to relax.
- I failed him.
- No.
No, he loves you.
I left him,
and you put him inside.
I had no choice, you know that.
But I brought him back
here to you.
Thank you.
Thank you for bringing him back.
I have him now.
And he has me.
And I think...
I think that we don't
need you anymore.
What are you doing?
Maggie. Maggie.
Just... come and sit
and we'll talk.
I will do anything
for my children.
Shit!
Ah...
Maggie.
You need to calm down.
Baby's crying. He doesn't
like that we're arguing.
No, no, please!
Let's just talk,
let's just talk.
Don't move or I'll stab you
in the fucking neck.
Why?!
Why did you do that?
I can't fathom this.
I came to you
with the greatest gift,
and this is what you do.
Without me, there is no him.
Can't you see that?
We're one, and we love you!
Stop that, Maggie!
Just... no more.
Just stay where you are!
Drop it! Just...
Just drop it! Yaaah!
No, Maggie.
Please, no more.
No more, Maggie.
We need to go to a hospital.
Together, we can do it.
We can... fix this.
We can fix this, Maggie.
Oh, God, someone's hurt you.
But I'll save you.
I'll save you.
We can be family.
No. No, Maggie, please.
Don't.
You're killing him.
You're murdering your own son.
God, it stinks!
It stinks in here!
He was wrong, yes, so wrong.
You're a terrible mother.
I am a good mother.
You're a murderer.
You kill me, you kill him.
Then I'll have to do it
while you're alive.
Don't do it, Maggie.
Please, please don't do it.
Don't do it.
Don't do it, don't.
Don't, Maggie, don't do it.
Don't do it!
Please don't do it!
Arggh!
It's not my fault.
I just did what you wanted.
I would have done anything.
I came back, I came back.
Because I see you, Maggie.
I see you.
Hey.
Hey, you.
It's good to see you again.
I saved you.
Oh, shh, shh, shh!
Oh, shh, shh, shh, shh!
Oh!
I'm all packed.
You want to hold him?
Okay.
Shh! Shh, shh, shh!
You got the head?
There you go.
Shh, shh, shh!
Thanks, Mom.
Hey, little fat-ass.
Hey, you.
Shh!
Abbie-pooh.
And the claw!
The claw!
Mom.
What? What is it?
I just wanted to tell you
I'm not scared anymore.
You made everything okay.
So I'm not scared.
Oh, shh!
It's okay, huh?
It's okay.
Enjoy Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP