This whole living situation
with Severide,
it's not a permanent thing.
I'm gonna start
that apartment search again.
No rush.
Severide, we are running out of time
for you to shut down those leaks.
Yeah, copy that, Chief.
Whoa!
Wait, where are you going?
I'm headed for the roof.
Where's Casey?
He went to get Severide.
- Get ready!
- This is insane.
One, two,
three!
Let's go round back!
- Let's go!
- To the river!
Where are they?
Casey!
Severide!
There!
Where's Severide?
Severide!
I got Severide!
Kelly!
I'm gonna harness up and get him, Chief.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com.
- Otis, extend the aerial.
- Yeah, copy.
Severide!
Casey, come to shore.
Kidd will get him with the aerial.
Squad, get him out. Get him out now.
Watch your back.
Okay, swing right.
Swing stop.
Show me what you do.
Take her up.
Stella, you got this.
Good.
Swing right.
Hey!
You need to back up. Let us do our work.
- Get out of here!
- Okay. All right, yeah.
You got it. Go get your man.
Kelly!
Do it! Bring me down, bring me down!
Bring us up!
Kelly...
Talk to me.
Kelly! Kelly!
Kelly.
Can you hear me?
- Easy.
- Got him.
Got him, got him.
Nice and easy.
- Kelly!
- Watch his head.
Severide, can you hear me?
Kelly...
Come on, Lieutenant, talk to us.
All right.
- Casey. Where's Casey?
- He's good.
- He's fine.
- Come on, come on.
We got you.
What the hell were you two thinking?
We weren't.
That was incredible.
Get over here.
You're not moving the rest of the day.
I'm good.
Didn't we have an understanding?
No fivestory jumps into the river.
I told you, I'm trying
to qualify for Tokyo 2020.
High dive, gold medal.
I got to get my practice in where I can.
Well, you didn't stick the landing.
Actually I think I did.
Tens from all the judges.
Must have missed it.
I am happy to miss any and all of that.
Can I get you anything else?
You want hot chocolate? Apple cider?
You.
- You always have me.
- Well...
Then I don't need anything else.
What took you so long?
Boden called over to Med.
Made Halstead's brother check
me out for a concussion.
- Will?
- Yeah, that's the one.
What'd he say?
Take some Tylenol.
- Seriously?
- More or less.
Okay, look, I'm supposed
to go into Molly's North
to train some new bartender,
but I'm gonna cancel
and just make sure you're okay.
Kelly?
- Hey.
- Yeah. I'm okay.
I'm just, can you walk me
over to the couch?
Yeah, of course. Come here.
Here, come on.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Man, just breathe.
What!
You...
- You think that's funny?
- Yeah, it's funny.
I was kidding. I'm fine.
- Get your ass to Molly's.
- Gladly.
You're a terrible person.
I want a cleareyed selfassessment.
I'm sore all over. I'm not gonna lie.
- But good to go, Chief.
- And you?
Went through the concussion protocol.
Flying colors. Fine.
And if you weren't,
you wouldn't tell me anyway.
- Chief Huffhines.
- Wallace, Matt.
- Kelly Severide, Chief.
- Kelly.
See the coverage
in the "SunTimes" last night?
Yes, I did. Very nice.
Well, let me tell you,
the office of public relations
has heard from everyone.
The commissioner's office,
mayor's office.
- Everyone is tickled pink.
- I'm glad.
So I reached out to the photographer
who captured these amazing photographs.
I'm sorry. This is...
Nate Isaacs,
professional photo journalist.
Right, and I said to Mr. Isaacs,
I said, "Would you be
interested in doing"
a dayinthelife
pictorial spread?"
A real inside look at what we do here.
And I could not think of a better house
than the one that produced
this stellar shot.
Okay, so when are you thinking to, um...
Right now. Today, this shift.
Chief, listen, if this
is an intrusion at all,
you just tell me and I'll take
a big step back, just like at the scene.
You tell me to move back,
and I do as I am told.
- Okay, why not.
- Great.
Nate, I'll leave you to it.
Thanks.
So how do you want to do this?
Go about your shift normally.
At the end of the day,
we'll see what we have?
- Good.
- Okay.
I heard from Hope.
You did?
Yeah, she sent me an email,
said she's back in Fowlerton.
She wants to drive up and have lunch
so she can mend fences.
What did you say?
Delete.
Hey, so I am alerting you, ladies,
we have a photographer in our midst.
- What does that mean?
- It's some press guy.
He's doing a dayinthelife
photo shoot.
Help.
Help, Dawson.
It hurts.
Gerald?
- It hurts.
- You know this guy?
He's a frequent flyer. He's harmless.
- What happened?
- It's broke.
Let me take a look, Gerald.
Okay, well, I don't think it's broken,
but we can get you to the hospital.
What happened?
I... I fell.
Where'd this happen?
Home.
You walked all the way over here?
Okay, listen, Gerald,
we're gonna get you a sling
for your arm so you
won't keep cradling it.
We're gonna take an xray
at the hospital
just to make sure it's not broken, okay?
- Come on.
- I got it.
Come on, buddy. Let me help you up.
There we go.
That's the guy.
Do you want me to tell him to back off?
No, no, it's fine.
Come on, Gerald. Let's go.
Hey, close the blinds so we can hide
from this photographer.
Psst, hey.
He's hiding in here.
What do you need, Kidd?
Actually, it can wait.
Well, don't mind me.
Okay.
I just wanted to ask
if I could swap next week
with Grigsby on third shift.
I have a lead on an apartment
and the building manager
wants to meet with me.
Yeah, sure. No problem.
Just write it down on a sticky note,
put it in my office.
Okay. Will do.
- Trouble at home?
- Not on my end.
I told her she could stay
as long as she wants.
My God. She didn't.
- Who didn't?
- Hope.
You know how I deleted her email?
Now she's trashing me on Facebook.
Nah.
These are mutual friends
she's stirring up in Fowlerton.
Who knows what she's saying
in real life.
You got to drag her.
You send out a blast,
and you let everybody back home
know the stunts
that she pulled in Chicago.
Yeah, I saw these two
celebrities brawling on Twitter
and it was everything.
Do something like that.
You know what, I'm just gonna
go with my first instinct
and ignore her.
Come on, girl, you got
to stand up for yourself.
I stand up when it's
something worth standing up to.
Hope isn't worth it.
Ambulance 61.
Man down from unknown causes.
8451 Racine.
Everything?
It's hyperbole.
Why a goat?
Well there are many guesses about that.
The only plausible one I heard is
that this house was built
on an old goat farm.
No, no, no, just go about your business.
- Ignore me.
- No, what we were gonna do
is smoke a couple cigars.
You know, I could put my camera down,
and, join you guys.
How do you get impaled on an iron fence?
He was trying to kill himself.
- Jumped out a fourstory window.
- Ouch.
SGBS isn't fixing that?
Super glue, baking soda.
Medics in the field, they swore by it.
Said it was better than gauze
for packing a wound.
- Where were you embedded?
- Afghanistan, five months.
Of course, Chicago can be
its own war zone sometimes.
Don't ask.
I'm gonna shower and change now.
Got a call, guy was face down on Racine.
Turned him over and...
All over Dawson.
50/50 chance it could have been me.
Listen, I'm gonna go get some coffee.
Anybody want anything?
Be right back. Nobody touch my cigar.
Don't worry.
Captain, did you get a chance to look
- over my furlough request?
- Not yet.
Everybody wants Fourth of July off.
That's why I put in five months early.
Okay, I'll be sure to look at
that pressing concern after I...
I need to know.
Casey!
Hey, take it easy, man.
Are you kidding me?
Hey, what's going on?
Found this scumbag lurking
outside your shower.
I had no idea that
these were coed bathrooms.
So you just decided to
explore the bathroom
you didn't know was coed?
Right after I said I was going
to take a shower?
- Get out.
- Just hold on for a moment...
Get your camera and get out
before I beat the hell out of you.
I mean it!
That was freaky.
- What happened?
- The photographer you brought
into my firehouse was playing
peeping tom in the bathroom.
I, I can't even...
It happened while I was in the shower.
Okay, well, I'll,
I'll call the paper.
And we'll call CPD.
You want him arrested?
I want a formal complaint.
- On the record.
- If it happened here,
it ain't the first time.
Someone needs to know.
Well...
You're right. You're right, um.
I'm, I'm embarrassed
this happened.
And I should have done
a better job at vetting him
before I proposed this.
It's not your fault.
You just got caught up in the buzz.
You know what?
Let me call the CPD?
- I should be the one.
- I'll do it.
Okay.
Again...
I'm sorry.
Okay, we are on the Blue Cobras.
- They'll announce it.
- Okay.
So you have done this before?
I'm in league.
And we happen to have
a spot open for tonight
which you're filling.
I will bring it. Don't you worry.
How's the apartment search coming?
I got a lead.
- Yeah?
- Yes. Yeah.
You excited about living alone again?
My God, you play WhirlyBall?
- Hi.
- She is a firsttimer.
- Hi, Stella.
- Lily.
Brian and I are thinking of
going on the championship circuit.
I'm not gonna say we
perfected the Malachi Crunch
but...
- What team you guys on?
- The, um...
Next up on Court 2, the Dig Dug Express
- against the Blue Cobras.
- That's us.
Us too.
You guys are going so down.
Okay.
Ready for a refill, buddy?
Sure. Thanks.
Okay, look, I'm not one to pry,
but as your bartender,
I got responsibilities.
So, what's going on?
Come on, maybe I can help.
I've seen stuff.
It's my girlfriend, Alice.
She wants to move in,
but I think it's too soon.
- Do you love her?
- It's only been six months.
What's your name, pal?
- Kevin.
- Okay, Kevin.
Look at it like this, okay?
- Life, it's like a fire.
- Boy.
You go in too far too fast,
you're gonna get burnt up, right?
- I guess.
- Yeah.
But if you throw water on too soon,
you know, you're in
a rush to cool it down,
then you are going to boil
those firefighters
like, you know, a bunch of lobsters.
- Okay.
- So, listen.
You and Alice, you got some heat, right?
- I think so.
- Well, what you got to try
to figure out is, is it the kind of heat
that you want to run into
- or you want to run out of?
- Yeah, I don't think
- that's a usefu...
- No, actually,
- that makes total sense.
- Yeah.
See?
Thanks, man. I really appreciate it.
You got it.
That was pretty good,
what you did over there.
Yeah? I'm just helping out where I can.
"Mitchell Monroe,
Life Coach Managers."
- Whoo.
- I'm a talent manager
for life coaches.
I help turn, you know, advice
into a profitable business.
Okay.
Tell me more about profitable.
Well, my coaches charge
$40 an hour to start.
I provide the training,
I manage the paperwork
and the invoices,
I take 10% off the top.
And it's my job to, what?
Coach people's lives?
Something you seem
to be doing pretty naturally
from what I just witnessed.
Your words of wisdom, they have value.
You give me a call
when you're ready to take the next step.
- Hey.
Have you played WhirlyBall before?
Because it is not as easy as it looks.
Yeah, well, I mean
we should get a team together.
Otis and Lily are, like, regulars.
And then Zach knows the manager,
so, you know, I mean we could
go whenever we wanted.
Sounds interesting.
Are you,
- you staying up?
- Nah, I'm gonna go to bed.
You sure? 'Cause it's me
and you, I can,
I can rally.
Nah, it's okay.
Gonna get some shuteye.
Okay.
Could have been worse.
Had he taken pictures of you?
No, I mean for him.
Matt was about to rip his head off,
and I was ready to help.
He's lucky to be alive.
Is that Gerald again?
Gerald?
I... I need medicine.
Gerald, what's going on?
It hurts.
Okay, we're gonna get you something
out of the back of the ambulance.
Just give us a second here.
What do you think?
I think he's being messed with.
He walks all the way over here, twice?
R. E. Fire!
The reason why you are here
is you need to get your life
in order, and I am here
to help you with that.
- What's the "F" stand for?
- "F" stands for
fire pole.
The thing that connects
the two floors of a firehouse is a pole.
Pole starts with a "P."
It's a fire pole. Fire.
It is always there when you need it,
and in an emergency, it will help you
quickly get to the things that you need.
- Yes, Joseph?
- Why are you doing
this thing so formal?
The thing that makes you unique
is that you are not formal.
Clients are going to pay
a lot of money for this.
You need to, um,
"show them that you are a professional
in dress and manner and in method."
Well, continue then.
Thank you.
Hello?
Hey, Lester.
- How's your foot?
- It's a lot better, thanks.
You looking for Gerald?
No, actually,
we know where Gerald is.
Do you know if anyone's bothering him?
Hey, it's okay. You can tell us.
I don't want nothing to do with this.
That's Gerald's tent right there.
Hey, whoever's in Gerald's tent
needs to come out.
What do you want?
That's Gerald's house.
- Not no more.
- Come on, let's go.
- No, Dawson, no.
- This is my house.
This is my street. Go home, skanks.
No, this is not your street. It's mine.
Along with his and his and theirs.
You know who else's streets these are?
Every paramedic
and firefighter in Chicago.
We've been on every block in this city
and helped someone on every one of them.
And all those people we've helped,
they're on our team, not yours.
You mess with Gerald again
or anyone else in this camp,
then you'll be picking a fight with us
and everyone that's loyal to us,
and then you'll find out
whose streets these are.
She used to be my friend.
Are you sure you don't want
to go to the shelter, Gerald?
You call us if anybody
messes with you again, okay?
I think I will email Hope back.
Tell her straight up
I'm not interested in
anything she has to say,
just so there's no misunderstandings.
Hey! What's up?
Just thought I'd drop
in with some cookies.
Aw.
I swear you are an angel.
- Good time for it.
- Hey!
We're losing all faith
in humanity around here.
- Rough call?
- Worse.
Pervert came into the firehouse.
- Thanks.
- Good.
All right, question for the group.
I am gonna need some help
getting this life coach thing
off the ground.
Why don't I be your first client?
- No.
- Yeah, great!
Done! You are not gonna be disappointed.
Okay, let's,
get you signed up, and then
we'll get you started.
- Okay?
- Now?
- Why not?
- Okay, we gonna... no?
- You said.
- No, okay, I didn't...
We'll just go on back here.
I got stuff to talk about.
What just happened?
You see the "F"
is for you're...
How was it?
Brett was awesome as always.
I just got off the phone
with both the "SunTimes"
and "The Tribune."
They said they're severing
all ties with Nate Isaacs
and will blast his name to
all the press in the area.
They assured me they
took it very seriously.
Good riddance.
Well, I thought you would like to know.
You thought right.
So, how was it?
Really good actually.
- He's a very wise man.
- Really?
Really, really.
Yeah, I told him about my sister,
and he said I should reach out to her
which is what I've been
thinking for a long time.
You have a sister?
Then we started to talk about Hawaii.
You know, how I wanted to go
there after college
but my parents put the kibosh
on that particular dream.
He said, "Sometimes ladders
don't reach the highest floor",
but we have to hump up the stairs,"
which is really solid advice.
So, yeah, I'm gonna think about it.
About what?
You know, moving to Hawaii.
Anyway, today was really fun.
I'll see you tomorrow at Molly's North?
Yeah.
Definitely.
Right after I murder someone.
Hey.
What's up?
I just think things are
getting weird between us.
It's not weird for me.
Look, I'd like to say what I mean.
You know I'm not much
for dancing around subjects.
Me either.
Um, it's just this Zach guy
is really cool.
And we have a lot of fun together.
And it may get serious.
Who knows? It feels like
it's heading in that direction.
But you...
are so special to me.
And, um...
so important.
And I just feel like it'll... it'll
clear up a lot
of things once I move out.
Okay?
All right, well, um,
thank you for, listening to that.
Do you want to hear my opinion?
Yeah.
I don't want you to leave.
Truck 81, Ambulance 61.
Single vehicle accident.
500 block West Harrison Street
Eastbound.
Crowd control, block off the sidewalk.
Give us some room to work.
Otis, Mouch, with me.
Stand back, sir.
Excuse me. Stand back, please.
Ma'am, can you tell us what happened?
I don't know, I just
looked down for a second.
And the car started spinning.
We're gonna have
our medics take a look, okay?
Back up. Thank you.
Okay.
Captain.
Hey!
Get off the scene.
I got a right to be here.
I ain't asking.
Freedom of the press, buddy.
You can try to destroy my name
but I can still sell photos
of public employees
wherever and whenever I want!
Casey, don't. He's not worth it.
- How you doing? You all right?
- I'm okay.
Hey, you gonna give us
the room to do our jobs?
It's a public street, lady.
How you feeling, honey?
- Okay, I guess.
- We can get her out
as soon as we pop the door.
Call for a second ambo!
Casey!
Pulse is strong. He's alert.
What happened?
You stepped in the street
and got hit by a car.
But the captain saved you.
One hell of a call.
Could say that.
Herrmann says you didn't hesitate.
Not for a second.
Nope.
That's good.
You sure about that?
'Cause I'm not.
And what if the man you saved today
is different from the one
he was yesterday?
You think he's magically reformed
- because he got hit by a car?
- No.
I think if we start
wondering if one life
has more value than another,
we can't do our job.
Today you gave Isaacs the
second half of his life back.
You can't control what he does with it.
But a life saved...
That's one for the win column.
I will take that win any day,
no matter who it is.
So...
I am proud of you, Captain.
Isaacs is stable.
Well, you know, physically anyway.
What, too soon?
Yeah.
Well...
Thank you.
For what?
For being the sort of man who
will protect me from a creep.
And then run into traffic
to save the creep.
I love you.
I love you too.
Two, three, and four.
- What's this?
- 10%. I had my first client.
And it went pretty damn well
if I do say so myself.
We can settle up
when you get a few more.
- All right.
- Speaking of which,
I need a check from you for $800.
What for?
Well, I added you to my gold roster
which is for active life coaches
who have completed the bronze workbook
- which you did.
- What now?
- You!
- What? Me?
I took your stupid advice.
I told Alice that moving in with her
made me feel like
I was being cooked alive.
Listen, I didn't say to say that.
I definitely didn't tell
you to say that.
- She dumped me!
- Look.
I mean, you...
Hey, hey, take it easy.
You ruined my life.
Okay, buddy.
So that was a setback.
I think that you need to leave.
Okay.
That's all right.
Excuse me.
What was all that?
Listening to me for advice
might be the dumbest thing
that you could do.
No.
Lily was very appreciative.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You gave her some excellent
things to think about.
Well, you know what, you tell her
that I don't think that I'm gonna be
in, you know,
life coaching business anymore.
I'm gonna stick with what I know.
Firefighting and running this bar.
You know what? Actually I
might run over to Molly's North
right now and let her know
that before she decides.
- Cover for me.
- Yeah.
You got it, buddy.
Something to get you started.
- Thank you.
- Ooh.
Fancy. Fancy.
My God, Severide would be
completely busting my balls
about eating in a place like this.
He's always like,
"Lou Malnati's is all I need."
And I'm like, "No, sometimes"
a girl's gotta be wined and dined."
I...
I didn't... I was, that was rude.
Let's talk about you.
No, no, no sweat. It's all good.
Actually, you know what? There is...
There is something I wanted
to talk to you about.
I wasn't sure if it was too soon.
What... what is it?
Okay, well, my sister
is gonna be in town next week.
And she's cool, and I think
you'd like each other so...
I wanted to know
if you want to meet her?
Of course. Yes.
Yes, I would love to.
Good.
- Hey. What's up?
- I tried to text you.
My phone's on the charger.
Just seeing if you were around.
Yeah, come on in.
Did Kelly get stood up tonight?
Nah, I just wanted to hang
with the old married couple tonight.
So sweet.
- I'll grab the wine.
- Beer?
- I will grab the beers.
- Yeah.
You all right?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thanks, babe.
Cheers, guys.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com