Mayday. Emergency. Gas explosion.
Firefighters down.
I screwed up.
I deliberately broke protocol.
It's my fault that they're dead.
Don't do this, Jason...
taking the blame.
You don't tell the truth
about what happened,
you'll never ride a rig again.
- What's the prognosis?
- The cancer's in my bones.
My odds are not good.
I'm not thinking about odds,
I'm here and so are you
and that's enough.
Her latest numbers look good.
It's a big jump for
just a couple days treatment.
Yeah, she just hasn't been eating,
and she's sleeping all the time.
That's the chemo.
Not much we can do about that.
Hey, ladies, quit gossiping about me.
Doc says you're doing great.
Yeah, well, no offense, Doc,
but my definition of great
doesn't include tossing
my cookies every hour.
I'm sorry about that, Anna.
I'll order you something for that.
Hang in there.
It's good.
- I'm gonna take the shift off.
- Come on, Kelly.
You've been watching me sleep
for, like, two days.
My dad's gonna be here in,
like, half an hour.
- Just go to work.
- I don't mind.
Go!
I'm fine.
Just a phone call away.
So...
How'd it go with Kannell?
He's determined to take the fall.
Protecting Doyle's memory.
It'd be noble as hell if
he weren't tanking his career.
Well, that's his choice.
The case is being closed
at today's monthly review panel.
So we go to the panel.
Ask them to postpone it.
We don't have the standing.
Kannell is sticking to his story.
Then we gotta change the story somehow.
Okay.
Whatever you need.
Hey, I'm not gonna
rush into this and end up
with some serial killer, okay?
Then you can pay the extra rent.
What, you guys still looking
for a roommate?
In your place? Where would you put them?
A three bedroom unit
just opened up in our building.
Those are great.
Yeah, so Otis said, "Let's grab one."
"We'll get a third roommate.
It'll be cheaper," he said.
One third of more money
is less than half of less money.
That's just math.
So we moved in and lined up Levantini.
- From first shift.
- But his girlfriend asked him
to move in with her,
so now we're screwed.
This was supposed to
save me money, not cast me.
Leon is starting
community college in Florida,
and Cruz is footing the bill.
I get this new bouncer gig
and that helps, but...
What about me?
For a roommate.
'Cause I've been going nuts
trying to find a new place
within my price range before
my landlord doubles my rent,
so it would really help me out.
And you know
I'm not a serial killer, so...
- Do we?
- Just think about it.
People in this house really can't help
moving in with each other?
It's like a compulsion.
Wai... didn't you invite
Severide to stay with you
after he moved out of Casey's?
That was different.
- Yeah.
- Squad 3, Engine 51.
- It was.
- Yeah, waga, waga, waga.
- Big difference.
- Structure fire.
Capp, Tony, you guys vent.
Cruz, through the front with me.
- Yup.
- Got it.
Hello?
Fire Department! Call out!
Hey, 51.
We're gonna need a line in the kitchen.
Copy that, Squad 3.
Lieutenant!
Hey, ma'am?
Ma'am, hey, you're gonna
have to come with us.
Lieutenant!
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com.
Ma'am! Can you hear me?
We gotta get you out of here!
- Come on. We got you.
- No.
- We got you, come on.
- No, I'm okay.
- One, two...
- I'm okay.
Come on.
Fire's headed for the eaves.
Get a line on that back roof.
Copy that, Lieutenant.
- There.
- Lay down. We got you.
Running from firefighters?
A couple pictures
aren't worth your life.
That house is my whole life.
- We'll save what we can.
- Thank you.
Think this guy'll listen?
Of all the Chiefs on
the panel, he's our best bet.
- Harry!
- Wallace.
I'm already running late,
but you knew that.
Just need a moment of your time before
- you go into the panel.
- Who's this?
Chief Harry Moran,
Lieutenant Matt Casey.
- The alderman.
- Yes, sir.
I wanted to talk to you about
the Squad 6
sewer tunnel incident.
We've already lost so many men.
I'd hate to see us lose Kannell, too.
I think getting two firefighters killed
is a pretty good reason to end a career.
Unless he wasn't the one who screwed up.
He's already admitted as such.
All due respect, sir,
it wasn't Kannell's fault.
It was Doyle's.
That's a hell of an accusation to make
of a man who can't defend himself.
The way Kannell says it went down...
him dropping the meter,
running back to the rig...
we're talking 50 feet.
If those levels were normal
before he dropped the meter...
There's no way the air
saturated while he ran 50 feet.
The only way
this could've happened is if
Doyle got a high reading, and
then took them in there anyway.
Then why is Kannell taking the blame?
Because he didn't want
Doyle's wife and kids to think
he died anything but a hero...
and neither do we.
What if there were another option?
One that clears Kannell,
and keeps Doyle out of it?
I'm all ears.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm just...
just looking up stuff for Anna.
Homeopathic?
That's pretty far out for you.
She's just always so damn tired.
She's barely eating.
- Chemo side effects?
- Yeah. One says acupuncture.
One says massage, one...
Ginger milk thistle...
When I was in rehab...
everybody had a different theory
about how to get through it.
Drink a lot of water.
Don't drink any water.
Blah, blah, blah.
Know what got me through it?
Hamburger and French fries.
Every day.
Give Anna my best.
We're all thinking about her over here.
Okay. Hear me out.
The whole appeal of Levantini
was that he was from a different shift.
Okay, but I'm so quiet,
it'll be like I'm on a different shift.
Yes, because you're so low-key
and unobtrusive.
Look, Brett, no offense, it's just...
I don't know about
having a girl roommate.
Okay, but I'm not just any girl.
I spend a third of every week
surrounded by men.
I know enough not to
hang my bra on the shower rod,
and I can tell a good dirty joke
when I need to.
Let's hear one.
Yup. She's got nothing.
- What about the parking space?
- Yes! Look.
The landlord only gave us
one parking spot in the garage,
which me and Otis
are already trading off on,
which sucks, by the way.
I'll park on the street.
You're gonna love that
come December.
You know what, just write down
every question you would ask
any other potential roommate...
a man, a stranger,
and if I pass, I get to move in.
Ambulance 61. Person injured from fall.
725 Barrington Avenue.
You guys, over here.
I don't know what happened.
I thought I had her.
The rope slipped out of my hands.
Let me look at your hands.
Hey.
- What's your name?
- Laurie.
Hey, Laurie. I'm Gabby. This is Sylvie.
This place is closed.
- What are you guys doing here?
- We snuck in.
- Thought it'd be fun.
- It was my idea, not Aidan's.
You... you guys aren't gonna
call the cops, are you?
Hey, Brett?
Yeah, what's going on?
Spinal fluid.
Separation between
her skull and her C-1.
All right, Laurie.
I want you to do me a favor.
I want you to squeeze my hand
as hard as you can, okay?
Good job.
Okay, so Laurie, it's possible
you have something called
an internal decapitation.
I need you to stay completely still.
I'm gonna be right here to help you
so that you don't move at all.
- Okay.
- All right, we can't risk
putting her on the backboard.
I'm gonna grab the scoop
stretcher and head rolls.
- And spider straps!
- Yeah.
Stay calm.
Stay calm for me.
So how long have you guys been together?
Yeah, like, a month.
We met on Saint Patrick's Day,
but he didn't text me
for, like, three weeks.
Sounds like a player.
No, he's sweet.
All right, Aidan. I want you to tuck in
on Laurie's side right there.
We're gonna slide
these two pieces underneath her
until we feel the middle connect.
Really slow, really gently.
Then we're gonna take these head rolls.
We're gonna put them
on either side of her neck.
You're doing great.
Just stay calm for me.
Feet first.
- I'm scared.
- I know you are, honey,
but you're doing great. Okay, guys,
on my count. One...
two, three.
- Head rolls.
- Take one.
Hold this in really tight.
Doing a good job.
Okay.
Let's secure her with the spider straps
and get her to Med.
Good job.
Excuse me?
I'm looking for Lieutenant Severide.
Yeah, you found him. How can I help you?
I'm Hope Norwich.
You saved my mom, Ellie, this morning.
I just wanted to bring you
some cookies as a thank you.
Thank you. How's...
how is she doing?
Doctor said she only has
minor smoke inhalation.
Mom's pretty tough.
- I noticed.
- Yeah, she's already
back in the house.
Claims the bedroom's fine,
and she'll clean the rest as she goes.
The fire was in the roof.
It's not safe.
I figured.
I called the city about having
the property condemned, but even then,
if she refuses to go, I'll have
to call the police to remove her.
She is the most stubborn woman
on the planet.
Anyway, I just wanted
to thank you for helping her.
Sure.
What does Baba's
favorite knitting stitch
have to do with me being
a good roommate?
It shows that you pay attention.
Fine. A garter stitch.
- Ooh!
- Sorry!
The answer we were looking
for was "Stockinette."
Minus 3,000 points.
What?
That "Battlestar Galactica"
question I got right
was only worth a hundred!
The points are at the discretion
of the management, I'm afraid.
Now on to a more delicate subject.
You and Cruz used to date.
You and I, we had a moment.
Now if you had to choo...
You know what,
don't even finish that question.
Minus 2,000 points.
Come on!
Okay. Forget it.
I'm gonna sleep in my car.
No, no. Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, all right?
You can still win it all back?
The final question is worth...
wait for it...
11,000 points!
Two guards stand in front of two doors.
- One door leads to heaven.
- The other to hell.
One guard always tells the truth,
The other always lies.
You may ask one guard one question.
What is your question?
Who wants a parking spot?
Let me be more specific.
How about three parking spots?
One for each of us, which
I negotiated with the landlord.
And FYI, your landlord loves me.
I brought him baklava,
so you're not getting this deal
with any other roommate.
Congratulations, roomie!
- Welcome!
- Yay!
My God.
What do I smell?
Guess.
A cheeseburger from Small Cheval?
- And fries.
- Bring it here!
You really do love me, don't you?
I do.
And I love you.
All right, all right.
Enough of this schmlatzy crap.
- Can I eat now?
- Go, go, go, go, go.
It's good, isn't it?
They got you on something new?
I started to run a fever
so they put me on
an antibiotic just to be safe.
- Everything else good?
- Supposedly.
My God, this is so good.
What... what are those cookies?
Thanks from a woman today.
We pulled her mom out of a burning house
and the old lady kept running
back in trying to save things.
- Nearly got herself killed.
- What kind of things?
Family pictures.
Daughter stopped by and said
that she already moved back in.
- She refuses to move out.
- Was that safe?
No. Probably not, but...
Woman loves her house.
It's not about the house.
When you have to really, like,
look at the things
that you're scared of losing,
it's not...
it's not the things
you don't want to let go of.
It's just...
- it's just this.
- Hey.
Hey.
Anna, you don't have to
worry about that.
I'm right here.
Yeah.
Anyway...
I bet once you go talk to her,
you'll find out
it's not the things for her, either.
When you find out what it is,
you can help her.
Who says I'm gonna go talk to her?
I did.
- I already told...
- You're cleared.
What?
Boden and I talked to Chief Moran.
The panel chalked the whole thing up
to equipment failure.
Saying the meter was faulty.
But that's not what happened.
Doyle's clear. You're clear.
The whole thing's closed for good.
Your job's waiting for you
whenever you're ready.
You really don't get it.
That doesn't change anything, Casey.
I watched three men die
and now I'm done with the CFD.
It's over.
I'm out.
Hey. Hey, Doc!
What the hell is up with the DNR?
Would you give us a minute?
Whether or not to authorize
life-saving measures
- is the patient's choice.
- It's your job
- to tell her not to give up.
- No, it isn't.
You said her numbers
were good. You're optimistic.
I am and so is Anna,
but she also knows that
if treatment stops working,
extreme measure won't turn the tide.
Look, this isn't a white flag.
It's a worst case scenario.
She said she had a fever.
She does, but we're treating it.
Go home. Get a shower.
Do what you gotta do to get back here
and help her keep fighting.
It's not right.
Kannell did everything he should have,
on the call and after.
Really?
You think that lying about
how the call went down
was the right thing?
To protect his lieutenant's good name?
Absolutely.
I'd do it for Boden in a second if...
God forbid.
Me, too.
He can't just give up.
Am I being an ass?
That's a shift.
The guy lost his brothers,
and I'm riding him
because he wants to walk away.
Maybe I should let him go.
No, baby.
And quitting isn't exactly who you are.
You fought back after losing Darden
and you got Severide back
after we lost Shay.
You're not gonna
start quitting now, are you?
Hello?
Ma'am? Mrs. Norwich?
- The firefighter.
- Yeah, Kelly.
Severide. How's it going?
I got it covered.
Okay, well, your daughter
stopped in the firehouse
yesterday, and she seemed
pretty worried about you.
"Worried" is Hope's natural setting.
- I'm fine.
- Okay, well, just so you know,
it's not safe to be living here.
What's this nonsense?
All it needs a little cleaning up.
If you really want to be useful,
come help in the kitchen.
Ma'am.
Ma'am?
You ma'am me one more time,
you'll be wearing what's in that bucket.
It's Ellie.
Ellie, nice to meet you.
Look, I know that
you've probably been living here
- for a long time...
- 37 years.
But it's gonna take
a lot more than cleaning
to make this place safe.
The roof supports have been destroyed.
Not to mention the exposed
insulation is a health hazard.
It's too dangerous.
This place has stood here
for a long time.
I'm sure it has a few more years in it.
What's your story?
Sorry?
You have something weighing on you.
Someone that I care about is sick.
It's my girlfriend.
It's bad?
It's cancer, but she's...
She's fighting. She's gonna beat it.
Good.
True love...
like Hal and I had,
made a life worth living.
Hal's your husband?
Was.
Had a heart attack last summer.
No warning.
We built this place.
That backsplash,
I hand painted every one of those tiles.
These marks,
this is where we marked
Hope's height every six months.
Till she was 18.
Ellie, I get it. I understand.
You understand, do you?
You understand what it's like
to think you're gonna spend
the rest of your life with someone,
and then one day,
all you have is memories?
I'm sorry.
You just...
make sure you grab
all the memories you can.
Man.
We are two sorry sons of bitches?
You wanna...
Drag that stove out to the curb for me?
And then get back to your girlfriend.
Bring her some flowers from my garden.
Yeah, sure.
Hey, Snow White!
What happened in here?
I just straightened up a bit.
I think it looks great!
Where my door chair stuff?
- What?
- My door chair stuff.
The stuff that I keep here on the chair.
You can't just move
a guy's door chair stuff.
I gotta get to work.
Everything's in the front closet.
What? Who keeps clothes in the closet?
Whoa.
Everything's labeled with
a different font.
The one for winter gloves is all frosty.
See, easy peasy.
Not as easy as my door chair, though.
Jason?
Jason, I know you're here.
Your car's out front.
Fine, just listen.
I've been here.
I've lost people.
But if we quit because of
the ones that don't make it,
we quit on all the people
we could save in the future.
I know you love being a firefighter.
It's in your blood.
So when you're ready, just...
come find me.
How's it looking?
Had to talk a couple of
college girls from dancing
on the tables, but other than that,
- it's been pretty quiet.
- What the hell, dude?
- No, man. You're done.
- I said go get me a beer!
- I think eight's your limit.
- What?
- You're done.
- What did you say?
I said you're done.
Hey, we got a problem here?
Yeah, I got money to spend
and I want a beer.
Yeah, I think you're at your limit.
Thinking ain't your job, okay?
Your job is to take my money
and bring me my beer.
Okay, buddy, hey, time to go.
- I ain't done nothing.
- Look, you're disrupting
the other patrons, all right?
Don't make this a thing.
Get off me, all right?
Go get me a beer, all right?
- I said go get me a beer!
- Come on...
- Get off me.
- Hey, man, take it easy.
Whoa, buddy,
we gotta get you to a hospital.
Get away from me!
You got fired?
You were a bouncer. You bounced him.
Yeah, well, owner says
he didn't specifically tell me
to lay hands on the guy,
so he's not responsible
for what happened after that.
How else were you supposed to
kick a belligerent drunk out?
Look, you guys,
I know you're trying to help,
but I really don't wanna
Monday morning quarterback this.
I can pay rent
a little earlier this month
- if that helps.
- You know what would help?
If my life weren't
turned upside down at home, too.
- What?
- You can't just come
into somebody's place
and start moving stuff around.
- Hey, now.
- You know, forget it.
My bad. Right? As usual.
Cruz, the screw up.
Squad 3. Car pinned by fallen tree.
84 Andrews.
Branch landed on the car
with the driver inside.
He says he's not hurt,
but the impact jammed the doors.
Okay.
Hey, sir,
can you lower your window more?
You know, I was just
getting ready to head to work,
- and then bam.
- Yeah.
We'll get you out of here.
My landscaper said
the tree had some dry rot,
and my wife said
I should take care of it.
Yeah, I hear ya. Just give us a second.
Okay.
My God.
Um, there's too much weight.
This whole roof's
gonna collapse any second.
Cruz, why don't you grab a blanket
- so we can shield him.
- You got it, Lieutenant.
- Tony, grab a backboard.
- Got it.
Hey! Let's get that backboard!
- Coming in!
- Okay! Okay!
Hey, sir, when I pop this window,
- I want you to push yourself out.
- Okay.
Okay.
All right. Here you go.
- We got you.
- You're okay.
My God.
Severide!
Hospital called. It's Anna.
There's been a change. You gotta go.
Go on. Go!
I'll take over.
- Kelly.
- Hey...
- What's going on?
- The infection's taken over.
Anna's immune system was
too compromised by the chemo.
Unfortunately, she's septic.
What... What does that mean?
- I'm sorry, Kelly.
- Sorry?
There's nothing more we can do.
We're given her something to
make her comfortable.
If there's anything you have to say,
now is the time.
Okay.
Did you go see her?
What?
The lady from the house.
Okay.
Thank you...
for these last few months.
No. No, no, no. Don't do that.
Don't say goodbye.
We're gonna beat this.
Honey.
Hey, we got a miracle once.
We're gonna get another one.
Why don't you tell me about her.
Ellie?
You were right.
It wasn't about the house.
It was about her husband, Hal.
You should hear her.
It's,
Hal this, Hal that.
They were married for 37 years.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's why she wouldn't leave the house.
All of the memories there.
She can't move with it on her shoulders.
What, babe?
You can't carry a house
on your shoulders.
Hey, just stay right here
and look at me, okay?
I love you.
Carry me.
No. Baby? Baby?
Baby, you gotta... you gotta fight.
You gotta fight.
Hey, Anna, you gotta fight.
Honey, don't go.
Don't go.
Hey, you guys, you gotta help her.
You gotta help her.
Hey, guys, okay?
Anna, honey? Honey?
Why aren't you guys helping her?
- Do something!
- We can't.
Forget the DNR.
I know her, I know what she wants.
Okay? You're doctors.
You're doctors. Do your job!
- Kelly.
- She wouldn't give up.
- Kelly...
- She wouldn't...
Will you do something?
Time of death 9:21 a.m.
What?
- Anna...
- It's okay, Kelly.
It's okay.
Hey, guys, let's clear out.
- Give Severide some space.
- Absolutely.
Call us if...
It's everything from her bulletin board.
Her dad said she'd want you to have it.
You put it all back?
Yeah.
I don't want to
make your life any worse.
I'm almost done packing my stuff.
No. Look, I'm sorry.
I was a jerk.
Please don't move out.
Are you sure?
Things get tough, we stick together.
You give a hell of a speech.
You should think about
going into politics.
Yeah, I'll think about it.
I can't go back to 53.
Every time I think about
walking in there
and not seeing those guys...
If that makes me a quitter
in your eyes, then so be it,
but I can't face that house
without them in it.
What if there were a spot
for you at another house?
Specifically, here.
It might take a while to set up, but...
When I made it back,
I did it because
of the people in this house.
Jason, it's gotta come from you.
You gotta want it.
But I know if there's a way back
from where you are right now...
It's through this house.
What now?
Where are you going?
What the hell are you doing?
You can't stay here.
But you can take this with you anywhere.
That way...
you'll always carry him with you.
My girlfriend died.
I'm so sorry.
Will you help me pack?
Yes.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com