[Knocks on door] [Door opening]
Come on in.
What did I do now?
Nothin'.
You are acting lieutenant today.
O... kay.
It's my fault. Casey and
Dawson, they have this
charity thing over at Chicago Med.
I forgot to file the paperwork for him.
I've already got Rafferty
covering for Dawson.
You got it ***, Chief. I got to
get prepared. Mentally, I got...
- Right, got you covered.
- Thank you.
- Close the door.
- Yeah.
[Man over P.A.]
Please make sure you register at least
30 minutes before the race begins.
[Sighs] Really?
Goat shirts?
Those are collectors' items.
Yeah, garbage collectors.
You guys gonna run the 10k?
Uh, I am. Casey chickened out.
I'm more of a sprinter.
Heard you're gonna introduce
the commissioner later.
Yeah. Not sure how that fell on me.
Well, a ceiling fell on you
while you were saving a baby, baby.
[Clatter] I got it.
Hey. It's... it's Kim, right?
- Yeah. Hey.
- Hey, you... you need some help?
I... I kind of have no idea what I'm doing.
[Laughing]
She was part of the
team that got Diego back.
On it.
Firefighters bailing out
cops is a long tradition.
Oh, okay.
Well, when you need a police officer to...
- I've got nothing.
- [Laughs]
Who's this?
Oh, this is my niece Zoe.
- How old are you, Zoe?
- I'm nine.
Really? Let me see your driver's license.
- I'm nine too.
- Wow.
Well, uh, you're the designated driver
because she doesn't have her license.
- [Giggles]
- Imogene, don't bother them.
- They're setting up.
- Oh, no, it's totally fine.
Do you want to go see
them unload the animals
for the petting zoo?
Go ahead.
- Stay where I can see you.
- Okay.
Hey, you're the new pediatrician, right?
- Yeah, Holly Thelan.
- Hey.
Nice to meet you. I just
moved here from New York.
Well, welcome. Thanks for
volunteering on your day off.
Yeah, my pleasure. I'll see you guys.
Hey, I guess I'll go get
started with registration.
- Have a good race.
- I'll be rooting for you.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Over P.A.] Dr. Flores dial 123.
Oh, hey! Dr. Arata.
- Gabriela Dawson.
- Dawson.
- Yes?
- [Clears throat]
Do you happen to know where
the race registration is?
Race reg...
Uh, I'm sorry, Dawson.
I'm kind of busy saving lives.
Oh, be nice, Dr. Arata.
They're doing the race registration
over in "A" wing.
Great.
Thank you.
I'm gonna talk to Gabby. You got this?
- Yeah, no problem.
- Thanks.
[Girls laughing]
Wait for me!
Hey, I like the balloons.
[Explosion]
[Glass shattering]
[People screaming]
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
- [Sustained high-pitched tone]
- [Coughing]
[Sighs]
[People screaming]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[Coughs]
[Screaming]
Come on!
[All coughing, moaning]
Help! Help!
Somebody, over here!
Girls!
Girls, can you hear me?
- Are you hurt?
- My head.
My tummy hurts.
Hey. What's your name?
- Vaughn.
I need you to run around
to the other side of the hospital...
and check to see if ICU is intact...
- Hey! Hey!
- Oh, my God! Zoe!
Imogene got knocked in the head.
Zoe said her stomach hurts.
- This man just passed out.
- Im?
Im, talk to me, sweetheart.
You know where you are?
- I'm at the race.
- That's right, honey.
- Are you okay, baby?
- What happened?
I don't know. I don't know.
- Ow!
- Oh, my God.
[Coughing]
I think she might have a cracked rib.
Hey. E.R.'s gone.
We'll use that tent as triage.
- Okay, good.
- Okay.
Im, grab on to my sweater, okay?
Ow! It hurts.
Everyone, this tent will serve as triage!
Start moving people off the street
and out of the rubble!
Anyone that can help us, help us!
- Can you move?
- I think so.
[Both grunting]
[Siren wailing]
You got this, Herrmann. Lieutenant.
Every bit of training we've
had was for today, boys.
[Coughing]
[Chatter on emergency radio]
Raferty, grab everything off the ambulance.
Chief! Chief!
Big explosion, no idea of the cause.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Triage in that tent. E.R. took it hard.
All right, people are gonna be trapped
up on those higher floors.
Okay, you, Otis, and Mouch...
you get the aerial moving.
On it.
Exterior oxygen and fuel tanks
are on the other side of the building.
This couldn't have been an accident.
A bomb?
The structure's unstable.
Where's Dawson?
Oh, God. She went inside.
- Dawson's in there?
- I think so.
- We'll get her.
- Go!
Let's go.
Cruz, Mills, stay back!
You did bomb-tech
training with Squad, right?
- Yeah.
- Tell me what you think.
[Sighs] Car bombing.
It looks just like Oklahoma City.
- Exactly what I thought.
- Okay, so what do we know?
If there's one car bomb,
there's probably a second.
- We're on it.
- Yeah.
- Go!
- Let's go.
- You check the structure.
- Yeah.
Stay there!
[Groaning]
She... she said the pain's getting worse.
Imogene is my sister.
I think she has a concussion,
but she's responsive and alert.
Zoe.
- Kim, is this girl yours?
- No, I'm her aunt.
I've been trying to call my sister.
I can't get through.
She says she has stomach pain.
We got to take a look
in there somehow, now.
I'm gonna head in and see if
radiology is up and running.
All right, I'll go with you.
If there's more injured
inside, I want to help.
I'll work here.
You radio me as soon as you
know a C.T. scanner is up.
You got it.
Girls, be strong.
Im, take care of Zoe. I'll be back, okay?
Okay. [Zoe coughs]
Zoe, squeeze the pain
into me. I can take it.
[Indistinct chatter over radio]
Fire department, call out!
[Debris falling]
I got you.
- Got her?
- Here.
Got her.
Call out!
Gabby?
[Groans]
- Hey! Dr. Arata, right?
- Yeah.
Did Gabby Dawson come in
here? Did you seen her?
Dawson... I did.
I left her at the nurses' station.
- She on this floor?
- [Coughing]
Hey! Casey, there's a
ton of pockets in here.
We'll find her.
Hey!
If you can move at all, get
away from the exposed wall!
Move back towards the center!
Okay.
Gabby! Anyone! Call out!
Sir, you had a head injury
and you need a cat scan, okay?
[Debris falling]
[Gasps, groans]
[Sighs] Are you okay?
[Groans]
Yeah.
Yeah, it's... it's just a little scratch.
- If you need...
- No, I'm, uh...
I'm good. Just... let's keep going.
- Okay.
- [Groans]
Look for a rental car or a
van parked near the building.
It'll have a rental tag
in the front windshield
and one of those license plate borders.
[Radio beeps] Copy that, Chief.
Yeah.
Steve!
You hold your men back.
We believe it's a car bomb.
We're searching for a
possible second one nearby.
Ain't no reason to have
more men unnecessar...
Wallace, I'll be damned if you think
you're gonna keep us out of here.
Okay, we got sector one
and two, here and here.
You move your men to three and four.
We got triage going over in the tent.
I just got word from the
other side of the hospital.
They are undamaged.
Okay, let's go, men.
Don't look back tomorrow and
say you could've done more!
[Radio beeps] Cruz, talk to me.
- Nothing yet, Chief.
- Yo! Over here!
Rental car. There's a blanket in the back!
[Grunts] Nothing underneath.
[Sighs]
All clean. Let's keep moving.
[Breathing heavily] Yeah.
[Radio beeps] Rafferty.
[Radio beeps] Go for Rafferty.
Okay, we got a working cat
scan in the trauma wing.
On my way.
Let's see what's going on with Zoe.
I'm coming too.
No, sweetie, you should stay here.
She's my friend, and I'm coming.
Okay.
Guys, I need a lift.
Help!
Up here!
Don't move! We're coming!
Don't even breathe on those walls.
Roger that.
[Men speaking native language]
Hey! [Man groans]
Hey!
Seriously? What's your problem?
We need to get this man out of here.
- Here, take it.
- [Man groans]
Hey, listen!
A lot of people need to
get out of here, all right?
Casey, get back!
- Casey
- [Coughs]
[Grunts] I'm okay.
I'm okay. [Coughs]
- [Coughs]
- Hey, stand back.
No, you get back!
This is Alim Al Safir,
ambassador from Syria to the United States.
Ambassador Safir was here
in your city's protection.
- Capp!
- And if he's dead...
Capp, Tony, get this guy
to the to the "A" wing.
You got it.
[Grunts] Severide!
Yeah!
There's plenty of room under the debris,
the way it's fallen.
I'm going in. If Gabby's under there...
Casey, I don't know if that's safe.
You guys get stuck under there...
- we won't get stuck.
Casey.
Ready?
[Breathing heavily]
[Wincing]
- Dr. Thelan.
- Dr. Arata.
So, it's your tummy?
She says the pain's getting worse, fast.
Hmm. Let's see.
[Moaning]
- We're gonna take a look.
- Everybody clear out, please.
Uh...
I'll be right outside.
Come on, Imogene.
I want you to stay very still.
All right?
- Unh.
- It's okay.
- Leslie.
- Yeah?
- Dawson's missing.
- What?
Apparently she was near the blast.
- All right, I'm gonna go help.
- No, no, no, no, no.
The guys are doing
everything that they can.
We do our jobs, no matter what, right?
I guess you're right.
I'm coming with you.
Im, just stay here, okay?
Is Zoe gonna be okay?
She's has the best doctor
in the city with her.
I'll be back.
- [Building creaking]
- Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
Please hurry.
How you doing?
[Breathing heavily] I could be better.
Bad day at the hospital, huh?
- Please don't joke.
- Ah.
Anybody else here in the room with you?
No. Clearly.
- You'll be all right.
- [Crying]
[Creaking, crack] Please!
All right, listen, lady...
- You got to relax.
- It's "doctor."
My apologies, doctor.
But if you don't relax, I'm
gonna call you a lot worse.
[Aerial whirring]
[Crying]
- This is the way to go.
- All right, swing her out!
Swing her out. [Grunting]
Got her!
I checked everything in both lots,
and I got nothing.
[Breathing heavily]
Chief...
We found our second bomb.
Where?
Northwest parking lot,
close to the hospital.
Steve, when's that Bomb
Squad gonna get here?
Ten minutes.
I'm on my way.
[Debris falling]
Gabby!
Hello?
Hey!
Gabby! Anyone! Call out!
- Casey.
- Yeah.
If we don't find a space
big enough to turn around,
we're going to have to do this backwards.
I know.
Well, it might not be the
smartest course of action.
We're going to be smart about this now?
No.
Keep going.
- It hurts.
- I know, honey. I'm sorry.
- It hurts so bad.
- I'm sorry.
Can I speak to you for a moment?
Your niece has a crushed liver.
She's bleeding internally.
I need to operate before she bleeds out.
Oh, my God.
Do you have authority to give consent?
Consent? I don't know. I...
That's good enough for
me. We'll get her ready.
Make a hole!
Nurse, we'll take that gurney.
- Doctor!
- What?
- This man...
- He's in bad shape.
He's not in bad shape. He's dead.
Cruz, grab me your center punch.
[Horn blares]
Cruz, Mills...
I'm gonna ask you to leave the area.
- Forget it.
- Not a chance.
[Timer ticking]
It's on a timer.
[Grunts]
Can't see what it's set for though.
Yeah, this is amateur
hour... bomb making 101.
Which means?
Which means that it could
go off at any moment.
So...
Can you?
Yeah.
Careful, Mills.
Hey, Tone!
Where's Severide and Casey?
Down there somewhere.
All right, let's spread
out. Let's go, guys.
Dig 'em out.
[Grunting]
I see someone!
Call out if you can hear me!
[Grunts]
- It's not her!
- What?
- She's dead.
It's not Dawson!
Oh, thank the sweet lord.
For anyone who's not tagged...
It looks like all these
people have been seen.
Not here. Down there.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Okay, it's 8:29.
If this thing is set to go at 8:30pm...
Chief!
Respectfully, shut up.
[Breathing heavily]
Cover your ears.
Are you serious?
[Breathing heavily]
[Sighs]
Amateur hour.
God bless that Rescue Squad training!
Oh!
Come on! Come on!
Here we go, Chief.
- [Heart monitor beeping]
- Marker.
Have suction ready. This
isn't gonna be pretty.
Retractor.
Bowel retractor.
[Grunts]
The liver looks even worse
than it did on the cat scan.
I can't find the bleed.
Uh, give me a clamp for a pringle maneuver.
[Sighs] Uh, she's stable for now...
But, uh, she's getting worse.
There's nothing left of the liver.
I can't stop the bleeding.
What... what does that
mean? You can fix her, right?
You can transplant a liver, but you...
you can't fix the damage in one...
I'll donate right now.
You have the same blood type?
I'm, um... I'm "A" positive.
No, your niece is "O" positive.
It wouldn't work.
But I've tried... I've
tried calling my sister,
and I have tried calling my parents,
and no one's picking up.
She's only nine years old!
You know what?
Uh, stay here.
Gabby! Anyone! Call out!
[Debris falls]
[Groans]
[Coughs]
Gabby!
- Gabby!
- [Gasps]
Call out!
[Groans]
[Softly] Help.
Help.
[Groans]
[Grunting]
Come on, come, come.
[Grunts]
[Distant metal clanging]
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
I hear something.
Keep going!
The space up ahead is too small.
You can do it. I'm right behind you.
[Coughs]
[Radio beeps] Hey, Herrmann?
Can you hear the banging?
Hey! Quiet everyone!
Kill that torch!
[Indistinct chatter over radio]
[Faint metal banging]
[Radio beeps]
Is that you, Severide?
[Radio beeps] No.
[Banging continues]
That's from over there!
[Indistinct chatter]
We need a medic out here.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Take a rest. I'm gonna go back out front.
I promise I'll radio
with anything they find.
Okay.
[Winces]
[Breathing heavily]
I'm gonna head up to check on Zoe.
All right. I'll, uh... I'll come with you.
[Clears throat]
Hey, trouper.
You were gone a long time.
Yeah, we were just trying
to help who we could.
- She's hurt, isn't she?
- Worse than we thought.
She is... very.
Good thoughts, you know?
If that's all you can
give, give good thoughts.
Yeah. Good thoughts.
Yeah.
- [Gagging, coughing]
- Imogene! Imogene!
- Hey! We need help over here!
- I need a line.
Get a line in her...
2.5 Diazepam I.V., push.
- What is it?
- Seizure.
We need that broken arm out of two!
She was fine. She was talking.
- She was near the explosion?
- Yes.
It looked like a concussion.
Pupil's blown, got to be
an epidural hematoma...
blood swelling the brain.
Get her a C.T. and an open
operating room immediately!
I'll do this.
- [Speaking native language]
- Out of the way.
[Mutters]
"O" positive. Yes!
[Speaking native language]
[Groans]
[Grunting]
Gabby!
Gabby.
You came.
How bad?
It's just my head, but I think I'm okay.
You okay?
Damn, Dawson. You look like hell.
[Laughter]
I'm not 100% sure I'm not dreaming.
- For real.
- [Laughing]
Hey, guys, Casey and I have Dawson.
She's alive.
[Cheers and applause]
We're not out of the woods yet, boys!
Let's get this concrete off of them!
I got your message. How is she?
[Sobbing]
You got to believe, okay?
You just got to believe.
Greta!
It's "O" positive.
- That's good, right?
- We'll start prepping.
It's a chance.
It's an adult liver, but
we just use the left lobe.
[Overlapping chatter]
I see 'em!
Everyone careful now!
All right.
No.
Something must have happened
to it in the explosion.
It's warm. [Slams table]
[Sighs]
The, uh, liver
seemed to be damaged,
maybe in the explosion.
I can't use it.
I'm sorry.
[Crying]
Drop the basket.
Ready to get out of here?
Yeah.
I love you.
Lift her up!
[Cheers and applause]
- Welcome back!
- All right!
Yeah! Hey!
- Good to see you.
- Hey, mama.
[Grunting] [Cheers and applause]
Hey, Lieutenant!
Ladies first. [Laughter]
Hey, boys.
- Terrorism?
- Possibly.
The ambassador to Syria
was checked into Chicago Med
for a liver transplant, Alim Al Safir.
That's his security detail over there.
[Speaking native language]
Hey, friends.
I'm aware of your sidearms.
I have one of my own.
We're diplomatic protection
within our legal right
to bear arms in this country.
Not today.
I'm gonna take your weapons from you.
This isn't a question.
If you do anything that makes me
the least bit uncomfortable,
I will end you.
Do you understand?
We're diplomatic protection
from the Syrian Arab Republic.
We will cooperate any way we can.
We're gonna want first
crack at questioning.
- I'll wait my turn.
- Just know it's coming.
[Heart monitor beeping]
[Instrument whirs]
[Sighs] Come on.
Come on.
- Pupil's unresponsive.
- [Sighs]
Come on, girl. Give me something.
[Siren wailing]
Hey, Chief, commissioner's here.
Wallace?
Fire commissioner.
Deputy District Chief just
brought me up to speed.
Dark day, sir.
That, it is.
Listen, I am informed that you
and your men from Firehouse 51
were first on scene and
saved dozens of lives today.
Yeah. Plus one of our own.
Well...
You can fall back, let
some relief do some digging.
We think we'll stay.
[Overlapping chatter]
[Over radio] Shay, we got Dawson.
She's okay.
Shay?
Hey! We need a doctor over here.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN