It's the new drug called "gray."
Two people OD'd on it last week.
You know who's moving it?
No. Still working on it.
Sienna, I need something real
or I have to file that
coke possession charge.
I keep telling you it wasn't mine.
- This guy paid me to...
- Yeah, I believe you.
Which is why I gave you
a month to work it off.
So far, nothing.
Now you only have three days left.
Wait, wait, wait,
I've got something else.
My friend, Isabel... she works
at the club with me sometimes.
Anyway, she has this new boyfriend.
He hits her.
That's horrible, but we
don't do domestic abuse cases.
Um, how about murder?
What?
She said her boyfriend killed someone.
An old girlfriend, he beat her to death.
That's why I'm so scared for Isabel.
Did Isabel say anything else... a name?
She just said her boyfriend
dumped the body near a factory.
- Wyatt, I think.
- Who's the boyfriend?
She calls him D.
I didn't push for details.
Look, I've got enough drama of my own.
When's the last time you
talked to Isabel?
Three weeks ago.
I've been texting her,
but she's not answering.
And I don't know where she lives.
You're using again, I can see it.
- No, that's not true, I swear.
- You have three days
to find me something real
or I file those charges.
- She have anything good?
- No.
I mean, some B.S.
about her friend's boyfriend
killing someone, dumping the
body behind the Wyatt factory.
She's just trying to buy more time
because her month's almost up.
She looked pretty upset.
- Yeah, she's a good actor.
- Maybe.
It might still be worth
calling in though.
No.
Does that mean you're not going
to give her any more time?
Well, you're not
supposed to extend deals
according to the book, so.
This is my first C.I.
Yeah, the book's not always right.
Sometimes you got to trust your gut.
So Woods bought the money gag.
Thinks I'm on his side again.
- All right, good.
- Okay, so what's next?
When do we take him down?
We find his biggest weakness.
Booze, women, gambling.
I've already found it, boss. It's you.
Thanks, Adam.
Yeah.
Still not convinced?
No, I believe him.
Doesn't mean I forgive him.
Sarge, you got a minute?
Um...
I just wanted to apologize
for what happened with Camilla.
I put the team in a bad situation.
A really bad situation,
and it won't happen again.
You have my word.
Well, you're on desk duty
until further notice,
and you've got an appointment
with the psychologist at 1:00.
- Hey.
- Bless your heart.
Double shot latte, three sugars.
Have I told you
you're my favorite member
of Intelligence?
Never.
- Hey.
- You.
- Thanks.
Hey, so did you
make a decision on Sienna?
Yeah. She doesn't deliver,
I'm going to file the charges.
I gave her a chance and she blew it.
Ooh, nice to see you toughen up.
Don't let anyone take advantage.
Detective Upton.
Yeah, I'll be there in 10 minutes.
- We got to go.
- What? Where?
- Homicide.
- Okay.
Looks like she was beaten to death.
It's pretty gruesome.
Yeah. Hey, thanks for following up.
- Nice work.
- It cost me 50 bucks.
How's that?
Gave Winters over here tentoone odds
your snitch was talking crap.
Her snitch.
Hey, can you do me a favor
and make the appropriate notifications?
- Yeah.
- Thanks, guys.
Like I said, it was just a hunch.
Sienna's story was
a little too weird to be fake.
- I'm sorry if I overstepped.
- You did.
Well, at least now you know
Sienna isn't playing you, right?
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com.
She's a Jane Doe.
We ran her prints;
They're not in the system.
And my CI doesn't know her name either,
but her friend's name is Isabel Perez.
And she's dating the same guy
that looks good for this murder.
What do we know about her?
- Isabel?
- Yeah.
Latina, 21, used to work
on and off at a strip club
on the west side.
A place called Alibi.
Okay, so we think her
boyfriend killed the Jane Doe?
Yeah, yeah, and maybe Isabel too.
Because she's been missing three weeks,
I tried tracking her phone. It's dead.
All right, well,
talk to your C.I. again.
See what you can find out.
Meanwhile, let's dig into this Jane Doe.
What's her name? What's her story?
Let me know if you want me to jump in.
No, we're good.
Your appointment's in ten minutes.
If I were you, I'd be on time.
I'm Dr. Rebecca Sloan.
Have you ever been in therapy before?
Um, I talked to someone
a while back, yeah.
- After a shooting.
- Right, it's mandatory.
So, so you ask me
questions, and I talk, right?
This is your time.
If you have something
you want to talk about,
I'll listen.
And if I don't?
C.O.D. was blunt force trauma.
She was beaten repeatedly
with a long object,
like a pipe or a tire iron.
You can tell by the parallel tracks.
When'd she die?
Based on decomp, about a month ago.
Find any evidence on her body?
I'm running semen samples now.
- Sexual assault?
- Hard to say.
No tearing of tissues.
Any offensive or defensive wounds?
No, doesn't look like
there was much of a struggle.
Probably knew her killer.
That syncs up with the C.I. story,
boyfriend killed girlfriend.
There's one other thing
worth pointing out.
She's had lots of cosmetic procedures.
Injections into
the breasts, buttocks, lips.
All right, we'll get a list
of nearby plastic surgeons.
Probably a waste of time.
It appears she was injected
with motor oil.
So this guy Isabel is with
really killed somebody?
- Damn.
- Looks that way.
We found the body
behind the Wyatt factory,
just like Isabel said.
I'm glad I told you about it.
I wasn't sure, you know, Izzy,
she says a lot of wacky things.
But this was crazy, even for her.
I can't have no felony on my record.
I'll never get a good job
at a restaurant.
I'm training to be a chef.
That's great. So just stay focused.
Do what I need you to do,
and you'll be fine.
Let's start at the beginning, okay?
Where was Isabel living
before she met D?
A shelter. Like a charity thing.
You know, beds, counselors, food.
Izzy was always trying
to get her life right.
She just never could.
What's it called?
No, she doesn't look familiar.
But we talk to over
a hundred women a month.
Many of them are timid,
or so scared they won't even
tell us their real names.
But we let them in nonetheless.
What's this about?
She was reported missing.
Can we look through some of your files?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, I can help with that.
Great. Thanks, Juan.
Okay, you're right.
Isabel Perez, here she is.
Turns out she's been here several times.
Well, when was
the last time she was here?
Two months ago.
All right, Amanda was her counselor.
Amanda.
The police are asking about
someone named Isabel Perez.
Why, did something happen to her?
We're not sure.
We just want to ask a few questions.
Sure. Truth is, I'm glad you're here.
I've been worried about her.
I've been calling and texting her...
When was the last time
you heard from her?
About three weeks ago.
Did she say anything unusual?
Did she seem sad, happy, upset?
More like excited.
She was on her way
to get cosmetic surgery.
An injection in her buttocks, I think.
Made me sad. She's so young and pretty,
but her boyfriend
really wanted her to do it
and she wants to make him happy.
Did Isabel tell you
the name of her boyfriend?
What about the doctor, or the clinic?
No, sorry.
Okay, well, if you hear from her,
you call me.
Absolutely, and please call
if you have any other questions.
Yeah, thanks.
Good to see you, Raul. What's up?
Maria made cheese tamales.
Come on, don't tell me
they're against the rules.
- I know you love them.
- I do, thank you.
I wish I had something
to tell you, herma,
but business has been soft.
Haven't installed a drug
compartment in two months.
I came to talk to you
about something else.
There was a murder.
Young woman, twenties.
A murder?
Hell no, that's not for me.
Listen, I tell you
about hidden compartments
in narco's cars. That's our deal.
All right, I didn't come to
talk to you about the murder.
I just wanted to know if you
know of any offthebooks
medical clinics in Pilsen.
Somewhere that women go to get
plastic surgery, injections.
It's your hood, I figured
you might know something.
Yeah, that's easy. Let me ask around.
Okay, great. Thank you.
- All right.
- Thank Maria for the tamales.
I will.
We got good news.
We got a positive ID on the Jane Doe.
She goes by the name of Sylvia Castro.
We stopped by the strip club
that Isabel used to work at.
It turns out Sylvia worked there too.
Boss ID'd the crime scene photo,
but he did not know anything
about a boyfriend.
Okay, what else do we know?
We know she's 19,
originally from Cleveland,
and she's been missing from
work for about three months.
All right, track down the family
and let them know what happened.
All right, talk to Sylvia's
friends, coworkers, roommates.
Someone's got to know
who this boyfriend was.
Are you sure this is it?
It's the address Raul gave me.
Doesn't look like a medical clinic.
I think that's the point.
Chicago PD!
- Time to go, ma'am.
- Give me that.
Don't come back.
This isn't a real doctor.
No, no, I never said
I was a real doctor.
I don't operate,
I don't do surgery, I just...
You just inject women with motor oil.
We're trying to find
one of your patients.
Recognize her?
Yeah. Isabella, I think
her last name is Perez.
Okay, what about her boyfriend?
Do you know his name?
No.
What about her, you recognize her?
She was one of your patients.
Her name was Sylvia Castro,
same boyfriend as Isabel.
We want a name now.
And given what's going on here,
you're going to want to cooperate.
Because you're going to need
all the help you can get.
Hey, Sarge, just talked
to our DOA's sister.
Right before she met
this mystery boyfriend,
she was living in a shelter
called Jenny's Haven.
Wait.
- Did you say Jenny's Haven?
- Yeah.
That's the same place Isabel stayed at.
That's now two things
Isabel and our DOA have in common.
They both got plastic surgery
at the same underground clinic.
Paid for by the same guy, Damien Soto.
Yeah, I got him right here. Two priors.
One for assault and battery,
one for pandering.
So he's a pimp.
We got a photo of this prick?
All right, give me one sec.
That's Juan. From Jenny's Haven.
You're telling me this guy
works at the shelter?
No, he's the founder.
That's a fox guarding the henhouse.
All right, grab this son of a bitch now.
Chicago PD!
Upton.
Go forward.
- Clear!
- I got the kitchen.
Clear.
Three empty beds.
- Well, they left in a hurry.
- Yeah, who tipped them off?
Looks like Isabel wasn't his only girl.
You mean prisoner. He's locking them up.
5021 Eddie, roll the crime lab
to 540 Water Street.
We need a scene processed for prints.
Copy that, 5021 Eddie.
Burgess.
I'll be there in 15.
Hey, guys, we're going to break off.
Yeah, copy that.
So your friend saw Isabel
on Racine Avenue last night?
Yeah, around midnight.
- She was with some guy.
- Doing what?
Don't know, but I'm guessing
looking for dope.
She's got to have it, and
I've been trying to help her,
- but...
- Well, at least you know
she's still alive.
- That's something, right?
- Right.
Now we just need to get her
away from that awful boyfriend.
You mean pimp.
His name is Damien Soto.
He's got six other girls, too.
Makes me sick.
You said Isabel has a drug habit.
That means she'll be looking
to score sometime soon.
So why don't you ask around,
see who's selling to her.
We'll track her down that way.
Walk around Pilsen
talking to heroin dealers?
Nah, I'm clean.
I don't like hanging out in that area.
Yeah, that's dangerous, no doubt.
Sienna, we had a deal.
I said if you help find the killer,
I wouldn't file charges.
So far, you haven't done much helping.
Wow. That's pretty hardcore.
Don't blow it.
You're taking cooking classes.
You're working hard to be a chef.
Real hard. And I'm good, too.
It doesn't matter.
If you don't cooperate,
the only place you'll
be cooking is Stateville.
Okay, okay, I'll give it a shot.
That's a good choice.
Here's 500, grease the dealers.
Tell them there's more cash
if they deliver a lead.
Look, I'm not going to tell
you how to do your job,
but that was pretty hardcore.
She's a C.I., Haley.
That's what she signed up for.
So I figured I'd check out
the Latino papers,
see if this pimp was advertising.
Look what I found.
That is definitely Isabel.
So call them, we'll go grab her up.
I already did.
The phone's been disconnected.
The website's down too.
He's smart.
Staying under the radar
until the heat dies down.
I talked to three current residents
and seven past residents
of Jenny's Haven.
One of the girls was 16.
Damien buys her jewelry,
takes her out to dinner.
What he does is
he treats them like gold,
then turns them out
to the highest bidder.
Yeah, and if they get out of line,
he just beats them to death
with a tire iron.
The crime lab
pulled eight sets of prints
from Damien's house,
but the only match is to Damien.
And we also managed
to pick up Damien's vehicle information.
All right, put out a BOLO right away.
In the meantime, hit the streets.
Get his picture out there.
Damien Soto? Never heard of him.
We think he runs a small
operation somewhere in Pilsen.
I don't pay much attention
to the mom and pops.
This guy isn't exactly warm and fuzzy.
He killed one of his girls
with a tire iron.
I wish I could help, Hank.
But I don't run in that crowd.
You know that.
My girls are highend, educated.
They do what they do
because they want to.
Patricia, I'm not here to judge.
I'm just trying to get some help.
I know, sorry.
So let me ask.
Okay, a guy like that.
You know, a pimp on the lam
afraid to work his girls.
How does he make his money?
Well, he can't pimp them,
he'll sell them.
It's coldblooded,
but that's how these guys roll.
Thanks.
And by the way.
How do you like Nicole?
She's nice.
She says you two just talk.
Like it's a therapy session
or something.
Please tell me you got a lead.
Well, we've been going through
all the surveillance footage we can,
but we're still coming up empty, so.
- Any luck with Damien's phone?
- No, sir.
And no hit on the car, either.
Right, well, he has got to
come up for air at some point,
- so stay on it.
- You got it, boss.
I've got patrol canvassing
the neighborhood 24/7.
All right, thanks.
You get word from your C.I.?
Yeah, I talked to her a few hours ago.
She found a dealer
who sold Isabel heroin two days ago.
Said he'd text her again when
Isabel was looking to score.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
Burgess.
What?
When?
Okay, thanks.
Are you okay?
It's just down here.
Shot twice in the chest.
Found your number in her cell
on the recently called list.
- Her name is...
- Sienna.
I know, she's my informant.
Patrol has found Sienna's
phone at the scene.
She had a text message from
the drug dealer last night
at 10:12, saying he was
meeting up with Isabel
in the park,
same place we found the body.
Could be a robbery?
No, she had her wallet in her pocket.
She had some cash in there, too.
It was a setup.
The dealer texted Damien,
Damien killed her.
He didn't want anyone getting
in the way of his business.
Okay, what do we know about this dealer?
Eduardo Varela.
Two priors, heroin distribution.
We have his address, too.
134 Hoover Road.
So pay Eduardo a visit.
And squeeze him. I want answers.
Yeah.
- Hey, you all right?
- Yeah.
Listen, I'm sorry about Sienna, but...
You know, that's not on you.
I think I pushed too hard.
No, that's how it goes.
You were doing your job, okay?
You're either playing
or you're getting played.
Okay, let's go talk
to this heroin dealer.
All right?
Chicago PD!
- Hey, you Eduardo Varela?
- What's going on?
Move your punk ass out the way!
You have no right talking
to me like that.
Hey, don't talk to me like that, Eddie,
'cause I'm not in the mood.
Turn around, get your hands up.
Hands up!
- Hey, hey, hey.
- We're good.
All right, sit down.
- Hey.
- Have a seat.
Where's Damien Soto?
Don't know nobody with that name.
Dude, we don't got time for that.
We know you just got off
the phone with him
right after you met with Sienna.
And then you sent her a text,
and now she's dead.
Somebody's got to answer
for that, Eddie.
Look what we found.
Heroin? I'm not surprised.
You have two choices, Eduardo.
One, we bust you for heroin possession
and conspiracy to commit murder.
Or two, you help us find Isabel Perez.
Or Damien Soto's bitch ass.
It's up to you.
Okay, okay. I know who he is.
And I know Izzy, but I didn't
help get no one killed.
That's not what I'm about.
Right, because you teach Sunday school.
Damien told me to send that text
so Isabel could talk to her friend.
Tell us where Damien Soto is.
I don't know.
But I do know that Izzy's
coming over in a few hours
to score some product.
All right, that wasn't
that hard, was it, Eddie?
Now, you're going to pretend
like everything's normal
and let us do our job.
Okay. What happens after that?
You work for me as
an informant or you go to jail.
Antonio, man... now I know why
he's got so many C.I.'s.
He sees the opportunity,
he just makes the ask.
Right? I mean, we were all there.
I feel like Eduardo should be
a group C.I. or something.
I mean, I don't understand
how Antonio gets dibs.
Because he asked.
Hey, look out.
The target has just arrived.
It's an unknown driver.
We can't really tell.
We'll take Isabel, you take the driver.
Copy that.
Um, I only have $40 bucks. But I...
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey, hey, it's okay, it's
okay, you're not in trouble.
We're here to help.
Get out the vehicle.
Put your hands where I can see them.
Turn off the car. Turn off the car now!
Hey! Do not move. Do not move.
- Damn!
- Son of a bitch!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Hey, listen.
Hey.
Look, just to be clear...
We don't want to press
charges against you, okay?
Where are you living right now?
In a house.
But I don't know where it is.
I don't pay attention.
Your boyfriend. This is Damien?
We need to talk to him.
How come?
We think he killed a young
woman named Sylvia Castro.
And your friend, Sienna.
What?
Yeah.
SSienna's dead?
Died last night.
Damien shot her in the chest twice.
She was trying to find you.
She was trying to help you.
Last night, did Damien
have blood on his clothes?
Hands? Shoes?
Isabel, the other girls
you live with are in danger.
They need your help.
Sorry, I don't remember anything.
Give us a minute. Come on, Kim.
We're not going to get
anything out of her tonight.
I think we should just give her
something for her withdrawal,
put her up in one of our safe houses,
let her get some rest.
We'll take another run at her tomorrow.
Okay.
Still haven't found
the driver or the car.
I'm sorry, boss.
He showed up earlier than we thought.
Upton and Olinsky hadn't arrived yet,
but we put the plates out
over the radio.
Just waiting on a hit.
Well, your night isn't over.
I want you to go with Kim,
help get Isabel squared away.
Copy that.
All right, no one knows you're here.
Don't open the door unless
you look through the peephole
and you see a badge, all right?
I brought you a change of clothes.
You'll feel better after a shower.
And, um, if you need anything,
you use this phone to call us.
Okay. Thank you.
Yeah.
So, um, will there be any police around?
Yeah, there will be
a patrol car out front.
Do you feel all right
in here by yourself?
Yeah, I'm fine.
- II feel safe.
- Good. You are.
All right, you're all set.
Listen, before we go,
I've got to ask you again.
Where's Damien? Where's he staying?
Adam, would you just stop?
Would you stop?
Stop. She's not ready.
You're okay. Get some rest, okay?
Why is she protecting
that son of a bitch?
I don't get it.
Because she's in love with him.
In love with him?
- Yeah.
- That's not love.
That's Stockholm Syndrome.
Try telling her it's not love.
Sometimes people...
They trick themselves
into believing
what they want to believe,
because it feels better
than the alternative.
Well, sometimes it's real.
And there's no tricks or delusions.
It's just good.
It might be complicated,
but it's honest.
Come on.
I don't know if leaving the phone
was a really good idea, Kim.
I just, I don't know if
she's going to take the bait.
Whether she loves him or not,
she's terrified of the guy.
Hold on, she's making a call.
- Damien, it's me.
- Where are you, baby?
I've been so worried about you.
The police have me in a safe house.
- Are they there?
- Um...
No, they left.
Okay, I'll come get you.
But just in case,
meet me a few blocks away.
Okay, meet me in the alley
between Irving and 15th.
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
- I love you, D.
- I love you too, baby.
Isabel just made contact
with Damien Soto.
We have the number she dialed.
I'm calling it in now.
I need someone to ping it, ASAP.
Well, like I said, it was a good idea.
That's a male Hispanic,
approaching from the east.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Hey, you good?
Yeah.
Chicago PD!
You set me up, you lying whore!
No, no, don't shoot.
- Drop your weapon!
- I didn't tell them!
Drop your weapon!
- Nice shot.
- No, no!
I didn't know they were here.
I swear I didn't set you up.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
Why did you shoot him?
- Please don't die, I love you.
- 1521, Frank emergency.
Shots fired by the police.
Offender down.
- Stop hurting him, please...
- You're okay, just breathe.
4200 West Irving, we're in the alley.
Why would you do that?
Copy that.
- Just breathe.
- No.
Damien took two to the shoulder.
Yeah, he's in surgery right now.
He's going to live.
All right, where's Isabel?
Antonio took her to a clinic.
She's in bad shape.
Between the withdrawals
and seeing Damien get shot,
she's a mess.
Okay, well, what about the phone call?
We got a location?
Yeah, pinged off a cell tower
on the south side,
near a bar named Vinnie's.
The waitress there confirmed
he was there from 10 to 11.
I dumped his phone, but I got nothing.
Checked his car too,
no navigation system.
So we still have no idea
where this bastard's living?
Well, Pilsen isn't that big, guys.
I want boots on the ground.
Circulate photos of Damien and Isabel.
I mean, you've got C.I.'s in
the area, get on the phone.
Call in a favor.
We need to find these girls, soon.
Hey, how you doing? How's therapy?
Not really my thing.
All right, well, if you're
not going to take it seriously
or even attempt to take it
seriously, let me know.
For real, because I need to
find a new partner.
This guy, he owns a lot of houses.
Rents them out to pimps, dealers.
He gets a cut of the action.
- You got this guy's name?
- I know of him.
There's six girls out there.
In trouble, locked up.
You'd be doing a good thing.
I ain't in this to be no hero.
I'm just saying,
this isn't our typical deal.
All right, look,
I can get the guy's name.
Problem is, my connect is a Latin Cobra.
- So if you hit the house...
- You could get burnt.
Or get dead.
So you're saying Raul has a lead,
but you told him not to chase it?
Okay, think about it.
Raul asks his Latin Cobra
connect for the address.
And then we hit
the house five minutes later.
It doesn't take a lot of math
to figure out who our source is.
So it's okay for my C.I.
to take on a risk,
but not yours.
That's what you're saying?
Kim, he has a wife and two kids.
Not to mention I've known him
for over five years,
and he's given me over 20 cases.
And let's be clear.
It was your choice
to push Sienna, not mine.
I know, because there's
six girls out there,
probably locked in some basement.
And I'm not just going
to sit here and let them die.
I want to find them as badly as you do,
and I will do everything in
my power to make that happen.
Yeah, everything but ask your informant.
Raul's job, an informant's job,
is to provide information.
He is an asset of
the Chicago Police Department.
No, he is a person.
And he is a friend.
Damien, hey. Wake up, Chicago PD.
I'm Sergeant Voight,
this is Detective Olinsky.
We need to ask you some questions.
Laywer.
Hey, look at me.
Trust me when I tell you,
this will go a lot easier
if you cooperate.
So where are you keeping the girls?
- You think I'm stupid?
- Well, we already have Isabel.
She loves me.
More than you can possibly imagine.
The second you get discharged from here,
you're going to jail.
And those girls, they're going
to find a new pimp.
When they do,
they will give you up
for a slice of pizza.
Well, good thing they're locked up.
And one of them has diabetes, too.
Needs insulin.
Yeah, well, they die,
that just goes on your tab too.
So do yourself a favor,
and tell us where they are
while you still have
a chance to make a deal.
All right, I'll tell
you where they are...
When you offer me total immunity.
Until then,
you can kiss my Colombian ass.
Kiss his Colombian ass.
A guy I know,
he had a real bad accident.
A motorcycle accident. It was years ago.
I mean, he was in a lot of pain.
He ended up dying in the hospital.
But it wasn't from his injuries.
You know what ended up getting him?
A morphine overdose.
You know, they just figured somebody
punched in the wrong numbers.
Happens all the time.
If... if... if I die, so do the girls.
No, we'll just find them
a different way.
- You're bluffing.
- Am I?
Last chance, Damien.
Like I said, kiss my ass.
You see this face?
You get a good look at it.
It's the last thing
you're ever going to see.
Mr. Soto?
- Hank.
- Excuse me.
Hey, doc.
He's all yours.
Son of a bitch could care less
if these girls live or die.
They're not girls to him.
They're assets.
A guy like that,
he doesn't let a money maker
die for no reason.
Hey, excuse me.
Damien Soto, is he one of your patients?
Yes, why?
I need you to do me a favor.
I want you to leave
a cell phone in Damien's room.
Just pretend you forgot it.
- Hello?
- It's me, Damien.
Look, man, I'm in a situation,
like for real.
I need some cash.
So, what are you looking to do?
- Sell some product.
- How many you got?
Seven.
The other voice belongs to Cesar Ramos.
He's another pimp working out of Pilsen.
Track him down. And follow him.
Ramos just stopped at
the possible target location.
Get ready to move.
Let's go.
Cesar Ramos, Chicago PD. Turn around.
Drop the bolt cutters. Drop them.
Hands in the air, come down the stairs.
That's it, come on.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Chicago PD!
- Let me see your hands.
- It's okay, ladies.
As long as we can see
your hands, you're all good.
It's okay, we're the police.
We're here to help.
Hold on, hold on, okay. Okay, go.
I got the kitchen.
- Is she okay?
- Upstairs!
- You're good.
- Okay, you're good. Clear!
Clear!
Burgess.
- Anything?
- She didn't make it.
Man.
She must be the diabetic.
I'll go check on the others.
We found the other girls.
One of them was dead.
Because your friend Damien
wouldn't tell us where they were.
We need your help to convict him.
Lydia.
You know Lydia.
She's diabetic, needed insulin.
But Damien didn't care
if she lived or died.
He doesn't care
if any of you live or die.
That's not true.
You know what, actually she's right.
You are right, he did care.
He cared a lot.
He wanted you all to live
because he wanted to sell you.
We recorded a call he made today.
It's me, Damien.
Look, man, I'm in a situation,
like for real.
- I need some cash, so.
- What are you looking to do?
- Sell some product.
- How many you got?
Seven.
- How much?
- 90K, for all of them.
I can keep playing the tape if you want,
but it's not pretty.
Tell us what you know, Isabel.
He doesn't love you, Isabel.
He pretends he does
so he can control you.
Look, I know you want to
believe in your relationship.
You want to hold out hope.
We all do that.
But I know that somewhere deep down,
you know that that is a lie.
I know because I've been there.
I was in love with someone once,
and they didn't really love me.
And I kept pretending, and I kept...
Hoping.
And then eventually I just said enough.
God, no more.
And it hurt so much.
But you know what?
Eventually, I felt better.
Until one day, I felt whole again.
And now the only thing that I regret
is not doing that sooner.
It's time for you to say enough.
I know where Damien hid the tire iron
that he used to kill Sylvia.
You're good.
It's okay. It's good.
Nice job, Kim. You were amazing.
We have enough
to charge Damien with murder,
so not a bad result,
all things considered.
I'm not so sure about that.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Look, I don't... I don't
regret protecting my C.I.
Not for a second.
But that girl dying, Lydia?
I've got to live with that
for the rest of my life.
It's hard to figure out
what we're supposed to do.
Get the bad guys, save
the victims, protect our C.Is.
I mean, if I didn't push Sienna,
maybe we'd never find
Damien and the girls.
But Sienna would still be alive.
It's a hard needle to thread sometimes.
More like impossible.
You just got to trust your instincts.
Right. Go with your gut, not the book.
- That's right.
- Sweet.
Hey, do you want to grab some dinner
or something this weekend?
Yeah, that sounds good.
Okay, cool.
Cool.
Thanks for seeing me so last minute.
Seems like you're ready to talk.
Yeah, I am.
So that story you told Isabel...
- That wasn't you.
- Good.
- I'm serious.
- Okay.
Yeah, I believe you.
But just in case you're lying,
- I would like you to know that...
- Adam, Adam, I was just trying
to get a witness to flip,
simple as that.
There's no need to go backwards, okay?
I'm just... I'm not in the mood.
Yeah, well, if you want,
we could head back to my place.
Talk about going backwards.
Maybe we can move things forward.
No, we won't.
Why not? Why not give it a shot?
Because...
I don't know, we work together.
We're in totally different places.
Okay.
Having said that...
I feel like having a little fun tonight.
Let's get out of here.
Okay.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com