- How you feeling?
- Scared.
Donna has a high risk
of life-threatening hemorrhage
in the third trimester.
Our baby is gonna be okay.
[device beeping]
Come on, Jason.
I tried everything to save
your boy,
and I wish
that I could have saved him.
- You're dead.
- Lullo is the real deal.
You got to stay on your toes
for a while.
It's a lot of pressure
working together.
It's not the work part
that's tough.
It's the home part.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Peter Mills.
Yeah.
Look, I just wanted to come
down here to say
that I regret my behavior
the other day.
And I've got nothing
but respect for you
and what everyone does here.
I was upset.
I know
you tried to save my son.
Look, Mr. Lullo, you should
know that...
in the back of that ambulance,
your son was talking about you,
how important family was.
He said that you were the best
and he loved you.
It struck a chord with me.
My father died
when I was young,
and I know that I felt
the same way about him.
Thank you.
Hey, Lieutenant.
Look, I just want you to know,
I'm not trying to insert myself
in yours and Gabby's business.
Noted, Mills.
Matt, listen, um...
I need to apologize.
So...
I apologize.
And you know I got
this bad habit
of letting words fall out
willy-nilly,
and I don't... I don't really
remember what I even said.
Hey, uh, sorry.
Chief wants a word with us.
Bunch of static.
[knock at door]
Hey, come on in.
Hey, I just want to let both
of you know
that Donna is in the red zone,
as far as the baby's arrival.
Hey.
That's great, Chief.
Congrats.
You guys have a name
for him yet?
We are keeping that
under wraps.
- Of course.
- [Wallace chuckles]
Just in case I got to get
out of here in a hurry,
I may not be able to bring
a relief fire chief
over here fast enough.
No problem.
We got you covered.
- Thank you.
- You ready to be a dad?
Nope, not at all.
[all laugh]
- You tell your father yet?
- Yeah.
He cried so hard, I nearly sent
the Orlando Fire Department
over to check on him.
[alarm blares, buzzes]
He's happy.
[over P.A.] Truck 81,
squad 3, ambulance...
- See you, dad.
- Get out of here!
- [Matthew and Kelly laugh]
- Come on! What's wrong with you?
[siren blaring]
[horn blaring]
That's the Carlisle home,
and they haven't come out!
Any children?
We'll take the bottom floor!
Otis!
[window shatters]
Watch out!
Help!
- Mouch, swing the ladder!
- Copy that.
Get me down from here!
There you go.
[coughing]
[grunts]
[grunts] Damn it!
Who else is inside?
My wife.
She was in the bathroom.
- Severide.
- Yeah!
The wife is still in
the bathroom.
Got it!
- Let's find the bathroom!
- Copy that!
[oxygen mask hissing]
Fire department!
Call out!
[fire whooshing]
Fire department!
- I don't see her!
- Severide!
This is too much!
We got to pull out!
Yeah! Okay!
All right!
[grunts]
Chicago Fire S03E10
"Santa Bites"
Sync and corrected by
Gianluca Belfiglio
Help.
Oh.
Capp!
I got her! I see her!
Let's go!
Ready? Go!
[indistinct chatter]
Do you believe this clown?
Last winter we have a guy
literally lay across
his entire family to save them,
and he can't get out that window
fast enough.
[explosion]
Oh, God, is she breathing?
I'll get a line in.
I'll get the airway.
All right.
Hey, you can meet us
at Chicago Med.
Hey.
Nice save.
I'd like to throw the husband
back through the window.
Hey, Chaplain Orlovsky!
Great to see you, Padre.
Yeah, give me your boot there,
Christopher.
- What?
- Give me your boot.
All right!
I want this boot filled
by the end of the week.
[all grumbling]
It's always something.
- Come on!
- Listen up, listen up.
The Good Shepherd Soup Kitchen
that I run
has an oven that doesn't get
above 100 degrees,
has a kitchen that the city
is going to condemn.
Now, that means a lot of cold,
homeless Chicagoans
are gonna get turned away
during the holidays.
- I can't have that.
- We'll fill it up, chaplain.
I'll come collect
after next shift.
Don't let me down.
You, you, you,
yeah, you, and you.
Don't let him down.
Hey, there she is.
Chaplain.
Hey, good to see you.
Mm.
Hey, can I tell you
the hardest thing about my job?
What's that?
People come to my office
when they're
in the deepest valley,
but they stop coming
once they've climbed out of it.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I've been meaning to come by
and say hi.
Well, don't give it
a second thought.
Hey, I'm hearing great things
about you as a firefighter.
Oh. [chuckles]
That's nice.
Everything else good?
[sighs]
One day at a time.
Well, keep it up.
You make me so proud.
Thanks, chaplain.
Don't be crying poor
on me, Capp.
I know what your side job
pulls in, come on.
You don't even know
what my side job is.
Sure I do.
You're a...
Come on, just throw a 20 in.
Cheap.
Come on, Cruz, pony up.
Every extra dollar I've got
is in Molly's truck.
Me too.
Don't even ask.
Hey, Mouch, turn it up.
Severide, check it out.
I saw she was down,
and something inside me
was screaming out,
"Do something, do something,"
you know?
So I picked up
the heaviest thing I could find,
and I threw it through
the window, and I yelled out,
"Over here, over here!"
The fire was out of control
at that point,
and all I could think of was,
"I have to help my wife."
The smoke was so thick...
- [Joe scoffs]
- I was choking on it.
- And, anyway, I'm thrilled...
- Oh, come on.
I could help alert those guys
and save my wife in time.
[reporter] And this was
the scene earlier
where the Chicago Fire
Department arrived
just in time to save
Veronica Carlisle,
but not quickly enough
to save the house.
Compelling story, Glenn.
Glad there's still some local
heroes this time of year.
- In other news...
- Oh, compelling story, Glenn.
Sir, could you tell us exactly
what happened?
Oh, of course, Dwight.
Well, um, my house was on fire,
and I nearly wet myself,
so I barreled out of a window,
nearly killing a fireman, while
leaving my poor wife to die.
Oh!
[laughter]
We should call the station
and tell our side of the story.
Who cares?
Let the guy say what he wants.
- Hey, hey.
- Whoo! Hey.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Everything's fine.
I'm just stopping by
on my way to the Grogans.
Okay.
Can I get you something?
- A... wheelbarrow.
- [both chuckle]
I got one of those.
Come on.
Would you like some lunch?
I have no idea
what those guys are making.
No, no.
Come here.
[chuckles]
Melissa's got ten ladies
coming over
to look at jewelry
or something.
Don't worry.
I'm only looking.
Hey, you remember
meeting her... Melissa?
They had a daughter, Samantha,
last year,
and when it came time
to name her,
they hyphenated her surname,
so it's
Samantha Nash-McGuire.
And I was thinking
that maybe we could do that.
Terrance Robbins-Boden.
- Uh...
- [Donna chuckles]
No.
- "No," just like that?
- Yeah, just like that.
Well, maybe you should take
longer than one second
- to think about it.
- Donna...
there's no way that our child's
going to have two last names...
End of story.
Come on.
Look, I love you, but...
Bodens have just been Bodens.
Tradition
still means something.
- Okay, well...
- What?
I'm gonna be on my way.
- Oh, Donna.
- No, no, no.
I'll see you after shift.
- Great news, Herrmann.
- Hear ye, hear ye.
I present to you the debut
of Molly's II.
- I don't understand.
- It was jammed last year,
and there's gonna be
news coverage to boot.
Newhouse got the permits
cleared, and all we have to do
is sell Chief Hale's
energy water out of the van.
You guys are messing with me.
No, no, no, Hermie-Herm!
Not at all!
Molly's II is finally
in business.
It's everything
we dreamed about...
Serving great food while being
a giant billboard for your bar.
Did Hale say anything
about my lieutenantship?
Right, right, right.
Forget about it.
No, all right, this is great.
This is...
I'm really proud of you boys.
I am. Yeah.
[knock at door]
- Come on in, you two.
- Chief, I wanted to tell you
that Anthony Lullo was waiting
for me outside this morning.
He apologized for his actions
the other day.
He says he knows that we did
all that we could.
And you believe him?
I do.
And looking back,
I'm glad that I didn't file
a police report on him.
He's in deep grief,
and he deserves a pass on this.
Okay.
Glad you trusted your gut.
You too, Chief.
[clears throat]
Matt, can we talk?
Hey.
You know I didn't mean
what I said last night.
So now you remember?
It was just stupid bar talk,
that's all.
"The tough part
isn't the work part.
It's the home part."
That's what you said, right?
Doesn't sound like
stupid bar talk to me.
I mean, it sounds like you knew
exactly what you were saying.
Okay, I was frustrated,
I admit.
You bust my chops at work.
we both bring it home.
It affects us in ways
that aren't exactly healthy.
You're the one who signed up
for this...
- Working for your fiance.
- We both did.
Yeah, because I thought you
could handle it.
- Me?
- I'm not the one crawling back
to my old flame to complain
about my future spouse.
I didn't crawl back
to anything.
I watched it happen.
I heard what I heard!
You two...
maybe you should take
this conversation elsewhere.
Yeah, I'm done talking.
What is this?
50 bucks?
This is pathetic!
Okay, out of the way.
Out of the way.
What's this?
Sylvie and I have been trying
something for the holiday fest.
We call it Santa Bites.
- Wait. We do?
- Mm-hmm.
Santa Bites.
Oh, okay.
Wow!
It's turkey, potatoes and
cranberries all baked in a bun.
- Mmm.
- Oh, ho! Ho, ho ho, mmm!
Is it... a double overhead
shaka, twice in one year?
Yeah!
Damn, I hate to say it,
but this food-truck thing
is just what Molly's needs.
Aw, holy smokes!
Mmm!
You want to try it?
Don't you want to try it?
It's so good.
For the last time,
edges first.
Too easy.
Oh, will you look at this?
- Is that the husband?
- Yeah.
Can I help you?
Uh, I think so.
I was told you were
the firefighters who rescued me
and my wife.
Yeah, we were there.
Yeah, well, I just wanted
to say thank you.
I don't know if you saw
the news,
but they're telling people
I was some sort of hero,
which I know is the exact
opposite of what I am.
Uh...
Okay.
I'm Fred Carlisle.
My wife's Veronica.
She's still in I.C.U.,
but the doctors tell me
there's hope.
Well, again, thank you.
Yeah.
I see the way you guys
are looking at me.
I know what you must be
thinking.
So I want you guys to know.
When I was 16, I was
in the garage with my old man,
and this kiln we had
in there exploded.
All I remember is waking up
in the burn unit.
Spent the next eight months
in the I.C.U.
So, when that fire broke out
this morning...
I panicked.
I just... I panicked.
Hey, man, you don't have
to explain yourself to us.
I know, but I felt...
I felt...
I don't know what I felt.
Thanks for hearing me out.
Yeah, no worries.
And we're all pulling
for your wife.
Walk a mile, men.
Walk a mile.
Are you done with the washer?
What?
Oh, yeah.
Is there some kind of sign-in
sheet for when we can use these?
Uh, no, it's more of
a first-come first-serve.
You okay?
There's not a lot of estrogen
in this house, so...
if you ever want to download,
I'm here.
Thanks.
I found this shirt at the bottom
of my locker.
It's, um... It's from this
barbeque a couple years ago
when I was a paramedic
and Casey was engaged to this
doctor, and...
I remember him playing with
a couple of these kids
in the park, and...
I don't know.
I don't know, I guess
it just... Things seemed...
simpler.
Simpler?
The man you loved was engaged
to another woman.
- Yeah.
- [both chuckle]
You're gonna look back a year
from now and be on
the other side of whatever's
going on, I know that.
Here.
What's this?
Put it in the bottom of your
locker, and then
a year from now when you find
it, you can remember this day.
Sev.
- Plans after shift?
- Uh, home, rest.
Nope, you and me.
Good old-fashioned
Chicago bar crawl.
I can't do it, man.
I'm barely dried out
from the last month or so.
Fine.
One drink, and we'll head home.
- Come on.
- I'm serious.
One drink?
That's all I'm asking.
- Bar...
- Go Hawks!
- Bartender! Hey!
- Go!
Shots for any girl who's above
a nine, all right?
That's so wrong.
Sexist!
What are you talking...
All right, hey, Tim.
Equality for all, all right?
six and up!
- Six and up!
- That's better!
- All right.
- Yeah.
So what's up, dude?
Talk to me.
Ah...
Change of pace, is all.
Couldn't do another night at
home talking about my feelings.
Well, how's everything
on that front?
If I wanted to talk about
my feelings,
- I wouldn't be in a bar...
- I get it, I get it!
I don't blame you, all right?
Hey, whoa!
Hey, not so fast.
Where you going so fast?
What are your names?
- Chloe.
- Huh?
- Oh.
This is Yuma.
Yuma! Like the movie!
I love that movie!
- Like the city!
- Like the city.
Oh ho.
Okay, well...
- Thank you.
- You two, we're doing shots.
Okay, you're staying,
We're doing shots, on me.
Apparently you made the cut.
[crowd cheering]
Yeah!
- Yes!
- Cheers, huh?
Cheers.
[chattering, whooping]
- Yeah!
[applause, cheering fades]
[groans]
[wood creaking]
Well, good morning.
♪ Jingle bell, jingle bell,
jingle bell rock ♪
♪ Jingle bells swing
and jingle bells ring ♪
♪ Snowin' and blowin' ♪
♪ up bushels of fun ♪
♪ Now the jingle...♪
I was proud when
all five of
these kids were born,
- but today!
- Today what, Christopher?
Ah, today is somewhere after
all those days, honey.
Hey, buddy.
10 minutes till serving.
All right!
[grunts] Oh, sorry!
Hey.
- [Matt groans]
- Ugh.
Only one drink, huh?
One thing led to another,
and...
ended up being
an all-night thing.
I tried texting you, like,
50 times.
Lost my phone along the way
somewhere.
Listen, I'm... I'm sorry.
I was a jerk.
It only took eight shots for me
to figure that out.
We can do this.
You and me.
We'll work it out.
- My God, you smell so horrible.
- I'm sorry.
Hey. So this is it, huh?
Ah, yeah, this is it,
Lieutenant.
Aw, hey!
It's Melissa Brosh-McKenna!
- Aw, News 4!
- Yeah!
I'm a big fan of yours.
I love your news.
It's the only news we watch!
Tell 'em, Cindy.
- He's a big fan of yours.
- Oh, thanks, so sweet.
Hey, this is the debut of
Molly's II, our new food truck.
Maybe you guys could put it in
a... You know, in a shot.
Um... why not?
Come on, let's go.
All right, come on Charles,
let's go.
- Guys!
- Come on!
This'll be fun, all right?
Here we go.
We're gonna go in 3-2-1.
We're down at the 42nd Annual
Chicago Holiday Festival,
where families have gathered for
good cheer and good eating.
Sir, can you tell me your name?
Uh, Herrmann,
Christopher Herrmann.
And you're saying this is
the debut of your food truck?
Uh, yeah.
That... That... That...
Th... That's right, that's
something we've been working on,
and working on, like,
three months, because, you know,
we wanted to get it perfect.
Our bar, Molly's, has
gone... gone mobile, and, uh,
that's "Molly's" with two "l"s
and a "y."
It's at, uh, well, uh,
1925 West Wolcott...
Oh my... Oh, my God.
Sir, your... your truck!
[all yelling]
Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no...
Look out!
Save the baby!
Oh!
Hey, that's
the Molly's truck!
Morning, fellas.
- What?
- Seen a lot of firefighters
make the morning paper,
but never like this.
- Connie?
- Chief, you need something?
You ever been invited to a
friend's place for Thanksgiving,
sat down for a big, beautiful,
once-a-year meal,
got excited about
a perfectly-cooked turkey
and then they served up a ham?
- A ham?
- Instead of the turkey.
No, I got that part, but
what I'm not sure about is...
See?
Tradition is important,
is it not?
- I suppose it is.
- Thank you, Connie.
Woman that understands.
I mean... who knows
if the pilgrims ate turkey
at the first Thanksgiving?
Maybe they had nothing but hams
lined up for miles.
But me, as long I can remember,
turkey is the traditional
Thanksgiving food.
And gravy... brown, made from
the drippings of the turkey.
Not some fancy, foo-foo stuff
made with...
pears
and sun-dried tomatoes.
I do like a good gravy.
Got to stand up
for tradition, Connie.
Otherwise, what do we have?
Ham and pear gravy.
Thank you, Connie.
Here's what I remember
from the other night.
Okay,
I don't remember anything.
Mm-hmm.
You had to plug your phone in.
We went to Chloe's apartment
near the bar,
you passed out on the couch...
and I didn't.
So, you and Chloe...
Uh, yeah.
What did...
What did you think?
I didn't know what to think!
Well, when I woke up, you were
still sawing logs on the couch.
So I just took off.
Oh, thank God.
Wait, you did...
You thought you...
I...
[laughs]
- So much for me drying out.
- Yep.
In my defense, the emergency
brake should not be right there.
You were suppose to chock
the tires!
- Mouch was supposed to do that!
- Do we even have tire chocks?
Never in all my life have
I been that humiliated.
- I beg to differ.
- Yeah, me too.
Look, any press is good press,
right?
- Yeah, except that.
- Yeah, that reads like
Molly's is responsible
for the death of Jesus,
again.
That truck is cursed.
It is not the truck's fault,
all right?
I gave you guys eight weeks
to make money
out of the name "Molly's II."
That was a challenge.
- But you never said...
- But, but, but!
- How much money have you made?
- We're just getting started!
You're fired.
[whistling]
Hey.
Did you know Kim Kardashian
went to an all-girls school?
That... explains a lot.
- I got you something.
- What's this?
It's nothing, really.
I know I jumped your case
a while back, and...
you stepped up.
I wanted to say thank you.
[alarm blares, buzzes]
Aww.
[over P.A.] Ambulance 61,
injuries from a fall.
- 815 South Nebraska.
- That's around the corner.
- I'll open this after the call.
- Yeah.
[siren blaring]
[man screaming]
[screaming in pain]
- Where'd you fall from?
- You fell, sir?
Ooh! My legs,
- my legs, my legs!
- Okay, deep breaths.
- What's your name?
- Walter.
Help me, help me, help me...
help me, help me, help me!
He didn't fall.
He was run over.
[screaming]
He's passed out from
blood loss.
Let's get him to Chicago Med.
Who's that?
Hyphenated last name.
Can you believe that?
So the kid, he has three names.
You put in the middle name,
that's four.
That's ridiculous.
Oh, yeah, yeah, I agree.
What was your mother's
maiden name?
- Um... Panchoulidze.
- Can you imagine saying
"Hi, I'm Brian..."
What was it?
- Panchoulidze.
- Panchoulidze-Zvonecek?
Imagine kindergarten,
writing that at the top
- of the damn page.
- Whoa, no, that would've been...
Where would you be sitting
right now?
- Huh?
- You? You would be
an accountant.
Or, uh, working in a bakery
- or something like that.
- Yeah, huh.
I don't... I don't know
that that would...
I mean, yeah, totally.
- Utterly asinine, right?
- Mm.
[swallows]
- Chief?
- What?
You and Donna...
You're gonna make great parents.
[knock at door]
Yeah.
Uh, Chief, a Mac McCoy from
the City Building Department
- is on the phone.
- Yeah, yeah.
Connie, I'll take it.
I...
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Chief Boden.
That's what he told me,
right?
It was good.
Did you watch last night?
Hey, Kelly.
Fire from last shift.
City's looking to condemn
the structure,
want us to take a look.
Yeah, we'll head over there.
Thanks.
I'd slap the red "x" on it
if it were up to me.
You guys hear anything more
from the wife?
No, she's still in
the burn unit.
You guys know Dr. Kendra
over there?
She sometimes keeps me posted
on things.
Yeah, I know her.
She's a lesbian.
Interesting.
All right, yeah,
this place is done, let's get...
What?
Fire started here, and here.
And there.
Three different places
at the same time.
That son of a bitch.
Call OFI and the CPD, will ya?
On it.
That's him right there.
Mr. Carlisle?
You need to come with us.
We've got some questions.
Yeah, sure.
You were burned yourself,
buddy.
How the hell could you do that
to another person?
Your own wife?
Maybe we could, uh... mm.
Yeah, never mind.
What about...
Forget it.
Here you go, fellas.
Grab a spoon.
- Hey, chaplain!
- Ah!
You raised some money for us,
Christopher.
Yeah...
Is this the best you could do
for us, 51?
Nah, chaplain.
Not exactly.
Your new soup kitchen now has
its own set of wheels.
Just know the parking brake
can be a little tricky.
This is the best Christmas
gift this old chaplain's
- ever gotten.
- Merry Christmas, Father.
There you go, brother.
All right.
- Come on.
- Hey.
Let us show you the inside.
- It's all yours, Padre.
- Yeah.
Careful with
the parking brake!
Anyone heard from Mills
and Brett?
Nope.
Hey.
Does a fireman named Matt
work here?
Um, yeah.
Yeah, he does.
He left his cell phone
in my apartment.
Can you give it to him for me?
Excuse me?
Found your phone.
'Cause you left it at some
blonde bimbo's apartment.
Wait, wait.
I can explain that.
Great, explain it.
I'd really love to hear it.
Me and Severide, we... we went
back to that girl's apartment
to plug in my phone.
I fell asleep on the couch.
Severide is the one who slept
with her.
And this is how
you want to tell me?
Tell you what?
Nothing happened!
You know, Kelly really brings
out the worst in you.
What brings out the worst
in me is you telling Mills
you don't know if you want
to be with me.
You think an apology
was gonna fix that?
I thought we agreed that
we were past that!
Well, apparently not!
Maybe this whole thing is
too big for us.
I'm trying to be a lieutenant
and your fiance,
and you can't respect
either one.
Request permission to leave
shift, Lieutenant.
Granted, candidate.
You know, I was gonna drop it
and not say anything else.
In fact, I've kept my mouth shut
all week.
But then, I thought to myself,
"Why shouldn't I have some say
- in the naming of my child?"
- Donna, it's my family name,
it's important to me,
there are traditions involved.
Oh! well, some traditions
need to be put to bed!
Not this one.
You sound...
like some old... [gasping]
- What...
- ...dinosaur that can't even...
Hey.
What is it?
Oh, it's...
I think it's coming!
- What... What's coming?
- Oof!
Oh... Oh, God...
Can I have some help up in here?
- [Donna groans]
- Breathe, breathe.
- Look at me... Breathe, breathe.
She's going into labor,
where are our paramedics?
- Uh... out.
- Where's Dawson?
- Went home sick.
- [Donna groans]
Oh, okay, I'm here!
I'm right here, baby.
Uh, uh, squad... Everyone,
let's help her, let's go.
- Let's go, help him carry her.
- Move!
[overlapping chatter]
Come on, come on, come on!
[Donna yells in pain]
Oh!
Okay, okay, okay.
[engine turns]
Go!
[siren blaring]
[horn honking]
- Oh!
- Tony, get us moving.
- Oh, my God!
- There's nowhere to go, Chief.
- What is it?
- Oh, the baby's coming.
- What?
The baby is coming!
The baby's coming!
[horns honking]
[Donna yelling in pain]
- Okay, lay her down.
- Okay, okay, okay...
- Come on, baby.
- Uhh!
- Lay back down.
- You done this before, Chief?
More times than I can count.
Just never with my own son.
- Do you want me to...
- Not a chance in hell.
Okay, wait, wait, wait,
Wallace.
- I'm right here.
- Wallace.
I'm right here.
This old dinosaur knows
what he's doing,
I promise you.
Anyway, what's better than to
bring little Terrance
in the world than from
a CFD squad truck?
- Okay.
- Okay?
Lie back down.
Just breathe.
Okay, baby,
I can see the crown.
He's coming.
He's crowning.
Okay?
I'm gonna need you to push.
No, I can't do this!
- Yes, you can... Yes, you can.
- No, no...
Look at me, look at me.
It's just you and me.
Okay?
You can do this.
Come on.
- Okay.
- Now...
And... push!
[grunts]
[yells]
Yes!
You're doing great.
Doing so good.
Oh, God!
I'm just gonna need
one more little push,
one more little push.
Okay?
Okay. [grunts]
[all] Push!
Oh, my God!
He's out, baby, he's out!
[baby whimpering]
I got a little boy.
I got a little boy!
Hey-hey!
[baby wailing]
- Oh, gosh!
- Oh...
Here he is.
You did good, baby.
- So good.
- Okay.
You did good.
[sighs]
Hey, Lieutenant?
We still haven't heard
hide nor hair of ambo
since they left this morning.
Yeah, this is Lieutenant Casey
at 51.
Do you guys have a location
on ambulance 61, please?
Okay.
You know what?
I'm gonna run by there
and have a look.
Thanks.
61 is still on scene
at 815 South Nebraska.
The alarm office said their
computers have been up and down
all day and they haven't been
able to check status.
- Let's go!
- Yep, load up.
[siren blaring]
Terrance Boden.
Some traditions
are worth keeping.
Oh... Ohh!
Thank you.
[groaning]
- I don't want to let him go.
- It's okay.
Hi.
Doctor,
the baby's turning blue.
What's going on?
Wallace?
Respiratory distress.
Meconium aspiration.
- What's going on?
- Lungs aren't absorbing oxygen.
Wallace, what's going on?
Call respiratory and let peds
know we're on our way, now!
Talk to me!
You talk to me, now!
No!
What's happening?
[honking]
[garbage rustling]
Mills?
Brett?
Sync and corrected by
Gianluca Belfiglio
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org