[MAN] Previously on The Chi...
I wanna confess to the
murder of Coogie Johnson.
- I quit.
- What? Why?
Trying to do the right thing, I guess.
It would be nice to
start something of my own.
[BRANDON] A food truck, but I
don't have the money for that.
Even if the house sells tomorrow,
it could take three months,
if not longer for you to get paid.
They can get that truck fixed.
- What you got, big man?
- Soul food in a taco.
It says right there, you his father.
- I just want you to do better.
- I'm tryin'.
I see that; it's not all about you anymore.
EJ's good, but his mama is... damn.
- She's back?
- Yeah, and she's staying
- with some random dude.
- Who killed
that basketball star up
near your stash house?
Trice did your boy.
Look, man, we worried about you.
- Don't be.
- What about school?
- Reg didn't go to school.
- Yeah, he's a drug dealer.
You happen to see Trice around?
Yeah, I picked him up this morning
and dropped him off at his crib.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
[TRUNK OPENS]
Get your bitch ass the fuck out my car.
- [GRUNTS]
- Stand your motherfuckin' ass up, dude.
Get the fuck up.
[PANTING, GRUNTING]
Hey, stay your ass right here.
- You hear me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, all right.
- Come on. Come on, dude.
Yeah, get the fuck on your left.
Get your bitch ass in there.
Get the fuck in there, dude.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING SOFTLY]
We've got this.
Take little man outside and wait.
All right.
Didn't I tell you to wait
your ass outside? Come on.
Stanley, your shuffle's
really coming along.
Kevin, I'm gonna need you to project.
You have a really good voice. Use it.
He's just afraid of greatness, Mr. Gasca.
Man, shut up, Papa.
- You guys talk to Jake?
- You talk to those dancers?
The ones messing up our play?
I will. Now, did you talk to Jake?
- Yeah, we did.
- He's exploring other options,
Mr. Gasca, in the family business.
- Family business?
- Yeah, with his brother Reg.
[PAPA] I've been praying for
him every night, Mr. Gasca.
Even whittled a cross for him,
but my mom says he's lost his way.
Well, sometimes you
gotta do more than that.
Maybe I'll have a chat
with this brother of his.
I wouldn't do that if I was you, Mr. Gasca.
- Reg is a bad mother.
- Real bad.
I'll take that into consideration.
But for tonight, our play needs us.
Let's see about this
yellow brick road, huh?
[TENSE MUSIC]
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
♪
Hey. Hey!
Look at me.
[PANTING]
So, Michael,
how do you wanna do this?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
My mother needs to be
able to look at me after.
Hm. Okay.
I'll tell you what, you
tell me what I wanna know
and...
the knife stays right here.
I take you on your word on that.
I spoke with your friend, Wallace.
The cop.
He told me you were
the one who shot my boy.
Your boy?
[JASON] I'll be there
in, like, ten.
No. Of course I love you.
I mean, my ass is out here
getting you ice cream, ain't I?
[LAUGHS] No.
All right, all right.
Okay.
Hold on.
- Wait.
- We got eyes. Lock up. Lock up.
Hey, lemme... lemme call
you... Lemme call you back.
[TENSE MUSIC]
[TRICE] Hey. You lost, youngblood?
Who you got on the phone?
N-no.
No, man, I... I was just leavin'. I...
Who you with?
Nobody, I... I swear.
Oh. You look like you
was playing hide and seek.
What you doin' around here?
I was goin' to my girl house.
She... just gettin' her... Gettin' her...
Gettin' her ice cream.
Oh, that's cute. [LAUGHS]
What kinda ice cream you get her?
Mint... mint chocolate chip.
Not bad.
All right. Look, I didn't see nothin'.
I... I didn't see nothin'.
Who said anything about seeing something?
Nigga, what was you doin' hiding there?
[GUNSHOTS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
I had no choice.
They gon' kill him?
Don't matter. The man
said wait, we gon' wait.
- But what happens next?
- Bro.
See, that's why I knew I shouldn't have
brought your ass with me.
I'm good.
All right.
Come on.
Go on.
Finish it.
You stick here, little man.
[GUNSHOT]
[AMBIENT MUSIC]
♪
Go on.
Take a look if you want.
♪
Synced and corrected by louvette
www.addic7ed.com
[RONNIE] I asked about
the chain he was wearing.
- [ARMANDO] Jason's chain.
- Yeah.
This is outside the corner store?
- Mm-hmm.
- Go on.
[RONNIE] We argue.
I took out the gun, and...
I need to hear you say it.
I shot him.
That was it.
[ARMANDO] You remove
anything from the body?
Just my boy's chain.
It was the last thing that I gave him.
[ARMANDO] Okay.
Let's talk about after.
You tell anybody else what you did?
- No.
- And the gun?
Sold it.
Who'd you sell the gun to?
A guy on the street.
- [ARMANDO] What street?
- 63rd and King.
[ARMANDO] What'd the guy look like?
I don't know.
You're lying about the gun.
[RONNIE] I sold it to Meldrick.
I don't know his last name.
[ARMANDO] Yeah, I know
who you're talking about.
Anybody see you shoot Coogie?
What's that matter?
[ARMANDO] Corroborate the story.
Everything helps.
Anybody witness you shooting Coogie?
Yeah.
Name?
[GATE BUZZES]
- Three.
- [WOMAN] Copy.
Opening cell three.
- [BUZZING]
- [LOCKS UNLATCHING]
What you lookin' at?
Nothin'.
So you taking the truck out tonight?
Yeah, I gotta start
makin' some kinda money.
Brandon, what are you
lookin' at me like that for?
The guy that you messed with,
you... you work with him?
[SIGHS]
I just wanna know.
I thought you said this
wasn't gonna be a thing.
- It's not.
- Then why you askin'?
'Cause look what you got on.
Oh, I can't look cute at work
now 'cause Marcus is there?
[SCOFFS] See?
I knew y'all worked together.
Do you see me all up in your shit
because you fucked your boss, Sarah?
She's not even my boss no more, J.
Can we just not do this?
I'm moving on and so should you.
Okay.
It's already in my rearview.
Good.
So guess what? I just got a solid offer
on your mom's house.
- That's a good thing, right?
- Yeah, so you can get paid
- and fix up that roach coach.
- I'm sorry, what?
- [LAUGHS]
- Not too much on my truck, okay?
Back... back it all the way up.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- It's a work in progress
- is what it is.
- Sure, let's go with that.
I'm taking the offer over to them now.
You comin'?
[PLAYFUL BLUES MUSIC]
Yeah, I'm comin'. I'm comin'.
Ooh! There you go.
There you go. Ooh!
- Whoo!
- [BABY SQUEALS]
There you go, there you go.
Oh, oh, ohh [LAUGHS]
- Ah!
- [LAUGHS]
I got you. I got you.
Hm?
[SUCKS TEETH] Well, it's almost time
for you to get back with
your moms, young man.
- [BABY COOING]
- You gonna miss Pops?
We both gonna miss Grams,
'cause she might be leaving us.
How you feel about that?
Just gonna be the two of us, man.
Emmett?
How many Pampers is left in that bag?
'Cause I gotta make a few
stops before I go home.
Say, "Hi, Mommy." Tell
her, "I had ice cream today,
and now I got gas."
[BABY SQUEALS]
[LAUGHS MOCKINGLY]
What happened to your face?
Nothin'.
Is everything all right?
Why don't you just mind
your business, Emmett?
Tiff, just because we
ain't what we used to be
don't mean you can't talk to me.
I gotta roll.
- Come on.
- [CRYING]
It's okay.
I gotta go.
[AMBIENT MUSIC]
♪
Just walked in and confessed.
- Huh? Your guy.
- Yeah.
[CHUCKLES] Why would he do that?
I don't know. He felt guilty.
Did he leave out the part where
you gave him Coogie Johnson?
Ah...
Oh, you wanna pull down on me?
- Fuckin'...
- [GRUNTS]
This is where you're
supposed to pull the trigger.
Yeah. [SLAPS BACK] I thought so.
- [GRUNTS]
- Oh!
Fuck!
[GRUNTING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
You're a dead man.
What are you doing?
You said meet you outside so we could
walk to the play together.
Somebody sees you like that, you gonna get
your lollipopped ass kicked.
Nobody's gonna whoop my ass.
You figure?
In jail the last person you wanna fight
is the crazy one because
they unpredictable.
How do you know this?
Locked Up Abroad.
I watch it with my mom.
She says it's important
to see the path of sin.
- What?
- Did you know that
they bring narcotics into the penitentiary
up their asses?
Cell phones too.
I-I don't wanna know that.
Okay.
You okay?
Just... nervous about the play.
My whole family's coming.
Don't worry. I got your back.
Maybe we could run the lines together?
All right, let's do it.
We're gonna lock this Wiz down and shine.
Check this, got the
Cold Duck all chilled up.
Rosé, too.
[LAUGHTER]
We ain't sold it yet, crazy.
Shit, we got the offer, Laverne.
It was the paint, wasn't it?
Motherfuckin' Quaking Grass.
[LAUGHTER]
- They didn't say.
- Laid that rest, did you?
[LAUGHTER]
[SIGHS] So what's the offer for?
It's 5,000 over your asking price.
- That's good, isn't it?
- In this market? Yes.
Told you we shoulda asked for more.
- We?
- You think that Italian tile
just laid itself?
Hell no. I got some
serious sweat equity in this joint.
Can we sign, please?
We ain't fuckin' signing
with no cheap ass Bics.
This used to be my father's.
- Look who bougie now.
- Now, now!
- [LAUGHTER]
- [CELL PHONE RINGING]
I thought it was me.
Let me take this real quick.
- Hello?
- All right so,
- you're gonna sign here.
- Yes, this is he.
Everywhere it says seller initial.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay?
- When?
- Every page.
Everywhere... okay.
Everywhere you see the X.
Uh, yeah, I'll let her
know. I'll let her know.
No, that's it. Thank you.
I appreciate it.
All right, you too.
I hope you see everything.
I'm sure he'll read it all.
That was Detective Cruz. He, um...
He said they got the guy who shot Coogie.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
Yo... Mom.
I'm sorry.
They helped... Fuck.
[SIGHS]
[COCKS GUN]
See how I got my shit tucked?
Tuck your shit in the back, just like that.
Ready?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
Fellas.
So listen up.
Trice gone.
Man, what the fuck is you talkin' about?
Big Mike, you heard exactly
what the fuck I just told you.
That nigga gone, and he ain't comin' back.
So what's up, then?
So you the boss now, huh?
[CHUCKLES] That's the way it's lookin'.
I wanna know, my paper the same?
Hell yeah.
Well, you just made the
boogey man smile, then.
- We good, man.
- [LAUGHS] That's what it is.
Yes, sir.
[LAUGHS] Ha, but yeah,
check it out, check it out.
So, look, hey, this block is
too motherfuckin' hot right now.
We have to find us a new hustle, ASAP.
Well, you need to come up
with some new moves, then,
- my brother.
- Indeed. So look, check it out.
I want you to round up everybody,
take 'em to the park, lay
low for a little minute,
bust a couple syrups.
As soon as I got somethin' new,
I'm gon' hit you.
- My man.
- Yeah.
All right. Right there.
All right, y'all. I'ma holla at you.
What's up, man? No pressure, no pressure.
[LAUGHS]
So what's up, uh... What you wanna do now?
Wanna go get some new kicks?
We can go to That's A Burger.
- Nah, I'm not hungry.
- Yeah?
So what else you wanna do?
- [MUSICAL SCORE PLAYING]
- [LAUGHTER]
♪
[LAUGHTER]
I gotta admit it, Andrea's doing all right.
Saved it all for show time.
You threw all that shade for no reason.
Huh, whatever.
- [APPLAUSE]
- [PROP CLATTERS]
[CROWD EXCLAIMS]
[LAUGHTER]
See? Damn, girl. Mind the trees.
- Be happy she dumped you.
- She didn't dump me, all right?
All right.
You're friends with a girl
that can't dance for shit.
Whatever.
[BRIGHT PIANO MUSIC]
All right, it's show time.
You ready?
[SIGHS] I think so.
[SIGHS] Just remember, follow my lead.
Ah!
[RAP MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Rain down, Zion ♪
♪ It's gonna rain ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪
[LAUGHTER]
Hell yeah, Papa. Kill that shit, big boy.
That's how you move, big boy!
♪ Rain down, Zion ♪
♪ It's gonna rain ♪
♪ You better come on in this house ♪
♪ 'Cause it's gonna rain ♪
♪ Rain down, Zion ♪
♪ It's gonna rain ♪
♪ You gotta move it slowly ♪
♪ Take and eat my body like it's holy ♪
♪ I been waitin' for
you for the whole week ♪
♪ I been praying for you,
you're my Sunday candy ♪
♪ You gotta move slowly ♪
♪ Take and eat my body like it's holy ♪
♪ I've been waitin' for
you for this whole week ♪
♪ I've been praying for you,
you're my Sunday candy ♪
♪ Slowly, take and eat
my body like it's holy ♪
♪ I've been waitin' for
you for the whole week ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[WOMAN] Good job, Kevin!
Go, Kevin!
We love you, Kevin! Whoo!
Yes, go, Kevin!
[CHEERING CONTINUES]
[WOMAN] Kevin, Kevin! Kev...
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[WOMAN] You just jealous.
[LAUGHTER]
I see him looking at you.
- Girl, don't be stupid.
- He got a pretty smile.
- [LAUGHS] What's up?
- [CHATTER]
Yo, Emmett.
Come here.
[CHATTER CONTINUES]
The hell is wrong with you, boy?
Those ladies out there
shootin' hard at you,
and you mopin' around
like your dog just died.
Still got some shit on my mind.
What's got you so twisted up?
It's Tiffany, I...
Boy, you need to find new tune to whistle.
When she came to pick EJ up,
she had a bruise on her cheek.
Uh-huh.
[SIGHS]
I can't have my son around that.
No, you can't.
[NINA] Okay, just a few more, Kevin.
- Just a few more. Stay there.
- Mom.
Oh, come on. Hush yourself.
Wait. There it is.
Stay, don't move.
Oh, that's so cute.
Hey, come on.
All right, last one. I'm hungry.
- Let's go.
- Come on, smile, Kevin.
[LAUGHS] By the way, Keisha,
you look exceptionally beautiful today.
- Thank you, Papa.
- Mm-hmm.
- What are you doing?
- Come on, what are you doing?
Oh, hey, hey, call me when
you're ready to come home
and I'll come and pick you up.
All right.
Never hit on my sister like that.
- She was lookin' good.
- Shut up.
Keisha!
- Ooh. Girl.
- You was walking around.
You said take a picture, I took a picture.
You just fightin'.
♪ All my fellas poppin' bottles ♪
♪ All my ladies lookin' fly ♪
♪ We just tryin' to have some fun ♪
Hey man, what were you doin'?
Keisha was feelin' me.
My sister?
Hey, man. What can I say?
When you got mad skills,
all the ladies in the house
- want some of that.
- I thought Jesus was about
being humble and thankful.
- Do I look like Jesus to you?
- No, but you're always
- bringing him up and shit.
- I aspire.
And don't curse when you say His name.
All I said was "shit."
- What are you doing?
- I'm not getting hit
by Jesus' lightning 'cause of you.
We're inside, dummy.
And Jesus is the son of God
and can strike down
lightning wherever He wants.
Jesus don't play.
- What's up, fools?
- [LAUGHS] Jake.
Came to bust our balls?
Nah, man. Y'all were great.
So, uh, you comin' back to the school?
[SIGHS] I don't know.
What you gonna do?
I guess see what's what.
Look, man, you could always
stay with me if you want to.
- Now why would I do that?
- I don't know.
Maybe if you wanna run
away from your brother?
- He's my blood, Kevin.
- All right.
If you get in trouble, that's on you.
Man, fuck you.
Hey, Jake, hold up.
I made this for you.
It's rosewood.
All right, thanks.
You wanna hang, hit my line.
Kev's just worried about you.
Ain't none of his business to worry about.
[SIGHS]
- I'll check you later.
- All right.
- You tried.
- Hope he all right.
Ain't nothing we can do
now but go to this party
and bust it out.
♪ I feel so alive ♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[WOMAN] Thank you.
Sheriff, please bring in Ronald Davis.
[DOOR OPENS]
Look at the judge.
What are the charges?
[MAN] First degree murder for the killing
of Charles "Coogie" Johnson.
This motherfucker better not get no bail.
- Shh.
- Don't be shushin' me.
- That's my...
- Not in my court, ma'am.
Please be quiet.
- Ms. Sabloff?
- Ronald Garvey Davis
- is a military veteran.
- Employment?
None currently, but in the past,
he's worked in construction
and as a stock clerk.
[AMBIENT MUSIC]
No bond. Suspect is remanded
to Cook County Jail, pending trial date.
[BANGS GAVEL]
Thank you.
♪
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
[WOMAN] Get out of my fuckin' face!
[SHOUTING, BABY CRYING]
[TIFFANY] Stay the
fuck away from me.
Stay over there.
Yo, Tiffany. Tiffany!
- [BABY CRYING]
- Tiffany!
Ohh, shit! Fuck.
[The Cool Kids' "Break Your Legs"]
♪ Oh, you thought you was gon' speak ♪
♪ Leave you talkin' with no teeth ♪
♪ Oh, you talkin', it's so sweet ♪
♪ We can shoot this fade
right here for free ♪
♪ Let's get it on ♪
♪ Cool J shots to the dome ♪
Tiffany!
♪ Rubber grip pumps on the chrome ♪
[GRUNTING AND STRUGGLING IN DISTANCE]
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, man, it's okay.
It's okay. Wait up, wait up, wait up.
- Tiffany! Tiff!
- No, fuck you. Fuck you!
Oh, shit! Tiff, Tiff, Tiff, Tiff.
Stop, stop!
Touch me again, I'ma fuckin' kill your ass!
Stop, stop, stop, yo.
The fuck is you doin' here, Emmett?
I was worried. I thought
you might need some help.
Do I look like I fuckin' need help, Emmett?
- No, but I was tryin'...
- But what?
I told your ass, stay
out my fuckin' business.
Yeah, nigga, step the fuck off!
- You shut the fuck up!
- Sit, babe... I...
Tired of your shit too.
Come on! Hey, hey, hey... shit! Hey...
- Fuck the both of y'all.
- Hey, cool out, man.
- Hey, chill...
- [BABY CRYING]
I'm takin' EJ with me. Y'all call me
when y'all figure this shit out.
- Emmett, wait!
- Hey, chill out, man.
- Wait! Don't fuckin' touch me!
- Hey, Tiff...
- Don't fuckin' touch me.
- Hey...
- Come on.
Emmett, wait! Emmett, where the fuck
are you going with my kid?
Man, look... relax! Fuckin' chill.
Fuck you lookin' at?
That's what the fuck I thought.
[AMBIENT MUSIC]
♪
[GATE BUZZES]
[BELL RINGING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[MAN] Next, come on through.
You plugged?
What?
With anybody?
- No, man.
- Get to the back
of the fuckin' line, then, neutron.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[MAN] Hey! Back up!
[UPBEAT JAZZY MUSIC PLAYING]
♪
Ahh, Detective Wallace.
Please, let's have a drink.
[MAN] You got it.
Now, what the fuck happened to you?
- Yeah, wife.
- Ah.
I had one like that. [LAUGHS]
To Trice.
Mm.
And the less you know
about that, the better.
Right. Fuck him.
[LAUGHS]
Fuck him.
[LAUGHTER]
What's so fuckin' funny?
Well, that's exactly
what he said about you.
"Fuck him."
Right before he told me
the rest of the story.
What the fuck you talkin' about?
[DARK TONE]
♪
[GUNSHOTS]
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTING]
[GUN COCKS]
♪
- [SIGHS]
- What the fuck was he doing?
I don't know. He said he was trying
to get home to his lady.
Get the fuck out of here. I got it.
[GASPING]
Help.
- [CHOKING]
- [STRUGGLING]
- [STRUGGLED BREATHING]
- [GRUNTS]
[COUGHS]
♪
- That's some bullshit.
- No.
No, Trice was telling the truth.
Trust me.
You know, and the bitch of this is
is that I left here so
that my boy would be safe.
Didn't want my shit spilling over on him.
[FUNKY MUSIC PLAYING]
He was a good boy.
Was gonna go to school, play ball.
- But now...
- It was Trice, not me.
- He shot your boy.
- Aha.
Ah! Fuck!
Uh!
Hey.
How is she?
Coogie's room. In a mood.
I saw the way that man looked
at you in the courtroom today.
You knew him, didn't you?
- Ma, I...
- Don't lie to me, boy.
I just know him from around.
Brandon, please.
I saw... remember that
night you came up in here,
talkin' 'bout you got hurt at work.
Ma, I didn't go lookin' for him
if that's what you askin' me.
- I didn't do that.
- I'm not askin' you nothin'.
I'm just glad nothing happened, baby.
And nothing's gonna happen, Mom.
Hey, don't cry. Look, after we...
After we sell this house,
it's... we can just put all this behind us.
All right?
Uh-uh.
I can't sell, baby.
What?
I gotta stay.
I gotta go through this
trial and see this man
pay for what he done to my baby.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
We'll be all right.
♪
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
Who is it?
Detective Cruz, CPD.
How can I help you?
I need to speak with a parent
or parents of Kevin Williams.
Kevin's my son. What's
happening? What's going on?
I'm sorry to bother
you this evening, ma'am,
but, uh, I need to question your son.
About what?
The murder of Charles "Coogie" Johnson.
- Uh...
- Killer claims that
your son saw him commit the crime.
[SIGHS]
If Kevin saw something like that,
he would've told me about it.
And he didn't, so I'm sorry
we can't help you.
Coogie Johnson was 16 years old.
I need your help.
Ah... [SIGHS]
♪
It's all taken care of.
He was just at the wrong
place at the wrong time, Tracy.
That's all.
I'm sorry.
[Oscar Brown Jr.'s "Brother Where Are You"]
♪
♪ Brother, where are you? ♪
♪ A small boy walked ♪
♪ Down a city street ♪
♪ Hope was in his eyes ♪
♪ As he searched the faces ♪
♪ Of the people he'd meet ♪
♪ For one he could recognize ♪
♪ Brother, where are you? ♪
♪ They told me that you came this way ♪
Hey, you got a cellmate.
Right.
♪
♪ Brother, where are you ♪
♪ Brother, where are you? ♪
♪ The eyes of the people who passed him by ♪
♪ Were as cold and as hard as stone ♪
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
♪ And the poor boy whimpered ♪
♪ And began to cry ♪
You good with this?
Yeah.
Good. 'Cause it's your case, now.
♪ They told me that you came this way ♪
♪ Brother, where are you? ♪
♪ They said you came this way ♪
Tiff freakin' out that I took EJ.
She said she gon' call the cops on me.
Baby, you did the right thing.
How am I supposed to protect him next time?
You gon' have to get custody.
Well, Sonny told me that
wasn't gonna be easy.
Yeah, it's damn near impossible.
I don't know how I'm gonna do this one.
You'll figure it out.
♪ Brother, where are you? ♪
♪ They told me that you came this way ♪
♪ They said you came this way ♪
♪ Brother, where are you? ♪
♪ They told me that you came this way ♪
Hey, taco. Remember me?
You showed up at the crib, talkin' 'bout
you fucked up and lost my pole.
Yeah, I remember.
I'm here to collect.
Look, if you want money, dog, I could...
Ah hell no. Don't trip on none of that.
We gon' make a whole lot of money.
Yeah, we goin' fuckin' mobile.
Nice truck.
Big Mike, we gone.
Hey, um...
I'ma holla at you.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[WINDOW WHIRRING]
♪ That's why I love the moon ♪
[Phony Ppl's "Why I Love The Moon."]
♪ Every night it's there for you ♪
♪ Who lie about what it seems to be ♪
♪ You think the earth is where you stand ♪
♪ You're in the palms of someone's hand ♪
♪ And that's why I love the moon ♪
♪ 'Cause it's always there for me ♪
♪ Every night about my window ♪
Man, what's up with you not dancing?
I gotta go handle something.
You need backup?
- No, I got it.
- Oh, no.
Man, what do you want?
'Cause I know you don't wanna
dance with someone like me.
Look, I messed up, all right?
- Yeah, you did.
- I just got caught up
with the whole Andrea thing
and I forgot about your feelings.
You were disrespectful, man.
I know, and I'm sorry.
I-I just didn't want
to hurt your feelings.
Can you please forgive me?
Okay. I forgive you.
- For real?
- Yeah.
It's the Christian thing to do.
Besides, I don't even like you anymore.
Okay.
Can you put in a word for me with Papa?
Really?
Yeah. I like the way he moves.
- All right.
- Ask him if he wants
to come dance with me.
Okay.
- Hey, uh, Papa, uh...
- No, no, no, no.
Hey.
You were great.
You too.
You wanna dance?
But I thought...
It's just dancing.
Come on.
[Noname's "Reality Check"]
♪
♪ Opportunity knockin, a
nigga was out for coffee ♪
♪ Inadequate like my windows ♪
♪ The Grammy's is way too lofty ♪
♪ And I could stay here forever ♪
♪ I could die here I
don't have to try here ♪
♪ Can I get my two sugars please? ♪
♪ Jesus made an album I'm still waiting ♪
♪ In the line for cream
she dream in Technicolor ♪
♪ Live black and white
opportunity knockin' ♪
♪ A nigga just got her nails done ♪
♪ Skeletons in my closet ♪
♪ Gon' open the door when Yale come ♪
♪ They ain't gonna wanna
see my silhouette rap ♪
♪ He's fucking cognac ♪
♪ My smile in all black ♪
♪ Mississippi vagabond ♪
♪ Granny gon' turn up in her grave ♪
♪ And say, my granny really
was a slave for this ♪
♪ All your uncompleted
similes and pages ripped ♪
♪ You know they whipped us niggas ♪
♪ How you afraid to rap it ♪
♪ You went to heaven after
so we could free them now ♪
♪ Ain't no ocean floor when
you can be a Yeezus now ♪
♪ Don't fear the light ♪
♪ That dwells deep within ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ You are powerful ♪
♪ Beyond what you imagine ♪
♪ Just let your light glow ♪
♪ Seventeen moments and
cloudy days on my snap ♪
♪ Mysterious aberration,
illuminated the trap ♪
♪ My telefone-calications
synonymous with the sunrise ♪
♪ Mountains against the foreground ♪
♪ Forever me coming back ♪
♪ I ain't gonna cry ♪
♪ The last time Ali marched Chicago ♪
♪ Twenty four and a late mojo
teaching me how to drive ♪
♪ Whole world inside my rear view ♪
♪ This feel in me so alive ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org