Right. What you having?
Hey, hey, hey! Come on.
Mammy'll make you some eggs, then.
Have a bit more in there.
Can't we have the chocolate ones?
No, darling.
Not unless you don't want any teeth!
Do you know, my grandad, he didn't
have any teeth, darling?
And do you know what he looked like?
He looked like an old tortoise.
Like this.
Uhhhhh.
Now is this how you want to look?
Is that how you want to look?
It's not how you
want to look, is it?!
Right, who wants an egg? Hmm?
These are Mammy's favourite.
You don't want one?
I've made them all nice for you,
Rhods!
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on. Try it.
It's nice and cool. Here you go.
Oh, Rhodri will have it, look!
Arghhh.
Right let's see where Alys is, huh?
Alys! It is twenty past eight,
darling!
She'll be on the headphones. Oh,
she'll be hearing me in a minute.
You won't forget my things
from the art shop, Mam?
Glitter, felt... And blue card, yes.
Alys, do you know this
is not funny any more?
Morning, morning.
Hell, it was choppy last night.
Need to find myself
some digs on dry land, I do.
There's a spare room going above the
pub, isn't there? Oh, tell you what.
I miss Terry and his quiz team.
Why don't your start one yourself
then, huh? Fill his shoes.
...This is pretty,
did you do that today?
I'm not worthy. You all right?
Right. Alys!
Alys, come down now,
or you will go to school hungry!
Where is she? Tell her. Here you go,
sort yourself out, go on.
That girl. Honestly,
she's turning me into my mother.
What? Your mam was a MILF remember?
That's disgusting, Arthur. She was.
Right, then.
Alys, come on, then! Right.
Alys!
Give me a kiss. I love your hair
this morning, it's beautiful.
And you, my precious boy.
Special coat. Special coat.
Can we make pizzas tonight?
Pizza? You bet, my darling.
Because Mammy hasn't had breakfast.
Mammy's very thirsty,
and don't tell Arthur about this.
Bye, Mam.
It's a phase. It's a phase.
Oh, right. Yeah.
For a year and a half?
Right, I love you! Bye-bye!
Bye. Bye-bye, Mammy! Behave!
Bye-bye! Bye, Mammy. Bye!
Right, then, what have we got?
Cornflakes?
Ych a fi. Right, who wants
Choco Wheats? Me! Yeah?
Just keep going.
Got it.
Lewis. Court 4, 12 o'clock.
Who's the judge?
Oh, no!
No, call the list office.
You'll have to change that.
Well, you'll have to. Not Merrick,
Delyth. Anyone but Merrick.
There's cake in it for you!
You people make me sick.
Corran Energy still owe us
£32,000 in outstanding fees.
You need to talk to them. Mmm.
I know they're your friends, Tom,
but this is business.
Right. Who's the judge?
Still Merrick.
Oh, Delyth!
Faith, I want to talk to you about
this. Is this it? Yes.
The family stuff. Mm.
I thought we'd all agreed we were
going to move things
in a more commercial direction.
Tom? We are struggling, OK?
Mm-hm. We can't depend
on waifs and strays.
Corran Energy paid up yet?
Right. I shall be sticking with
the waifs and strays, then.
Faith, come on!
Thank you very much.
Faith, for God's sake.
I'm, uh...
Oh, I love these!
I'm going to court.
I'll see you later!
Am I the only one
trying to run a business here?
No.
Thank you, Delyth.
♪ Out of my cage
and I've been doing just fine
♪ Because I got it all
♪ Started out with a kiss
♪ How did it end up like this?
♪ It was only a kiss,
it was only a kiss!
it was only a kiss... ♪
Dad, quick come on!
Mammy's here! Quick!
♪ I gave my heart
♪ Whole, I did
♪ And although it's lost
♪ It is still beating
♪ And I gave my whole
♪ Soul, I did
♪ Well, I gave my soul
♪ And although I'm broken
♪ I am still breathing. ♪
Where have you been, Dad?
I had to go away.
Business.
I'm sorry.
You won't do it again? Please.
No.
I'm not going anywhere, OK?
Now, sleep.
OK? It's late.
Night-night.
Bastard.
You coward.
I had a gun...
I had a fucking gun
pulled on me tonight.
And Alys, she saw everything,
and it's because of you.
It's because of you.
You're a bastard.
They abducted her.
No.
They took our little girl.
They took her,
and they had a fucking gun.
What are you going to to tell her,
huh? What are you going to tell her?
You think that she's going to get
over something like this?
Do you think that?
You've scarred her,
you piece of shit.
You've scarred our little girl.
Forever.
You've fucking broke me!
You've broke me!
What kind of man does that?
What kind of a man?!
Get out of my house.
You coward.
I love those kids.
I love them.
Get out!
I know what you've done.
I know everything.
DCI Parry.
Morgan.
The Glynns.
Your affair.
You can't hurt me any more, Evan.
I fucking hate you.
Faith. I fucking hate you.
Hi, Cath.
OK?
Did you get Megan's letter?
Yeah.
And her picture. Did you?
She's very good. Mm-hm.
She doesn't get that from me.
No, she doesn't.
No.
How's Rhodri?
He's growing.
Half term next week, um...
...week after next...
...I'll bring them in.
No, Faith...
They want to, Evan, so...
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I miss you all so much.
Although I, er, don't miss all
the phone calls from my mother.
Mmm.
Do you still go to the gym?
Oh, when I can.
Work?
So-so, you know?
But you're managing OK?
Yeah, same as usual, really.
Well, more or less.
What's the matter, Faith?
Nothing's the matter, Evan.
What's the matter with you?
You don't have to be...
Just be quiet.
Just please...
How's Alys?
Halfway to Goth.
And you know that thing
that your mother does,
when she turns away,
and she pretends she can't hear you?
Yeah. She's got your genes,
Evan Howells, your genes.
Job for you.
Something for you
to look forward to.
Right.
No.
Gayle.
Yes, I've got the package.
No need to shout.
I'll drop it off tonight.
I'm at work.
Anya! Cerys.
How's business?
Well, Howells of Abercorran is never
going to make me a millionaire,
so let's talk about this.
Client owns a hotel on the coast,
wants to treble it in size,
and turn it into a spa resort.
Am I speaking with you now,
or the firm?
Strictly personal. Just you and me.
How much are they looking for?
Three-point-two.
I'd need a cast-iron business case
to sell a loan that size to
Head Office.
Trust me. I wrote it.
These profit projections...
Blue tab. I've explained
everything to the last penny.
Our fee comes from the architect
and project management lines.
25k. Each.
Lunch is on you.
Yes, Marion,
of course I'm happy to talk.
Yes, well, maybe on the weekend.
But, in all honestly, I'm not
looking to sell the house.
No.
OK, well, speak later.
I have to go now.
Yep. OK, we'll try to get them.
I'll call you back.
What's happening? Stay behind
the line, please. What's happened?
I need you to stay back.
Have you made an arrest?
No arrest has been made.
I represent this family...
Madlen, please.
This is not the time.
Susan?
What's going on?
A body.
Male.
Oh, God. Not Will Vaughan, is it?
Drowned?
Well, what?
We're not sure yet.
Sus...
Sorry, sir, this is a crime scene...
I just need to confirm one thing.
The body, possible client of mine.
I'm the local solicitor,
as you probably know.
Delyth, please, please tell me
that we've got a different judge.
Please...
Madlen?
Oh, Madlen From Ty Melin?
Oh!
Will Vaughan?
Oh, for God's sake. In Abercorran?
He's been murdered?
Yeah, of course.
Murder?!
Aaahh!
Susan.
Mrs Howells.
I'm here for Madlen.
Would you like to come through?
Mm-hm.
Is she OK?
Hey!
William Vaughan,
shot in the chest!
I'm afraid this
is all we have at present.
Shot?
There must be some sort of mistake.
I mean, I know, Madlen. Our children
are in the same year, this is...
She is the last person who would
do something like this, it's...
So often the way. Uh, Mrs Howells?
Detective Inspector Breeze.
Swansea CID.
Though, technically, on secondment
from Scotland Yard.
We've met.
Still here?
London too peaceful for you?
You can have ten minutes.
Thank you.
Madlen? What's happened?
I need to tell Dyfan, he'll be
home from school soon. OK.
All right. What about his
Auntie Hannah?
Yeah, can you phone her? Yeah.
Um...
He's got swimming this afternoon.
OK, I can call her.
Oh, God...
OK, come here. Come here.
It's all right.
All right. Listen, you're going
to have to tell me what's happened.
They can't charge you
without evidence.
They have to have something concrete
to link you
to what happened to Will.
Do you understand that?
Do you understand that, Madlen?
Is there anything I need to know?
You have to tell me.
Right. I will make sure
that Dyfan is fine.
And, I will be back first thing.
What's going on?
Who would do this?
We'll find out.
Do you think Dyfan's safe?
Yes.
I understand he was having
a lot of financial trouble.
Maybe he owed people?
I hope that what happened between us
in the past is all forgotten now...
We've both had a price to pay.
Hi. Uh, it's fine, I'm here.
I'll wait for him.
Yeah.
OK.
Bye, Hannah.
Dyfan? Hey, Dyfan.
Hey.
Hi! Hi, Dyfan.
Um... Hiya.
I'm Megan's mum, Megan Howells.
Your auntie, she's...
She's coming in a minute.
I need you to just,
just to wait with me.
Where's Mam? Your mam...
She's... She's in the town,
and she's helping the police.,
and I'm helping her, so just come
and wait with me in the car...
OK, good boy. No, no!
Dyfan!
Shit!
Hey. Hey, what are you...?
No, you can't come...!
Faith? Yeah?
I've just had Saran James in...
...sounding off at me
about a blackmail threat.
She says you're representing
Gael Reardon.
Oh, look,
the line is really bad, Tom.
I'm going to have to phone
you later. OK? Bye-bye.
Faith?
Faith?!
Gael.
The package is on your desk.
That's it. I'm done. I'm out.
Not till I say.
When Evan and the others
went to trial
it was me who made sure that the
police stayed away from you, Gael.
That was nearly 18 months ago.
I think we're pretty square now.
Well, 120 grand.
That's a big debt.
You know, just running a few errands
doesn't begin to cover it.
What is it you want?
What's your endgame here?
I understand that, um,
your firm acts for Corran Energy?
Yes.
They're in trouble.
Now you get me the right deal,
and... we'll call it quits.
They employ a lot of people
round here with families.
So... help me save them.
That morning I...
I wasn't thinking straight.
DCI Parry phoned before... before
you woke up.
I know all this, Evan.
He's told me everything.
He was coming to arrest you.
You have no idea, Evan.
The woman you left is not the woman
sitting in front of you now.
Mark my words.
And I've dealt with Parry.
So, carry on.
Dealt with him how?
I'm asking the fucking
questions here!
Me!
I jumped.
Off the harbour wall in Port Talbot.
And I swam out.
I wanted the sea to take me...
...but the tide washed me back in.
You left us.
I remember getting on a train
and then there's...
...blank.
Days of it.
I remember wandering at night.
And I remember a hospital
waiting room,
and it being warm.
And I heard Alys's voice.
It was a video on someone's phone.
I love you, Faith.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry? You and Steve Baldini.
You were in his arms. Well, he's
been looking out for us, Evan.
He's the only one
who has done that, actually,
because he thinks and he cares.
And he knows what it means to care.
Are you and him...?
Is that what you think of me?
You go and get your stuff.
My God!
You jumped?
You wanted to drown yourself.
You tell me why you took
the money from the Glynns.
We needed it. The company needed it.
It was going under.
But you didn't tell me any of this.
I tried to. No, you didn't.
You wouldn't listen.
Do you know what this is?
This is about bastard pride.
That's what this is about.
I faced reality, Faith,
and you avoided it.
Alys?
Alys, why aren't you at home?
Alys?!
Arthur know where you are?
Ah, you haven't told him.
I see. This is great. Why not?
Who's this?
Hiya, we haven't met.
Angie.
Angie. Hi, Angie.
Your parents,
any idea where you are?
There's my dad. Sorry, can't hear
you. What? There's my dad now.
Your dad? Good.
I don't think it was meant
to happen like this. No.
Faith.
Steve.
Been a while.
Mm-hm.
You OK?
Oh, Faith, look after yourself.
Angie.
See you.
♪ If I could hold you
♪ If only for a second
I could hold you... ♪
Come on, please.
♪ ..Cling to each other
in the eye of a storm
♪ Eye of a storm
♪ If I could reach... ♪
Come on.
♪ ..If only for a second
I could reach you
♪ And let it all go to hell
♪ Hold on together
till we go there, as well
♪ Go there, as well
♪ Cos I know I
♪ Could never be what you need
♪ Never see what you see
♪ Never be anything more... ♪
Where's Angie come from, then?
Tenby. Ohh.
Her mam's just had a baby.
She couldn't stand it
so came to live with her dad.
Oh, dear.
She knows about us, Mam.
What do you mean, "Knows about us"?
How Dad... was a drug dealer.
Daddy's not a drug dealer, Alys.
He made a mistake.
I've told you this.
Some people let him down.
Your dad would never hurt anybody.
It was just a business thing. Yeah.
And Steve's just a friend?
Exactly.
Sorry I'm late.
Oh, hello. Hi.
You were too late to make pizzas.
Sorry, darling.
Mammy's sorry, OK?
Er... tomorrow, I promise.
OK?
Is it true, Dyfan's dad's dead?
Who told you that, darling?
I heard Gwen's mam say.
Well, um...
It's very, very sad.
And we're going
to look out for Dyfan.
That's what we're going to do.
OK?
Good girl.
I just popped in
to say hello to the kids.
Rhodri been eating chocolate again?
How many times, Tom?
It's not going to
spoil his appetite, is it? Look.
I did tell him, babes.
Forgot about Alys, did you? Nope.
She was by the swings.
My phone tracks her
to the last yard.
See, everything is under control!
Look at us, it's a team effort!
Did you get my things
from the art shop, Mam?
I've had the most fantastic idea.
This is, uh, thank you very much.
This...
Shells.
You've got a big bag of them,
haven't you?
We could cut up an old box,
paint it,
make a collage.
Eco-friendly,
and won't cost a penny.
OK. OK!
Right. Alys, Meg, dinner's ready.
Come on.
Go on.
Go. Go and see what
delicious treats he's got.
Quick word, Faith?
I've got a table booked soon. OK.
Going anywhere nice?
Hmm? Gael Reardon.
She asked me to convey an offer.
That's all I did.
For a fee? For a fee.
You know the history there, Tom.
You blame Evan, not me.
You kept this quiet.
Something of a firm tradition
then, isn't it?
I'll get rid of her. You have to.
She wants to buy Corran Energy.
And, if I negotiate
the right price...
...she's prepared
to put an end to it.
And, seeing as we'll never
see that 32 grand again,
unless someone does takes them over,
I think it might be
in our best interests.
All right. All right.
I'm prepared to make soundings.
But you're not to defend
Madlen Vaughan. Oh!
You being serious? Yes.
Are you? I'm very serious.
Tom, that's a very serious face!
Stop it.
Really? Yeah.
Tom! Mm-hm.
This is a murder case.
And... are you being serious?
Absolutely.
For one of our oldest clients,
Tom, it's...
William Vaughan was our client,
Faith.
Yeah. If we defend his murderer,
we'll be shunned.
Alleged murderer.
We'll be shunned.
Innocent until proven guilty, Tom.
Do you remember that?
God, nobody knows what that poor
girl is going through more than me.
Nobody! Oh, come on, Faith.
You've never done a murder case.
Well, then let this be the first.
They've picked on the... Well, on
the easiest suspect, haven't they?
Oh, what?! And they've decided
that she's guilty,
and they're doing what they always
do... Listen to yourself!
They just go after the evidence
that fits their theory.
You're already too invested.
She's innocent.
You'd be a danger to her.
Well, that's harsh.
That's, um...
We'd all rather life were just...
Mm-hm.
Sorry about the chocolate.
Right then, sausages. Bye-bye.
And bye-bye to you.
Bye-bye. Right, bye, guys.
Babes, I've got to dash. All right?
Tom, he's giving me a lift.
OK. Love you. Love you. Bye, guys!
Bye, Rhods! Thank you.
Eat up please, Alys.
Stop playing with it.
Slipped her the invite
just before you got home.
Smooth as velvet, he was.
Yup.
Oh, dear God, no. Uh-huh.
Oh, no.
Oh, dear God, no.
And the five little monkeys
all came home together,
and they all snuggled up together
in their little monkey nest.
And one of the five
little monkeys had fluffed.
And they all went to sleep,
happily... ever... wafter.
What did you think?
Did you like that?
Maybe a seven.
A seven? Megan Howells,
it's at least an eight!
Come on, then.
Shall we go up to bed.
Megs?
I miss Daddy while he's in prison.
I know, darling.
And he misses you very much, too.
You've got your milk,
oop-a-pah.
Saran.
Tom said you came to the office.
Uh, I just...
I just wanted to reassure that
your visit from Mrs Reardon had
nothing to do with me or my firm.
And, in any event, I apologise.
You go on to the dentist.
I'll follow you there. OK.
As for the police, their
involvement won't be necessary.
Mrs Reardon won't be
troubling you any further.
This all goes back to Evan,
doesn't it?
Look, Faith, I've only
one thing to say to you,
as a friend...
...leave.
Do it.
Get out and find your own life...
...before you drown with him.
Hi.
Sorry. We've, um... had
some forensics back.
It's not looking good for her,
I'm afraid.
Er...
Look, Susan,
I may not be staying long.
Um...
My partners, they think that
she may benefit
from lawyers more used
to this sort of stuff.
Oh, I see.
Well, if it helps, I suppose you'll
be looking for a guilty plea.
Your fingerprints were found
on the gun, the cabinet and the key.
I locked it in there.
When? When I fetched the Ranger
back from the field.
When I went down there, it was
on the grass, next to the trailer.
You didn't mention this yesterday.
Did you pick it up, Madlen?
I took it back to the house
in the Ranger.
And you just left
the trailer in the field?
The ground was wet.
The wheels were spinning.
Let's talk about the arguments,
Mrs Vaughan. Were they about money?
I tried to keep things nice
for Dyfan.
But... But Will, he'd snap a bit,
and go into himself.
Great, we'll get Dyfan in.
Get him to verify it.
Dyfan? It's got nothing to do
with him. I'll go with them.
He's a potential defence witness.
I've every right to be there.
Faith? Yes.
I've contacted a firm in Cardiff.
They're sending someone to see
Madlen Vaughan this afternoon.
Now, you have told her
you're withdrawing, haven't you?
Look, I'll phone you back, OK?
To be clear, I'm allowing
you to observe, Mrs Howells,
not to intervene.
Hi, Dyfan.
Mammy sends her love.
You'll see her very soon.
Now, she wants you
to answer this man's questions
as best as you can, all right?
But only tell him
what you can remember.
I'll be right here.
That's enough, thank you.
Right here.
Hello, Dyfan.
My name's Laurence.
It's nice to meet you.
Corran Energy owes
Howells Abercorran £32,000.
We're going to have to call it in.
We may need a little longer.
We've been approached by a party
interested in buying the business.
They've asked for your price.
So, what happened
when you couldn't find your dad?
Mam kept calling,
but he didn't answer.
Did you see your mum pick up a gun?
What did she do with it?
Put it in the Ranger.
Oh, the Ranger?
Was it this one?
I think he's had enough for one day.
Yeah, and I've nearly finished.
How far away from the river
was the Ranger when you found it?
Was it near or was it far?
Dyfan?
85 steps.
Dyfan likes to count things,
don't you, love?
So you went down to the river?
Mam, she called me back.
Did your mum go down to the river?
Why didn't you go down to the river,
Mrs Vaughan?
Why didn't you go down to the river?
Take your time, Madlen. It's OK.
I was scared.
What were you scared of, Madlen?
That I'd find him
hanging from a tree.
Madlen Vaughan, I am charging you
with the murder of your husband,
William Andras Vaughan. You can't
charge her. You cannot charge her!
This interview is terminated
at 16.08... You've no evidence!
Listen to me! We'll see you
in court tomorrow morning.
That's enough, Mrs Howells.
No! Calm down!
You're all... You're bastards!
What is wrong with you people?!
What is wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
No, I'm not the police.
I'm a defence lawyer,
defending a murder case,
and I require access
to your network's location data.
Yeah, well, can you...?
Thank you.
Can you give me the number, please?
OK, just a second,
I'm going to write this down.
As in...
Yeah, just a little bit slower
this time.
OK.
Yeah, that's great, thank you.
That's a great help.
Thank you very much.
Faith, you promised.
We had an agreement.
Yeah, well, she's innocent, Tom.
Well, at least I've kept
my side of the bargain.
I got a figure out of Corran Energy.
Are you going to tell me? Yeah.
You've got to step away, Faith.
She trusts me, Cerys.
Look, Faith.
You've got three children,
you've got a mortgage to pay
and a husband in prison.
She's innocent.
She's innocent. Christ's sakes!
Wake up!
We're meant to be a team.
Partners building a business,
making decent money.
What happened, Faith?
I feel like
we've lost you somewhere.
71, 72, 73, 74,
75, 76, 77, 78,
79, 80,
81, 82, 83, 84,
85, 86.
Gael.
I've got a figure from Corran.
It's six.
Six mil.
Tell them it's not
even in the right ballpark, Faith.
Yeah, they'll be lucky to get two.
Hi, mam!
Hello! I smell pizza!
Oh, Mam's here! Sorry about
the mess. Weren't expecting you.
Hiya! Hello!
Hey, don't mind me, Babes.
I'm just here for the freebies,
isn't that right?
Get that inside of you.
Thank you!
And I need a word with you later.
More importantly...
...what did Miss Gwynn
think of your collage?
Oh, she only put it
up on the wall, Mam!
She didn't put it on the wall? She
put it on the wall, I'm telling you!
She put your collage on the wall?!
You're brilliant, you are!
You're absolutely brilliant,
do you know that?!
Right. Let Mammy have a go at this.
This looks fun.
Can I have a go?
Oh, come on, then.
Let's see what
you're made of. There we are.
Oh, no, no.
She's going to be rubbish at that.
What do you mean, I'm going to be
rubbish?! We haven't got a dog, Lis.
What? That's a dog's pizza,
isn't it? Garlic bread!
That's my spicy surprise.
It's a spicy something.
I don't think
you've got enough balls on it.
Sorry, it's the best we can do.
Sorry.
When can I see my son?
Oh, we'll see what happens in court.
Can't I phone him?
Well, it's not permitted.
Please.
Right.
Five minutes. Speak quietly.
Thanks.
Mrs Howells, she's a good lawyer,
isn't she?
Yeah, yeah, she is.
Yeah, I'll tell him.
No Tom tonight?
It was just a meal.
And a little bit of footsie
and back to the boat?
Babe! He's old enough to be my dad.
Now stop it.
Wouldn't be the first time.
Who?! Well, it wouldn't
be the first time, would it?
Do you remember... Oh, Edwin?
Oh! "Hello, my name is Edwin.
"Nice to meet you. This is my dog."
Please, stop! Why did he take
his dog everywhere with him?
Don't talk about Edwin!
It's embarrassing. I was drunk,
and I was... I was really,
really desperate.
You were thinking
"Oh, I'm hungry" at the time.
Can I have some of that please?
Mm. I'm not... Oh!
Right, careful now. Oh...!
Oh, oh, nice.
It's a nice one this, isn't it?
Talking about being desperate.
You're not really going to wait for
him, are you? I mean, seriously?
Two years?
Look at you babe,
you're in your prime.
They'd be queuing round
the block for you.
Lisa, stop it. Well, they would!
Please, Lis.
It doesn't interest me.
Right, enjoy.
Won't be long. OK.
I should never have come home.
I should have gone
straight to the police.
Then both us
of would have got arrested.
Steve Baldini shifted the drugs
you ordered from Gael Reardon...
...to pay off the Glynns
and the firm's debts.
I made a deal with Parry, which just
leaves Gael Reardon out of the deal.
I'll sort it.
What did you expect me to do, Evan?
See us all turfed out on the street?
Now I've just dug you out of
a very, very, very big hole.
Now you need to decide
what you want to do.
You have three children upstairs.
Alys...
...Megan...
...and Rhodri.
I want to look after you all.
I want to start again.
I want to show you who I am.
Who are you, then?
Who are you?
We've established that
you're a really shit lawyer.
I just want us to be happy.
I've decided to hand
myself in to the police.
So, what's stopping you?
Look at me.
I'm still here.
And I am,
for the sake of our children,
for what's most precious to us,
Evan.
Will you forgive me, Faith?
It's morning.
I'll go make the packed lunches.
You make the breakfast.
Stop whimpering like a little child.
Wakey, wakey.
Ma'am, Mrs Vaughan is charged
with the murder of her husband,
William Vaughan.
We ask that the matter's transferred
directly to the Crown Court.
We don't envisage
any application for bail.
Ma'am, I appear
on behalf of Mrs Vaughan.
While we make no application
for bail this morning,
we will certainly do so if the Crown
proceeds in anything less
than a timely fashion.
Mrs Vaughan is a single mother
and now the sole proprietor
of a farm.
Faith, why aren't you helping me?
Faith, please!
The evidence against her
is circumstantial at best.
Justice will not be served by a long
period awaiting trial.
♪ If I could hold you
♪ If only for a second
I could hold you
♪ And let the fear rage on
♪ Cling to each other
in the eye of a storm
♪ Eye of a storm
♪ If I could reach you
♪ If only for a second
I could reach you
♪ And let it all go to hell
♪ Hold on together till
we go there, as well
♪ Cos I know I could never
♪ Be what you need
♪ Never see what you see
♪ Never be
♪ Anything more than just
somewhere to run to
♪ When you're scared to come to... ♪
Mr Howells, I give you credit
for offering yourself
as a police informant and for giving
evidence for the Crown in this case.
Nevertheless, you've committed
a serious offence
and abused your position
of trust as a solicitor.
For the offence of
converting criminal property,
namely the sum of £250,000
acquired on
behalf of Mr Dewi Glynn, you will go
to prison for four years.
♪ ..Light up the sky,
let them see who you are
♪ Cos I know I could never
♪ Be what you need
♪ Never see what you see
♪ Never be
♪ Anything more than
♪ Just somewhere to run to
♪ When you're scared to come to
♪ I'll be there
♪ Someone who knows
♪ I won't be anything
I won't be anything
♪ I won't be anything, no
♪ I won't be anything, no. ♪