Hey, I forgot my ID.
Could you hook me
up with some beer?
Get out of here, kid.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Oh.
Were y'all using these?
My bad. Listen, I think
we need to have a talk
about civic responsibilities.
What do you think you're doing?
Turning ourselves in
for armed robbery.
And after serving our sentences,
we're going to devote our
lives to community service.
Improved By M_I_S
www.opensubtitles.org
What is that sound?
I'm humming.
A song.
Are you unwell?
Quite the opposite. Everything
is right in the world.
Lizzie and I are friends again,
Landon's back, and I haven't
seen any new monsters,
which means the defensive
perimeter I spelled around
the school is working.
Today is going to be a good day.
I hope. Morning, Cleo.
Morning. I got tea.
See? Scones. Hi.
Uh, um...
Are you feeling okay?
Why does everybody
keep asking me that?
Yeah, um, uh, you didn't happen
to see any slugs
crawling around, did you?
No. No?
What is it with you guys?
Can't a girl just be happy?
Of course you can. It's
just, um... it's just, um...
Unexpected. It's unexpected.
No. Nope. Nothing is putting
me in a bad mood today because
today is the day
that I figure out
the one thing we have
left to worry about...
Why the monsters
are still coming.
How are we gonna
figure that out?
Well, you are gonna help
Dr. Saltzman with research
while Cleo and I are going to
get some quality roomie time.
Lizzie.
What are you doing
here? You scared me.
You forgot your sweater.
I thought you might need
it after the ice-cold way
that you violated twin code.
Oh, here we go. You have
a crush, and you told
our father before telling me.
'Cause it's already over.
I made things weird and
I can't un-weird them.
That's because, sweetie...
And I love you...
But you have zero game.
What you do have,
however, is a sister
with magical powers and
an encyclopedic knowledge
of every rom-com ever.
I'm here to help.
No, Lizzie. I beg
of you, please,
let me fix this on my own.
Finch is a completely
normal human.
I want to fix this the
regular way, without magic.
Just promise me.
Lizzie.
So great to see you.
What's up? We have
a monster problem?
Oh, it is way worse,
Mr. Williams. We have
an angsty, teenage, high school,
impossible crush problem.
Right, right, that, uh...
that-that is worse, and, um
thankfully,not my department.
So best of luck to you both.
That's actually totally okay,
'cause Lizzie was just leaving.
Everything alone. Mm.
Right, Lizzie? Perfect. Awesome.
Love you. Uh...
Invisique.
Well, well, well.
Heard you might've
had a late night
doing totally normal,
completely unheroic things.
Um... keep it down, E.
What are we doing
next? Any leads?
Um...
I was thinking we
could just lay low.
But yesterday was awesome.
I want to do it again.
And this way
you won't have to compel
people all the time.
You can keep your
identity a secret.
You'll look...Blur-some.
Mm-hmm.
First of all,
do not ever say that terrible
superhero name to me ever again.
Second, we just got
lucky last night.
Mystic Falls barely has
one robbery a decade.
Yeah, that we know about.
My mom's old police scanner.
I figure, if I'm
your human sidekick,
the least I can do is
help you find our next case.
Do you want to skip P.E.
and bring down Mystic
Falls' vast underworld
of petty criminals?
Or am I the only one
that had fun yesterday?
Yeah, you're right.
Thanks.
So... you're back.
Yeah. All that drama at my
old school is completely done.
I'm just focusing on the now.
Making myself open
and available to anything
or, you know, whatever.
Does that whatever include
staying on campus for lunch?
I'd love that.
I'll be there. Here.
For lunch. Yeah.
Then maybe I'll see you.
Yeah, cool.
I totally get it. She's hot.
Lizzie?
I told you that
you needed my help.
Stop it.
You knocked away my books?
It's called a "meet-cute," my
young Padawan, rom-com 101.
And step one is now
officially complete.
Well, what's step number two?
Don't look so worried, and
I'll be happy to tell you.
Stand up straight. Chin up.
There. Much better.
You're gonna get
the girl for sure.
This is so cool.
You said Rasputin,
Napoleon and Einstein
all held this thing?
And Queen Elizabeth I.
What? How far back does this go?
That's what we have to find out.
Monsters started appearing
after Hope opened it,
so my theory
is,they're connected.
But first we just
have to figure out
where it originated.
Um, Dr. Saltzman, not
that I'm not thrilled
to be on Team Library. I
am... it's nice to be useful,
especially since I can't even
be monster bait anymore...
But it kind of feels like
a vampire would be able
to look through these
books a lot faster than me.
Maybe I just like your company.
Mm-hmm.
So why the crossbow?
Okay.
Hope asked me to
keep an eye on you
and make sure you're safe
while she's testing out
her new theory.
What theory?
This was your great idea?
Consider it a brainstorming
session... with brie.
I must say,you
seem rather relaxed
about our lives being in danger.
Perhaps if you had been the one
at the bottom of that well...
Actually, that was sort of what
I wanted to talk to you about.
We've been assuming
that the gremlin
just happened to grab you,
but what if it wasn't random?
What if you're what
Malivore wants?
Why would he want me? No clue.
Next step would be
testing my theory.
Hmm, and how would we test that?
Well, first we'd have
to use you as bait
to see if it would happen again,
if you're willing, that is.
But don't worry, I'd be there
to keep you safe the whole time.
We'd just have to lower
the perimeter spells
and pretend like we're
having a good time.
You know, sort of like...
What we are doing right now.
Don't be mad, we
can totally stop.
I just figured you might
need a little bit of a push.
And if we can get
a talking monster,
we might actually
get some answers.
What do you say?
You lead me into very strange
situations, Hope Mikaelson.
Fine. But why a picnic?
I mean, I figured if one of
us is gonna be used as bait,
we might as well enjoy it.
Besides, not all the
monsters are that bad.
One of them was even
sort of... whimsical.
That didn't take long.
Here.
This one doesn't
feel very whimsical.
It might not be as
bad as it seems.
Probably as bad as it seems.
Corrupan vinea.
Foolish girls.
Oo ni le soro.
Good thing you were
here to keep me safe.
At least we know the monsters
are definitely after you.
Now we just have
to find out why.
What's with the lights?
She's a walking horror
movie. That's awesome.
What is she?
Besides some creepy chick
putting a damper on my
positivity, no clue.
Either way, I owe
Gaby some money.
I had a wendigo in
the monster pool.
Rookie mistake.
It's never a wendigo.
But we still should be
able to get answers.
She talks, right?
Not exactly.
I recommend covering your ears.
Dr. S, I think, I think she's...
A banshee.
Okay, well,how do we get answers
out of a banshee without
our brains melting?
Don't know.
Until we figure that out,
she's not going anywhere.
Well, we have all the
time in the world, right?
I'm sure you're wondering
what happens next.
"Step two" You need to sneak
out of a bad party together.
I call this the "You want
to get out of here?" moment.
That's really specific.
Step three. We
can skip this one.
It involves a missing pet
or some sort of non-life-
threatening emergency.
But step four, this is where
the real fireworks happen.
The spontaneous life highlight.
I'm talking night swimming. I'm
talking impromptu road trip.
I'm talking...
Moonlit dance in the parking lot
during an actual school dance.
I thought you said this
wasn't your department.
They're painting my office.
At least someone gets it.
If we can just get to
step four, it's automatic.
She will have no choice
but to fall for you.
Well, I don't want
to manipulate Finch.
I want her to actually like me.
Never gonna happen.
Why not?
'Cause that would require you
to actually shoot your shot.
Well, then, I'll ask
her out on a real date.
Tonight.
"Alternate step two"
Extroverted sister provokes
introverted sister out
of her comfort zone.
Our little secret.
It's good.
Do werewolves just
work out anywhere?
No.
I just came up here 'cause
the gym was occupied by
whatever that thing is.
She is a banshee,or
so I am told.
Well, I just lost 20 bucks.
Totally had wendigo.
Apparently, it's
never a wendigo.
I wouldn't know.
I've been relegated
to the Junior Squad
ever since I... Hurt MG?
I heard. Yeah. Everyone has.
I keep thinking I'll find a
way to make it up to all them.
And you will.
Why are you up here?
I am supposed to be researching
how to allow the
banshee to speak
without using her mouth, but...
I just found out that
the monsters are coming
here because of me.
I needed a moment
to process that.
Because if you can't
get the monster to talk,
you can't figure out
why they... want you.
Are you all right?
Something just came over me.
I think I know how we can
solve both our problems
at the same time.
All the good stuff must
happen at night, right?
You know what this
mission needs? Snacks.
Every stakeout involves
cheap snacks and coffee.
Ethan...
I dig the enthusiasm.
I really do.
But, you know, we
can just hang out
without it having
to be a mission.
Except now I know that
superhuman vampires exist.
It's pretty hard to go back
to normal life after that.
I mean, think about
it. If you exist,
then what else is out there?
Maybe there's an
evil version of you.
A superpowered bad guy
just waiting to attack
and your destinies are
bound to intersect,
so whenever
he or she shows up,
we have to be ready.
Well, until they do...
I'm gonna head to class.
Cool. I'll just, uh, let
you know if I hear anything.
Are you sure you don't
want to come with? Yeah.
After everything else that's
happened this year, it's
it's just nice to have
something to care about.
You know?
Okay, so what kind of,
uh, stakeout snacks
are we talking about here?
I know that look.
Why don't you just
tell me what's wrong?
Because you're in a good mood.
Let me guess. A banshee
can only be stopped
with a certain enchanted
blah, blah, blah
from the mountains
of blah, blah, blah.
Look, we always find a
way to stop the monster.
I'm sure I can handle it.
According to Irish mythology,
the banshee is a harbinger.
Whenever they appear,
death is not far behind.
Okay, that just means
that death could be coming
for anybody in Mystic Falls.
And when has that
ever been our luck?
Hope, we have to
prepare ourselves
for the very real possibility
that she may say something to us
we don't want to hear.
Dr. Saltzman?
Cleo and I know how to
get this monster to talk.
Here's the spell. Alias Vocem.
It allows one to speak
through another as a conduit,
without being able to
burst our eardrums.
It's brilliant.
You thought of this?
Yeah, I know, right?
Oh, but I know what's
missing! Wait, wait.
You all right?
Ask me in a few moments.
Hope, we're ready.
I found it. Blue Calamus.
Josie told me it's
basically a truth weed.
If we give it to Jed, the
banshee can't lie to us.
Well done, Team Library.
There's not much time
till the full moon.
When Jed turns, we don't
want a monster in his head.
Yeah.
Well, now we just need
something of hers.
Vauntidictus calimus vox.
Ah.
Clever girl.
Trapping my voice in a body
that cannot scream.
Or lie.
Now we can have a
civilized conversation.
Are you sure you want to
hear what I have to say?
Why are you here?
Malivore promised me
freedom from the darkness
in exchange for
bringing him that girl.
And why does he want her?
You are forcing me
to tell the truth,
but that does not
mean I have to answer.
This is not the question
that troubles you.
Go on, little girl.
Ask what you really
wish to know.
Who's gonna die?
There are many possible roads.
But one is clearer
than the others.
If she stays here
he dies.
Wow, tea twice in one day.
Hope, can we talk about...
There's no need to.
It's not happening.
No one's dying today.
The banshee does not agree.
I know you're new here, but
there's always a loophole, okay?
It's basically our school
motto. We'll find it.
Mm. If you are so
confidant, then why did you
spell Landon into his room?
I think it is time
that we talked.
You made it.
You guys, this is Josie...
I know that there's been
weird energy between us
since the first
moment I saw you.
And then things got weirder
when I bailed on you.
But it's not because I'm
not into you, because I am
into you, I'm just cautious,
because I usually mess
things like this up
and I really don't
want to mess this up.
And you're hot, okay?
And worse, you're also really
cool, and that's scary,
because I think that if we
became a thing, it would be
a thing.
But I like you. I like you
in a way that I haven't
liked somebody in
a really long time.
So I think that we
should give this a shot.
So, do you, maybe,
want to hang out
tonight?
I...
can't tonight.
Got plans.
Uh, yeah. That's
totally understandable.
Um, short notice.
Uh, tomorrow night, then, maybe?
Tomorrow might be bad, too.
Sorry.
For a long time, I searched for
a place like this.
A place to call home.
But I cannot be the reason that
trouble comes into your lives.
Which is why I need to
go. You don't have to.
The monsters are always
coming after someone.
We've never made anyone
leave because of it.
But is that what you want?
Be honest.
Would you be happier
if I left? Yes.
I didn't mean that. You did.
Because truth weed can
also be used to make tea.
No.
She said she had plans,
which didn't even involve
coming up with a good excuse.
Obviously just means that...
She's seeing someone else.
You were right.
I waited too long.
Or we're just in a slightly
different rom-com now,
the "steal her back from less
worthy competition" story.
Don't worry, it's
a total classic,
and there's usually a really
great music moment, so...
Lizzie.
I know.
You wanted to do this
the "natural way."
Actually, I kind of just
want to know who she's seeing
and if it's serious.
So you mean, like, if
someone could do some magic?
Invisible spying?
Go home. I'll find
out how serious it is.
I think I know how
I can help you.
Legend says
that a banshee is a demon
drawn to inconsolable grief.
That they seek out women
who've died of a broken heart
and possess them.
The person that you once
were is still in there.
You are not this thing.
Tell us why he wants Cleo,
and we will find a way
to set you free.
It's no use trying to talk
to the human woman.
She won't believe you.
After her child was taken,
no one could tell her
what happened to it.
No one could heal the
hole in her heart.
She was abandoned by everyone...
Her village, her husband.
They couldn't stand
to hear her cries.
They fled from her grief.
That's when I found her.
She knows you will be no
different than anyone else.
Humans run from
grief like a sickness
afraid that it will spread,
that they will catch it.
Oh, it is their nature.
I'm not like everyone else.
But you are out of time.
The full moon rises,
and this body is about to turn.
I've never felt such strength.
Cleo left.
I tried to stop her,
but she wouldn't listen.
What's going on?
We need to unlink Jed
from the banshee
before he turns.
Pondas.
Hope, what's wrong?
I just need to know.
Now that Cleo's
gone, is Landon safe?
No.
Don't listen to her. I am bound
to tell the truth, remember?
I was not sent to capture Cleo.
I was sent to drive her
away from your protection.
One road darkens, the
other grows clearer.
Cleo dies, too.
Where you going?
Cleo cloaked herself
from my locator spell,
so I'm gonna have to find
her the old-fashioned way.
And before you try to stop me,
I just wanted to say
that I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that it apparently
always has to be
this way for us.
We can never just be happy.
But I can't let her die
when I'm the one
that sent her away.
I know.
I think you'll want
these when you find her.
A bag of clothes?
You don't need a locator spell.
You're a wolf.
Hold on, we're almost there!
Dr. Saltzman
when she was inside my head,
making me do things...
All right, let's just worry
about you right now, okay, Jed?
I think I saw something.
A memory. I-I think
I know her name.
Nearby units, 10-33.
Possible alarm trip
at Mystic Falls High.
Uh, copy that.
Probably a false alarm.
Happens about once a month.
It's go time. Hey,
hold on, hold on.
You heard them.
They said it's
probably a false alarm.
Or it's what I've
been talking about.
Another powerful creature.
I've seen my mom's files.
Our high school has
a weird history of
unexplained events.
Then I'll go.
I'm sorry, but you
said it yourself.
You're just a human sidekick.
Who's there?
I can smell you.
Invisique saeclum.
I-I'm sorry.
I didn't know that you were
a werewolf. I thought...
Who are you? Uh,
it's complicated.
You came here to
turn. I'll help you.
No. Run!
Please tell me Dorian
has at least one
magical object in this...
Very funny.
Lizzie?
What the hell are
you doing here?
I was able to lure it away.
Werewolves are always
gonna chase vampires first.
You have to get out of here.
We're getting out of here.
You take the back exit.
I'll lure it out the front.
MG, I...
Go.
I know your instincts
are telling you to
bite me right now,
but you can fight it.
We don't have to
hurt each other.
Not bad for a sidekick, huh?
I know who you were
before you died.
Kaelan.
My Old Irish is a little rusty,
but this is from
the Clan Kinelarty.
From the year 1014.
Very good, but you're too late.
I know what happened
to your son!
What did you say?
Your son.
Drystan.
The one they took from you.
Don't listen to him. He's lying!
How old was he when
the English took him
from you to fight in their wars?
11? 12?
And you never knew
what happened to him.
No, don't listen! He survived.
He survived the battle.
Tell me!
There was a survey done
in England 50 years later
called the Domesday Book.
He's here.
Living in a small village.
Drystan... Kinelarty.
He lived a long time, too. Look.
Just below his name, he had...
Children.
Grandchildren.
One of them was named after you.
I'm so sorry.
I can only imagine if
somebody took my child
and I never knew what
happened to them.
They shouldn't have left
you to grieve like that.
No one should have to
grieve alone like that.
Thank you.
You can sleep now.
I know why Malivore wants Cleo.
You just gave me
a weapon, buddy.
Hope, thank you.
Like I said,
nobody's dying today.
Let's get you home.
I suppose it was a good thing
you were there to keep me safe.
After I put you in danger.
Look, what I said before.
It was true that was how I felt,
but it's not the whole truth.
I know I've been distracted
and-and not in the best of
moods since you got here,
but that has nothing
to do with you.
Because the truth
is that you are
a kind and brilliant badass,
and I'm lucky to have
you as my friend.
As far as I'm concerned,
this is your home.
No matter what.
Even if it brings danger?
We're kind of used
to that around here.
And what of that creature?
It must be working for Malivore.
Our monster problem
is multiplying.
Why do you think it ran away?
I don't know, but
something about
it felt familiar.
Almost like I've
fought it before.
Werewolves.
Who knew, right?
I did kind of call it.
I mean, it was no
supervillain, but
that thing was pretty
scary either way.
I get why you wanted
me to stay behind.
I'd be dead if you had.
And then I never would've
saw this sweet hero base
you've been working on.
That's what sidekicks
are for, right?
Actually
you're not really
sidekick material, E.
But I'm gonna need
you to go ahead
and make another one
of those janky masks.
I have a feeling
you're gonna need it.
Partner.
I'm gonna need a superhero name.
Now I will handle the
hero names, all right?
Okay.
Uh, first things first, partner.
What are we gonna do about
her?
That bad, huh?
Finch is
seeing somebody else.
And it's really serious.
I'm afraid you'd just
get your heart broken.
That's okay.
You just saved me
months of spiraling.
But I should've let you
find out on your own.
I'm sorry.
I guess I just felt like
maybe you
didn't need me anymore.
Believe me,
I know the feeling.
Does twin code say anything
against cuddling after
one twin has moved out?
It's encouraged, actually.
So much for this
being a good day.
There's still another
monster out there,
and I'm gonna get
zero sleep worrying
that what the banshee
said is gonna come true.
All's well that ends well.
Easy for Shakespeare to say.
He's dead.
The rest of us actually
have to work to be positive.
Now I feel so much
pressure, you know?
Like I have to be
happy no matter what.
Like, I'm afraid that if...
The happiness went away,
it might never come back?
But it will. I promise.
We just have to find
the moments of happiness
between the monsters.
And screw fate, you know?
Screw fate.
Dr. Saltzman told
me what happened.
Your plan worked.
Seriously?
You underestimate yourself.
Because of you, the
banshee found peace.
And you have reclaimed
your rightful
place in the Squad.
Thanks for believing in me.
When you were inside her mind,
did you discover why
Malivore wants me?
Not right away.
It was kind of hazy.
I didn't understand
what it meant,
but now I think I get it.
Because I have literally
never had a genius
monster-hunting idea
until I was standing
next to you.
This part of the
job I did not miss.
To Kaelan.
And now
it's your turn with this thing.
Oh, you still don't know
where it came from, huh?
No, but today's still a win.
We know why
Malivore's after Cleo.
She's a Muse.
A Muse?
Like inspiration muse?
A witch who's the
seventh daughter
of a seventh daughter
has a special magical
power, the power
of inspiration.
Why does Malivore
need inspiration?
He has a problem
he needs to solve.
If I had to guess,
he's looking for a way
out of the prison world.
Captioning sponsored by
WARNER BROS. TELEVISION
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6x52e
Help other users to choose the best subtitles