My son was hired by
someone to kill your father.
You're saving his skin.
I'm telling the truth.
Fuck!
Whoever ordered
that hit is more dangerous
than the fella who
pulled the trigger.Fuck.
I'll be the judge
of that. Have I got
your word you'll
leave my son alone?
You have my word I won't
shoot you when you walk away.
I'm not giving you my son.
I'm not sorry. Open the fucking
door! I'm not the
one who should be.
- Head west...
- ..to Evie.
She'll have a boat waiting. Once
they get tired
of tracking him...
Watch over him, Mal, for me.
Of course.
15 north, east 30
over the brook, north 25.
And then we dig.
Big or small? What?
North 15 baby steps will put
you a fair fucking distance away
from north 15 daddy steps.
Daddy steps?
Fucking daddy steps?
It's in metres, you twat.
Fuck me, Darren.
What? What's the problem?
Did it have to be your initial?
Doesn't fucking matter,
we found it first.
The guy's a fucking paedo.
One shot and it'll
pay for everything.
We can get away...
from all of them.
Just us.
Load it.
Oi! Oi! Get away
from that window!
Please, Mal. I've been
stuck in here for days.
Can I not just get
some fresh air?
Just for a minute.
No, you can't.
You're staying here
until that boat arrives.
But you can't just
make me get on
a fucking boat.
I can and I will.
Now sit down.
That lad and his family
want you dead.
Every day you spend here, the
more they'll come
looking for you.
And your dad too.
You think I give two shits about
that cunt after
what he did to loan?
He wouldn't have
had any reason to do it,
would he, had you not
killed who you did? Huh?
Hey, this is big, Darren.
Way too big to fix.
A lot of us are hurting now
because of what you fucking did.
But I'm still here and you're
still alive. The
least you can do
is make sure that we don't
hurt any more than we have to.
Understand?
Is there really no WiFi? Are you
still bloody going
on about that?
There's no WiFi. There was
none last week, none yesterday
and there's none
today and there'll
be none tomorrow
when you ask again.
What about next
week? Well, the boat
will have come
and got you by then.
Thank God. Thank fuck. There's
fuck all to do here anyway.
He won't even let me
look out of the window.
Read a book, play the piano. Do
something other
than fucking mope.
Here, Mal, I need you to
go up to the inn at the top.
I've got supplies waiting and
the kids have got the wheels.
They're out selling my stock.
Your legs don't work, do they?
What? That hill?
These knees? Fucking suicide.
I'll go. The fuck you will.
You must've done
something awful, huh?
Can't even get my
bread and beans
without looking over your
shoulder. No,
it's fine. I'll go.
Just the bread and the beans, is
it? Frank'll have a box ready.
A box? Oh, great. Not heavy.
I promise.
How far is that pub again?
About a mile if you cut
through the woods
and up the ridge.
Don't worry.
I'll give you the cash for it.
Oh, thank you for that.
Argh!
Ugh! Argh!
Uugghh! Argh!
Ugh! Uugghh!
Baxter, come here!
Requesting F/R
support teams on all CCTV,
petrol stations,
transport routes, roads,
high streets, all surrounding
areas. Suspect code
Alpha-Foxtrot-Echo-7-3-8-4.
Edwards, Kinney.
Leif!
Hey! You've been told
not to come down here.
I swear,
if you've taken any bullets...
I haven't, I wouldn't. I
promise. Well, if you had,
you'd be hard pressed to
shoot fuck all with that.
That calibre won't fit inside
your starter pistol, boy.
Interesting piece of metal
you've got there.
Who gave it to you, eh?
Because, round your way,
I only know Mikey Cartwright
make a toy like that
capable of killing a man.
You know I can't tell you.
The same goes for anyone
who asks where I am now.
Good answer.
How much do you make with
all this? Enough not to worry.
Enough to keep this place going.
But still not enough to pay for
a fucking internet connection?
Cheeky bastard.
How do you even start
with something like this?
You make what you know.
When you see one
that close up, you...
Yeah.
So...
when are you planning on
telling me who you killed?
Frank?
Frank!
Service is... slow.
Is it?
Frank, you there? I'm coming!
Can I help you? Excuse me?
Your pint is going flat. Why
don't you fucking drink it?
Thank you. Sure.
For Baxter.
Christ, I haven't seen you in
years. What is it this time?
Evie sent me.
I hope you drove. I've got
a week of supplies for her.
You know old Evie likes a drink.
Can hardly blame her,
living up here.
You ever thought about doing
a door-to-door service?
There's only five doors
within five miles around here
and in 15 years you're
the first one to complain.
Fucking city boys.
Get fucked, would you?
Right, now you
tell her, I got no
luncheon meat for her this week
but I've thrown in
some extra beef paste.
Her Albert loves the stuff.
Lovely. Whatever. Yeah.
Aside from that, no changes
from what she asked for.
Well, other than the
two extra mouths to feed. Ha!
About that.
How long is he there? The boy?
Look, like I said, five doors,
five miles and 15 years.
We all help each other out with
whatever we need to get by.
And no questions
asked I thought.
You're a talkative fucker,
aren't you?! Oi!
Once Albert docks tonight, sure
to Christ, I'll be the bastard
helping him refuel that boat
for you ready for the morning.
A bit of respect
and trust wouldn't
go amiss, right? I'm sorry.
Look, um, if you want anything,
or if the lad needs anything...
All the lad wants
is his fucking WiFi.
Well, we got fuck all of that.
Are you lost?
Toilet? Right next to you.
Where it says toilet. Piss only.
Shitter's out of order.
Lucky me.
Lucky for both of us.
Here, cop hold of that.
Terrific. Yeah. Can you manage?
Argh!
Ugh! Uugghh!
Are you almost done? Almost.
Go on, love. Set the table.
OK.
Ugh! Uugghh!
Stay here.
I want nothing to do with you.
Just the jeep and your gun.
It's not a barter.
Cock the barrel open
and hand it to me.
Come on.
She full?
Two-thirds. She'll do a couple
of hundred before she stops.
It's more than I need. Dad?
Jules, stay there! Hey! Dad?
Please, don't.
I wasn't planning to. But I will
if you take another
fucking step.
Now I've got a way to go, so
tomorrow you can call the police
and report it stolen,
not a moment before.
You don't want me as an enemy.
Do you understand? Now go.
Be with your kin.
The number you have called
is unavailable. Fuck!
Please leave a message
after the tone.
Mal...
Shouldn't you be inside?
Mal he said that I could...
I won't tell him if you won't.
Are you not gonna fold them?
Albert and I have been in
creases since the day we met.
Our laziness is one of the
few things we have in common.
And the kids, of course.
Er, Albert and I, it's made
us, having them here.
They came to us
in different ways
but we love them all the same.
So, when's this boat arriving?
Before dark. What, today?
Well,
Albert won't want to set off
for at least another day or two.
And if Mal gets his arse in
gear with the food and drink,
we'll be able to have
a proper send off for you.
Can't I just stay? Can't you
just take me in like the others?
Ah, love. I can work.
I'll do whatever you want.
I know you would. But
you killed someone, Darren.
Staying here longer than needed,
it's not safe for you, nor us.
Oh! Argh!
Argh!
Are you lost?
Toilet? Right next to you.
Where it says toilet.
Piss only. Shitter's
out of order.
Lucky me. Lucky for both of us.
What can I get you?
Oh, no, no, no.
Oi, come on!
All right? Yeah, all right.
Who are you? No-one.
New recruit, Mum?
Nah. Just passing
through. Be gone by morning.
Hey, what's all this? Are you
fucking kidding me or what?!
Hey! You stop walking,
old man! Evie... Stop talking!
I'm telling you now, son,
if he drops my shopping,
there'll be bloody hell
to pay. He's with the boy.
Go on. Give him a hand.
No, you fucking don't!
You just drove right
past me with these bags.
I could just about throw
these in the house from here.
Where were you when
I needed you, halfway to
breaking my fucking
neck, huh? Are you his dad?
Darren, get back inside!
Oi! There's a lot of stock left
over, you've been
gone over a week.
I expected you to shift
the lot. We couldn't deliver
owt to Mikey
Cartwright. Not gonna
be able to anytime soon either.
Someone torched
him in his kiosk.
Torched him? Aye, he
went up with all his stock.
Police had cordoned it off
before we got there.
You! Evie!
I knew there was
something wrong. Evie!
Gimme the gun,
gimme the fucking gun!
Ugh! Ah! Hah!
That's Mikey's metal.
And this, this is my slug.
Ugh! Tell me the truth!
Who the fuck did you kill? Evie.
Look at me, look at me. Evie.
Tell me! Evie! Who the fuck
did you kill? Finn Wallace.
Finn?
Yeah.
Finn? No.I couldn't in all
right tell you, could I? No, no.
Because you knew, you knew that
I'd never fucking hide him.
Get away from the window!
Why? Why?
Just tell me one thing.
Why would you go after him?
We didn't.
He didn't know who he was.
Darren! Will you step away
from the fucking window.
Dad...
Aarrgghh! Aarrgghh!
Come on!
Get Darren!
Mum, please...
Liam! Don't let them
surround the house!
Argh! Argh! Ugh!
Evie!
Ugh! Argh! Argh!
Argh!
Jesus! The roof!
Now! Get on the roof!
You see anybody's
feet other than ours,
you fucking shoot
them, you hear me?
Darren! Darren!
Get off me!
Go, go, go!
Cover me!
Come on.
Take your hands off me.
You fucking killed him.
You fucking killed loan.
You're fucking evil.
Get off me. Get off me!
I'll hold them back
as long as I can. Thank you.
No, Evie, please,
come with us. Evie! No!
Be worth it, boy.
No, no, please, come with us!
Please, Evie!
No, get off me!
Please, Evie, come with us.
No! Evie! No! Evie!
Where does it lead?
Give me the gun.
Hey, give that to
me! That's mine.
Here.
Here. It's worth something now.
That'll be Al.
Come on.
We can still make it.
For a week, I've had
one bullet left in this gun.
And every day I saw it,
I swore I'd use it on you.
Take more than
that to put me down.
I've done it before.
It only took a second.
No, son. It took a lot more.
- Come on.
You let me get
you on that boat...
and I'll let you
pull the fucking trigger.
- Come on.
Come on.
No, no, no, no, Evie.
Keep her running.
We had a fucking deal! Kinney,
where the fuck is my wife?!
Aarrgghh!
Ugh! You get on that boat!
You head straight. Dad, please.
Ssh!
You push it as hard as you can.
As far as she'll go.
Come on, boy.
Stay strong.
Dad...
Son.
Why did you pick him?
Hello. Mr Kapadia's office.
Yellow 2-4-6.
Yes, sir, immediately.
We're done here. Everyone?
More. Remove all trace
and return to London.
Orders just came in.
We've got a new target.
Another son.