EPISODE 6
My name is Niels Thormod.
I'm a psychologist.
- Will you tell me your names?
- We want to talk to Henrik.
We saw the guy we took the phone from.
The murderer.
- Can't you just go?
- Did you really think you could hide?
Leave my family alone.
Understand?
We're going to go home and get Mom.
We need to shift focus. The horse was
directed at Vibeke. Leonora, at William.
I want to find that fucker
who killed Leonora.
The victims aren't the victims.
It's the ones closest to them who suffer.
We need to find a connection between them.
- Is it the baby?
- I had an abortion.
Henrik.
I think I'm in love with you.
You're not in love with me because
you can't love. Now get out.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Lillian!
I think I've found the link.
It's Tommy.
It's all about Tommy.
FIVE YEARS EARLIER
Tommy!
Hey, hey.
Something came up.
Do you have a smoke?
What's up?
KG went into William's turf.
We're going there this afternoon.
- What's going to happen?
- He's pushing them out.
- When?
- We're meeting at their clubhouse at 4PM.
How are you going to get them to leave?
- I just know that William's pissed.
- Is William going?
I couldn't ask him directly,
but I assume so.
Okay. I'll talk to Lillian.
- You're coming?
- Yeah, I'll take care of it.
I mean it.
I need to get out of this.
Tommy, you're going to get out.
I'm going to take care of it.
Okay.
KG is on the way into William's turf.
It could be violent.
It could also be nothing.
A business meeting.
Two men talking together.
- Tommy didn't mean that.
- He didn't know, either.
Is William going to be there at all?
If we show up, they might think
we have an informer there.
- We wait.
- Tommy's counting on us.
We need to be 100% sure.
Otherwise, months of work are wasted.
- Henrik promised Tommy we'd come.
- Then he's going to break that promise.
We wait to see what happens.
Okay.
Hi, honey.
- Is there going to be a party?
- Where have you been?
- You know I can't tell you.
- Or you don't want to.
I wasn't here, anyway.
- I miss you all the time.
- Yeah, sure.
- Put that on the gift table.
- But it's for you.
- You're really sucking up, huh?
- Exactly.
Is it working?
Because I saw it and thought
that you usually like it.
I want to say happy birthday to Brian.
We'll just go out so we don't bother you.
- You can just help, too.
- No, I can't.
There's way too many treats.
I can't keep my hands to myself.
- Where is he?
- He's in the bedroom.
Brian! Your dad is here.
Hi, Dad.
Hi, my boy.
Congrats. Put your jacket on.
We're going out.
When I turned 17, I wanted a motorcycle.
Dad gave me a chain lock.
My dad thought it was a good start.
Grandma's coming this afternoon.
- Are you staying?
- No, I have to take care of something.
But say hi for me.
- Congrats.
- Thanks.
Yeah, we're going to Manchester.
To a home game.
- Old Trafford. You and me.
- What? We are?
- No, thanks.
- Hello! Didn't you turn 17?
It's just a joint.
You can't say anything to Mom.
I know there's been all sorts of shit
these last years -
but it's going to be better now.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing you need to be mixed up in.
- Is it dangerous?
- No, of course not.
But it ends today.
Hey, Moyo!
What's up?
Not a bad birthday, eh?
Where the fuck are you?
It's about to go to hell here.
What's going on, man?
Shoot!
Hey, hey, hey. Easy now.
Henrik!
Why the fuck didn't you come?
You said you were coming.
Because the others wanted to wait.
I couldn't do anything.
- You fucking had them. They were there.
- I tried. The others didn't want to.
They wanted more information.
I couldn't do shit.
People died.
The guys that came out, they...
We shot them.
How many?
A lot.
There was blood everywhere.
Shit, man.
I'm done here.
I'm getting out now.
Okay, okay. Tommy,
you just need to stay a little longer.
Because we need to get William
and the people above him.
- You'll get money, a new identity.
- Fuck you.
- We're going to take care of you.
Now we're just waiting
for them to retaliate.
I can't do this anymore.
I told him. They won't listen.
What would happen if you stopped?
Then the whole deal's off.
Then it's prison and all that shit.
I can't do this anymore.
Can't you say I'm mentally unstable?
That I can't continue if I'm sick?
I understand you're afraid, and
I understand you don't want to continue.
I understand you have regrets.
But I can't say that you can't do it.
I can make sure you get a prescription
for some sedatives.
Is it because the police pay for me
to be here? Are you afraid to lose money?
No, I just can't say you have a diagnosis.
It won't work.
- I thought you wanted to help me.
- Yeah, I'm trying to.
Go fuck yourself, you fucking fool.
Tommy? Tommy?
Are you Richard?
- You wanted to talk about something.
- Yeah, I want to talk about something.
- I'm just going to start this here.
- Yeah, that's fine.
[ SIX DEAD IN GANG WAR
POLICE INFORMED BUT DIDN'T ACT. ]
For fuck's sake.
- Can I do anything?
- Like what?
It wasn't your decision.
- You think that makes a difference?
- Yeah, it should.
- Yeah?
- Did you read it?
We need to bring Tommy in.
They're going to kill him.
We know it was Tommy,
but the article didn't expose him.
It said, "The informant nervously
breaks the filter from his cigarette."
Tommy always does that.
He breaks the filter off.
Okay. We'll take him in. Go there.
I'll call for backup.
- This is Moyo.
- Yeah, it's me.
William wanted to meet.
I need to ask for your help.
You know the farm. There's a stop
at the end of the main road.
Just to the left.
Wait there with the car.
I may need to leave in a hurry.
Fuck, Tommy, what's this about?
Just wait there. I'll call you.
Can you be there in 15 minutes?
Okay.
Okay. I need to go now.
And Moyo? Thanks.
Looks cool.
It turned out really good.
Where are the others?
They're coming.
Sit down.
- Something to eat?
- No, thanks.
- What are we doing now?
- We need to find out who it is.
And how much he told the police.
So...
Everyone knows
what happens to an informer.
- I need to piss. Is there a...?
- Out in the hall.
No, no, no!
Come on, for fuck's sake!
Are you done pissing?
THE BRIDGE IV
NOW
We should have seen the connection.
Yeah.
- Who is Tommy?
- Lillian can explain.
Who is it?
Tommy Petersen. Criminal and informer.
Promised a reduced sentence.
He was caught, tortured, and murdered.
And Henrik was his contact.
I understand why you were criticized.
The case was investigated.
No one was to blame for what happened.
That doesn't mean you didn't
make mistakes. Six people died.
- Seven including Tommy.
- Hi, Henrik.
Let's concentrate on Tommy's family.
They have the strongest motive.
Nicole Johansson. The car is connected
to her husband's garage.
What's he doing there?
That's Tommy and Nicole's son, Brian.
He's 21 and in a wheelchair.
Henrik, where are you going?
- Let's keep going.
- Solveig Petersen. We know her.
Yes, what do we know about her?
Tommy's mother. She's still looking
to bring Tommy's killers to justice.
Most recently, at the Human Rights Court.
- And where is she located now?
- She lives in a camper. No phone.
We'll put out a bulletin on the camper.
What do we know about Brian Petersen?
Hi, Henrik.
What are you doing here?
What the fuck are you up to?
Your name isn't Kevin.
You're pretending you're my friend.
Maybe you can walk, too?
Can you?
Can you walk?
- What are you doing? Stop it.
- Come on. Walk!
What the fuck are you doing?
Okay, sorry.
Sorry. Here.
- Come on.
- No, stop.
Just go inside. I'm from the police.
Nothing happened.
Just go inside. Here.
- It's okay.
- We're just talking.
Your name isn't Kevin.
No, well...
I wanted to be anonymous at the meetings.
Not use my real name. Lots of people do.
What are you doing at those
NA meetings? Why do you come?
You know I'm trying not to do drugs!
Tommy? Tommy Petersen?
- What about him?
- Yeah, what about him?
- What does it have to do with my dad?
- Where were you on the 28th?
- Why?
- Because I'm asking.
I was home. I didn't do anything.
I played on the computer.
- Alone?
- Yeah.
- What about the night of the 29th?
- I was home then, too.
Alone.
Okay.
Henrik!
- What are we doing?
- We're going to chop wood.
Chop wood? Seriously?
- We need to help each other.
- But they don't like us.
- Not me, anyway.
- That's not true, Christoffer.
Theo wanted the house for his son,
then we came along.
It's our fault, you mean?
You take the blame for everything.
I want to go back to my old class.
- It won't work now that we live here.
- Then we can move back.
Now that Dan is...
Yeah, maybe.
Come on.
You don't think it was
the last break-in we'll have?
We have open doors. We trust each other.
That's how we do it.
If someone can't deal with that,
they shouldn't live here.
It's not about whether we like them.
It's about our values and peace of mind.
We need to react
before the whole town goes to...
- We wanted to help.
- What?
- We wanted to help with the wood.
- Go ahead.
Hi.
He doesn't have an alibi for the 28th and
29th. Same for Patrik's killing.
- But he's in a wheelchair.
- Thanks, I know that.
- He has an alibi for the clown and horse.
- I'll double-check.
Three executions left. If the motive is
revenge for Tommy, you may be victims.
Are you sure he needs everyone?
We need to find the others
who betrayed Tommy.
Who's closest to you?
Family, siblings?
Sex partner?
That guy from the Prosecution Service?
I don't know. There's actually no one
I'm that close to anymore.
- You love no one and no one loves you?
- Not that I can think of, no.
You're the closest to Henrik.
- Maybe.
- Then you need a bodyguard.
- I don't want that.
- Yeah, but you need it.
Beheading and hanging I can take care of.
A bodyguard won't help if they shoot me.
But all precautions from now on.
Start by questioning Nicole.
- I want to look into Kevin.
- You mean Brian.
- I want to see if what he said is true.
- But his name is Brian.
Okay.
But I've left that all behind me.
My old life with Tommy.
- We just want to check some dates.
- You should talk to Solveig.
- Tommy's mother.
- Do you know where she's located?
No, I don't want to know, either,
because she's a real bitch. Right?
- Yeah, she's real special.
- How was your and Tommy's relationship?
Well, he was totally hopeless.
But you were always happy and carefree
when he was around.
- If you know what I mean.
- No.
No, but it never would've
worked out anyway.
I think he was seeing someone else
at the end.
- Do you know her name?
- No, because I'm not sure.
I just need to go to the bathroom.
Would you like to hold him?
- How old is it?
- Almost seven months.
It's so big.
Was she in pain, your wife?
Did she have abdominal cramps?
Did she give birth vaginally?
Yeah, she did, but...
I don't know.
- Who's the father?
- I am.
- No, you're not.
- What the hell do you mean?
The baby has brown eyes, and you both
have blue. It's physically impossible.
That was stupid.
Yeah, they weren't too crazy about it.
But now we have someone
who fucked around in this case.
- Should I go back and say I'm sorry?
- No, I think it's too late.
Do you understand now
why I don't do smalltalk with you?
- What are you doing?
- Providing security.
- What nonsense.
- If it stops break-ins, is it stupid?
Does Harriet know you've started
your own little security service?
If she listened,
it wouldn't be necessary.
Go home.
Hey.
I talked to Christoffer.
- More problems with Theo?
- No, absolutely not. But...
He misses his old school.
The commute is too far from here.
- To his old school?
- Yeah.
So we thought that maybe
we could move back.
To Malmo.
So Dan can find you?
You're safe here.
Christoffer told me, Frank.
I know what happened.
I'm so grateful.
For everything you've done
to protect him and us.
Is this gratitude? You just leave
when you don't need me anymore.
He shot his father.
He'd be in prison
if it wasn't for me.
I made myself an accomplice
in a murder for your sake.
But he wants to go back to school, so you
just go. Is that fair after all I've done?
- No.
- No, it's not.
I'm sorry. I wasn't thinking.
I'm sorry.
I've done it before.
Helped people who shit all over me.
We're not shitting on you. Without you,
we'd never have managed.
We'll stay.
Of course we'll stay.
Good.
How did you betray Tommy?
The last time I saw him,
he was upset and scared.
He wanted out and asked for help.
- With what?
- Talking with you. The police.
Declaring him unfit.
Mentally ill.
I couldn't do it.
But I made sure sedatives
were prescribed.
- Did he mention a lover?
- No.
Other relatives besides his mother,
son, and wife?
No, not that I can remember.
If there's someone...
...getting revenge on the people
who betrayed Tommy...
Does that mean it's my fault
that Margrethe was murdered?
Yes, she was an innocent victim
used to get at you.
Yeah. Jonas Mandrup.
This is Tobias Johansson.
I just wanted to say that...
My wife has the code to the key cabinet
at the garage.
She's borrowed cars before.
No, not you! Why did you go and
destroy everything, you ugly bitch?
Hey! Take it easy.
I'll take this questioning.
Sit down.
- I'm going to fucking report her.
- Yeah, you do that.
The Swedes like being reprimanded.
But we're not talking about that now.
We have evidence that you left
the hospital the night of the 28th.
From who?
From Tobias?
Yeah, okay. That's right.
I went home -
because it wasn't necessary
for us both to be there.
That's the only alibi you have.
Do you know what you did this week?
No, but that's why people
have a calendar, right?
I don't need a calendar.
I don't do anything. I'm only with Sonny.
I breastfeed, then he wakes up,
and then he shits -
and then I change diapers,
and then I clean up vomit.
It's nothing I need to
write in a calendar.
No. So you don't have an alibi?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm coming!
It's you?
- You fucking destroyed everything!
- What's going on?
You can ask your husband about that.
- I checked Kevin's journal.
- His name is Brian.
- You know what I mean.
- Yes, but his name...
- Do you understand who I'm talking about?
- Yes.
Good. So stop.
He's wheelchair-bound.
He fell from a balcony. He was on drugs.
He couldn't commit those murders.
And we checked all his accounts
and cell phones.
Both Nicole's and Brian's.
Nothing stands out.
So what do we do with
white trash wife and her baby?
We keep her. No alibis,
access to the car, strong motive.
- Solveig Petersen?
- We haven't found her yet. Let's go.
Henrik, Saga?
Come with me.
What the hell is with you two?
He's angry at me
because I had an abortion.
You were pregnant with Henrik's...?
Yes. I had an abortion because
it would've come between us.
- Can you work together?
- Yes.
I need both of you for this.
So I expect you to act professionally
and keep your private lives outside.
Okay.
For your sake.
It's easy to be wise in retrospect,
but you could've handled it better.
Yes. I just tried to appreciate
what I have.
Thanks.
You can't blame yourself.
What should you have done?
- Should you have lied for Tommy?
- I could have done something.
He was desperate and what did I do?
I gave him some sedatives.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going out to the girls.
But they don't want to talk to you.
No, they need me.
I know I can help them.
This time I'll do it right.
I know what you're thinking,
that this is just my job.
But it means something to me,
and I'd like to help you.
I can make sure you have it better.
I can make sure you get out of here.
- You just need to tell me your names.
- What do we get out of it?
We want to go to the movies.
I'd like that too,
but this isn't a negotiation.
Decide if you want to talk to me,
and ask the staff to contact me.
It's up to you now.
I'd like to help you.
He's a bit like Henrik.
I think he's sweet.
Sweet people can be useful.
How?
If he thinks we trust him,
he'll trust us.
When we get the chance,
we take off.
Bye.
- Yeah?
- It's Douglas. Can we meet?
- Of course. When?
- Just come.
- What's this about?
- It's best that we meet.
Okay. I'll try for tonight.
Good. See you later. Bye.
You said you know how
to resolve the conflict with Henrik?
Yes. I'll find his daughters.
And you think that will
resolve something?
Then he can't be disappointed
and angry with me.
- Why wouldn't he be?
- Then he'll have children. His own.
Do you feel guilty about the abortion?
No, but I didn't know
Henrik would react the way he did.
If you had known that,
would you have handled it differently?
It wouldn't have made a difference.
If Henrik had had the child,
we couldn't have been together.
- But now you want to make it all better?
- Yes.
- By finding his daughters.
Do you see the pattern?
I want you to think about it
for next time.
I'll walk you out.
I'm going out to another patient.
Not everyone can come to me,
so I go to them.
What are you doing?
I live here.
I can't live at Henrik's -
and it's not safe at the hotel,
so I live here.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Goodnight.
Make a list of people you'd really miss.
They need to be protected.
Okay. Thanks.
You're welcome.
Goodnight.
- Can't you just turn it off?
- No, I can't.
- Seriously?
- Yeah. What do you want?
Alice paid taxes on personal benefits
the year before she disappeared.
- Yeah?
- Something about wellness and health.
- Do you know what it was?
- No.
Did she talk to a psychologist
or therapist at work?
I don't know.
She didn't tell me, anyway.
- Hang up.
- Who's that?
Her name's Tanja.
- Are you having sex?
- We are.
And we're going to continue now.
Come on.
It's Saga Norén, Malmo Police.
I contacted you about Alice Sabroe.
Yes, it's...
11:56PM.
No, it can't wait until tomorrow.
I want to know about benefits
Alice used for health and wellness.
You didn't have therapists there.
Could she have talked to someone else?
Do you remember his name?
What do you want?
I told you everything about Dan and Sofie.
This is about another case.
Alice Sabroe.
You were her coach
when you worked at Parsimonia.
Yeah. It was a long time ago.
She disappeared.
You reacted to my colleague's surname.
Why didn't you ask about Alice?
I didn't know how much she told him,
and we have a confidentiality agreement.
- Did she come back?
- No, she was found murdered.
That's terrible.
What about the children?
- They haven't been found.
- I have a daughter myself.
Okay. Come with me.
- What did you usually talk about?
- Mostly about her home life.
About her husband, Henrik.
What did she say about him?
That it wasn't going well. I suggested
couple's therapy. Alice didn't want to.
Why not?
She'd met another man.
- Did she mention his name?
- No, she didn't.
I think she was considering
leaving her husband.
Could she have mentioned him, and
you forgot you wrote it down?
Yeah. I'll look at my notes
and see if I can find anything.
Do that. And call me.
Okay.
Hi.
I'm happy you wanted
to see me again.
I assume you don't trust adults.
Is that something
you want to talk about?
Our stepdad.
We couldn't stay there.
- Does he live here in Copenhagen?
- Jutland. We don't want to go back.
Do you want to explain
why you don't want to go back?
He wasn't very nice.
What's his name?
My name is Julie.
And this is my little sister, Ida.
Julie and Ida.
That's really nice.
We got a match on Solveig's car.
She's on the way.
Alice met a coach at work.
He wasn't an employee, but I found him...
Is this leading anywhere?
If she had someone else,
would you want to know?
- Did she?
- Yes, but the coach didn't know who.
- Are you sure?
- Not 100%.
If you don't have evidence,
then don't tell me that.
- Easy.
- Let me go!
- It's easier if you cooperate.
- Go with my colleague...
- Who's questioning her?
- You and me.
Lillian would really like us
to do it together.
Good.
Where were you on the 28th?
Figure it out yourselves.
Write where you were on these dates.
Oh, now you want to talk to me, huh?
When I wanted to contact you after
Tommy's death, I didn't feel very welcome.
- I didn't work on that case.
- No, but he did.
You have a strong motive for revenge.
When society betrays you, you need to
take the law into your own hands.
Is that what you did?
Not at all. I'm just happy
someone's avenging Tommy's death.
The people that did it deserve it.
We're going to keep you until
you give us what we need.
So we'll start again.
Where were you on the 28th?
- Saga, it's me. I found a letter.
- Good.
From Tommy to his mother. He mentions
a Steph. They had a relationship.
How does it feel to know
that you're next?
- Are you threatening me?
- No.
But with them out of the way
it'll be your turn soon.
- Tommy wrote letters to you.
- Did you mess with my things?
- We have a search warrant.
- It's my private property.
If you're suspected of a crime
punishable by imprisonment -
a search must be undertaken
to look for evidence in the case.
Tommy mentioned a Steph in the letters.
Who is that?
Why should I tell you?
Steph, is that a man or a woman?
- Steph? It's a man.
- It's a man?
No, wait a minute.
I think it's a woman.
It's a woman?
Was there anything else
I can help you with?
Why did you go?
We decided that we would
act professional together.
Malene Sonning has a daughter
named Stephanie.
Stephanie Balling, 33.
Daughter of Malene and Peder Balling.
Volunteered in Colombia,
but came home three months ago.
- Address?
- She hasn't registered an address.
That's all we have on her.
If it's Morgan you're after,
you'll have to talk to my divorce lawyer.
We're here because of
your daughter, Stephanie.
- Stephanie?
- Do you know where she is?
She's in Colombia.
Did something happen?
She came home three months ago.
You didn't know she came home?
No, I didn't.
Do you know if she had a relationship
with Tommy Petersen four years ago?
I didn't even know
she came home.
Do you think she tells me
about her boyfriends?
- Does she have keys to the house?
- Yeah.
You were the one who figured it out about
Morgan and Nicole and the baby, huh?
Yes, and I'm sorry for that.
You don't need to be.
It was good for me to know.
- Yeah, was there anything else?
- No. Thanks.
Thanks.
Stephanie could've taken the extra key to
Morgan's car when they were in Hamburg.
- Why then?
- She needed a car. They didn't get along.
Her mail is being sent to Christiania.
We have surveillance there.
No news.
Hello?
Yeah.
Okay. I'm coming down.
Kevin.
Hey.
- Sorry if I'm disturbing.
- It's okay.
We're friends.
I mean, you mean something to me.
Then you come and rip me out of my chair
and ask what I've done -
and talk about my dad...
What the fuck is going on?
We think the killings we're investigating
are connected to your father.
Why do you think that?
Do you know anything
about a Stephanie or a Steph?
- Someone in contact with your father.
- No.
- Did you ask Grandma?
- Yeah, we tried, but...
It was hopeless.
What about Moyo, my dad's friend?
- The guy who works in the shop in Malmo?
- Yeah.
My mom helped him
get a job at Tobias' place.
Okay.
Thanks, my...
For coming here, too.
How are you doing really?
- Did you fall off the wagon again?
- No.
See you at the next meeting.
Of course. See ya.
What was your relationship to Tommy?
Me and Tommy were like brothers.
We had big plans.
Then it all went to hell.
It was your fault.
What did you do after Tommy's death?
Sandra and I moved to Sweden
to get away from it all.
Then Nicole got me a job at the shop.
- Are you almost finished with that?
- I haven't done anything.
It's fucking unreal that you all got off.
But I have Sandra, and I won't lose her.
Sandra, Sandra, and Sandra. Convenient.
Your wife is your only alibi.
- We're good together.
- Are you?
Then maybe I'll go talk to her
while you stay there.
Can you let me out?
I dreamed about you a few nights ago.
It was a long time ago.
And I was happy to see you.
Astrid.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- Why are you speaking Danish?
- I wasn't.
I heard you.
It wasn't me.
It was Magdalena.
- But you aren't dressed up.
- One doesn't always need to be.
[ Anna. Beloved daughter.
Beloved sister. ]
Is that your sister?
Don't tell anyone.
Not to Frank or your mother.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Hello?
Sandra?
I'm from the police.
Hello?
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN