Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app
Should we say it one last time?
One cannot live fully
without embracing suicide and crime.
Say it.
A pact made with relentless fire
that requires that some live...
...others die.
On three.
One...
...two...
...three!
Each of us has within us
a weak aspect...
...eager to give up freedom
to be dominated.
But we also have a will that
desires freedom, that insists...
...on deciding for ourselves,
each of us individually...
...what is good...
...and what is evil.
Are there any questions?
Doesn't anyone want to challenge
Justin's thesis?
Do you all submit to this
Darwinian struggle of egos?
I got a question.
Mr. Haywood, you're awake!
Let's hear it.
What's a dork like you
know about power?
What would an ass like you
know about philosophy?
Keep it civil.
Are you talking about crime?
You should wake up more often.
-What about it?
-All freedom risks crime.
Freedom is crime. It thinks of itself
and not of the group.
-Thank you, Justin. Very daring.
-Thank you.
For those of you interested
in the source of his report...
...take a look at Nietzsche.
You really need to get laid,
Bonaparte.
Hey, Justin.
-Remember me?
-What do you want?
I want to blow your brains out.
And I'll make it look like a suicide.
Everyone would believe that
you killed yourself.
You won't get away with it.
Your shoe prints are unique.
They'd be traced back to you.
The fibers on your shirt
are all over me.
Your hair too.
It's called transference.
More importantly, your fingerprints...
...on my neck...
...where you touched me.
-You can't get them off skin.
-You can with a Magna-Brush...
...or a fingerprint cam or an iodine gun
and silver transfer sheets.
You don't have the discipline
to commit a murder.
Is that right?
Let's see.
Bang!
You're dead.
What took you so long?
I've been waiting.
No, I have something better.
-What is it?
-Absinthe. Wormwood-infused alcohol.
The molecular structure is almost
identical to tetrahedral chlorine.
Tetra what?
The active ingredient in marijuana.
Where did you get it?
Poets drank it for inspiration.
It's been illegal since
the turn of the century.
Even better.
To the systematic derangement
of our senses.
Forget the senses.
Let's derange the world.
We will.
When?
Soon.
What about tonight?
-What about right now?
-I have a biology--
Fuck your biology!
You always have excuses.
Let's forget it.
We've been planning this for months.
I'm sick of planning.
That's all it is with you.
It's talk and plans and dreams.
You're a jerk-off.
So jerk off.
Richard, wait.
Just be patient.
Here comes The Hyena.
Why can't I go inside the perimeter?
I told them not to let anybody in.
It's your first homicide. I didn't
want you stepping on your tongue.
Take this.
-What is it?
-Important tool. Hey, boys!
Snack time! Set up a staging area.
This place will be crawling
with people...
...including our chief.
-Rod?
-Yeah, Rod is not a cop.
Darnell, get out of my crime scene!
Come on!
Sorry, Cassie.
There's only one way
into a crime scene.
Put your foot where mine goes
and nowhere else.
Ready?
Ever do this in vice?
No.
Right there.
Looks like some kind of boot.
What's that smell like?
Smells like vomit.
That's what I thought.
Bag some for the lab.
-What's the matter?
-Nothing.
-Notice the hemorrhaging?
-She was strangled.
Finger-shaped marks around the neck.
Look at this.
Clean cut.
-Trophy?
-That'd be my guess.
Defensive wounds.
She put up a fight.
Good for you.
This is a secondary crime scene. Why?
This wound would produce lots
of blood. There's very little here.
What about these?
-Piquerism.
-Pre or postmortem?
Post, no blood.
Not bad, vice.
Probably aced your detective's exam.
The wind is picking up,
we'll lose evidence.
Hold on to everything we find.
-Any idea who she is?
-No. No car, no l.D.
Jane Doe.
Hey, Bonaparte.
What's the matter?
Miss Mills?
Time's up. Put your pens down.
Exchange your test with a neighbor.
Number 20 is C...
..."Burnt Norton."
I suppose you find it funny.
What?
Me flunking a pop quiz.
You didn't flunk. You got 1 9 out of 20.
Please pass the tests forward.
Wait up, I want to talk to you.
-Why did you do that?
-I have motives.
Like what?
I need your help
for my physics midterm.
Why me?
Because you're a genius, okay?
I live at 1 1 08 Chandler.
Can you remember that?
Around 5?
Hi, Lisa.
-This friend--
-Turn right.
-It's right here.
-A houseboat. Neat.
Neat indeed.
I like it out here.
Not too many people.
Thanks. See you tomorrow.
-You gonna see me to the door?
-Of course.
You made detective in four years?
-Must be smarter than you look.
-Thank you.
It'll only get worse, I warn you.
-You been talking to the boys?
-I heard a few things.
They tell you why
I was called The Hyena?
-Why?
-Female hyenas have a mock penis.
-Draw your own conclusions.
-Does that bother you?
I just wear loose slacks.
It's really not a problem.
See you later.
No prints.
The killer must have worn gloves.
-So it's not a husband or boyfriend.
-Why?
You don't use gloves
to kill your wife.
Unless you've thought about it.
Missing ring finger.
Ritual? Serial killer?
-Maybe a comment on matrimony.
-A negative one.
Maybe we should investigate
every bad marriage in the county.
-Why don't you get on that?
-Let's start with you.
-Ever been married?
-Nope.
What's this?
An old murder case I was involved in.
The guy's up for parole,
they want me to testify.
What do we have on Jane Doe?
I'm checking missing persons
nationwide.
Run her prints,
have an artist do a sketch.
I got it.
Bonaparte!
I didn't think you'd show. Come in.
Who did these?
They're quite good.
Thank you.
-You did them?
-Don't look so surprised.
I modeled for them too.
Bonaparte, you're blushing.
Why do you call me that?
Ever take a career aptitude test?
No.
If you ever did, they'd recommend
you a career as a dictator.
Why?
Who would listen to me?
Where's your physics book?
You're overfeeding that thing.
It'll get as fat as you are.
I hope this is better
than that other stuff.
It's KGB.
For $400,
it better put me on the moon.
You'll be totally satisfied,
I guarantee it.
Money back?
Come on, can't we cut a deal?
-You don't want it?
-I want it.
Richie Rich.
-I hate it when you call me that.
-It's a deal.
Bring me a couple
pigtailed cheerleaders...
...then I give it to you free.
-How can I trust that?
-I love this part.
Can I just get the product already?
Check this out.
-Come on--
-You'll get it. Hang on.
Listen to her. She loves it.
We got our Jane Doe.
Her name was Olivia Lake.
She missed three days of work.
Her supervisor
found the place like this.
What do we know about the supervisor?
Married, two kids, solid alibi.
Maybe she caught somebody in the
middle of a 459, and he panicked?
And what, took the body with him?
Where did these mud prints come from?
There's a planting bed out here.
Looks dry as a bone.
Maybe she watered the lawn.
We got a time of death?
Based on stomach content,
between 9 and 1 0 Thursday night.
How about 9:27?
Can we come in?
Let the games begin.
Sam Kennedy, AI Swanson.
New assistant D.A.
and former member of our department.
Nice to meet you.
Miss Mayweather, always a pleasure.
Heard you finally passed the bar.
Did they make it true or false?
She hasn't lost her sting.
-What are you doing here?
-Staying informed.
Really?
Sam, please keep him informed.
Thank you.
What do we got here?
Sorry.
-Can I have you sign off?
-Okay.
Sam, it's me. I'll be a little late.
Why don't you get started?
Looks like a body dump.
Jesus, she's alive!
Nice detective work.
How'd you find me?
Rule one: Talk to the neighbors.
You said a little late,
and it's been three hours.
This about that D.A., Swanson?
That asshole? No.
-He seemed okay.
-Yeah, well, try dating him.
He got rough with me,
so I broke his nose with a cat.
A cat?
Well, a ceramic cat.
No, thanks.
-Good. Then you can walk me home.
-Sure.
Thank you.
Sit down.
I should get going.
What's the rush?
Can I ask you a personal question?
I can hardly wait.
How did you get into this work?
Why homicide?
Someone I knew was murdered,
and I got interested.
-Really?
-No.
I'm just bullshitting you.
It's just the kind of crap
people like to hear.
Wait.
What are you doing?
It's called sex.
It's fun, you should try it.
We gotta work together.
This is a bad idea.
Don't worry, I won't get possessive.
Wait.
-Why are you doing this?
-Because I want to.
What about what I want?
What do you want?
-Right now?
-Yeah.
This.
Wait. Slow down.
No, no, leave that on.
Just that. Please.
Sure.
What's the matter?
-You gotta get up, you gotta go.
-Why?
Because I gotta get some sleep.
-Can we sleep together?
-Bed's too small.
-No, it's not.
-Come on, you gotta go.
Jesus!
I'll see you tomorrow. Good night.
The evidence is so tiny,
you wouldn't recognize it.
A few red and yellow carpet fibers,
some hair.
That's it.
The fibers will be tested to find
generic and subgeneric classes...
...then compared to a database
for the manufacturer.
Fibers consistent with a mass-produced
variety, made in Denver.
Distributed in the United States
under several names.
-No help.
-Same with the red fibers.
Several trilobal nylon fibers...
...along with other fibers
will be matched with a brand.
It's sold by Hanover Sampson
for several discount stores.
That narrows it down.
They sold 50,000 in that color last year.
Examination of the cuticle,
cortex and medulla of the hair...
...will reveal them to be human.
Two brown human hairs.
Definitely not the victim's.
All but one.
At first, it will baffle them.
One hair of nonhuman origin, scale
matches Cynocephalus maimon.
It's a freaking baboon hair.
No fingerprints, no murder weapon.
They have their work cut out for them.
That's what they're paid for.
Coroner said strangulation was slow.
Perhaps the victim was being tortured.
The postmortem stab wounds
barely broke the surface.
Okay, that's it.
They'll decide that, given the sloppy
nature of the crime scene...
...the postmortem mutilation...
...the profile will be that
of a disorganized offender.
Poor social skills.
Nocturnal by nature.
Probably into pornography.
Intelligent, but uneducated.
Lives alone,
few relations with women.
Attack was spontaneous.
Unplanned.
He didn't drive down close
to the dump spot. That is planning.
But he left the footprints.
No evidence will lead to the suspect,
but they'll damn him.
-When will they have a suspect?
-They're eating out of our hands.
Poor Ray. He'll never see it coming.
Cassie, look at this.
Vigi boots.
What the hell are Vigi boots?
There he is, in the black coat.
Don't let him charm you too much.
Richard Haywood?
Cassie Mayweather, Sam Kennedy,
police. Can we talk to you?
Yeah, sure.
You're willing to speak
without an attorney?
Sure.
Where were you last Thursday night?
-What is this about?
-Answer the question.
I was cramming for this calculus
midterm. I was with a study group.
-How long?
-From about 7 until 3 Friday morning.
-That's quite a cram session.
-Yeah, well....
I got kind of a spotty record, and I
gotta keep my grades up for college.
Can you give us the names
of the other people there?
Sure. Am I in some kind of trouble?
You seem very particular
about your appearance.
Thanks.
I like your outfit too.
She looks good.
It's, like, feminine...
...but it still manages
to be professional.
Is that like a pleather?
Kmart.
We're interested in your shoes.
Let's talk about these.
-Vigis?
-You own a pair of these?
You bought them at Scarlatti's,
downtown Santa Barbara, for $637.50...
...on your platinum bankcard.
Size 1 2D.
This can't be about my shoes.
Why not?
This is about my shoes?
You got me freaked out
like I did something.
Did you find them or what?
I reported them stolen
three weeks ago.
I even filed a report
with the front office.
Did you find the shoes or not?
I think you should tell me
what's going on.
Because I'm spinning out here.
Shoe prints matching these were found
at a murder scene last week.
-The Covington woman?
-That's right.
You think the person who stole
my shoes committed this murder?
I'll cooperate in any way I can.
Any idea who stole your boots?
No, I don't. I wish I did now, though.
-Any enemies at school?
-Well, it's high school.
What does that mean?
Not to sound arrogant,
but there are people who envy me.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Why would they do that?
Well, let's just say
that I'm very fortunate...
...and that I've been blessed
in many ways.
-Must be nice being you, Richard.
-I got no complaints.
It all checked out.
He filed a report about the boots.
And made a big fuss to the principal.
Yeah, I bet he was a pain in the ass.
-She didn't say that.
-No, believe me. I hate kids like that.
Like what?
What about the study session?
Six kids were at his house with him
from 7 or 7:30 Thursday evening...
...till 3 a.m. Friday.
I talked to all of them.
He was there except for 1 5 minutes...
...he went to an ATM
to get cash for a pizza.
-Did you check that out?
-Yeah, he withdrew $40 at 9:1 9.
Get that enhanced.
-Why?
-Because I can't see his face.
It's him.
I can't see his face.
-You really think he's involved?
-I don't know.
But something's not right
with that kid.
Fifteen minutes.
It doesn't give him enough time.
He has to drive to Covington,
kill her, dump her body, get back.
He'd need at least an hour.
-They questioned me.
-And?
-It was so cool!
-Did they go for the shoes?
They grabbed it. I was so good.
I really was. Listen.
This can't be about my shoes.
-Why not?
-Did you find them?
You sure they didn't suspect anything?
You didn't overdo it?
A little bit.
I overdid it a little bit.
You think the person who stole
my shoes committed this murder?
I want you to know
I'm gonna cooperate in any way I can.
Meet me at the bluff tonight.
I can't.
-Why not?
-I have something to do.
-Like what?
-I'll tell you later. I should....
-Know who his father is?
-I wanna search his house.
Lawrence Haywood. He built the mall.
-Big campaign contributor?
-That's right.
And I won't fuck
with that guy on this.
I've grown much too fond of my own ass
to do anything that goddamned stupid!
And what is your problem?
Where are you on this, Sam?
-I don't care who his father is.
-I don't mean that.
Do you think we have enough
to go after him?
No. And if we go in too soon,
we could burn the whole case.
Really? And why is that, vice?
No judge would sign a warrant
based on what you have.
Shut up, Swanson!
-This kid with his attitude--
-Attitude isn't a crime.
-It's an indicator--
-But he doesn't fit the profile.
The profile doesn't fit!
The killer was smart. He didn't drive
to the site, he used Richard's boots...
-...but the attack was unplanned?
-But if we push too soon--
-Whose case is this?
-Just calm down.
No, I've been trying to find
Olivia's killer, busting my ass--
-Who's Olivia?
-The victim.
-Is this still my case?
-It's a coordinated effort!
You're getting way too involved
in this, Cassie.
-Cassie!
-What?
-You called her by her first name.
You said, "I've been trying
to find Olivia's killer."
No, I didn't.
Did l?
You're supposed to be identifying
with the killer, not the victim.
Remember that?
You don't have any witnesses
or fingerprints or powder burns....
I almost forgot.
Tobias always kept a gun,
right here. Loaded.
Can I come in?
Listen, I'm sorry
I didn't back you up in there.
I'm a big girl.
You said what you thought, right?
-Yes, but--
-Then you did the right thing.
-We can't just bust in there--
-I know. I heard you.
-So can you get out of the way?
-Know what your problem is?
Yeah, you're blocking Matlock.
Out of the way. Please.
I'm trying to apologize here.
All right, apology accepted.
You want to sit down?
You want to have a cookie?
-Hi.
-What's going on?
-We're making up.
-We're still friends, right?
-What's this?
I don't know, let's find out.
-We do this and you throw me out again?
-Or you stay. Or you leave.
I don't know.
It's hard to tell in advance.
What do you want?
You want promises? You want a ring?
-Is that what you want? A ring?
-Don't!
Look, it's not just about sex, okay?
I really respect you as a person.
Is that what you--?
Why do you always want to hurt people?
I wouldn't say always.
It kind of happens sometimes.
You're so good at breaking
other people down...
...but you never stop
and look at yourself.
-Where are you taking me?
-No peeking, we're almost there.
Step up.
Okay.
Open your eyes.
My God, Justin, this is beautiful!
Did you grow these?
What happened? You're different.
Yeah, I am different.
Mayweather.
Collect call from an inmate
in a corrections facility.
-The name of the inmate is....
-Carl Hudson.
If you wish to accept, press--
-I do not wish to accept any calls--
-Cassie?
-What?
-It's Sam.
Hi, I'm sorry. What can I do for you?
-Remember the puke at the body dump?
-Yeah.
Most of it was unidentifiable...
...but Kevin managed to isolate
some partially digested eggs.
-Fish eggs.
-Caviar?
Apparently so. I've compiled a list
of the local vendors selling caviar.
-What was his name?
-Richard Haywood.
Miles Haywood's kid?
He came in once around Christmas.
Not last week? Thursday?
I rarely see
any high-school kids here.
-Except Justin Pendleton.
-Who?
He used to come with his father,
but his parents split.
Now he comes in alone.
He's a senior at Jefferson.
Richard's a senior at Jefferson.
Justin eats alone?
He always brings a book.
He's a bit of a loner.
But a brilliant kid,
you should hear him talk.
When was he in here last?
The 5th. 7:30 p.m.
-What time did he leave?
-About 9.
Do you know what he ate?
Justin?
Cassie Mayweather,
with the San Benito Police.
-You're a police officer?
-I'm a homicide investigator.
-Can I ask you a couple questions?
-Sure.
You had dinner
at Maison Saint Croix on the 5th?
-Maison Saint Croix.
-Thank you.
The 5th was a Thursday, and they had
a caviar appetizer. Did you have it?
Yeah, I might have.
Can you tell me what happened?
-Do you know Richard Haywood?
-Everyone knows him.
Is he involved in this?
-Is he a friend of yours?
-No.
I mean, I tutored him for his bio
SAT last year, but we're not....
We don't have much in common.
-Are you in his study group?
-No. What study group?
When you left the restaurant,
did you take leftovers?
You didn't give your friends
at the study group leftovers?
Look, I told you, I barely know him.
He makes fun of me in class.
-Why would he do that?
-Because...
...he's like that.
He makes fun of everyone.
He's one of the cool kids.
What makes him cool?
You know, he's smart, he's rich...
...he's witty, and everyone likes him.
And you don't.
Yeah, I knew kids like that.
Superstars of high school.
Five years from now,
nobody will care who they are.
Well, Richard will always be cool.
His daddy's rich and I hate
to admit it, but he's actually smart.
He's lazy and didn't study,
but he got a 71 0 on that bio SAT.
-It kind of spun me out.
-Spinning out, huh?
You seem to know him well.
You can tell by his behavior in class.
Sorry.
Cassie, where have you been?
Sam l.D. 'd the suspect.
-Who is it?
-Ask Sam. He's in charge of the case.
S.I.D. is over there now
collecting evidence.
-Hi, Cass.
-Hi.
Look at this, sir.
-Could be a match.
-Log that.
I want samples of fabrics, soils,
any molds, plants in here and outside.
John's found a stash
of marijuana buds.
-You mind if we smoke up while we work?
-Yes, I do.
-So who is he?
-Raymond Lee Feathers.
He's a janitor at Jefferson.
I compiled a list of everyone
who might have stolen Richard's boots.
Then I cross-indexed that against
carpet purchases and up came this.
Apparently he sold grass
to the kids at school.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
Where is he?
I don't know. Seems like he took off.
-Did you run him for priors?
-A couple DUls, one pot bust.
But he hasn't shown up for work since
the day we talked to Richard there.
Did you find the boots?
Not yet, but we may have a match
on the yellow carpet fibers.
We've nothing on the vehicle fibers
till we find his car...
...but he's got a stash
of porno films, mostly bondage...
...just like the profile.
What?
-He's not a neatness freak.
-What are you saying?
Sloppy enough to leave footprints, but
smart enough to steal shoes in advance?
-This is our guy, no question.
-You find any caviar jars?
Come on, wait a minute.
You're ticked that I got him,
aren't you?
No. If you got him, I'm happy for you.
After we close this case, maybe we
should look for different partners.
Might be better.
Whatever you want.
Good.
-Nice work, guys.
-I gotta take a piss.
Don't worry,
I won't contaminate any evidence.
-She pees standing up, that one.
-Al.
Don't talk about her
like that, please.
You've slept with her already?
-What?
-You will. That's Cassie's m.o.
She lets you get close,
then pushes you away.
Ask her what's wrong, she picks
a fight. You're working with her...
...because no one else will.
Looks like a body dump.
Now we know where
that baboon hair came from.
It's okay.
Hey, Lisa.
-You want a ride?
-We already did that.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I want to talk to you.
-Want me to beg? Please.
-You'll get in an accident.
Please. I don't care.
You make me sad. Come on.
Come on. It's fun in here.
Hello, Justin.
How you doing?
What are you--?
What are you doing here?
-You stood me up for that slut?
-Lisa? She's not a slut.
-Did you tell her anything about us?
-Of course not.
-You fuck her?
-I was helping her with her physics.
-You fucked her, and I saw you.
We kissed.
-You kissed.
-That was it, I swear.
Oh, Justin.
You helped Lisa,
and you didn't even get laid?
-What a schmuck.
-She's not like that.
Bullshit. She spreads
like peanut butter.
You'd be surprised what a girl without
a dad will do for male attention.
Lisa.
Do you hate me?
I had to do it.
I don't want to hurt you, but I had
to show you what she's really like.
She's not good enough for you.
She doesn't appreciate you. She's
like your mom, dad and everyone else.
I'm the only person
who really cares about you.
I think I'm the only person who sees
how incredible you really are.
Don't go away, Justin. Come on.
What we did...
...together...
...how many people have done that?
We proved something to each other.
We showed what we're capable of.
There's no limits for men like us.
Did you hear about Ray?
They're onto him.
Just one last thing to do
and we're home free, right?
Do we have to?
You tell me.
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app