Previously on Young Sheldon...
You know that Mr. Rosenbloom
with the furniture store
over by the steak house?
He's asked me to dinner.
Is he your boyfriend?
Well, he's one of them,
so let's not bring that up.
All right, so what can I do for you?
What's it like to be Jewish?
Oh, it's terrible. I don't recommend it.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Yeah?
Connie, I would like to
have dinner with you tonight.
This is very promising.
SHELDON: Dr. Sturgis and Meemaw
had their first sleepover.
It's a big step in their relationship.
I'm going to go congratulate them.
Hey, put on a jacket, it's chilly out.
♪ You're just too good to be true... ♪
I have only seen you eat
vanilla ice cream for dessert.
- Why is that?
- Well, I've taken a page
from the great physicist
Richard Feynman.
In order to have
one less decision in his life,
he decided that dessert would
always be chocolate ice cream.
Sounds like it could get kind of boring.
Oh, it does.
But over the last 35 years,
I believe I've saved at
least a day and a half.
♪ Pardon the way that I stare... ♪
[LAUGHING]
Well, you have to let
me cook for you sometime.
But I enjoy cooking for you.
It's a means of expressing my affection.
It also allows me to
control the amount of garlic,
which gives me the burps.
Well, I do make a mean barbecue,
and I promise I can make it garlic-free.
Excellent!
Next time, you can express
your affection for me.
[CHUCKLES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Excuse me.
I bet it's Sheldon checking on us.
What?
Connie? It's Ira.
[CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY]: Hey... Hey...
I'm, uh...
I-It's Sheldon.
He... sounds a little agitated.
I'm gonna take it in the other room.
Just...
[PARTITION CLATTERING LOUDLY]
[QUIETLY]: Hello again.
Listen, I'm wondering what
you're doing this weekend.
I miss you.
Cool, cool.
You want to go to a movie
or bowl a few frames?
Uh, you know, listen, it's
not a great time right now.
Um, I have a little family over,
and can I call you later?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm sorry. I-I
don't want to interrupt.
I just miss hearing your voice.
Well... here it is,
coming right up out of my throat.
Um, okay,
so, uh, uh, bye.
Bye-bye.
How's Sheldon doing?
- What?
- Sheldon.
You were talking to Sheldon.
Oh... right, yes. [CHUCKLES]
Did you know he has a
picture of that fella Feynman
in his bedroom?
What? So do I.
Peas in a pod.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Oh, darn.
Excuse me.
Yes?
How's it going?
It's Sheldon again.
What do you mean "again"?
Speak.
I recently read an article
about a superconducting supercollider
that might be built in Texas.
What about it?
Well, I thought if there was a lull
in your dinner conversation,
you might casually drop
it as an icebreaker.
Our dinner conversation
is going just fine.
Well, now you have it
in your back pocket.
Carry on.
- [DIAL TONE]
- [CHUCKLES]
[HANGS UP PHONE]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Question... will we be
engaging in coitus tonight?
Because I believe I pulled a hamstring
on the bike ride over.
Why didn't you say something?
Well, I was trying to display machismo,
but it's becoming more and more clear
that there's something
askew in my groin.
Oh, John...
we don't have to do anything.
We can just be together.
Thanks.
But if it's all the same to you,
I'd like to give it the old college try.
[LAUGHING]
♪ Nobody else is stronger than I am ♪
♪ Yesterday I moved a mountain ♪
♪ I bet I could be your hero ♪
♪ I am a mighty little man ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Here you go.
Thank you.
So, you're really gonna go out
with this furniture store fella
while seeing Dr. Sturgis?
It's called playing the field.
And if you'd done some of that,
you wouldn't be saddled
with Bluto in there.
That's not nice.
And is that really necessary?
The Italians call it "corretto."
It means correcting the drink.
So, a drink without
alcohol in it is wrong?
Yep.
- Italian people, they know what's up.
- [SIGHS]
All right, one issue at a time.
So, you're really gonna
date two men simultaneously?
- Two that you know of.
- Oh, Mom.
Come on, don't be such a prude.
I'm not gonna have any babies.
I don't need these
men to take care of me.
Why shouldn't I just enjoy myself?
Well, it isn't very Christian of you.
I got no argument there.
Salute! [CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
Yeah, that fixed it.
Mmm.
♪ ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Oh, Meemaw, no.
Hey, who are you calling?
Dr. Sturgis.
Why?
I saw Meemaw get in a car
with Mr. Rosenbloom.
[DISTORTED]: No...
ADULT SHELDON: I don't know if
it really happened this way,
but to my nine-year-old mind,
my mother was flying.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
So, how's the brisket?
It's good.
It ain't my brisket, but it's good.
I should take you to New York
so you could taste some
authentic Jewish brisket.
How's it different?
Well, it's pretty much the same except
it's-it's a lot juicier
and you can feel the fat
go directly to your heart.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Oh, boy...
I miss that laugh.
So, uh...
what do you think of that idea?
- What idea?
- Going to New York.
Maybe we'll catch a
couple of Broadway shows,
uh, see some sights.
Oh, Ira, gee...
I don't know. [CHUCKLES]
- Seems like a big step.
- Is it?
I think at this time of our lives,
we should travel, see the world.
I guess.
I mean, we're not getting any younger.
What's that supposed to mean?
[STAMMERS]
I mean, I mean, I'm
not getting any younger.
You, on the other hand,
you are a blossoming tulip.
Better.
SHELDON: But I still don't understand.
Your grandmother's a single lady.
She's not committed to any one fella,
and she wants to see
what her options are.
But Dr. Sturgis is the best option.
Well, you might feel that way,
but she's not so sure.
Then we need to tell
her. I'll make the call.
No. We need to mind our business
and maybe pray for her to
make the right decision.
We're gonna leave this up to God?
You think you could do
a better job than God?
Maybe not with creating the universe,
but I bet I could free the Hebrews
with one good plague.
IRA: You can get lox, bagels,
all the trimmings at
3:30 in the morning.
[CHUCKLES] Why would I want that?
Well, you wouldn't. I
mean, it's too heavy.
But you could if you wanted.
[CHUCKLES]
So, what do you think?
Oh, Ira, I don't think so.
All right, what do you say
to a weekend in New Orleans, huh?
We could do one of those
Carnival Cruise things.
You're killing me. [LAUGHS]
I can't do this, I...
Can't do what?
Ira, you're just a wonderful man.
Oh, boy, I don't like
where this is going.
But to tell you the truth,
I'm seeing somebody else.
And we've gone there.
I thought I could do it, uh...
you know, date both of you,
but I-I can't, I can't, I just...
I'm not cut out for it.
Okay, suggestion.
And maybe you've already
thought of this...
but what do you say
you break up with him
and only see me?
[CHUCKLES]
[SOBBING]
I'm sorry.
I thought I could handle this.
- It's okay.
- You know,
you get older, and you
think your skin is thicker...
- It's okay.
- and your heart is tougher.
But it's not, it's the other way around.
I hope this guy knows
what a gift he has in you.
Well, "gift" is a strong word,
but he's enthusiastic.
Good.
May you both be very happy together!
I don't want to celebrate too soon,
but Meemaw and Mr. Rosenbloom
are back, and he was crying.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV]
There'll be more updates as they happen.
I'm done.
Can I please be excused?
Good Lord, did you even chew it?
Not the recommended amount, no.
What's your hurry?
I need to get back to my viewing post.
Fine, go ahead.
What's he expect to see,
staring at Meemaw's house?
[SIGHS] Did you just join this family?
The kid's an oddball.
He's just excited that Meemaw's dating
a man he looks up to.
I wish she could date Tony
Danza... that'd be cool.
What is it with you and Tony Danza?
Well, the show doesn't
come out and say it,
but I'm pretty sure he's the boss.
I think the blonde lady's the boss.
Angela?
Who's the oddball now?
I'm warning you,
once you try my barbecue,
it will ruin you to all the others.
That's what happened to me
with quilted toilet paper.
Once I tried the good stuff,
everything else felt like a Brillo pad.
You paint quite the picture, don't you?
[DOORBELL RINGING]
Oh, gosh.
Excuse me.
Sheldon, this is not cute anymore.
- Connie Tucker?
- Yes?
I have a dinette set from
Rosenbloom's Furniture.
Oh.
I didn't buy any furniture.
I think it's a gift.
Oh, boy.
TONY: I bent down to pick up a book,
and I'll be darned if she didn't
sneak a look at my derriere.
- [LAUGHTER ON TV]
- Oh, man.
You won't believe what's
happening at Meemaw's house.
Is it more interesting
than Who's the Boss?
Doubt it.
[PHONE RINGS]
Rosenbloom's Fine
Furniture. Ira speaking.
Why are you sending me furniture?
I've decided I can't go away quietly.
I'm fighting for your love.
With a dinette set?
Oh, this isn't just any dinette
set. It's our biggest seller.
And it's not pressed wood...
It's oak!
Ira, I don't like this.
Would you prefer a leather sectional?
Uh, what's going on? [CHUCKLES]
Uh,
can I call you back?
I look forward to it.
You shouldn't.
Okay.
I guess you could say
one of my former boyfriends
is trying to win me back with furniture.
Huh. Impressive.
This is real oak.
Was that him on the phone?
Yes. I'm sorry.
Interesting.
What?
Being challenged by another man
is making you more attractive to me.
I don't follow.
I'll have to do some research,
but I'm guessing this
is a genetic instinct
that's raising my libido.
[CHUCKLING]: I need a drink.
Can you believe he tried to
win me back with a dinette set?
I'd give you a dinette
set if you'd leave Texas.
So, would you return it?
Hell no, I'm keeping it.
But then you'll be beholden to him.
[SIGHS]
Would you ever take Ira back?
I don't know.
He's sweet as he can be, but...
there's just something about John.
He's like a cute little
teddy bear, you know?
A brilliant,
bicycle-riding
teddy bear.
I don't even understand
half of what he says.
But...
when he's not around, I just miss him.
Sounds like you're falling in love.
Maybe I am.
Excellent. I love him, too.
Get out of here!
If you don't understand
what Dr. Sturgis says,
I'm happy to explain it to you.
Get!
STURGIS: Excuse me.
I'm looking for Ira.
At your service. What can I do for you?
You, sir, have overstepped your bounds.
[CHUCKLES] I'm sorry, what?
Miss Constance Tucker
made it clear your courtship
was no longer welcome,
and you responded with six chairs,
a table, and an expansion leaf.
Who are you?
John Sturgis,
the man she chose
and your romantic rival.
I-I'm sorry, wait, what-what
is it you want from me?
I want you to give up
your pursuit of Connie.
All right, I'm gonna have
to ask you to leave my store.
Very well.
The line in the sand has been drawn.
Cross it at your own peril.
[QUIETLY]: Weirdo.
What was that?
You heard me.
Sir, I am a man with feelings.
And you have hurt them.
I know you've had a number of...
gentleman callers,
but I've never heard you
speak like this before.
"Gentleman callers"?
And we wonder where Sheldon gets it.
[LAUGHS]
I'm sorry y'all find this funny,
but this is the first time
my mother's expressed
real interest in a man
since Dad died.
Forgive me for wanting to know more.
You really want to know more?
Imagine you're getting on in years,
you and your husband about to retire,
get a little timeshare in Sarasota,
and... suddenly...
he's gone,
and you're all alone.
You mourn, you cry,
but eventually you move on.
You start dating a little,
and it's all good fun.
But always in the back of your mind,
there's that question...
"Will I be alone in the end?"
[SNIFFLES]
Why y'all looking at me for?
[SNIFFLING]
Haven't slept in days.
It's like I'm a lovesick teenager,
except I remember the Truman
administration. [CHUCKLES]
Your feelings are understandable.
Connie is a remarkable woman.
Yes, she is.
But, again, I'm sorry. I should
never have called you weird.
I mean, eh, it was rude.
I've been called much worse.
A professor once
called me ostrobogulous.
I had to look that one up.
What's it mean?
That I'm a weirdo.
[LAUGHS]
John, you're a great guy.
Well, you, too!
But I hope you understand, I just...
I can't give up on Connie.
That's all right.
To tell you the truth,
I'm finding the competition
quite exhilarating.
You are?
Oh, yes.
The night the dinette set arrived,
I did my first push-up in 40 years.
[LAUGHS, SNORTS]
I'm sorry, but I find that to be, uh...
What's the word... Astro-boobulous?
Ostrobogulous.
Exactly.
Now, give me your best price
on one of these
with a cup holder.
John! What a pleasant surprise.
- I have some news for you.
- Oh?
- Mwah. What is that?
- Mwah.
I went to the furniture
store and spoke to Ira.
- Why would you do that?
- To demand
that he respect your
wish to be left alone.
John, it was not your place to do that.
Well, if it helps,
he doesn't plan on leaving you alone.
What the hell were you thinking?!
That I was being chivalrous.
By going behind my back?
You seem upset.
I am upset!
And how I handle Ira is my business!
Well, I hope you do it gently.
He's very vulnerable these days.
You're friends now?
Well, I wouldn't say friends,
but I could see, over time,
- you know, we might...
- Are you two fighting?
No.
Oh, good. [CHUCKLES]
I was almost certain that we were.
We are.
- I'm confused.
- Me, too.
Is this because you went
to the furniture store?
He knows about this?
- BOTH: Yes.
- All right, now, listen,
if this relationship's
gonna have any chance at all,
we have to lay down some ground rules.
Great. I love rules.
I do, too.
I don't want you talking
to him about anything
having to do with anything about us.
Same with you.
And I want you to stop
spying on me with those binoculars
like you're on some
kind of African safari.
And you cannot talk
to Ira or any of my
ex-boyfriends, for that matter.
This list is getting long.
Maybe we should write it down.
Hey.
ADULT SHELDON: In that moment,
I had an epiphany.
I could draw up a contract
for any social relationship.
[WHIRRING]
It was a helpful way to remove ambiguity
in a world that was
often hard to understand.
Article three...
Sheldon will not spy
on Meemaw's house with binoculars.
Type that one in bold.
[CLICKING]
[WHIRRING]
Please sign and date.
You know, Sheldon, I'm
a notary, if that helps.
Just when I thought
you couldn't get cooler.
ADULT SHELDON: I would go on
to draw up such contracts
throughout my life...
With roommates,
with my wife.
Even with my own children.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org