Have been coveted by children
around the world.
I was not one of those children.
What do you think?
I won it bowling.
It was either that
or a Crock-Pot,
and I already got
three of those,
so I thought I'd surprise you.
No, thank you.
Video games are for children.
Sheldon, you are a child.
I just blew the hot
off your SpaghettiOs.
I'm sorry, Meemaw,
I just don't think
it's a very productive
use of my time.
You're a man of science.
Aren't you interested
in doing a little research here?
"Brave adventurer,
prepare to enter a world
"beyond your imagination.
"Where the only sound you'll
hear is your own heart pounding
as you race through
the dark woods."
This sounds terrifying. Really?
You don't even want to try it?
Honestly, I'd have more fun
with the Crock-Pot.
Fine. I'll just play by myself.
That's amusing. Why?
I guess it's the juxtaposition
of an old person
using new technology;
It tickles me.
What if this old person
really tickles you?
I'll play! I'll play!
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
I'm not getting any younger.
I have to read the
instructions first.
Did you know this document
gives us specific legal rights?
We may also have other rights
which vary from state to state?
I did not.
Well, now you do.
All right, I'm ready. Great!
To read the
manufacturer's warranty.
You're killing me.
Hey, George, how y'all been?
Good, good. Hey, fixed your
place up, looking snazzy.
Thanks. Even got
a new water cooler.
It's got those pointy cups,
look like Madonna's bra.
So, what's going on
with your truck,
other than the fact it's
got 130,000 miles on it?
She been running hot. I'm
worried I need a new radiator.
As your friend and neighbor,
I hope not,
but as a businessman,
that'd be pretty sweet.
It could just be the thermostat
not opening right.
That is correct.
How'd you know that?
I took auto repair last year.
And you actually paid attention?
I'm as surprised as you are.
Now we need to put in
a name before we start.
What are you thinking?
We should combine the
letters in our two names,
Sheldon and Meemaw.
Like, ShelMaw?
No, using all the
letters, like...
Emelda Showmen.
Did you just do that
in your head?
Yes, why?
Never mind, just put it down.
All right, here we go.
I thought I was playing.
You don't know how to play;
You didn't read the manual.
You're in charge, Emelda.
Thank you.
Should I go left or right?
Why don't you try going
in that cave?
Why would I do that?
It's probably dangerous.
Sheldon, they wouldn't
have put the cave there
if they didn't
want you to go in it.
Seems unnecessarily
reckless, but okay.
Dark and dangerous.
I told you.
Just keep going.
The box was right,
my heart is pounding.
All right,
good news.
Tell me.
Well, the kid was right...
It's just the thermostat.
Yeah, yeah.
So how long to fix it?
Nothing, 20 minutes. Can I help?
Well, sure. Grab yourself a pair
of coveralls and have at it.
Thanks.
Really?
I'm paying you
so my own son can fix my truck?
Well, we could have
my son do it,
but we know how
that's gonna end.
What are you doing?
Kill him! I'm trying!
Well, what's the problem?
I seem to have weak thumbs.
Pause it.
I'm a little winded.
Why don't you let the old person
give it a shot?
Would you like me to give
you a tutorial first?
Give it to me.
I'll figure it out.
We are such different
people, Meemaw.
Thank you.
Die, you sumbitches, die!
Very different people.
Die, you son bitches!
When I grow up, will I be
a Dallas Cowboys cheerleader?
"Not likely." Darn it.
Did you tell her?
Why don't you tell her?
Tell me what?
Herschel offered me
a part-time job.
Really?
Between that
and football practice,
when would you do your homework?
When does he do it?
Are you okay with this?
Yeah, I think it'll
be good for him.
I don't know, I think his
education should come first.
Come on, Mom. It's not like
I'm gonna graduate
"val-dictator-torian."
You heard him.
Fine, but I want you
here for dinner every night,
and if your grades slip,
you are done.
Thank you. Now go wash up.
And don't get grease
all over my towels.
He really did know his stuff
at the shop. It was impressive.
All right, well,
maybe it'll be a good thing.
How about a Houston
Oilers cheerleader?
"Signs point to yes."
I'm gonna marry a quarterback.
Over the next few days,
I ran to my meemaw's house
so we could save
the 8-bit princess.
And if it's unclear
how important this was,
I ran.
Right behind you,
monster, monster!
I see him!
You're losing life points,
do something!
Calm down, I've got this.
No, no, no, you're going to die!
We're going to have
to restart this level!
Okay, we need to set
a few ground rules.
Rules, love 'em.
Mazes, puzzles, panic attacks,
you're in charge.
Whooping monster butt,
that's my purview.
Understood. However...
Excuse me. Is there
a monster on that screen?
Yes, ma'am.
And can two players swing
the magic sword? No.
So what does that mean
as we go forward?
I have to shut my yap.
Attaboy.
Can I still have a panic attack?
If you do it quietly.
No, no, no.
So me and Herschel dropped
the engine on this Pacer today.
It was so cool.
I had a buddy in high school
had a Pacer
with the flames
painted on the side,
which was funny 'cause
the damn thing caught fire
during the Homecoming parade.
Too bad he didn't know Herschel.
He can fix anything.
Guy's a genius.
You mean a car genius.
Is Dad getting his
feelings hurt? "Yes."
The ball don't lie.
Sorry!
Excuse us.
Thank you.
See you later.
There it is! The cyclops!
I see it! Get it, get it!
I'm trying! Use the sword!
Use the sword! Your yap is open again.
Hello?
What?
It's past his bedtime. Let's go.
Come on, five more minutes?
No. Now say good night
to your grandson.
You'll play with him
again tomorrow.
Good night, Sheldon.
Good night, Meemaw.
Don't play without me.
Of course not.
How old are you?
And I got my answer.
Hey, neighbor, what's up?
Sorry to bother you so late,
but one of my guys
called in sick tomorrow...
So we couldn't find
the key to the palace,
but then I figured out it was
in the hay behind the stables.
Great.
Hey, Herschel. Mary.
I also found us extra life
points inside a demon.
There are demons in this game?
Don't worry, Meemaw
cut his head off.
Anyhoo, I was wondering
if Georgie could come by after
school tomorrow and help me out.
I don't know, Herschel,
he's got football practice.
What's going on?
Herschel's asking if you
want to work after school.
Great, I'll be there.
What about football? What about it?
I mostly sit
on the bench all day.
That's because
you got to earn your way
on to first string.
Or I can earn some money
working for Herschel.
Why don't you and I talk a bit
before you make a decision?
Sorry, I-I didn't mean
to cause a problem.
I'll find somebody else.
Y'all have a good night.
Night, Herschel.Night.
Thanks a lot.
You really want to quit football
to go work in a garage?
Hell yeah.
I thought you loved the game.
I do, but look at me.
I weigh 125 pounds.
That's not important. It's not?
Every time I get tackled,
somebody's got to run over
with smelling salts
just to wake me back up.
Well, this isn't your decision.
You're gonna play football.
You can't make me.
Yeah? Wait and see.
Screw this.
Even while sleeping,
my quest to save
the princess continued,
which was quite a departure
from my usual dreams,
such as determining
the coolest prime number...
Which, by the way, is 73.
Kill it, Meemaw! Kill it!
What do you think I'm trying
to do? It won't die.
Maybe you need
a different weapon.
I already tried the
slingshot and the boomerang.
All I have left is
the damn flute.
It's a piccolo.
Didn't you pay attention
when the old lady gave it to us?
Hello? Meemaw.
I'm sorry for waking you, but
I know how to kill the cyclops.
We have to play the piccolo.
Ooh.
What a great idea, moonpie.
We'll try it tomorrow.
Excellent... Wait.
How'd you answer your phone so
fast? It's not next to your bed.
Well, actually,
I was on my way to the bathroom.
You know us old people
and our bladders.
I'll call you right back.
That fibber.
You're playing
the game right now.
I am not.
I saw you with my binoculars.
How about that.
You promised not to play
without me.
We're a team.
Emelda Showmen, remember?
I'm turning off the game
and going to sleep right now.
You'd better.
I love you, good night.
Binoculars for his birthday.
What was I thinking?
Where's Georgie?
Don't worry about it.
I wasn't worried.
I was practicing chitchat.
Your mother's taking him
to school.
That's not very efficient.
Our car's already going there.
Not that it's any
of your business,
but I needed a break
from your brother.
I certainly understand that.
He's an acquired taste.
Like Grape-Nuts.
The first time I tried it,
I thought I was eating gravel.
But then I put a little sugar
on it and let it get soggy.
Now it's in my top six cereals.
I'll try soaking Georgie
in a bowl of milk.
Sarcasm?
Yeah.
I had a feeling.
The clue was you don't normally
put people in bowls of milk.
I'm Sheldon Cooper's grandmother
and, I need to take him out
of school today.
Sure. What's the reason?
His Aunt Emelda's
not doing well,
and has asked to see him
'fore she goes.
I am so sorry.
Does she want to see
his older brother also?
Nah. She doesn't
like him as much.
Okay. I'll just
track down Sheldon, then.
Boy, do I love a pop quiz.
Will Sheldon Cooper please
come to the main office?
"Ooh," what?
This is hooky, Meemaw.
Hooky is a serious offense.
You're messing with me, right?
Any other kid would be
thrilled their grandma
took them out of school
to play a video game.
You've known me ten years.
When have I ever
messed with you?
I didn't see your kid
at practice today.
Everything all right?
Not really.
That's it? You're not gonna
ask me what's going on?
I just did. You shut me out.
Well, it doesn't mean
you can't persist a little.
You know, this is the kind
of crap I get from my wife.
I do not need it from you.
Sorry.
You're really not gonna ask?
Boy.
Well, moonpie, this is it.
Our final dungeon.
Hard to believe.
Yeah.
Would you like
to fight the last boss?
You think I'm ready?
We couldn't have gotten here
without you.
Well, except for the part
you did when I was sleeping.
We're having a moment here.
Don't ruin it.
I've fought many
digital battles in my life,
but none are as memorable as
this first one with my meemaw.
By handing me the controller,
she was telling me
she believed in me.
That inside my small, fragile
frame beat the heart of a hero.
Behind you, behind you!
What're you doing?
Hit the A. Hit... I know, I'm pressing it.
Hit the A button. I'm pressing it.
Throw a bomb, throw the bomb! Which way?
Throw the bomb.
Hey. You up for some company?
Sure. Come on in.
Sorry about the light beer,
but Brenda's got me
on this health kick.
You are melting away.
Shut up. So, listen...
I feel bad about Georgie
and this whole football thing.
Thanks, but it's not on you.
I appreciate that,
but you got to know
there's an upside to this.
And that would be?
Your son has got a special gift.
A gift?
We are talking
about Georgie, right?
Yeah. I mean, first off,
the kid really knows his way
around an engine,
which is all well and good.
But when it comes
to fixing tires,
I swear, I've never seen
anything like him.
Tires? How do you mean?
George, I've been patching flats
for 25 years.
You know,
slap some soapy water on them,
look for the air bubble.
But your son,
he doesn't need any tricks.
He knows
where the puncture holes are.
He knows?
He knows.
He's got a sixth sense
for tire damage.
I mean,
you got to see him in action.
I-It'll give you chills.
You know, now that you say it,
whenever we had
a leaky football,
he knew exactly
where the hole was.
I am telling you, your boy's got
a future in the tire business.
Goodyear, Firestone, somebody's
gonna scoop him up first round.
Thanks, Herschel.
That does my heart good.
So I guess you got two geniuses
in the family.
Guess I do.
Who knows,
maybe Missy'll make it three.
Or it's two.
I won. I saved the princess.
I knew you could do it!
Yes! We saved her!
We saved the princess!
We did it!
We did it.Yep.
So now what?
We just return
to our ordinary lives?
I guess so.
Or... we could just go to
the store and buy another game.
Since that night,
I've battled orcs, zombies,
Nazis, Nazi-zombies,
a dinosaur in a go-kart,
and played Van Halen's
"Hot for Teacher"
on a stringless, plastic guitar.
But nothing would ever compare
to that first quest
with my meemaw.
Although Leonard pulling
a groin muscle
doingDance Dance Revolution
was a close second.
Talk to me.
Tell me where it hurts.
Gotcha.
I got goose bumps.
Captioning sponsored by.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN