ADULT SHELDON: I'm very much
a creature of habit.
Perhaps it's a trait
I got from my father.
Every night he would go
through the mail,
and every night,
like clockwork,
he would get
very cranky.
- Damn bills.
- George.
ADULT SHELDON:
You'd think he'd get used to it,
but night after night
it upset him all over again.
Jury duty?
Son of a...
George.
ADULT SHELDON:
It was complicated.
I didn't like
seeing him upset,
but what can you do?
I love consistency.
IRS?
This can't be good.
Sure it can.
When is the IRS
ever good?
Perhaps they're writing
to congratulate me
on filing such a beautiful
tax return.
- What's it say?
- Okay. Not so bad.
We owe four dollars
and 22 cents.
What?
- That could've been worse.
- Yeah, tell me about it.
Let me see that.
I'm gonna wash up
for dinner.
You realize they're wrong.
My return was flawless.
I-It's four dollars.
Forget it.
But they're saying
I made a mistake.
You also got us a nice refund.
You did a great job.
ADULT SHELDON:
I appreciated my mother's love,
but what a boy
really craves
is the unconditional approval
of a government agency.
♪ Nobody else
is stronger than I am ♪
♪ Yesterday I moved a mountain
♪ I bet I could be your hero
♪ I am a mighty little man
♪ I am a mighty little man. ♪
*YOUNG SHELDON*
Season 04  Episode 14
Episode Title: "Mitch's Son and the Unconditional Approval of a Government Agency"
[♪]
Yippee-Ki-Yay, Mr. Falcon.
Wait, who is Mr. Falcon?
No one.
Then why'd he say it?
Well, in the real version,
he said a bad word,
but they had
to change it for TV.
TV is so lame.
What did he really say?
That's so much better.
This movie works
on a lot of levels.
Dad, I reviewed the tax
return and I was right.
They're the ones
who made the mistake.
Uh... What are you doing?
Writing a check to the IRS.
But we don't owe them anything.
They're claiming
that I underreported our income,
but I can prove
that they're wrong.
It's not worth
picking a fight with them
over a few bucks.
Just let me call them,
I can sort this out.
Just drop it, we don't want
to get on their radar.
But if you send that check,
it's like admitting
I made a mistake
when I didn't.
Sheldon, sometimes being right
isn't the most important thing.
I'm glad you feel that way,
because, boy, are you wrong.
We're done talking
about this.
ADULT SHELDON: And
there he goes, wrong again.
I'll have the rib eye,
medium rare.
And for you?
Uh, just the house salad,
please.
Very good.
House salad?
You watching your figure?
I have a physical tomorrow.
Oh, so your plan
is to start eating healthy now?
Can't hurt.
It ain't gonna undo 70 years
of red meat and beer.
I'm not trying
to undo it,
I'm just trying to hide it
under some lettuce.
Son of a Mitch.
Melissa Cooper.
What?
I said "Mitch."
There's nothing wrong
with that.
But you meant
another word.
I'm sorry,
what other word?
Just watch it.
Hold on. So you're saying
if I have a friend
whose dad's name is Mitch,
I'm not allowed
to talk about him?
I know what you're doing.
Okay, I just feel bad
for my friend.
That poor son of a Mitch.
Melissa Cooper.
How's that salad?
It sucks.
How's your steak?
You know how they overcook it
sometimes
- so it's a little bit dry?
- Uh-huh.
Not this time.
T's so good.
You know
what else is good?
This radish.
- Would you like some steak?
- Yes.
Then you probably
should've ordered some.
It's delicious.
You are not
a very nice lady.
[softly]:
Mmm.
MALE VOICE:
Psst. Hey-a, kid.
[grunts]
Who is it?
It's me.
The envelope with the IRS check.
What do you want?
You can't let him
send me.
You didn't make a mistake.
Oh, I know that,
but it's too late.
It's not.
The check isn't due for 30 days.
So?
Just go in the kitchen
and take me off the pile.
Buy yourself some time
to straighten this out.
But tampering with the mail
is a federal offense.
I'm not mail yet.
I'm not in the mailbox.
That's the law.
But what if my dad
notices you're missing?
Do it after he leaves for work.
He'll never know.
That's brilliant.
I'm not real,
so technically, you thought of it.
That makes more sense.
ADULT SHELDON:
The next morning, I patiently waited
for my father
to leave for work.
[♪]
Are you leaving for work?
Yeah?
See you. Bye.
Bye.
ADULT SHELDON:
I leapt into action.
My heart was pounding.
I don't know what kind
of bladder control
professional spies have,
but this first-timer
needed to pee pronto.
ADULT SHELDON: Now that I had
prevented my dad from saying
I made a mistake, it was time
to get the IRS to admit theirs.
IRS, Agent Green speaking.
Hello, my name
is Sheldon Cooper.
Forgive me for cutting
right to the chase,
but I'm outside
and my skin is incredibly fair.
Okay, how can I help you?
You sent my family a bill
saying we owe
an additional four dollars and
22 cents, but you're mistaken.
I filed a flawless return.
I'm sorry, how old are you?
That seems irrelevant,
but I'm 11.
Your parents let an 11-year-old
file their federal tax return?
This year. Two years ago,
they let a nine-year-old do it.
Look, these tax codes
are complicated.
If you only made
a four dollar mistake,
that's pretty impressive.
I didn't make a mistake at all.
You did.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
But don't feel bad,
these tax codes are complicated.
Uh-huh.
Okay, I've got your file
right here, and, uh,
looks like you underreported
your income.
Actually, if you check
under charitable donations,
you'll notice
that the money we made
at the garage sale
did not count as taxable income
because we donated it
to the church.
Well, I'll, uh,
I'll have a look into that.
In the future,
you might consider doing that
before you send out
the letter.
So how does this work?
Do you apologize now,
do I get it in writing?
It's no big deal.
It's a colonoscopy.
So?
So,
one of those words means
"colon," and the other means
"shoving a camera up it."
Mm.
I'm surprised you need one.
Did you tell him
about the salad?
It's not funny.
Stop being such a baby.
Something I have pushed out
of my body. You can do this.
Wait, wait,
I got an idea.
Why don't we do it together?
What?
No.
Come on.
It'll be romantic.
You're weird.
- MAN [over TV]: Hey, kids.
- GEORGE SR.: What the hell?
Why are we getting audited?
What? Are you sure
it doesn't say "applauded"?
Perhaps for a job well done?
We're being audited
for the last three years
of our tax returns.
I don't get it.
I mailed in that check
a week ago.
About that.
I can explain.
- Sheldon?
- I just needed some time
to prove there were
no errors in my work.
What did you do?
I took the check
- before Mom mailed it.
- What?
But I called the IRS
and sorted things out.
Clearly you didn't.
I told you to let it go.
I'm sorry.
This could end up
costing us a fortune.
- I can fix it.
- No.
I'm gonna hire an accountant
and have him handle it right.
- But I want to help.
- You've helped enough.
Go to your room.
Yes, sir.
- [groans]
- [laughs]
I feel bad beating you like this
after you bought me drinks.
Okay, I tell you what.
You want to make it
more interesting?
- Sure.
- Okay, how about this?
If I win, you get
a colonoscopy with me.
God, are you still on this?
Come on, why not?
'Cause
I don't wanna.
Well, I don't wanna, either,
but my doctor said I got to.
Well, my doctor
didn't say nothing.
When was the last time
you saw him?
I don't know,
it's been a while.
Yeah, well, like,
"six months" a while,
- "Watergate" a while?
- Drop it.
Uh, last time you saw him,
were they using leeches?
I'm about to take this
pool cue
and beat your doctor
to the punch.
Oh.
That long, huh?
Look, all I'm saying
is you could use a checkup.
I feel fine.
Okay.
At your age, there's nothing
wrong with going in...
I'm not going to the doctor,
so just...
mind your own business.
♪ The Texas honky-tonk blues.
Why didn't you eat with us?
I'm not hungry.
Dad's mad at me.
Mom's not thrilled
with me, either.
Why?
Mom made chicken,
and I said chickens cluck
a lot,
so they should be called
"cluckers."
And some chickens
are moms,
so you could
call them "mother..."
I don't care.
Mom sure did.
What did you do wrong?
I got Dad in trouble
with the IRS.
He has to hire an accountant,
which could cost us
a lot of money.
Dang, makes me not want
to have kids.
Hello.
Well, hey.
Well, you missed it.
Some old broad went
nuts over there
and threw her pool
cue on the table.
- She's crazy.
- Mm.
Sorry.
Well, you're not a
fan of doctors, huh?
They never have
good news.
They just want
to find something wrong.
It's kind of their job.
If something's wrong
with me,
I don't want
to know about it.
That's dumb.
No, it's not.
If I'm gonna drop dead,
I'd rather do it quick
and leave lookin' good.
I want to live so long
- I start looking like a mummy.
- [Chuckles]
You're off
to a strong start.
- Hey.
- [chuckles]
My husband went
to the doctor.
And they found something.
Two days later,
he was in surgery.
Nine months later,
he was dead.
Geez.
I don't want that.
And I, I don't want
to put anybody else
through that.
I'm sorry.
Mm.
I hope you stick
around long enough
to start looking
like a mummy, too.
[chuckles]
I always pictured myself
more the Bride of Frankenstein
type.
Well, you got
the hair for it.
So how's it look?
Do I owe a lot of money?
I don't have a lot of money.
Mm-hmm, I can see that.
Who did these?
Why?
Is it that bad?
They're impeccable.
Oh...
Actually, it was my son.
Well, why don't you just
use him for the audit?
He's 11.
An 11-year-old did these?
Actually, he might've been
nine at the time.
I'm not good with birthdays.
Hey.
Hello.
Playing with your trains?
I'm punishing myself by
looking at them,
but not allowing myself
to run them.
You don't have
to punish yourself.
Because you'd rather do it?
That's fair.
No.
It's okay.
I deserve it.
Actually...
I want you to represent us
at the audit.
But I messed everything up.
You did.
But I also know
if anyone's smart enough
to get us out of this, you are.
Why'd you change your mind?
No reason.
What did the accountant say?
Nothing.
They said my returns were
perfect, didn't they?
Play with your trains.
Why are you readin'
the Bible?
I felt bad about last night,
so I thought
it might be good for me.
Where are you going
with this?
Nowhere, I just want
to make you happy.
Uh-huh.
"And the man increased
"exceedingly,
and had much cattle,
"and maidservants,
and menservants,
- and camels, and asses."
- Okay. Stop.
What? I'm just reading
from Genesis.
- Well, cut it out.
- Fine.
Let's try Exodus.
"And on the seventh
day thou shalt rest:
That thine ox
and thine ass may rest."
That is it,
you are grounded.
For reading the Bible?
The way you are doing it, yes.
Go to your room.
Okay.
I don't have a donkey.
But if I did,
I'd take my ass out of here.
GEORGE SR.:
Hello.
I'm George Cooper.
This is my son Sheldon.
Yes, we spoke on the phone.
You look exactly like
you sound.
Not everybody does.
- Should we get started?
- Yes.
ADULT SHELDON:
I realize some people
may find the ins and outs
of tax law
a little tedious, so allow me
to spice this story up.
Instead of an audit,
imagine this is a showdown
between two warriors
in the most brutal
and exciting form
of combat there is...
chess.
[♪]
Am I the only one
who just got chills?
Let's start with the
business deductions
from Schedule A on the
tax return dated
1989.
ADULT SHELDON:
I know, bold opening move.
Don't worry,
I came to play.
Happy to.
I've got those receipts
right here.
Dated, highlighted...
and itemized.
ADULT SHELDON:
Told you.
[♪]
For the next three hours,
we battled it out.
Two mighty brains
locked in mortal tax code
combat.
[♪]
Justify this expense.
Our AGI was less than
50,000.
Improper classification.
Rolled over
from the previous fiscal year.
The receipt has
barbecue sauce on it.
- Dad.
- Sorry.
So,
you are remarkably well-versed
in the tax code.
Thank you. It's nice of you
to do your parents' returns
for free every year.
Oh, I don't do it
for free.
My dad buys me
a model train afterwards.
Interesting.
So you accept payment
even though you're not
a licensed tax professional?
[♪]
In clear violation
of federal law.
Check.
ADULT SHELDON: I had walked
right into his trap.
Excuse me, I need
to use the restroom.
[chuckles softly]
So,
catch that Cowboys game last...
- No.
- Yeah.
[phone rings]
Ballard's.
- Hello.
- Hey, what's up?
You'll be happy to know
I went out and got a checkup.
Fantastic.
Yeah, great, just great.
And now you can
shut up about it.
Well, how'd it go?
Good news,
bad news.
- Uh-oh.
- Good news is I'm fine.
Well, now, isn't that
comforting to know?
Don't be smug.
So what's the bad news?
He wants me to have
a colonoscopy.
Great!
Oh, my gosh,
we can do it together!
Can't you just feel
the romance?
No, you weirdo.
[chuckles]
There you are.
Hey,
we're waiting on you.
I want to go home.
What are you talking about?
We're not done yet.
Yes, we are.
I made a mistake
that's gonna cost us
a lot of money
that we don't have.
I feel so stupid.
Hey.
It's okay to feel stupid.
No, it's not.
It just means you're growing.
If you don't look back
and think you were dumb,
then you, then you haven't
learned anything.
So what do we do?
We get back in there.
What if we lose?
Doesn't matter...
win or lose,
we don't give up,
all right?
Now let's get
in there and show 'em
what we're made of...
What do you say?
I've heard you give that exact
same pep talk at football games.
Well, I didn't have
a special one prepared.
That's all right.
I feel properly pepped.
So...
where were we?
Check.
It's true.
I made a mistake.
But my dad taught me
that's okay.
Wait.
My dad's a teacher.
Which means, my doing our taxes
wasn't work for-hire,
but an economics lesson
he was teaching me.
[♪]
Therefore, the train
he bought me wasn't payment
for unlicensed work,
it was a reward
for successfully
completing my lesson.
So it does not violate
the statute,
and since the value of the train
is less than $10,000,
there's no additional gift tax.
Checkmate.
[sighs]
[applause]
Well, I guess
that wraps it up.
Is it over?
What happened?
We won.
Wait, we don't owe anything?
No, your returns are
all in order.
Well done.
Thank you.
Your son's
extremely intelligent.
Yep.
I hope you audit us next year,
so I can run circles
around you again.
Until he says something stupid.
Let's go.
[gags]
[grunts]
I can't believe
we have to drink
- so much of that garbage.
- [sighs]
Well, the important thing is,
we get to do it together, dear.
You are so
full of crap.
Well, not for much
longer.
Excuse me,
the festivities have begun.
You're taking
that whole thing with you?
I'm gonna be a while.
Subtitles
Synchronized by srjanapala