ADULT SHELDON: While my sister
and I are twins, we've always
been different. By the age of two,
I was reading books.
Missy was content to eat them.
By five, I had a healthy appreciation
for a well-organized work space.
My sister, less so.
- [MISSY GIGGLES]
- Which is not to say
she doesn't have qualities I admire.
Get it! Get it!
It's just a spider. Calm down.
It's got eight legs and fangs.
I see no reason to be calm.
Did you kill it?
- Yup.
- Are you sure?
- You tell me.
- [YELLING]
The bond between twins is
an incredibly close one,
which is why I moved
1,500 miles to California
the first chance I got.
♪ Nobody else is stronger than I am ♪
♪ Yesterday I moved a mountain ♪
♪ I bet I could be your hero ♪
♪ I am a mighty little man ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Hey.
- Hello.
- You got a minute?
John has something he
wants to talk to you about.
I brought you kolaches.
Ooh, yummy.
Mmm. Mmm. [CHUCKLES]
So, what's up?
You comin' to me to ask for
Connie's hand in marriage?
No.
But if that were to come to pass,
are you authorized to bless the union?
He was joking.
Oh.
- Tell him.
- Okay.
So, some colleagues of mine
at the university are doing
a research study on twins.
I told them about
Sheldon and his sister,
and they were most intrigued.
Uh, what kind of study?
It's a longitudinal investigation
of environmental and genetic factors
in the development of
cognitive and other capacities
in pairs of fraternal
and identical twins.
You asked.
[CHUCKLES]: Well, geez,
I don't... I don't know
if I want some scientists
pokin' and proddin' the kids.
Oh, but they wouldn't
be poked and prodded.
They just have to, you
know, answer some questions.
And maybe some puzzles and tests.
That's not too bad. Where is it?
Houston. Oh, it just got bad.
That's... that's a long drive.
It does pay $50 an hour
plus gas and expenses.
Really?
I told you to start with that.
Oh.
No. See, Mary, that's the best part...
There's no pokin' and proddin'. Plus,
you know how much Sheldon
loves puzzles and tests.
I'm not sure.
[SIGHS] Think about the money.
50 bucks an hour, four
or five hours a week.
That-That's more than our mortgage.
I know, I know.
But Sheldon's already self-conscious
about being different from other kids.
I worry how this might affect him.
You're being too
protective. He's a rock.
A rock?
Are we raising the same child?
And what about Missy?
Aren't these tests
gonna make her feel bad
that she's not as smart as Sheldon?
[SNORTS] I'm not as smart as Sheldon.
Doesn't make me feel bad.
And we could put the money aside
for their college education.
That's a good point.
It's a great point.
I don't have to tell
you, times are changing.
Kids are pitching in.
Like that Webster kid on TV...
He's making buckets of
money for his parents.
Well...
I suppose we could give it a try.
There you go. I'll call Sturgis,
tell him we're in.
Baby, I'm getting a fishing boat.
So, Sheldon, Missy, we
got some exciting news.
- Georgie took a bath?
- No.
And how come I don't get exciting news?
This isn't about you.
But after dinner, why
don't you go rinse off?
So, what's up?
Well, a couple of scientists at the college
where Dr. Sturgis teaches are doing
a research study on twins.
They want to meet you guys,
ask you some questions.
Oh, boy, a research study.
Will they give us written tests?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Oh, boy.
Now, you don't have to do
this if you don't want to.
It's purely volunteer.
I don't want to do it.
- Why not?
- They probably just want to find out
why you're so smart
and I'm just average.
[QUIETLY]: Average?
That's a little generous.
Why don't they want to test me?
- Georgie, not now.
- 'Cause I'm available.
Listen, why don't we just
go there this Saturday
and give it a try?
And if you don't like it,
we don't have to do it again.
Or they'll love it,
and they'll do it till
they're 18, 19 years old.
I already love it.
My man. Missy?
I believe there might be
a Dairy Queen on the way there.
Can I get an Oreo Blizzard?
You know what I think?
I think you're smarter than him.
Dr. Thorpe and Dr. Pilson,
here are your research volunteers,
Sheldon and Missy.
So nice to meet you.
Thank you for
participating in our study.
Always happy to help advance
our understanding of me.
I'm just in it for the Dairy Queen.
All right.
Um, if you two wouldn't
mind waiting here,
we'd like to start by talking
to your mom, dad, and grandma.
Why?
Jut to get some background information
on the both of you.
Smart. Ask how old I was when
I completed potty training.
You won't believe it.
I'll do that.
Will you keep an eye on 'em?
Well, I'll try, but
if they start running,
you may never see them again.
[LAUGHS]
Shall we?
We are on the clock, right?
- George.
- Hmm?
[CHUCKLES] Boy, this brings
back some memories.
- How come?
- Well, when I was your age,
I was also taken to a university
to be studied.
Because they thought
you were really smart?
Because they thought I
was clinically insane.
And it wasn't just me.
Did you know that when Albert Einstein
was a little boy, his parents worried
there was something wrong with him?
Because he couldn't comb his hair?
No, that was a choice
he made later in life.
When he was young,
he wanted nothing to
do with other children,
and would often have
extreme temper tantrums.
He sounds like you.
I know. Isn't it great?
Well, to be perfectly honest,
Sheldon has always avoided
children his own age.
Tell 'em about temper tantrums.
They're not temper tantrums,
he just has strong opinions.
[CHUCKLES] Yeah,
like when you yell and stomp your feet,
and slam the door off its hinge.
They're scientists. You can't trick 'em.
And, as for Missy,
she's just the opposite.
Loves to be around
people and other kids.
Makes friends easy.
Does she have temper tantrums as well?
Nope. She's very even-keeled.
Except for when she's eating.
You put your hand near her face
when she's working on a lamb chop,
she will bite off a finger.
[LAUGHS] Our daughter doesn't bite.
Right here, Thanksgiving, 1986.
Was there anything unusual
about your pregnancy?
- No, not that I remember.
- Really?
You cried for, like, seven months.
Those were tears of joy. [WEAK LAUGH]
What about all those
times you punched me?
Punches of joy.
You're not gonna get much
out of Fred and Wilma here.
Why don't you just get
crackin' on the kids?
Okay, Sheldon, this first
battery of tests measures
basic problem-solving abilities.
Is the Kaufman test or the
Wechsler Intelligence Scale?
Are you familiar with those?
It's embarrassing, but I
enjoy a little light reading
in the bathroom.
Okay. Are you ready?
- Will I be timed?
- Yes.
- Fantastic.
- [STOPWATCH CLICKS]
Okay, Missy,
the first thing we're gonna do is test
your problem-solving ability.
- Okay.
- You ready?
I just have one question.
What's that?
Do you always wear your hair up?
Uh, well, usually at work, yes.
I bet it looks cute down.
Thank you. Okay,
you're all set.
Is that camera gonna be on?
Yes.
Can you move it over to that side?
Why?
If I've learned one thing
from school picture day,
it's that I look better from that side.
Sure, I'll move it.
Okay...
And bring it a little closer.
How's that?
- Great.
- Okay.
- [SIGHS] Whenever you're ready.
- Wait.
Do I have any Oreos in my teeth?
No.
- Ready to start?
- One last thing.
Did you ever think of wearing
that white coat with a belt?
- No.
- You should.
'Cause you have a very nice figure,
and it's lost in there.
Hey, check this out.
Did you see Honey, I Shrunk the Kids?
- No.
- You should.
'Cause there's a lot of
good science stuff in it.
[LAUGHING]
Kudos on the question
"Which train gets to St. Louis first?"
Hmm.
I have to tell you something.
Why don't you finish the test first.
This can't wait.
The other doctor's got a crush on you.
Oh, dear Lord.
Oh, um...
I don't... I don't think so.
Let's get back to the test.
Okay.
Why? What did you see?
When you're not looking,
he stares at your tushy.
[WHISPERING]: Really?
Imagine if you wore the belt.
Clever girl.
That would accentuate her buttocks.
I can't watch. Switch
it back to Sheldon.
Hot dog, syllogisms.
If all squares are parallelograms,
and all squares are rectangles,
then some parallelograms are rectangles.
Who was this test made for, children?
I'm bored. Turn it back to Missy.
Go ahead.
This question about a
train going to "S-T" Louis
makes no sense.
DR. THORPE: It's okay to guess.
Take your time, baby.
The meter's running.
[CASH REGISTER DINGS]
DR. THORPE: Well,
thank you all very much.
This was a great start.
Thank you. Did you have fun?
I got to take a test on
a Saturday, heck yeah!
He's like a young version of
me, but without corrective shoes.
Missy, what'd you think?
The tests were just okay,
but I like Sandra.
Well, thank you, Missy. I like you, too.
PILSON: All right,
we'll see y'all next Saturday.
You bet we will.
Good God, George, have a little dignity.
Hm.
Are you doing something
different with your hair?
No, uh, why?
No reason, just looks nice.
Oh! [CHUCKLES] Thank you.
Um, uh, what do you
think about maybe stopping
for a drink after, to
discuss the test results?
I would like that.
♪ ♪
Oh, yeah.
Get down.
[DOOR OPENS]
- MARY: We're home.
- Hey.
- What you watching?
- Soul Train.
I like trains.
It's not that kind of train, dummy.
Well that seems like false advertising.
Ooh, you sexy little thing.
MARY: George!
Oh.
I do not like what this
study is doing to Sheldon.
What're you talking
about? He had a great time.
All the way home all he could talk about
is how that doctor thought he
was so smart. It's not healthy.
Would it make you feel any better
if I told you how much
money we made today?
No, it would not.
$300.
- Really?
- Cash.
Okay, well, still, I...
I'm not interested in
profiting off my children.
You see, honey, that's where
you and I are very different.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Boats.
Sheldon, what do you think
is happening in this picture?
Easy. There are four
chimpanzees in a living room.
PILSON: Okay, but what
can you tell me about them?
They're not behaving like chimpanzees.
Anything else?
Chimpanzees don't drink tea.
Is that it?
Well, I suppose it might be coffee,
but they don't drink that either.
Anything interesting
about their body language?
No.
I think they found his kryptonite.
THORPE: Missy,
what do you think is
happening in this picture?
The girl monkey on the couch
is telling the guy monkey a secret.
Must be something juicy,
'cause he's smiling.
Anything else?
It might be dirty,
'cause this girl monkey is sending
the kid monkey out of the room.
He doesn't want to go. He looks sad.
Is that all?
The monkeys on the
couch are drinking tea,
so it's a tea party.
Okay, very good. Let's
look at another picture.
I'm not done. The monkey in the painting
is wearing an old lady hat,
so she's probably a meemaw monkey.
She's not at the party,
so she must be bowling or dead.
Well, Missy won that round.
It's actually not a contest, George.
This is Texas. Everything's a contest.
A woman in a doorway.
Anything else?
She's holding her head with her hand.
And what do you think that means?
Um...
Wouldn't you rather ask me
about trains going to St. Louis?
Good gravy, she's sad, Sheldon, come on.
Oh, she's very upset.
I don't know why.
Oh! Maybe she wasn't invited
to the tea party at the monkey house.
[CHUCKLES]
Also, she's wearing
a belt, like you are.
Nice going. Very cute.
[MOUTHS]
And I'm loving the hair.
[WHISPERS]: Yeah.
A lion sitting in a
chair, holding a pipe.
Good.
But what do you think is on his mind?
How should I know? Maybe he's wondering
why he's posing for a silly picture
instead of eating a gazelle.
PILSON: Anything else?
What exactly are we doing here?
I thought the purpose of this study
was to find out how smart I am.
PILSON: That's what we're doing,
but there are different
kinds of intelligence.
Poppycock!
There's only one kind of intelligence...
George, Sheldon's getting upset.
I don't like it.
All right, I'll just
change it back to Missy.
You are an insightful young lady.
I don't know what that
means, but thank you.
It means perceptive.
You see things most people miss.
My name is Missy... go figure.
Have you always been that way?
I guess so. I think when
you're on your own a lot,
you get good at seeing
that kind of stuff.
- THORPE: Really?
- MISSY: My dad
does football with my older brother,
so they're like a team.
And my mom and meemaw spend all
their time fussing over Sheldon,
so they're like a team, too.
So no one's on your team?
Nope.
It's just me.
Oh, Lord.
Hey, what's up with
you and Dr. Pillsbury?
Dr. Pilson?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh.
You can't say 'cause we're on camera.
[SIGHS]
Insightful.
A little late for me to start cooking.
- Why don't we stop somewhere for dinner.
- Really?
The five of us? That's kind of pricey.
Would you rather buy a fishing boat?
You're a blabbermouth, you know that?
[MEEMAW LAUGHS]
Missy, we're gonna eat in a restaurant.
Where would you like to go?
I get to pick?
Why don't I get to pick?
Because your sister's getting to pick.
It's not just about you in this house.
What do you think, baby?
I pick...
Red Lobster.
You got it.
Damn.
There goes our per diem.
George, you got a minute?
- What's up?
- Not you, him.
What?
Sheldon told me that we get
paid to go to that college
and answer their questions.
Yeah, so?
I want to know how much we're making.
Why?
'Cause I want my fair share.
Is that so?
What do you think your fair share is?
Half.
Hm, guess that sounds right.
So how much are we making?
$7.50 a week.
- Really?
- Really.
Well, I want half that.
Which is?
Hang on.
Sheldon!
Can we put on Soul Train?
Why?
There's a girl on there
I kind of want to marry.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN