Subtitles: Luםs Filipe Bernardes
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
So, the key for the lock on top
and the one for below.
You're not staying?
No, I prefer not to.
Too many memories.
- It's good for you?
- Yeah, of course. I understand.
- See you later.
- Okay.
Lewis.
Lewis, is that you?
Maureen.
- I don't know when I fell asleep.
- So...
There was a presence.
I felt something... I just can't...
I can't tell, it was too far.
You must make contact.
I think there might need to be
two of us for that.
There wasn't enough pull
because I felt something,
it was just keeping its distance.
Come here.
Is it a cross?
Yes.
Has that always been there?
She said that she couldn't
make a contact.
Does she still feel a presence?
Yes, she says the house is inhabited.
Well, we can't buy unless we're sure.
We need to know if it's benevolent or not.
It's too much of an investment.
Hi, uh... so there...
...could be no one... uh...
but there could be something.
I need more time, I think,
It's extremely difficult to find
a porthole into the spirit world...
That's just the way that it is.
I was in Stockholm last week...
...and I saw a wonderful exhibition
at the Modern Art Museum.
Hilma af Klint,
have you ever heard of her?
No.
She said that spirits
commissioned her paintings.
She invented abstract art before
Kandinsky and Malevitch in 1906.
She claimed that the spirit world
communicated with us...
...through her.
"Abstract"
"Pioneer"
What fascinated me when I discovered
Hilma af Klint's work was...
that these grand and enigmatic paintings
had been painted in the early 1900's.
And that they were made
by a Swedish female artist...
...that I hadn't heard about before.
Maybe the most fascinating part
is that these pieces...
...were made before the conception
of abstract art.
But Hilma af Klint kept her art secret.
She was sure that they wouldn't
be understood during her life.
In her will she decided that they would
only be shown 20 years after her death.
A hundred years ago Hilma af Klint
painted for the future...
...and the future is here now.
Are you okay?
We didn't bore you too much
at reception?
No, no more than normal.
I lost my passport.
- How long will she be in Vienna for?
- Two days.
I put everything on a rack.
You have the leather pants
from the new collection.
They're Kyra's style.
I mean, I can see her in them.
Are we able to cut them,
is that possible? They'll be too big.
Let me look into this.
I'll get them for you from the studio.
We're not really supposed to, but...
Please, you bring them back
as soon as you can,
otherwise I'll be in big trouble.
Of course. She's going to need something
a little flashier for the AmFAR dinner.
Yes.
That's the stuff Louis set aside
for the dinner.
If Louis likes it, then she'll love it.
- You like it?
- Hm.
So does Louis.
It's no easy to wear.
It's sensual and strong.
I'll take it.
And some boots.
Okay.
Think I'll take both bags...
and this belt.
You know her.
I don't want to risk it.
Kyra will want the brown one for sure.
Or the blue, or neither.
Uh... she gave me a blank check.
Do you take deposits?
- Yes.
- Okay
It's 4.500.
500 for the belt
and 2.000 for each bag.
Great.
Maureen, I got back but I have
to leave right away.
We'll miss each other.
I'm off to Milan tomorrow morning.
I'm leaving an envelope with what
I owe you for the past two weeks.
Take care, Kyra.
P.S. I left my Mac on the desk.
Can you do the upgrade for me?
Hilma af Klint has moved
in spiritualist circles...
...and participated in sיances.
Later she was also a medium.
What actually is regarded
as the essence of spiritualism?
Well, the central idea of spiritualism...
...is the idea that there is a world
beyond our world.
And spiritualists try to give empirical
proof of this world.
In 1848, The Fox sisters heard rappings...
...and they interpreted these rappings
as messages from a deceased person.
And that was for them...
...a real proof of the existence
of this higher world beyond our world.
It's interesting that the Morse code
had been invented two years earlier.
Spiritualists were always very close
to technological avant-garde.
For example, the first
abstract photographs...
...have been taken by spiritualists.
Hilma af Klint believed that she received
the abstract paintings...
... from higher levels of consciousness.
When she started to paint as a medium...
...she rejected the skills she had learned
at the Art Academy.
And that was due to the influence
of spiritualism and of theosophy.
When you mention theosophy,
what was Rudolph Steiner's
view on abstract art?
Steiner rejected abstract paintings.
But that's not the whole story.
A lot of things...
- Hi.
- I'm trying to reach you for a week.
I know. I've been working...
a lot.
Okay.
How's it going with Kyra?
I... I never see her.
We leave each other messages.
I hate this job, actually.
I fucking hate her. She sucks.
That's not what you said before.
I know, I was just happy to stay
in Paris and pay my rent.
Yeah, but what's changed?
I spend my days doing bullshit
that doesn't interest me...
...and keeps me from what does.
It's driving me fucking crazy.
You should come here.
Yeah, to the Sultanate of Oman.
I'll be here another two months.
I thought you were almost done.
I finished reconfiguring
the Embassy's computer system...
...and now I'm just waiting
for the security protocols.
When do you think you'll get those?
It could be tomorrow,
it could be next month.
And once I get them I start
to install and configure them.
Come to Muscat.
Look. Came to the seaside
for the weekend.
- Wow.
- It's beautiful.
And what the hell
would I do in Muscat?
What the hell are you doing in Paris?
You know... I'm waiting.
I have to wait.
It's been three months.
I think I felt something.
I need to go back to Lewis's house.
I really think I felt something.
You think you felt something
or are you sure?
I just need to see it
to the end, that's all.
This is perfect.
This works... thank you.
Let's see this.
Actually this might be perfect.
I'd like to see them on you.
You don't want to try them on?
I... you know her.
I can't.
But you want to.
Sure, if you could keep
your mouth shut maybe.
But you totally dicked me over
the last time I did it.
Try on the shoes at least.
I'll get them.
They're the same size.
She won't have to send them back.
Okay, Vincent.
You have to promise me...
Not one word.
- Not one word.
- My lips are sealed.
Really? Okay, well, if there's traffic,
there's traffic.
There's nothing you can do about it.
They'll wait. They just need
a little daylight, it's okay.
No, I can't wait. I have an appointment.
I'll meet you at your place
later this afternoon.
Okay.
The leather pants.
They're great, right?
No, not these. You can't keep...
I promised...
I promised that I'd bring them
back in the morning.
Please don't do that to me. I...
I'm telling them right now.
It's no problem, don't worry. Okay.
Hey, so she is on her way. She's late.
Her plane from Milan was just delayed.
But where is she?
She's on the highway.
Just traffic apparently.
Can you stand in for her?
It will save us some time.
- I have to leave at 4 o'clock.
- Yes, it's okay.
Good, perfect. Come.
- You think she'll ditch everything?
- Yeah, she'll ditch everything.
- I brought you three options, so...
- And with that we'll make it through?
I... can't make any promises.
I'd feel more comfortable
if you stayed.
- You scared of Kyra?
- I hear she's a monster.
Okay.
Great.
This is your left ventricle.
It's just slightly larger in size.
It was exactly the same
for your twin brother.
You can live with it and die at 100.
Or at 27.
I treated Lewis
just like I'm treating you.
An ultrasound twice a year.
There was no sign, nothing.
One day it just gave way.
Don't be scared, Maureen. What happened
to Lewis was very exceptional.
You can get up.
Everything is fine.
You just need to keep avoiding
both intense physical efforts...
...and extreme emotions.
Like Lewis did.
- I mean... he built cabinets.
- I know.
You know, he wanted to turn
that house into a...
...a studio where he could teach
and just practice carpentry.
He really considered it his future.
I'll see you again in six months.
I have no idea where
I'm going to be in six months.
Good evening, Maureen.
Excuse me, we haven't met.
I'm Ingo.
Hi. Sorry, is Kyra here?
In her room with her lawyer. They've been
on a conference call for an hour.
Problems with the Foundation.
I'm just here to pick up
a few things. She was aware.
- Do you know where they are?
- There's one garment bag over there.
Um... just a random question,
but did you happen to know about
two pairs of leather pants?
They should be in the bags.
- She wants to keep them.
- Oh.
Okay.
She's just in there?
Oh, she's uh... She's a real fucking
pain in the ass, right?
We've been working on this
for six months.
We can't just call off the press trip
at the last minute.
Hey, Kyra.
We have a three-year-old gorilla
who's been gone for three weeks...
and now we have a problem
with the whole family.
Mrs. Gellman's husband invests
a lot of time and money...
...in gorilla habitat preservation.
He cares deeply about gorillas.
But if things go wrong, this reflects
really badly on his business interests.
I just want to ask you one question.
This is serious.
You need to take care of it.
- Hello!
- The female is depressive.
The male Ngabo, you've dealt with him,
is becoming aggressive.
Ngabo can become very aggressive
in stressful situations.
- I remember very well, thank you.
- Hey, Kyra...
Where are they now,
where are the gorillas?
Well, they wander off farther
and farther into the mountain.
- And it's difficult to monitor them.
- We can't cancel the reporters.
We have contractual obligations.
- We need those gorillas to be there.
- Just one quick question.
I'm hearing problems
but I'm not hearing solutions.
Do you mind if I smoke?
You have nothing to do
besides dresscue her?
Really find it worthy of your time?
Um... do you have a better offer?
Not exactly, but...
I'm a correspondent
for men's Vogue in Berlin.
I can put a word in for you.
Thank you.
But, you know, magazines
aren't really my thing.
They sell shit and...
mainly for advertisers rather than readers.
So what? You already have
a stupid job.
It wouldn't change a thing
and the pay is better.
Not for me.
Some highly regarded photographers
publish in fashion magazines.
- Are they free?
- I suppose so.
Yeah? They get to choose the brands
and the subjects they shoot?
No, that is correct.
I don't really see the freedom in that.
I'm gonna go.
I'll take the dress and the bags.
You really need to tell her
she's got to return those pants.
I'll call and come back tomorrow.
Do you know if she'll be here tomorrow?
Just ask her.
She told me to leave.
And you're not leaving.
I'm waiting for her to finish.
I want to speak with her.
She wants to dump me.
How long has it been?
Two years.
But she's scared her husband
will find out.
I'm sure he suspects something.
- Are you in love with her?
- Love?
It never crossed my mind, no...
It's just physical.
What are you doing in Paris?
I'm... waiting.
I'm gonna go.
What are you waiting for?
My uh... brother died here.
My twin brother died in Paris.
- Accident?
- No.
A heart attack.
I actually have the same malformation.
- Does it scare you?
- No.
And It didn't scare him.
You're going to stay here
to mourn him.
No, I'm waiting,
I told you I was waiting.
What are you waiting for?
So we made this oath...
...that whoever died first
would send the other a sign.
A sign?
From... from the afterlife?
You could call it that,
you could call it a million things.
But how do you know if it's a sign?
I'm a medium.
He was... he was a medium.
I'll just know it.
Have you communicated with spirits before?
Um... Lewis thought there were spirits.
I'm less sure.
But... yes.
Uh... somewhat.
There are invisible presences
around us...
...always.
Whether or not they're the souls
of the dead, I don't know but...
I mean, when you're a medium
you just sort of attune...
...to a sort of uh...
...vibe.
What do you mean by vibe?
It's an intuition thing...
it's a feeling you...
You see this door...
...it's only like slightly ajar.
I also think that.
The soul...
...continues to exist after death.
I don't even know if I believe in that.
But Lewis did.
And uh...
I have to give his spirit,
or whatever you want to call it...
...a chance to prove him right.
- Until when?
- I had a sign.
- Ah, yeah?
- Yeah.
Are you sure?
No. That's why I'm still waiting.
And then?
And then, I guess I'll live my life and...
...let it go.
I'll come for you in the morning.
Or before. Call when you want.
Okay.
Hey!
And thank you.
So we thought about it,
and we're renovating.
I think that's what Lewis
would've wanted.
I just wanted Maureen to be
at peace with this place.
And with Lewis's spirit.
I... I just wanted to say...
Lewis would have been very happy
that this house is in your hands and...
...that I'm very glad too.
Now, it's your house...
...and I'll forget it.
Come on.
I need more from you.
I'm gonna need more from you.
Give me one more sign.
Anything.
Give me the tiniest thing.
Is that it?
Is it to tell me
that there's no afterlife?
Is it to tell me you can see me,
you just cannot talk to me?
Because I don't care what you do
with the fucking plumbing.
I need you to fucking talk to me.
Please, I don't understand.
I know my brother.
And you're not my brother.
You're not.
Oh shit!
Ladies and gentlemen, train 9040,
departing to London at 9:35...
...is now ready for boarding.
Platform 10.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I prepared everything Kyra asked for.
Two dresses she picked
from the photograph...
...and a furred one that didn't
photograph so well...
...but I think she'll like it.
Which one?
This one there.
It's silk organza.
In the photo you kind of lose
some of the sheen but...
...it really plays well with the light.
Oh, yes, it's cool.
It's really cool.
The harness comes in
in different colors as well.
- Can I see them?
- Yeah.
There you go.
We've got gold, black and nude.
Black.
It's not for all tastes
but I think it'll look amazing on Kyra.
Do you want to try it?
Come.
Just a moment.
Do you want to try the dress?
No.
Well, I'll take it in two colors
so she has the option.
Cool. I'll get it all
packed up for you.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen,
we wish to inform you that train
9022, 14:20 departure to Paris...
...is now ready for boarding
at platform 5.
- Maureen.
- Oh, Kyra... I'm on...
I'm on the train to Paris.
I'll drop the stuff off this evening.
When do you get back?
Even if it's early afternoon, it's okay.
It'll be ready for you in a garment bag.
I have to pick up the jewelry from Cartier.
But everything else is ready.
I would prefer it in euros
if that's not a problem.
You could ask your driver to stop
at an ATM on the way back from CDT...
It'll take two seconds.
It was 400.
We agreed on 400.
There are a couple
of taxi receipts as well.
See you tomorrow.
Ladies and gentlemen, we will soon
be arriving at our final destination.
Please check all your luggage
before leaving the train.
Mind the gap.
Hi.
How are you?
You're sure the spirit
is not there anymore.
Yes.
She vomited this ectoplasm...
...and left.
The ectoplasm lingered for a minute
or less and then also just disappeared.
Do you have any idea
what she wanted?
She was really angry, and very violent.
Maybe she had a score to settle.
I think she was lost.
I don't think she wants to come back.
I don't think she'll be there again.
And what about Lewis?
It's been ninety-five days.
Jיrפme and Cassandre are going
to buy the house.
Good.
Lewis really loved them,
so that's perfect.
What about you?
What will you do with the money?
Nothing.
Nothing?
I don't know.
I'm not sure I can buy something else.
I'm not confident enough
about the future.
Let me show you.
I don't think you understand.
I definitely understand.
Trust me.
Uh... I met someone.
That's like you... oh.
Well...
You must have known him before.
Kind of uh...
...a friend of a friend.
After Lewis died
he reached out to me and...
we grew... we grew closer.
You're shocked.
No! Good.
I wasn't...
I wasn't expecting it but...
of course.
I will always love Lewis but I can't
spend my life in mourning.
I'm not interested in mourning.
Suffering and pain are hard enough.
And I think now I want life.
The other day you said
Victor Hugo actually, you know,
he said that he communicated with spirits.
But what do you mean by that?
- Like actually talk to them?
- Yes,
...when he was in exile in Jersey
he turned tables...
...he conversed with famous
historical figures...
...like, even biblical ones...
It's pretty out there.
How?
I don't really know.
No, I mean, literally.
Verbally, or with an alphabet?
Ah, not the alphabet.
They tried but the spirit refused.
So what did he do?
With a pedestal table...
...the leg would tap on the floor, like...
once for yes, twice for no.
Like one for a, two for b,
and so on, like 26 for z.
Well, that would take an unbelievable
amount of time.
Yeah, there are pages and pages
of transcriptions.
But, dude, it's got to be bullshit.
It's invented.
- I don't know.
- There's no way that happened.
No, he really believed it.
And it wasn't intended for publication,
so why make it up?
I think that whoever did the transcripts
must have adapted them,
filled in the gaps.
- Sounds like stenography, kind of.
- Yes, that's a good analogy.
But if you're interested,
there's a TV movie from the '60s...
...that depicts the sיance.
It's really tacky but seems accurate.
I'll find the title for you but...
if you type in, like,
Hugo + Jersey + turning tables
on YouTube, you'll find it.
- Crazy dog!
- So long.
Quiet, sit!
"Victor Hugo in Jersey"
The being called the white lady asked me
on the first day a thing that I did.
I know that a being,
afraid of coming, ran away.
Is there someone here?
If yes, knock once...
if no, knock twice.
Before I ask you who you are,
I'll ask you a question.
But first, this question:
do you see it in my thoughts?
Do you want to answer it?
Then talk.
The mountain is my grave.
I'm God's breath, I go up and down,
I want the sky and the earth wants me.
The stars pull me by my hair...
...and the nails of the coffin
hold me by my feet.
The darkness screams to me: "Down!"
and the suns say "Up!".
I'm the uncomforted of the horizon.
I'm the night watcher of countless graves,
emptying his eyes in empty skulls.
I'm the cause of bad dreams.
I want you to see us clearly,
and no longer in the shadows.
Is that two sides of one same face?
I'm everywhere but I'm only seen
at certain hours.
I get up and go to bed.
Souls have laws just like the stars.
They exist like planets.
There are stabile souls
and wandering souls.
The sky has two aspects:
the sun and the souls.
Night and death are but a resurrection.
Half of the night is eternity...
the other half is immensity.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
I need to know what name
room 724 was booked under?
Okay, just a second.
724...
It was...
Maureen Cartwright, I have.
No, I'm Maureen Cartwright.
Who paid for the room?
Just a sec.
I'm sorry, there is no credit
card information.
It was paid in advance in cash.
Do you remember if it was
a man or a woman?
I don't know. I was not working
at that moment.
Would you ask a colleague?
Do you know...?
It's a big hotel.
I'm not sure I can
help you with that.
Thank you. See you later.
These are the five pieces
of your selection.
And particularly the "Pont des Arts" clasp,
of the "Paris Nouvelle Vague" collection.
Made of 18-carat rose gold
and fine stones.
C'est bien. Yes, it's perfect.
The necklace, the bracelet,
the ring and the watch,
but excluding this.
I've never seen that.
Okay. All right, then we focus
on these four.
- Okay.
- I'll prepare them for you then.
- Merci.
- You're welcome.
And this one is brand new,
first time released.
So no one has it.
Oh, good. That's important.
Thank you.
Hey, Kyra, you back?
Sorry, I let myself in. I'm just gonna
drop these bags for you, okay?
Hey Kyra, you doing all right?
Hey?
Hey... hey.
Follow me, please.
I drove for...
2 minutes maybe before
I realized what I was doing,
and I came back and called.
Why didn't you do it earlier?
I fr...
I freaked... out. I...
I... I... I ran away.
You ran away from a presence.
There was a light on in the...
...back of the apartment,
I heard something. Yeah.
What were you doing at Mrs. Gellman's?
Dropping off a couple of bags.
I don't understand.
I'm a personal shopper.
You know, she was...
...very high profile and couldn't...
...do normal things,
didn't have the time and...
...I sort of assisted her in that.
You used Mrs. Gellman's computer
last night.
Um, maybe.
And again this morning.
You check your messages on Gmail.
We have the record.
So, why are you asking?
Did you sleep at her place?
Yes, I did. I slept at her place.
Why?
Um, I...
I don't know.
I... to be honest, I never do that.
Why did you hide it?
A stupid reaction.
Maybe, maybe I was...
...a little ashamed.
You knew she was coming home today?
Yeah. She was coming back from Milan,
and on her way to Marrakech.
I was dropping off some
accessories for her.
What accessories?
Jewelry.
What jewelry?
Very expensive jewelry from Cartier.
And you left it there?
Yeah. In four cases in two bags.
Were they still there
when you went back?
I... I... I don't know. I wasn't...
...I wasn't considering the jewelry
at that point...
I didn't notice.
Sorry, if I woke you up.
No... I was just stress-testing...
...one of the new security protocols.
They're really fucking hard
to configure.
So, it's gonna take me a month.
Best case.
I'm gonna come see you.
You giving up?
Yeah, it's not going to happen.
Maureen, it's not that
it isn't going to happen,
it's that it doesn't exist.
After death,
there's nothing.
I- I know.
And it's not that big a deal.
You told me that you had a hope.
Like you really hoped that...
Of course I do.
But, no.
I don't believe.
I don't want to be here anymore.
I don't want to be in Paris anymore.
I miss you.
I miss you too.
And um...
I'm actually heading up
the mountains for a few days.
If you want to, you can come quickly
and meet me there.
Maybe... It really...
...depends on what the police say.
If the travel ban's been lifted or not.
- The police?
- Yeah.
Kyra was murdered,
you didn't hear that? It's everywhere.
- What?
- It's all over the news.
- I found her.
- Murdered?
- Who murdered her?
- I don't know.
It was really horr... It was, uh...
Are you okay?
I can't talk about it.
It was fucking horrible.
Do you want me
to call you back later?
I'll call you.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- They... Can I have some of this?
- Yeah, sure.
They arrested Ingo, and he...
...he confessed to everything.
Did they lift the travel ban?
Yeah. The case is closed.
But you'll testify?
Yes, probably.
Do you want to come to my place?
Yeah. I feel, um...
I'm scared when I alone now.
You're going to see Gary, right?
Yes, Yep.
You should have gone a while ago.
I should have listened to you.
Let's go, I have my car.
- Good morning.
You're Lewis's sister.
I am.
We were together at l'ֹcole Boulle.
Now I work at the Gobelin workshops.
Actually, I should get going soon.
You should stay.
If you can.
- Maureen.
- Erwin.
Nice to meet you.
I understand that you might
feel uncomfortable.
Why?
Because I've taken Lewis's place.
So soon.
Not at all.
You're mistaken.
While he was alive,
there was nothing between Lara and me.
It didn't cross my mind.
Honestly.
You know how they say
the dead watch over the living?
I've thought about that a lot.
Not just because Lewis was a medium.
I don't know what that means.
For me, he was someone
deeply intuitive of others.
He, uh...
...understood things that went unspoken.
He did.
Maybe because he knew
he was going to die.
I mean, I felt that he
saw things which I didn't.
Maybe you do too.
He thought you had the same gifts.
I don't know.
I, uh...
...had a tendency to follow him.
He took things quite far.
Too far for me, at least.
I couldn't keep up.
All I mean is that with Lewis,
nothing seems impossible.
Many religions believe that
the soul wanders around for a while...
...before leaving this world.
Did he speak to you about that?
He was convinced of it.
You know, right after our mum died,
he was sure that...
...he was visited by her.
That she came to say goodbye to him.
That it felt like a dream,
but not, that it was very real.
He could smell her,
he could see her so clearly... you know.
Do you believe that?
Yeah, I do.
It's not a religion thing, but I...
I do.
Do you think Lewis is here?
Well, I...
I don't think so.
I feel his presence.
He's here.
That might be your guilt talking.
You don't need to feel guilty.
Lara deserves to be happy.
And you do too.
I'd like to think so but...
...something is stopping me.
- I hope it has nothing to do with me.
- No.
But you also have to
free yourself of Lewis.
Well, I wish he'd let me.
Wherever he is,
he would never forbid it.
And even if he's nowhere,
hold on to the memory
of his freedom.
Put it into practice.
I know...
I know what you mean.
You know, I have to get going.
Will you be staying a few days?
Just tonight. I leave tomorrow.
- So, I'll see you tonight.
- Okay
Uh-uh-uh! Stand still!
Good boy.
What happened?
A glass broke.
I thought you were outside?
Erwin just left.
He probably left it at the end
of the table, or something.
I hope you had a good trip.
Get some rest.
Your driver is named Salim.
It's best to leave a little
before daybreak.
Count on a five hour ride
and don't worry.
The road is safe,
even if it's not very busy.
Take the minimum.
I have everything we need.
In other words, not much.
If it's okay with you,
we'll stay for a week.
You'll have to be tolerant,
it's Spartan.
But you told me
this is what you wanted.
Haiji?
Lewis?
Are you here?
Have you been waiting for me?
Are you at peace?
Thank you.
Are you not at peace?
Are you playing with me?
Do you mean harm?
I don't know you.
Who are you?
Lewis, is it you?
Or is it just me?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org