CJ Entertainment Presents
A Filmmakers R&K Production
In Association With Film K
Skyline Pictures
"This story has been inspired by
true historical events"
(JAPANESE DIALOGUE IS IN BRACKET)
ALL OTHER SUBTITLED
DIALOGUE IS KOREAN
HWANG Jung-min
SO Ji-sub
SONG Joong-ki
LEE Jung-hyun KIM Suan
KIM Min-jae KIM Joong-hee
KIM In-woo SHIN Seunghwan
LEE Kyoung-young
Get down, quickly.
Get down there!
Move!
Keep in line!
Hey, we can't fit in here!
Someone small, okay?
Kids.
Send the young ones in there.
Get in there!
Co-executive Producer: PARK Ji-sung
Co-executive Producers:
Michelle KWON, Simon LEE
Associate Producer: CHO Sung-min
Co-producers: KIM Jeong-min, SHIN Kyoung-ill
Gas!
Help! Help!
Where are you going! Get back here!
Executive Producer: JEONG Tae-sung
Not today.
Get in.
Produced by KANG Hye-jung
Written by RYOO Seung-wan, SHIN Kyoung-ill
Directed by RYOO Seung-wan
"November 1944,
Japan - Hashima Coal Mine, Korean Quarters"
I'm sorry.
You've had to pay for my generation's sins.
I wish you success.
Grow old and fight for Korea.
We'll come back for you.
Don't you worry about an old man like me.
Just live a good life.
Time is running out.
Let's go.
Won't you come with us?
Then who will care for Mr. Yoon?
Even the weather is helping you out.
It's time. Hurry.
Go on! Be careful!
If one of you is killed on the way,
leave him or you'll all die.
Care only for yourself
until reaching Nomo Peninsula.
Hide there for a day to rest up,
then go to Nagasaki.
A lot of people get caught
in Nagasaki as well,
so don't rest easy until you reach Korea.
Please survive,
and let's meet in a better world.
Hurry!
(Don't move!)
(Stop or we'll shoot!)
You want to get killed too?
How much further?
What?
How much further to go?
We're almost there! Keep going!
(Yamada-san!)
(Should we fish them out?)
(Why bother?)
(Just report that we found them drowned.)
(With three catches, we'll get a bonus!)
(Let's go back, quickly!)
THE BATTLESHIP ISLAND
"Labor Mobilization for the Japanese Empire"
It's not the front line, why get so uptight?
It's no joke. I've been drafted.
Oh my, drafted?
Don't you intellectuals know that slogan?
"The people have a duty to the nation."
Then will you send your son to do his duty?
My son has tuberculosis!
If not for that, he could serve
in the rear like you, earn money,
and support
the Greater East Asia Co-Prosperity...
What's with this damned music?
Take this.
Mister Lee! Mister Lee!
Damn.
Are you going to play this music all night?
We're sending boys off
to war, it's too gloomy!
Don't you have any nice jazz?
Why?
You know that jazz is banned.
You want me arrested?
Who's going to arrest you?
This room is filled with high-ranking,
well-connected people.
We need some fun for once.
You want some fun?
That'll cost you a bit of hazard pay.
Oh gosh... all right.
"7th Feb 1945
Peninsula Hotel, Myeongdong Seoul"
Where's Gang-ok?
On the stage.
If he wants to stay out of jail,
tell him to come down and find me.
Huh, why? Did he make trouble again?
Damned idiot fooled around
with a section chief's wife!
Gang-ok!
The tap dance of love.
Until the night is gone,
Gang-ok!
Okay!
Give her a hand!
No, come on!
Come on, everyone!
With a glass of champagne,
let's have ourselves a dance.
Where's my wife!
Stand up!
Spin! Spin, you brat.
Wait, Daddy! Wait!
Are you out of your mind?
The section chief's wife likes my music.
She kept offering to buy dinner,
how can I turn it down?
And the theater owner
kept telling me to meet her.
All we did was eat.
If you get drafted for
this, what will she do?
I'm not going to be drafted!
You think you'll get away
with touching a section chief's wife?
Then today you play jazz?
Did you bring it?
Here.
It's nine musicians, including you.
And your daughter makes ten.
There'll be nothing left for me
and my police colleagues.
I'm always in your debt, Mr. Sugiyama.
Look.
I'll arrange a bribe for you and your band.
I'm asking around
the offices of Japanese factories.
Explain the situation to your band well.
And bring in some more cash.
You always said you wanted to work in Japan.
I heard the army was
driven out of the Philippines again?
Is Japan going to lose?
That's all just talk.
Don't you read the papers?
There are thousands of U. S.
POWs in Japan now.
It'll be over before
the cherry blossoms fall, trust me.
We're going to see cherry blossoms?
"12th Feb 1945 Ferry to Shimonoseki"
Get off, then.
Let's go.
God, what a smell.
You should be sucking on your mom's breasts!
What's a kid like you doing on this boat?
I was on my way home, and the town clerk
puts me in a truck saying
I'm about to earn money.
Okay, Okay.
Couldn't even tell my parents before leaving.
Tell me about it.
They dragged me off on my wedding night.
As a newlywed?
I am still hard down there
and already forgetting her face.
You in the glasses, how'd you end up here?
I go to Keijo University.
Whoa!
You an intellectual?
Better than being drafted
as a student soldier.
I heard if you work like crazy
for one year, you get a house?
Even still,
how could they drag off pre-pubescent boys?
Snatching them from the fields,
or when they're out wrestling.
Give me the case.
When the boat lands, we'll ditch these guys.
- So bear it until then.
- Okay.
All of you brought cash?
Take it out.
This is our lifeline.
Gimme that.
- If we lose this we're dead, okay?
- Okay.
Dad, where are we really going?
You'll see later. Stop asking me!
You asshole!
There's a fight.
Is that Choi Chil-sung?
The famous gangster?
Stupid Koreans...
can't help but fight each other.
(Stop fighting! Calm down!)
Sohee!
Go away! Go!
(Any more trouble,
we'll call it a riot and start shooting.)
What the fuck is he saying?
Hey!
Can anyone here speak Jap?
If you freak out again
they'll start shooting.
So shut the fuck up and calm down.
How'd your mouth get so filthy?
Is it as filthy between your legs?
Did you ever see between my legs?
- Did you?
- Do you even know who you're talking to?
(Sit down!)
You look like gangsters from some Seoul slum.
So if the Japs slap you around,
you take it out on Korean girls?
(Quiet! Sit down!)
All right, just let go.
Sit down, guys.
I said sit!
Not much worth grabbing there anyway.
Your poor mom probably felt happy
when you came out with balls.
Wow, she made a fool of him.
Stick out too much, and people hate you.
Sometimes you gotta keep your head down.
Some people bring on their fate.
"Shimonoseki Harbor, Japan"
(Dear passengers.)
(The ferry from Busan
to Shimonoseki has arrived.)
(Japanese passengers,
please await separate instructions.)
Sohee, listen to me.
If you lose my hand,
watch my back and follow me.
- You guys, hold those cases tight.
- Okay!
Stay focused.
Hold this.
Sohee!
(Excuse me.)
(Pardon me.)
(This letter)
(is from Detective Sugiyama)
(of Seoul Central Police Station.)
(Where can I find Shimura-san?)
(Shimura-san?)
(Yes, yes.)
(Detective Sugiyama from Seoul)
(told me to find Shimura-san.)
(There are lots of Shimuras here.)
(This way, please.)
(Hey, take them!)
(Wait...)
(Detective Sugiyama...)
"Recommendation letter"
(Wait, let go!)
(He told me to find Shimura!)
"Workers' ferry to Hashima
(Battleship Island)"
Sohee, are you okay?
I don't need that!
Asshole!
(Stop it!)
(Stop!)
Daddy!
Sohee! Sohee!
Sohee, it'll be okay! Stay with those women!
(Please stop!)
Next!
Take your bag and go!
It really is nothing, you see.
I just have cigarettes.
(What's this?)
(Give it here!)
Go, now!
Don't stare. Eyes forward!
Shut up and put your hands on your head!
Hands on your head! On your head!
(Nothing.)
(I have nothing.)
Foreheads on the ground!
(What do we do with these?)
It's war here, too.
Get rid of that
Korean habit of depending on everyone!
Sir! Sir! You're Korean?
Just a moment, please!
There's been some kind of mistake.
I was supposed to meet someone here.
We haven't been drafted like the others.
This is from Detective Sugiyama
at Seoul Central Police Station!
And this is our performing license.
I'm Lee Gang-ok of the Lee Gang-ok Band.
We released a record at Okay Record Company.
We performed at Government Hall,
Myungdong Theater,
- Peninsula Hotel, everywhere!
- Musicians?
1, 2, 3, 4!
(What the hell is that?)
They said it's a factory.
Why take off our clothes?
(Follow me!)
(Are those tattoos?)
(Here at Hashima Comfort Station, )
(we've received a special medal for)
(being free of venereal disease.)
(Please keep yourselves clean)
(and protect our perfect record.)
(Next.)
Sir, just a minute.
This is a luxury Western watch called Rolex.
It was a gift from someone
at the Governor-General's office.
I'm sure you'll take care of things,
but I came here with my daughter.
Lee Sohee. We came off the boat separately.
She's just a little girl.
If you could even tell me where she is...
(Can you play
'Cherry Blossoms of the Same Class'?)
(Yes!)
Damned music men are settling in comfortably.
(You and I are)
(cherry blossoms of the same class, )
(blooming in the same)
(naval training ground.)
(Any flower)
(is destined to fall, )
(so let us fall brilliantly, )
(for the sake of our nation.)
(I see some talented men
from Korea have arrived.)
(Welcome.)
(Yes!)
(Thank you.)
(My name is Lee...)
(Sorry... sorry.)
(I am the manager of Hashima Mine, )
(Shimazaki Daisuke.)
(We welcome you from distant Korea)
(to fulfill your duty here)
(as loyal subjects of His
Majesty the Emperor.)
(I grant you the honor of taking part
in the Imperial Army's war.)
(For 50 years already, )
(this historic site)
(has led as a supplier of coal)
(to the industry of the
Great Japanese Empire.)
(The coal we produce here
is not merely coal.)
(A single lump of coal)
(is a drop of blood, )
(a weapon, )
(and a piece of history!)
(Sons of the Emperor!)
(I urge you to fulfill your duties)
(as glorious soldiers of industry, )
(and to not dishonor
the Imperial Japanese Army.)
(Hurry up!)
"Japanese Residential Area Comfort Station"
(Filthy whore!)
(Dirty!)
Don't get pregnant at the comfort station...
One woman got pregnant at the Chinese station
they cut her stomach and took the baby out.
And a few days later
she was receiving soldiers again.
(We will now assign dormitories!)
(After locating your room, )
(prepare quickly and gather outside.)
(The account slips we give you)
(show the transport fees
you incurred while coming here.)
(Traveling costs from Seoul
and other cities to Busan, )
(the ferry to Shimonoseki, )
(and transport to Hashima Island)
(have been covered by the company, )
"Korean Living Quarters"
(and will be deducted from your pay.)
(Housing costs provided by the company)
(will be deducted from your pay.)
(All personal items supplied to you)
(are covered by the company)
(and will be deducted from your pay.)
(All expenses for meals)
(are covered by the company)
(and will be deducted from your pay.)
Hey, get up if you're done eating!
(For your future)
(national bond and savings fees, )
(health insurance and pension funds)
(are calculated in a lump sum)
(and will be deducted from your pay.)
"Insurance card / Savings account"
(For the sake of those
who don't speak our language)
(we employ translators, )
(and provide job training.)
(Various amenities and)
(necessary equipment are furnished.)
(All these items)
(will be deducted from your pay.)
(If your first month's pay)
(is less than the company's expenses)
(fees will be deducted from your next pay.)
What the hell will we have left?
I'll just run up debts here!
Hey, get moving!
(Consider today a workplace tour)
(to learn your duties.)
(We at Hashima Mine)
(do not underestimate you for being Koreans.)
(We believe you can excel
from the first day.)
Stop! Masks on!
Put your mask on, dammit!
Masks on!
Shit, he's falling down. You praying?
Get up now!
My fucking glasses broke!
Your glasses broke, so you're talking back?
Are you? Are you?
Stop it, you asshole!
Even dogs deserve to eat and wash in peace!
Why hit a young kid?
(Step aside!)
(What are you doing?)
(Everyone sit down!)
Fucking hell.
Hey music man!
You speak Jap, right?
Get over here!
Translate for me!
I'm ready to kick that yakuza wanna be's ass.
Translate, now!
(I request to duel that
Korean boss of yours.)
I'm that famous Seoul
gangster Choi Chil-sung.
I came here to beat your Korean yakuza boss.
(I am Choi Chil-sung.)
(I'm here to challenge
that Korean labor boss.)
We fight samurai style, and if I win,
me and my boys will watch over the Koreans.
(We fight samurai style, and if I win, )
(my boys and I will oversee the Koreans.)
If I lose, I'll treat him as my boss.
(If I lose, that Korean
boss will be my boss.)
You assholes.
(That was a swear word.)
Think you're a circus ringleader?
Drag him off!
(Wait!)
(That sounds like fun.)
(All you need to do is win.)
(There are new Korean girls
at the comfort station.)
(How about betting on a pass?)
(Comfort station?)
Everyone stop!
Koreans fighting each other
is just what they want!
The more we fight,
the more we play into their hands!
This bastard isn't Korean
like the rest of us.
What are you looking at, you stupid Koreans?
From now on, I'll be leading the Koreans!
If you back me, I'll keep
the Koreans in line.
(Go talk to the labor office.)
Hurrah for Choi Chil-sung!
And where did this freak come from?
Let's whistle for him,
new boss Choi Chil-sung!
(Everyone bow!)
(The beauties have arrived.)
(Everyone take a seat.)
(Sit!)
(Go ahead, sit!)
(Hurry.)
(Here.)
(This meal is to welcome you, )
(why so melancholy?)
(You, who will give up your bodies)
(to our soldiers fighting
in the Great East Asian War)
(and to our soldiers of industry, )
(are indeed invaluable assets.)
(Take pride in yourselves.)
(We used to employ first-class geisha)
(or former actresses from film studios.)
(Now mostly Korean women work here.)
(But this innocence is part of their charm!)
(This mood is too heavy
for a feast of welcome.)
(Play that record I brought.)
(Yes sir!)
(To help you feel comfortable, )
(I brought a Korean record which I enjoy.)
(It's quite lively.)
(We prepared beds for you here, )
(so relax, listen to some music)
(and get to bed early tonight.)
This is me singing!
I sang this song!
(Hey! What are you doing?)
(Give it back!)
Tell them I used to sing this song!
Tell them I sang it, please!
Tell them!
(She sang what's playing right now.)
I can sing and dance,
play instruments, whatever!
I can clean and do laundry!
(She can perform, play instruments
and is also good at housework.)
He asked what you did in Korea.
I played music in Seoul. The Yamamura Band.
(She performed at the Yamamura Band.)
My father and the rest of the band
are all here!
(Long live the Emperor!)
(Hurrah!)
"July 1945, OSS training camp,
Korean Liberation Army in China"
How is your training with the OSS soldiers?
I'm trying my best.
You've got higher marks than the Americans.
The Seoul infiltration operation
you've been planning...
I'm sorry, but we need
you for something else.
Some OSS intelligence was leaked to our side.
The U. S. has developed a new bomb.
They say its power is beyond imagination.
The blast radius is up to 200km.
If they drop that from a B-29
onto the Japanese mainland...
That's all unconfirmed talk for now.
The point is, the Soviets
are about to invade.
The U. S. has already taken Okinawa.
If the Soviets join in,
Japan won't last long.
It's time to focus on winning the war,
not the battle.
For a speedy liberation,
we must join together.
Yoon Hak-chul.
Only he can resolve the conflicts
between all the factions fighting
for Korean independence.
He handled fundraising at the KPG,
but two years ago he was
caught by the Japanese
and disappeared without a trace.
We assumed he was executed without trial,
but according to U. S. intel
he was detained near Nagasaki
at Hashima Coal Mine.
Go bring back Mr. Yoon.
"We will always be together. Our Hashima."
Gather around, everyone.
If we screw up again,
we'll be back in the mines.
Do your best! And smile!
If you don't smile I'll have Chil-sung
take you back to the mine.
Get ready, quick!
Hey, why don't you eat that?
Raw eggs are gross.
Eat when I tell you, kid!
It's great for your throat.
Some people can't eat at all! Hurry up!
Hey!
Abracadabra... ta-dah!
Look at that grin.
If you're gonna eat, then pay for it!
Newbies who arrived today,
just follow the man in front!
Fuckers don't feed us crap.
The fuck is he blabbering about?
Isn't that dynamite? What'll you do with it?
Stop sputtering and be quiet!
The liquid that seeps out is sweet.
Need to eat at least that to survive.
What if your stomach explodes?
Give me a taste!
Help me here!
It's okay.
It's just the coal dust in my lungs.
Sir, are you okay?
I'm fine!
Hey, there's gas coming out!
So what?
Block off the gas! And pump out sea water!
(At the center of Japan's leadership)
(in the Great East Asian War
is Hashima Coal Mine!)
(Long live the Emperor!)
(Long live the Japanese Empire!)
(For Hashima Mine and)
(its executives returning
to the head office!)
(Cheers!)
Rock, scissors, paper! Rock! Rock!
Okay, your turn.
You okay?
Support his back.
Are you hurt?
Hey kid, out of the way!
Kid!
Look out!
Huh? What's that noise?
Explosion!
Run out quick! Bring your tools!
Don't drop your tools, bring them!
(Thank you.)
(Thank you very much.)
(How many times has Mine No. 2 caught fire?)
(Do I need to step in
every time this happens?)
(What about the passage to Mine No.3?)
(It hasn't spread there yet.)
(How much is Mine 2 producing?)
(It has the lowest production.)
(We're already 1100 meters
below the seafloor, )
(so it'll be hard to mine deeper.)
Save me.
Save the young ones first!
Mr. Yoon! You must go up!
Don't let anyone die! Not one!
(That's the Korean section, right?)
(Seal them off.
Prevent damage spreading to other mines.)
There are people here! You bastards!
There are people here!
(Sir, Yoon Hak-chul is in the mine!)
(Out of the way!)
(I told you not to put him in the mine!)
(What if he dies and the Koreans riot?)
(By whatever means necessary, get him out!)
Hold on just a bit!
You gonna work all day? Huh?
They're waiting for you!
(Jong-gu! There's a problem in Mine 2!)
Damn, I worked all night!
Why'd they have to wake me up?
Isn't that where we plugged
the gas leak before?
Hey, just shut your mouth and follow orders!
Ah, are you back on duty?
Fuck!
You sure this connects to Mine 3?
Shouldn't you know that?
What? You prick!
Blast through it.
What?
There's no other way.
We point the gas
at these supports, and light it.
Newbie! Shut the fuck up!
There's no guarantee
we can get enough gas here.
You know...
I hid this thing here.
- We can't drill any deeper.
- We can't!
Gas keeps leaking, what if there's a fire?
That's why we called you technicians!
Okay, okay...
It's going in!
Keep drilling!
Drill! Drill!
Pull!
Pull it!
(The Koreans heard there was an accident, )
(but they don't know yet who lived or died.)
(Announce we'll move wounded Koreans
to a main hospital in Nagasaki, )
(then send them to the crematorium
and burn them with the corpses.)
(There are limits
to how many Koreans we can bring.)
(Given the war struggles, )
(will we allow the company
to keep losing money?)
(I'll be sure to contain the problem.)
(Chiba-san.)
(When do you plan to inspect our mine?)
- (The thing is...)
- I'm sorry!
(As I'm grateful for
your recommendation of our facility)
(I mean to send someone
to express my deepest gratitude.)
(I see.)
(You won't be disappointed.)
(Where is Yoon Hak-chul now?)
He's coming! He's coming!
Here he comes!
(If the company
doesn't release a list of casualties, )
(and draw up compensation and safety plans, )
(I will refuse all talks
with Manager Shimazaki!)
We support you!
That's enough!
Wait a minute! You give me this.
You're in charge of toilets now.
You'll scoop piss and shit!
Hey!
Fuck...
(Someone tell this madman not to hit me!)
(Then give me my money's worth!)
(I don't need
any Korean bitches glaring at me.)
(I'll drink when I want!)
(Hey, calm down!)
You got trained by the Americans,
but without their help
you think you can escort Mr.
Yoon out of here?
The plan was to use the network here
and contact Korean agents
at OSS headquarters.
Through an agent
planted on the food ship that stops here
we'll go by ship to the U. S. base in Okinawa.
How do we know you're not on their side?
You say you're OSS-trained resistance?
I was a student soldier
sent to Japanese unit 7991 in China,
then I escaped last July in Xuzhou,
and met KLA General Lee
Beom-seok in Chongqing.
Did he send any personal message to me?
He says he'll treat you
to your favorite trotter stew
at Hwapyung Restaurant.
When do you plan to move?
I'll send in another girl.
Just sit.
I said sit! I'm not here for romance.
Why not?
Do the marks on my chest make you go limp?
Hell...
Don't you need a Korean to complain to,
to breathe easier?
Fuck... even worse than the Japs
are these damned mosquitos.
At first I was dragged to China.
I had no idea. They said I was going to work.
They drove me to a Japanese army base.
Hell, the mosquitos bit me like crazy.
Some mosquito bites can kill a person.
One bite, and your whole
body swells with fever.
However much you drink, your insides burn.
There was a girl from Heungyang.
The Japanese said
she was pretending to be sick,
put her on nails and
rolled her back and forth.
She died in front of everyone.
I was too scared to tell them I was sick.
Figured I'd rather die fast, so I drank lye.
It was a Japanese doctor
who stopped me from dying.
But then a Korean pimp washed me
and threw me right back
at those Japanese guys.
It was a fucking Korean town clerk
who sent me to that comfort station!
When the unit retreated, I barely escaped,
but that Korean pimp caught and sent me here!
So I need a Korean to complain to?
To breathe easier?
Biting the hand that feeds you.
You need to control your temper.
Sooner or later, things will get better.
Fuck!
Are you doing a lousy job on purpose?
Try finding any guy who
won't get off on this!
Dragging me out of the hospital to do this...
Okay, here.
I send out so many of these,
why does so little come back?
Damned guards cut the rations.
You're not hoarding it yourself?
Shit...
Bro, just one cigarette.
You still didn't pay for last month's.
The damned Japanese raised
their pension funds or whatever!
We all had them raised!
So control your gambling!
If you're broke, just sleep.
Wait, pay me more!
Dammit.
Give this to the attendant for 10 cigarettes.
Yes, sir.
Manager Shimazaki is calling you.
Sohee!
What is it? Oh no...
- A splinter.
- Be more careful, kid!
What's that smell?
(I've been thinking of this for a while.)
(After today's accident, )
(I thought I should meet you)
(and propose something, )
(before it's too late.)
(I see.)
(About your daughter...)
(In the recent U. S. bombing
of our head office, )
(Chiba-san lost his daughter.)
(Rather than having her stay here,
where it's so dangerous, )
(I was thinking)
(to send her to Chiba-san
as an adopted daughter.)
(Mr. Lee.)
(We're in a war.)
(In wartime, winners don't always survive.)
(Survivors are true winners.)
(On the next freight ship out, )
(let's send Sohee.)
Huh?
Wow!
Meeting in this world of woe,
what is your wish?
Will being rich make you happy?
Airplane!
The post office key?
We'll pay whatever you want.
Hell, how would you know what I want?
We'll give you this in advance.
Wow, advance pay?
I need to know what this is about.
We need to check a package.
I don't team up with people who keep secrets.
If you need to check a package,
isn't it easier to just bribe
one of the labor officers?
- The thing is...
- We need the telegraph.
The telegraph?
Know how to use it?
Just get us the key.
A newbie wants to use the telegraph.
A Korean who looks like
an independence leader bribes me...
What's going on here?
Forget it, then.
I already know,
- how can I forget?
- Quiet!
Should I go ask the boss to look into this?
Park Mu-young!
Mr. Yoon will escape from here.
Hey Gang-ok,
all we need is the key, no trouble.
You decide.
If you don't cooperate,
then we'll kill you.
(Hey, Yamamura!)
(What are you doing out past curfew?)
(Where have you been?)
(I've been looking for you.)
(The drawings are done, )
(tell Maeda to see me tomorrow.)
(What, already?)
(I want one, too!)
(But what are you doing here?)
(They're fighting over gambling debts.)
(I'm trying to mediate.)
(Damn idiots!)
Shake hands!
(I'll take care of this, you go on.)
(All right, then.)
(Have a good night!)
You don't need to pay,
but I have one condition.
When he escapes, take me and my daughter.
Gang-ok!
I take it that old man won't be swimming?
Since you want the telegraph,
you must have something lined up.
Just kill me,
or have the Japanese kill you,
or take my daughter and me.
This time, you decide.
If our plan is leaked, I'll kill you myself.
One, two, three!
Where the hell did he go?
Can't he leave me alone?
Hey, go to my spot!
Hey painter!
Where's the guy who made me a lock that time?
Is he on the night shift?
Why don't I see him?
Bang!
They sent him to the tool repair factory...
to work as a technician,
since he's good with tools.
- Bang!
- Tool repair factory? Shit.
(Good afternoon!)
(I need a favor from the locksmith.)
What brings you out here?
You want another lock?
No, I've got a really important key.
I'm scared of losing it, so I'd like a copy.
Hand it over.
Yes but... I need to bring it back.
Something smells fishy.
How come you get all the luck?
Which woman's home?
You're quick.
Her husband carries the key around.
You know how it is.
(Here you go. See you later!)
Hello!
We'd still be nice to Sohee
without these gifts.
I know, but treat her well!
What are you sighing about?
I talked to your supervisor lady,
so move to her room.
If I call you at night, then run right out.
Can't you ask the manager
to let us stay together?
Why? Did he do something?
It's just that I'm lonely here...
The other women tell me I'm annoying
even when the manager takes care of me.
Damned bitches!
That's why I told you
to behave well with other people,
and be careful what impression you give!
What are you crying about?
Don't you know all that I'm doing for you?
Think you're the only one who's got it hard?
Why do you always say everything's my fault?
Never mind. What do I say to you?
Anyway...
Always be ready
so you can run right out if I call you.
Then we can be together, all right?
(Got a good movie for us?)
(Yes, a love story!)
(Good evening.)
(Want to see a dirty picture?)
(Oh good!)
(Come this way.)
The outside door, the office
and the director's room.
You remember my terms?
I have eyes everywhere, you know.
Hey, boss!
What is it now?
Nothing, I want to show you something.
What the hell? It won't open?
Gang-ok, that rat!
Hey, assholes!
"Hashima..."
"Hashima Eagle..."
"Hashima Eagle contacted"
"Preparations to..."
"Preparations to transport..."
"Preparations to transport Eagle..."
"Preparations to transport Eagle complete"
"Number..."
"Number of..."
"Number of passengers?"
"Yoon and Park"
"Two"
"Sending food..."
"Sending food transport ship..."
"Sending food transport ship in 48 hrs, 5AM"
"Find Takagura..."
"Find Takagura on transport..."
"Find Takagura on transport ship"
"Wishing safe..."
"Wishing safe return"
"End"
"Korean Account Records"
(Seems the war is going badly.)
(When was the last time Japan
used good paper like this?)
(What do propaganda pamphlets
have to do with the war?)
(The U. S. still has enough money)
(to make pamphlets with good paper.)
(Aren't wars ultimately won by
those with the most money?)
(Give me the relevant documents
for me and the other Koreans.)
(Ah...)
(More leaflets littering our island.)
(Those are bombers.)
(Citizens and employees, )
(because of U. S. bombardment,
turn off lights and stay indoors.)
(I repeat.)
(Citizens and employees, )
(because of U. S. bombardment,
turn off lights and stay indoors.)
It's time.
(Why so cheap this time?)
(Too many people involved now,
I want to wrap it up.)
(Where's the attendant?)
Let's go.
Damn those bastards!
Sir, it's time for your medicine.
Sir?
(Quiet around here.)
Sohee!
Sohee...
(What is it?)
(Gang-ok? Come on in.)
(All right. Where's Sohee?)
(Quick, Sohee...)
(I'll meet Sohee...)
(then go to your room.)
Shit.
When did you last see Park?
What?
Mr. Yoon is missing.
I couldn't say goodbye to anyone.
What kind of operation is this?
I had to keep everything completely secret.
And I have something to ask you first.
I found Koreans' pay records
in the post office safe.
The pensions and bond payments
taken from their paychecks
don't go to their accounts,
but to someone else's.
Your name is entered on their contracts,
and half the money flowing into your account
is forwarded into Manager
Shimazaki's account.
Are you aware of this?
Since coming here,
I heard that pay is embezzled by
the manager and several others...
but an account in my name?
Even dead workers' compensation
is going in there,
without their families being
told of their deaths.
Shimazaki... I never
thought he'd go this far.
Looking through the documents,
I kept seeing your signature.
Who could have made those files?
Didn't it occur to you that
Shimazaki could've made it?
No labor strike or escape plan
has ever succeeded here.
I wonder why.
If you set up a leader of the Koreans,
and then use him,
then this kind of control is possible.
Can you explain how a man
caught delivering huge sums for the KLA
could have received no
trial from the Japanese,
and ended up here?
This is just what Shimazaki wanted.
Should I answer for you?
You fool!
Shimazaki knew someone like you was coming.
You converted.
If you weren't on their
side, you'd be in jail.
Park Mu-young!
No one will follow you once they find out.
Why do you think
Shimazaki agreed to negotiate
over their protection?
Why?
Negotiate?
So dragging little boys off to mines
and stealing their money
was a negotiation?
If you're so convinced of my guilt
then right here,
shoot me.
You scoundrel! Trying to run off without us?
I warned you!
That if you betray me, I'll report you!
You stay there!
Gang-ok!
Listen closely to me.
This is an American spy
with no connection to Korea.
If you report him,
the two of you can escape.
If Shimazaki finds out, you all die!
What was your real goal in coming here?
Sohee!
When I shout,
run to Manager Shimazaki
and tell him everything!
He's on Shimazaki's side!
Goddamn fuckers!
Then when does the ship come?
Daddy!
Sohee, it's okay. Just stay still.
Why do you take the girl!
Let go of her.
Drop the gun first.
Sir, are you okay?
I'm fine, go watch over our men.
Park has betrayed us!
Put down the gun, now!
Our men are on the way.
Stop being stupid!
Try reading this.
What kind of plot is this?
Shut up, you scoundrel!
Coming to save someone like you...
Don't you feel sorry for them?
Ito Takamichi Yoon Hak-chul...
I will report your treason to
the Provisional Government of Korea.
You bastard!
Run, quick!
(This way, quick!)
(This way!)
(Hurry!)
(You Koreans, wait there!)
(Block the Koreans!)
(Shut the gate! Get in, quick!)
Help!
Sook, get up!
You want to die?
Let me go! Sook!
(Stop!)
(Don't shoot!)
(I'm Ito...)
Yoon Hak-chul!
Sir!
- Sir, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Are you hurt?
How are you?
I'm okay. Let's get away from here.
About that account book...
Don't worry about that.
I'll go back and get it.
Did you see what was in it?
Sir, I believe you to the end.
(Help!)
(Someone help!)
(Help me!)
That man, he shot...
Quiet!
Sir, are you all right?
Sir, what will we do?
How could this happen to us?
You there! Did Gang-ok die too?
Someone thought they saw his corpse,
so we're looking...
Gang-ok, where are you?
Dammit!
Daddy, I'm thirsty.
Why are you giving me that?
- Any food here?
- Probably.
(Drive out the Koreans!)
(Does the line work?)
(Hold out as long as you
can with the food and water you have.)
(Our manager's unrecoverable!)
(Are you telling us to just die?)
(Yesterday the U. S. dropped
a new bomb on Hiroshima!)
(A new bomb?)
(Word is coming in)
(that it's tremendously powerful.)
(There's no official report yet, )
(but it's said there are
100,000 casualties, )
(and no living thing survived.)
(The Americans have
created something unimaginable.)
(Are we going to lose this war?)
(After Hitler's death and
the fall of Germany, )
(industrialists who helped the Nazis)
(are being lined up
and tried as war criminals.)
(If you have any materials that
can be used against us, burn them!)
(If it's a war crimes trial, )
(shouldn't we kill the Koreans
who could testify against us?)
(That'd be the most effective solution, )
(but with Shimazaki in that state, )
(can it be done?)
(If you take care of things properly, )
(then surely you can take his place.)
(Drive out the Koreans!)
You little prick.
You ruined everything!
Does it hurt a lot?
I can't believe this.
(Corpses will be burned to prevent disease, )
(so finish identifying the bodies!)
(What about Japanese corpses?)
(Why is it only us
who are burned like garbage?)
(So as not to create more panic, )
(for now, only you and I
must know of the manager's death.)
Take this for now.
I couldn't find what you described,
so I just took anything.
(I hear a Japanese schoolgirl was murdered.)
(Korean attendant Song
Jong-gu says he saw it.)
(And the suspect is Korean.)
(That's good news.)
(Now we have a justification
to crack down on the Koreans.)
Hey!
Sohee!
Bro, you're alive?
You think I'm dead?
Why'd you want to meet here,
and not the kitchen?
There's someone
who can't know the two of us are alive.
Have this.
What the hell? Eat this?
Hey, take a can from my bag.
It disappeared in the bombing.
Huh? What about the cash?
All of it?
Goddammit!
It was a life-or-death situation!
Why didn't you get it? Where have you been?
It's a long story.
Is Yoon asking about me?
(Until the situation stabilizes, )
(I will carry out the duties
of our wounded manager.)
(During this vicious American attack)
(when everyone is heartbroken, )
(an innocent, pretty young girl)
(lost her life to a savage
who couldn't control his lust!)
(Can you see this innocent victim's family?)
(If you've any conscience, come forward!)
(What evidence do you have
that it was a Korean?)
(Witness, come forward!)
(Identify the suspect.)
He was with us yesterday!
You scumbag!
Don't overdo it, you thug.
Ah, I want some cold soy noodles!
With savory broth... salt on top.
I like it better with sugar.
All right, sugar it is.
Pull out a mouthful of those noodles...
With radish kimchi on the side...
Oh, let's stop this!
Only makes me hungrier.
When we get out of here,
let's go eat noodles first.
Then, we'll go back home?
Of course.
That's why your dad is helping me.
But right now...
there's something I need you to help me with.
Will you help me?
(Mr. Yoon.)
(If you get a chance to leave this island,
you'll take it?)
(If I take you to the U. S. occupied zone, )
(can you tell them I helped you
to look after the laborers, )
(and supported Korean liberation?)
(If the manager is dead,
you'll probably get his position.)
(Is that really necessary?)
(I've thought it over, )
(and we're both smart enough to know)
(how this war will end.)
(In return for getting you out, )
(give me the money
you pocketed with the manager.)
(Can I leave right away?)
(The coal transport ship is almost repaired.)
(Our communications are back, )
(and it's no problem to
leave here with you, )
(but if I want to take
my family from Nagasaki, )
(I'll have to follow
the head office's command, )
(and deal with all the Koreans.)
(Deal with?)
(No Korean who remembers what happened here)
(must be allowed to survive.)
Where did that old man Yoon hide it?
"Records of Korean laborers"
You lost your position as the Korean leader,
and took out your grudge
against a Japanese girl.
But she fought back,
and you strangled her.
Is that so hard to admit?
Hey! Just say it's true
and sign with your thumbprint.
Then I'll treat you like my older brother.
Song Jong-gu...
I'm gonna fold you like a blanket,
and chop you into pieces, you prick.
(Gather all the remaining dynamite!)
(Tomorrow we'll put
all the Koreans in the mine.)
Tomorrow morning...
Yamada plans to force all the Koreans
into the mine and kill us.
Women of course, and even children.
I beg you.
I won't ask for myself,
but please take Sohee away from here.
Surely you can manage to take her.
I'm going to escape.
With all the Koreans here.
In this place where we sweated and toiled,
we have a right to proper treatment!
Today's arrest of Choi Chil-sung
as a murder suspect
is no different from
what all us Koreans have suffered!
Therefore I
requested Manager Shimazaki
to stop Koreans from being unfairly accused,
and demanded an open trial!
- Out of the way.
- Let's go.
And furthermore,
I reached an agreement with the manager.
First!
We will be given the same quality
food as the Japanese!
Second!
The coal quotas raised last month
will be lowered!
Third!
Full time off on holidays!
Fourth!
Work to repair the island
will be compensated!
And finally! Injured young workers
will all be returned...
to our homeland Korea!
We'll send them home!
There's just one condition!
Given what we will receive,
we need to show our sincerity.
Tomorrow is Hashima Mine's
first opening since the bombing.
The manager has asked
as a show of our unity and for a new start,
that all Koreans including
women and children,
join the opening ceremony inside the mine.
What do you all think?
I object!
Yoon Hak-chul never met the manager today.
The manager is dead.
If you enter the mine tomorrow,
acting manager Yamada will have you buried.
What?
Park Mu-young, stop trying to stir chaos!
The U. S. has invaded Okinawa,
and the war is almost over.
Yoon Hak-chul and Yamada
plan to bury you here
and then escape to the U. S. army.
Friends!
That man is a spy trying
to divide us Koreans! A spy!
All of you here
are decisive witnesses
of Hashima's war crimes.
Therefore, this company
plans to bury you in the mine
to destroy all evidence.
People!
Tell me!
Who do you trust?
You fucker!
That old geezer is a real fox.
Listen up, everyone!
Park is an independence fighter
who came to rescue Yoon.
But... if you can believe it,
Park discovered that
Yoon was Shimazaki's informant.
So Yoon shot him with a gun!
And this here!
Written by Yoon and the manager,
lists all of the money
they skimmed off your paychecks.
People who died of accidents,
hunger, sickness, violence!
People who died trying to escape.
You stole their compensation!
This man Lee Gang-ok!
To kiss up to the Japanese,
sold his own daughter!
And that spy
is completely unknown to us,
coming from who knows where!
That's right!
How do we know Gang-ok
and that newbie aren't spies?
Calm down!
All of us need to band together!
Let's keep our heads and not be fooled!
These unknown guys coming in
and slandering our Mr. Yoon.
I saw it too!
Put down the gun, now!
Our men are on the way.
I saw it!
I saw you shoot him and Choong-ho too!
Jang-woo, have you been bought off too?
Why betray your own country?
Do you really have to sell me?
Stop it, Jang-woo! How could you do it too?
What if I show you this?
4088 Yoon Hak-chul.
Torn off your shirt by Choong-ho as he died.
Don't be fooled by appearances.
They're deceiving you.
I saw it too! He's a bad man!
That girl saw such an awful thing?
First, let's look at those documents.
Bleeding the people dry!
You need to prove what they say isn't true.
Ito Takamichi! Yoon Hak-chul!
That money you worked for
is dirty Japanese money!
Guilty of treason.
That money was for Korean independence!
Was that so wrong?
Bleeding the people dry!
It was for us!
Pretending to lead, and deceiving the people!
You fools!
For betraying the nation,
You think killing me will bring liberation?
I punish you in the name of Korea!
After all I've done!
So what are we going to do?
No one's ever managed to escape here.
Think we can all just hold hands and leave?
Yoon has always tipped off the manager.
That's why they failed.
If we take the coal transport ship
in the harbor,
- we can succeed.
- Wait a minute.
Who's gonna drive that big ship?
Hold on, we got a few boatmen here.
I've sailed fishing boats.
I know the route, so with
5 or 6 men to row...
Hold on!
That freight ship is not a fishing boat!
It's not just that, if we all run for it
won't they start shooting and stabbing us?
What then?
The guards who come to Hashima
were all judged unfit for the battlefield.
And after the bombing, they're still spooked.
There are much more of us.
And we got military training...
Instead,
how about we try negotiating
with the Japanese?
Right!
To be honest,
Japanese are more enlightened than us.
If we try dialogue...
Dialogue my ass!
If they were sensible,
would we be living this way?
Remember the Kanto Earthquake?
They spread rumors that
Koreans poisoned the wells,
and massacred all Koreans!
You say that because you have skills
and lived easy!
Who says I lived easy?
You're just trying to divide us, painter!
Hey!
Just decide who'd leave or stay!
This is wasting time!
He's right!
Those who want to go, can go.
Those who will stay, stay.
You really think they'd kill so many people?
- Right?
- Yeah!
Daddy, aren't we going?
Dammit, I'm gonna blow my top!
You stupid Koreans!
If you made it this far,
shouldn't you try to live?
Have you all grown so
used to being stepped on?
This girl and I want to live!
We'll go ourselves.
Wait! I'll go too.
I lost my leg and became a cripple,
but I won't let them bury me here.
But Mallyon, what if they really kill us all?
Even if just one of us survives,
we win. Just one.
My life was ruined,
but I won't die in their hands.
Wait!
I'll go too.
Are you really staying?
How can you trust them?
You should think it over.
Come on, we'll try talking to the Japanese!
- Let's go!
- There's no time,
so we won't try to persuade you.
Are you crazy? What's going on?
You telling them of our plan is only trouble.
So please understand.
And besides,
it'd be best if they found you tied up.
Don't need this! Damn you, Jang-woo!
Careful, careful...
Wait, I don't see Choi Chil-sung's gang.
If they tell the labor attendant...
They said they're going to rescue Choi.
Huh?
What'll they do then?
Let's hurry.
Boss!
What are you doing here?
They say they'll try you,
but let's go before things get worse.
Think of this as a drill, like in training.
We're going to move in groups.
When we're ready,
women, the wounded and children
will move first at our sign.
Our final goal
is to cross the coal belt over the wall,
board the ship and escape.
This is dynamite they prepared for the mine.
Explosives team,
tie them to the lantern batteries.
It will strengthen the blast.
The wounded, use tatami mats to make shields.
Mallyon and the women will
make rope from fundoshi underwear.
Weapons team, take tools and oil
from the tool factory.
Lee and his band will
gather bottles for bottle bombs.
Those who can steer the ship,
help me take control.
The rest of you, wait for our signal.
It's dangerous, don't touch!
Why do you always yell at me?
Why are you here?
If you're ready, I'll bring everyone.
Don't do this, come with us.
You really think 400 people
can sneak onto a ship?
With all those wounded people?
Then do you want to start a war here?
We'll all die tomorrow anyway.
If you try to kill Jong-gu, you'll die too!
Hey.
Did Park go without finishing them off?
They weren't here before.
Dammit!
(Who's there?)
(It's me! Me!)
(Shishido, it's me.)
(Gang-ok!)
(Why are you out so late? Go back inside.)
(I can't believe it either.)
Get over here, quick!
(With the big event tomorrow, )
(Yamada said to bring the girls
and pour everyone a drink.)
(Since you guys have it hardest, )
(I brought some girls... you know?)
(Really?)
(Where's the alcohol from?)
(Shimazaki had it stashed away, )
(and Yamada took it out.)
(Just one drink for each of you.)
(If it's just one, better not to have any.)
(We'll give it a taste.)
(Come this way.)
Bro! Quickly!
Women and the wounded first.
(Can we really do this?)
(I don't see any guards.)
(I spent so much on Korean girls.)
(If the manager finds out he'll be mad.)
(Who will know we started the fire?)
(They'll think the Koreans
kicked over a candle)
(while they were sleeping.)
Out of the way!
Go back!
Hey, it's women and the wounded first!
I'm wounded too!
And she's a young girl,
shouldn't we board first?
Bro! Don't you have any shame?
Take a look at these people!
Dammit.
Then at least let Sohee go first.
No!
Get up there, kid!
The sun will be up soon.
If you see a cripple go,
you can follow, right?
You'll be fine if you follow me,
so you come next.
Doong-ge, Doong-ge, Doong-ge.
My baby Doong-ge...
I am afraid of him being caught.
Don't cry, Doong-ge.
Will he ride in on the wind?
Will he ride in on the clouds?
Come without a sound.
Come without a trace.
We wanted to be together
We wanted to live as one
If not in this world,
I'll meet you in the next world.
Doong-ge, Doong-ge, Doong-ge.
My baby Doong-ge...
I am afraid of him being caught.
Don't cry, Doong-ge.
(Get to the coal depository!)
(The Koreans are escaping!)
They've been spotted.
I'll join you, so you go first.
I keep my promises.
As they board the ship,
we'll watch their backs.
You guys in the front, move!
(The Koreans started a fire!)
(The Koreans are escaping!)
(Check the back! Quickly!)
Don't move in the back!
Snipers! Explosives!
Hold on!
(It's a real war!)
(Kill every last one of them!)
You rotten bastards!
Sohee, stay right here!
(Kill every one of them!)
(Stop shooting! That way!)
Let's go home!
I said this would never work!
From the very start!
Sohee! Hide, quickly!
Go back, you!
It's dangerous here!
Lift! With all your strength!
Go over the wall and into the water!
Snipers and explosive team, move!
The rest of you, lift!
Light them here!
Let's fight to death!
1, 2, 3...!
Dae-yeop!
Lift it!
Lift!
Sohee, hide here!
Follow me, guys!
Bring this!
Help me!
Spread it out!
Throw!
Grab the rope and follow me!
(Bullets! I'm out of bullets!)
(Bayonets!)
Charge!
Bastards! We don't deserve this!
Daddy!
Get back there Sohee, it's dangerous!
Pull the rope!
Pull out!
Chil-sung, you asshole!
Come back here, bastard!
Pull it back, quick!
Pull it back!
(What are you holding back for?)
(Move!)
Pull the rope!
Pull!
Now push it!
A little more!
Lift it up!
Push!
That's it!
Climb up!
Everyone climb up!
Let the wounded climb up!
Sohee, where are you?
Daddy!
Hey!
Come on guys!
Get up!
Bastard!
Sorry for not keeping my promise.
You can rest now.
(I'm on your side!)
(Kill all the Koreans,
whatever side they're on!)
- Bro! What do we do?
- Keep climbing!
Sung-il!
Lee Gang-ok!
Sohee, stay there!
Stay there!
Daddy! Daddy!
(I've got you now!)
(Dirty Koreans!)
(Damn you!)
(Why aren't you grateful?)
(Why!)
(It's all over now!)
(Your manager is dead!)
(Your supervisor's dead, )
(and so is Yamada!)
(Now we're going back)
(to our home!)
Daddy...
I'm not going to die.
Why are you crying?
Stop!
Go over there, Sohee.
I'm older, so let me ask you a favor.
Give her some soy noodles with sugar.
That's what she likes best.
Please look after my girl.
Sorry I couldn't give you anything.
Don't turn your nose up at raw eggs.
Sing a song for me.
Daddy, Daddy!
Daddy!
You said you wouldn't die!
You promised!
Daddy!
"August 9, 1945, 11:02AM
Atomic bomb falls on Nagasaki"
Oh my gosh... look at that.
A lot of Koreans live there too.
"Hashima's coal mine
opened in September 1890."
"From the 1937 invasion of China
to the end of World War Il,"
"it contributed greatly
to Japan's military industrial sector."
"In the 1970s Japan adopted
new energy policies"
Sohee.
"and closed the mine in January 1974."
Look at me, girl!
"Battleship Island, as a part
of Japan's Meiji Industrial Revolution,"
"became a UNESCO World Heritage
Site in 2015." Don't laugh!
Don't be nervous.
"One of UNESCO's conditions"
Answer me!
"was to post notices about forced labor"
Round your lips, with confidence!
"and other historical facts by December
2017." Did my little girl prepare well?
"But Japan has yet to comply."
Did my little girl prepare well?
Answer me!
Two, three!