Watch free HD Movies and TV Shows at
StreamingSites.com
‐ General Grant.
‐ Retain your sidearms, General.
‐ You'll go after Lee.
You'll go after him
until he's finished.
It all depends on you.
‐ Gentlemen.
‐ Grant may have won
some victories in the west,
but this is Virginia.
‐ We'll cross the Rapidan
into the Wilderness.
‐ His army is twice ours, sir.
‐ Well, we'll just have
to even the odds,
catch them before they get
through the Wilderness.
‐ Scouts say Grant's packing up.
Finally retreating, sir.
‐ No, he's not a retreating man.
‐ We're heading south?
‐ To Richmond.
‐ Richmond?
‐ We're headed south!
‐ Very few people really know
who Ulysses S. Grant was.
‐ Today there is this sense
that he's forgotten.
‐ He's been called
so many things over the years.
‐ The greatest general
of his time.
‐ A military genius.
‐ A bloody butcher.
‐ A corrupt president.
‐ A belligerent drunk
who got lucky.
He didn't get lucky.
‐ Ulysses S. Grant
is this perfectly average,
humble individual from a poor,
hardscrabble background.
‐ With a lot of hard times
and failures in his life.
‐ But he's got
this dogged determination,
this bulldog mentality.
‐ This guy comes from nothing,
rises to the highest ranks
of the Union army.
‐ Fights bloody,
terrible battles.
‐ With indomitable will.
‐ To save the Union.
‐ To heal his country.
‐ To lead the nation
towards justice for everybody.
‐ He's the unheroic hero
of our greatest national epic,
the American Civil War.
‐ It's truly an American story
not only of patriotism
to the nation
but for the values of who we are
and who we aspire to be.
‐ Fall in!
‐ The armies were now
ready to move
for the accomplishment
of a single goal:
Lee, in the capital
of the Confederacy, Richmond.
That was the main end
to which all were working.
‐ When Grant marches off
in 1864,
it's gonna set off
a titanic struggle
for the end of the war.
Grant is going to keep
their focus lasered on
to Robert E. Lee and
the Army of Northern Virginia
because Grant understood
the destruction of Lee's army
meant the destruction
of the Confederacy.
At the beginning
of the campaign,
Grant mentions
to a correspondent
who's headed off
to Washington, D. C.‐‐
he says to him,
"If you get through the lines
"and you make it
and you see President Lincoln,
"tell him from me
that whatever happens,
there will be
no turning back."
‐ After the Wilderness,
Grant heads south,
and it's just sustained combat.
He just keeps seeing these
opportunities, and he attacks,
and he attacks, and he attacks.
And it rains,
and the weather is miserable,
but they just keep going
for weeks.
‐ The battles of the Wilderness,
Spotsylvania, and North Anna,
bloody and terrible
though they were on our side,
were even more damaging
to our enemy.
‐ In some of the most savage
fighting of the war,
you see 5 1/2 weeks
of constant movement,
constant entrenching,
constant fighting
that ultimately will produce
55,000 Union casualties,
35,000 Confederate casualties.
Now Grant's men
are simply exhausted.
By the time Grant reaches
the crucial crossroads
of Cold Harbor,
these soldiers understand
keenly what's ahead.
And it's more loss.
It's more rivers of blood.
‐ If you're a soldier,
you think,
"Our chances aren't good."
And this is when we have
heartbreaking stories of men
writing on sheets of paper,
"Today was the day
I was killed at Cold Harbor,"
and pinning that to the inside
of their uniforms.
But Grant still believes that
Lee's army is almost broken.
"All I have to do
is push a little bit harder,
and they will break."
Company, prepare!
Keep pressing forward!
Hold your ground!
Come on, boys!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Come on!
Move it!
Let's go!
Go, go, go!
Let's show them
what Ohio's worth!
Advance!
‐ Cold Harbor was a disaster.
Robert E. Lee's army had
set up crossfire positions.
They had an enormous advantage,
and within only
five hours' time,
Grant's army had sustained
thousands of casualties
in one morning assault.
‐ One Union soldier likened
that combat at Cold Harbor
to a volcanic blast,
that wasn't war;
it was murder.
‐ Grant is
a very aggressive general,
and we see that
in several mistakes
that he makes
throughout the war,
including Cold Harbor.
Some have said Cold Harbor
was the price that the Union
had to pay to have Grant
as their commander.
‐ I have always regretted
the last assault at Cold Harbor.
No advantage whatever
was gained to compensate
for the heavy loss we sustained.
‐ By 1864, people are tired.
There is no clear winner,
and there is no clear end
in sight
for this conflict.
We have over
600,000 people dead,
and people are tired of it.
‐ The Northern public
was craving some good news.
Initially, the morale
in the North had been buoyed
by this new decisiveness
of Grant after the Wilderness,
and they demanded
a quick victory.
But by the time
Grant reaches Cold Harbor,
they were impatient
as the rivers
of blood continued.
‐ That's it, General.
One more in a minute, sir.
‐ General Grant, our readers
are keen to understand
how you lost so many men
during this campaign.
‐ Lee had the advantage
of being on the defensive.
He was entrenched.
I had to attack his army
where it was,
and I made him pay.
‐ Cold Harbor, General,
12,000 good Union men dead,
wounded, and missing.
‐ Do you have a question?
‐ Was it worth it, sir?
What did you gain?
‐ General Grant, sir,
if you please?
‐ General, you haven't
answered my question.
‐ Hold, please.
‐ Cold Harbor, 12,000.
What did we gain?
‐ We lost a lot
of boys your age...
fighting to keep
this country together.
What have you done
for the Union?
‐ General Grant, sir,
if you please?
‐ They called me a butcher.
‐ Hold, please.
‐ I sometimes
could hardly bring myself
to give an order at battle.
‐ He wasn't a butcher.
Many casualties came out
of the overland campaign,
but it was
fundamentally necessary
in order to win the war.
Robert E. Lee lost 50%
of his entire army
during the exact same duration,
but is Lee remembered
as a butcher?
‐ Being in command of a‐‐
of a large effort,
being the commander
is a pretty unique experience.
You know, there's no one
in whom you can confide.
It's a‐‐it is a lo‐‐it's lonely
at the top, as they say.
And the casualties
are going to be tough,
and Grant is experiencing
the butcher's bill,
as they termed it.
And it takes a great deal of,
again, just sheer fortitude,
sheer determination
to continue on
and not let this grind you down.
‐ What Grant accomplishes
after Cold Harbor is, I think,
one of his most impressive
feats of the war.
Grant decides to flank
the Army of Northern Virginia
and then cross the even more
formidable obstacle
of the James River.
‐ He's trying to keep
the initiative,
continue the momentum,
drive the energy,
and force Lee to react
to what he's doing.
This is one
of his great strengths.
‐ It's an incredibly
dangerous maneuver
to move an army of that size
across a major body of water,
especially whenever you're
faced off against an enemy
as wily as the Gray Fox,
Robert E. Lee.
And so he finds a way,
secretly, at night,
to take an army of 115,000
and disappear.
And Robert E. Lee misses this.
He misses the movement
of Grant's army.
‐ To my dear wife, Julia.
Since Sunday,
we have been engaged
in one of the most perilous
movements ever executed
by a large army,
that of withdrawing
from the front of an enemy
and moving past his flank,
crossing the James River with
a bridge we have to improvise.
‐ U. S. Grant
sets out to construct
something that nobody thought
could be constructed:
an actual pontoon bridge
across a 2,000‐foot span
of the James River.
The bridge consists
of pontoon boats,
rather large boats
that have excellent buoyancy,
strung together and connected
by wooden planks.
And through these bridges,
you could march
not only soldiers
but also artillery,
supplies, and whatnot.
‐ This is the largest
pontoon bridge
built during the entire war.
They built it in seven hours.
I mean, think about that.
He's gonna cross 100,000 men
across the James River,
including these wagons
and artillery.
But just think about the
engineering feat that that is.
That's remarkable.
‐ And so Grant gets across
the James River,
which will put his forces
in assaulting position
onto the crucial rail hub
of Petersburg, Virginia.
‐ Petersburg
is the logistics hub,
the transportation hub.
It's connected
to all the supplies
that can come up from the south.
If Lee is gonna
maintain his army,
let alone Richmond, the city,
he needs Petersburg.
So Grant understands this.
And so by threatening
Petersburg,
he, in fact, threatens Richmond.
And now
we are talking about a siege.
‐ Colonel Pleasants,
what's this plan of yours?
‐ Our Pennsylvania boys
are coal miners.
They can tunnel right
underneath their lines.
‐ How far?
‐ About 150 yards, sir.
They dig a shaft
right underneath them.
We fill the chamber with powder
and blow those rebs sky‐high.
‐ Could it break through
their fortifications?
‐ General, we have no
assurances this will work.
‐ My boys can do it.
‐ We have to consider‐‐
‐ Once the line is broken,
we go in.
We need to move quickly
after the blast.
Have artillery ready
to support the charge.
How big a hole will it blow?
‐ No one can say, sir.
But it'll be
an awful lot of powder.
‐ Ulysses S. Grant had been
familiar with the use of mines
tunneling under the enemy
positions at Vicksburg.
He tried it several times
with limited success.
The Confederates heard
the Union working.
They feared that there was
a mine tunneling under.
They dug countermines down
to try to drop in
onto the Union troops.
They could never find it
in time, however.
‐ We learned through deserters
that the people believed
very wild rumors
about what was going on.
They said that we had mined
the whole of Petersburg
and they were resting
on a slumbering volcano
and did not know at what moment
they might expect that eruption.
‐ The mine was constructed
and ready to be exploded.
And I wanted to take
the occasion
to carry Petersburg, if I could.
‐ They packed the mine
underneath
the Confederate trenches
with 8,000 pounds of explosives
to try to blast a hole into
the Confederate earthworks.
‐ The fuse starts burning.
They pack sandbags
so the explosion
doesn't come out
toward the Union troops.
‐ Go!
Move, move, move!
‐ Let's go!
‐ Faster, faster!
‐ Go!
‐ And then the earth just shook.
It immediately killed
and disintegrated
300 South Carolinians,
blowing a massive hole
in the Confederate line.
‐ And then the Union army
gets ready
to launch frontal assaults.
‐ Despite all the thought
that went into this attack,
Grant's commanders put the
worst possible guy in command,
a guy named James Ledlie,
known to be a drunk
and a coward,
in command of the attack.
‐ The problem is that instead
of going around
to the rim of the crater,
as initially planned,
James Ledlie
blunders his division
right into the middle
of the crater,
and it becomes
a virtual turkey shoot.
‐ I expected our troops not
to stop in the crater at all
but to push on
to the top of the hill,
which would have
given us everything.
‐ And then they send in
the United States
Colored Troop regiments.
Nothing incited the rage
of a Confederate soldier
like the sight
of an African‐American soldier
wielding a musket
in a blue uniform.
‐ They just start killing
these guys wholesale.
Many blacks that tried
to surrender
are shot or bayoneted.
And even white Union officers,
realizing that they also have
a death sentence
for leading black troops,
they turn their pistols
on their own soldiers
to try to save themselves.
‐ And so at the crater,
what you have
is a racial massacre.
A North Carolinian
recalled his delight
at bayoneting these
African‐American soldiers.
It was an all‐out slaughter.
‐ They slaughtered us all.
No place to go...
except to die.
‐ The effort was
a stupendous failure.
It was the saddest affair
I witnessed in the war.
‐ Grant is really at fault
at Petersburg
in delegating so much
that it interfered
with the execution of the plan.
He tries the experiment
of the crater
because he knows
how important a victory is
during the election year.
‐ 1864 is an election year.
You see Abraham Lincoln
running for reelection
on the Republican ticket.
The Democratic nominee
is George McClellan,
who is running
on a platform of peace.
The Democrats in 1864
want to end the war
as soon as possible.
They are fine with letting
the Confederacy go.
‐ McClellan was on record
that he was willing
to trade emancipation for peace.
Grant considered this little
short of outright treason.
‐ People forget that there
was not uniform support
for the Union effort
in the Northern states.
Back in 1863 in New York City,
there were huge draft riots.
There was a lot of unrest
because it didn't seem
as if the Union was prevailing.
So now Lee's only hope
was that Lincoln
would be defeated.
McClellan would win
and sue for peace.
‐ To have peace on any terms,
the South would demand
the restoration
of their slaves already freed.
They would demand a treaty
which would make the North
slave hunters for the South.
‐ So '64 is a big year.
The war's now no longer just
about preserving the Union.
Now it's become
a war for freedom.
And with the election,
everything's at stake.
‐ General Grant...
I hold you
in the highest esteem,
but this catastrophe
in the crater...
Every day, I hear from
the press that I'm too timid
or too tyrannical,
too weak or... too tall.
My reelection and the outcome
of this miserable war...
depends on you.
‐ General Sherman is at
the threshold of Atlanta,
and I am at the threshold
of Petersburg‐‐
‐ And I am at the threshold
of losing the presidency.
‐ Mr. President,
you will never hear of me
farther from Richmond
than I am now.
I will fight it out
till the end.
‐ Hold on with a bulldog grip,
and chew and choke
as much as possible.
‐ Grant is working with Lincoln,
very much in concert,
on how they want
to conduct this war.
And we see that in how Grant
plans his campaigns.
He's really, I think,
the first general
that Lincoln had
that had an overall strategy
for the entire war.
‐ I mean, this is still
a very fluid war, even by '64.
So the Union needs
some decisive wins.
‐ One of the key prongs
of Grant's strategy
for the reduction of the South
is, of course, to take Atlanta.
‐ If you don't topple Georgia,
which was one of the top
manpower‐delivering states
behind the Confederate
war effort,
and you don't topple Atlanta,
which is a hub of industry
for the South,
then it makes it
possible to sustain
the Confederate war effort
for a prolonged period of time.
‐ This is a no‐fail mission,
and you give it to the person
who you've developed
a level of trust
and who you know
is hard enough to do it,
smart enough to do it,
and also will do the intent
of what you want them to do
rather than getting off base,
and Sherman is that person.
‐ Send this
to General Grant at once.
"We are in close proximity
and constantly skirmishing
"but are not yet able
to penetrate
the city's fortifications."
‐ William Tecumseh Sherman
would lead
the military division
of Mississippi
through northwest Georgia,
targeting the industrial heart
of Georgia at Atlanta:
the machine shops, the mills,
the factories that were
keeping the Confederate army
in the west going.
‐ And it's Grant who, from afar,
is choreographing this effort.
And Grant and Sherman
maintain a constant
communication via telegraph
despite the more
than 1,000 miles
that intervened between them.
‐ "If you can hold tight
as you are now,
you will destroy
most of that army."
"I would never advise
going backward."
‐ As Sherman
is approaching Atlanta,
Grant is sort of pushing him
that, "We need to get this done.
We need to take Atlanta
before the election comes."
‐ "I have lost
a good many regiments."
Continue sending.
"I might have to circle Atlanta
before I take it,
but I will take it."
‐ We learned that Sherman
had our troops in Atlanta.
The news of his success
set the country aglow.
‐ Sherman drives on Atlanta,
delivering Atlanta,
and effectively, you do have
some aspects of total war.
We are about collapsing the
will of the Confederate people
to realize,
"You are being defeated."
‐ The fall of Atlanta
boosts Northern morale.
People now begin to see
that a Union victory is,
while not inevitable,
at least in sight.
And it has an enormous impact
on the election of 1864.
‐ Lincoln would win
the election.
What ultimately gave Lincoln
that election on the battlefield
was Sherman's capture
of Atlanta.
This was part of Grant's
grand strategy
for how to bring about
an end to the war.
Grant has a brilliant
strategic plan.
He's going to move multiple
armies simultaneously
to bring about maximum
pressure on the Confederacy
while also holding down
Robert E. Lee's
much‐vaunted
Army of Northern Virginia
at Petersburg.
‐ When Grant starts
to settle in at Petersburg,
he sees, "If I put Lee
into a siege, he can't move."
"And a Robert E. Lee
who cannot maneuver
"is a Robert E. Lee that's not
nearly as dangerous.
"So if I pin Lee,
"we'll eat the rest
of the Confederacy
while we stand here and watch
this all take place."
‐ So Grant decides to move
Phil Sheridan
up the Shenandoah Valley,
threatening
the logistical supply line
of Robert E. Lee's army,
threatening the bread basket
of the Confederacy
that for three years
had supplied
the Army of Northern Virginia.
‐ To General Sheridan:
Do all the damage to railroads
and crops you can.
We want the Shenandoah Valley
to remain a barren waste.
Move quickly with the goal of
destroying all in your path.
‐ After Philip Sheridan
destroys the Shenandoah Valley,
William Tecumseh Sherman
marches through Georgia.
Grant famously says,
"The Confederacy
is a hollow shell.
I know it, and Sherman
is about to prove it."
‐ To General Sherman:
If you are satisfied
the trip to the seacoast
can be made,
you may make it,
destroying all the railroad
as you think best.
‐ What Sherman is doing
in Georgia
is sending a message
to Lee's army:
"You guys hold out here
in Richmond
"and you hold out here
in Petersburg,
but we're just tearing out
the guts of the Confederacy."
‐ And meanwhile,
Robert E. Lee's army
is becoming malnourished.
His men are living in conditions
that are rife for disease.
The biological decline
of his men
is beginning to show
to Robert E. Lee
in a way
that he'd never seen before.
‐ They are severely worn down,
and they are the ones that
have to defend Petersburg.
Petersburg is the logistics hub,
the transportation hub
connected
to five separate railroads
that come into Petersburg
that feed Richmond,
the capital of the Confederacy.
Robert E. Lee
can't lose Petersburg,
or he loses Richmond.
‐ By April of 1865,
Grant has captured
all of the important railroads
at Petersburg
with the exception of one,
and that's
the Southside Railroad.
And there's
a crucial intersection
that commands control
of the Southside Railroad.
It's known as Five Forks.
‐ Everything looked favorable
to the defeat of the enemy
and the capture
of Petersburg and Richmond
if the proper effort was made.
‐ And so Grant will unleash
Phil Sheridan
to get out in front
of Robert E. Lee
and keep him from getting
to that railroad
and those supplies.
‐ It's a vicious fight.
At one point, Sheridan, he's
actually on horseback himself
and launches himself
over Confederate attackers,
ordering the men to surrender.
‐ The Confederates
will lose this battle,
and they lose
the Southside Railroad.
‐ And now, finally, we find
Grant is able
to sever those supply lines
that come into Petersburg,
and Robert E. Lee
now has to realize,
"We have to abandon Richmond."
‐ Richmond was in
the most utter confusion.
The city was on fire,
started by some connected
with the retreating army.
When it was evacuated,
the Confederacy at once
began to crumble and fade away.
‐ The Confederates
now scramble to the west
to make this desperate attempt
to link up
with Joe Johnston's
Army of Tennessee.
And if they can link up again,
they can prolong the war.
And so it becomes a chase.
‐ Lee's troops were pursued
by our cavalry so hotly
and closely that they threw
away ammunition, clothing,
and almost everything
to lighten their loads.
‐ No sooner has Lee
evacuated his lines
than Grant takes off after him.
Any other Union general would
have marched into Petersburg
and marched into Richmond
with bands playing and great
celebrations and parties
and all kinds of
self‐congratulatory speeches
and reviews and messages
sent back to Washington
about how wonderful it was,
they have now captured Richmond.
Not Grant.
‐ One of ours, sir.
A messenger
from General Sheridan
who made it through their lines.
‐ Soldier.
Good job, soldier.
Sheridan wants me
to come to him at Jetersville.
Says he can finish Lee.
We'll go right away.
I'll take the advance troops.
‐ General, you're the commander.
You've gotta stay‐‐
‐ We'll go right away.
‐ Grant is managing more people
than anyone else
in the world at this moment.
And then he gets a message
from Phil Sheridan saying,
"I think we can capture
or destroy
the Confederate army now."
As the commander
of all those armies,
sometimes your presence
is simply needed.
No matter how tired he was,
no matter how far away
Sheridan was,
Grant was gonna get there.
‐ I then started
with a few of my staff
going directly
through the woods.
The night being dark,
our progress was slow.
Sometimes I had great difficulty
in getting through the lines.
‐ We've got Lee
in a box, General.
‐ We should be protecting
our position at Richmond,
not chasing Lee.
‐ We can't let him slip.
I can capture
his whole damn army!
‐ Holding Richmond
won't end this war.
Destroying Lee's army will.
Go after him.
‐ Yes, sir.
‐ It now became
a life‐and‐death struggle
for Lee
to get south to his provisions.
We wanted to get ahead of Lee
and cut him off.
‐ The armies finally met
on Sailor's Creek.
The enemy's loss was very heavy.
Lee's army
was rapidly crumbling.
‐ The final battle between
Grant's army and Robert E. Lee
comes at Sailor's Creek,
April 6, 1865.
‐ Lee's army haven't eaten
for five days.
He's had 2/3 of his force
whittled away
by attacks from his rear.
He is out of options.
‐ Robert E. Lee sees the men
streaming from
the battlefield in chaos,
and Lee turns, and he says
to one of his staff officers,
"My God,
has the army dissolved?"
‐ 7,000 of his men
were made prisoners.
I knew that the men
who had fought so gallantly
and so long for the cause
which they believed in
had lost hope.
‐ Come on, keep moving!
‐ Grant knows
Lee's out of options,
and he is counting on Lee
to be chivalrous
and end the war.
‐ To General R.E. Lee:
The result of the last week
must convince you
of the hopelessness
of further resistance.
I regard it as my duty
to shift from myself
the responsibility of any
further effusion of blood...
By asking of you
the surrender of that portion
of the Confederate States Army
known as
the Army of Northern Virginia.
‐ Lee realizes
that the game is over,
and so he sends
a message to Grant:
"If we could discuss matters
"as you had previously
indicated,
I would be happy
to meet with you."
‐ When Lee talks
about having to go
and capitulate to Grant,
Lee says,
"I would rather go die
a thousand deaths
than go do
what I'm about to do."
But he asks for the cease‐fire
to talk about
terms of surrender.
‐ A messenger came up to Grant
and gave him the letter
from Lee saying,
"Can you meet me at the McLean
house in Appomattox?'
And so he went to Appomattox
to meet Lee.
‐ It all ends at the
Wilbur McLean farmhouse.
Robert E. Lee
stands in his best uniform.
Lee dreads having to do this.
‐ Dismount!
‐ General Lee.
‐ General Grant.
‐ Perhaps you remember,
we met once
back in the Mexican War.
‐ Yes, I'm sure you're right.
I don't quite recall.
‐ I was with
the Fourth Regiment.
‐ It was a long time ago.
‐ Please.
‐ As they sit there
in that room,
it's truly a remarkable scene.
You capture this whole nature
of the changing character
of war in that farmhouse.
You have Robert E. Lee,
immaculately dressed
with his sash and his sword,
a patrician
of the Virginia caste society,
the son of
a Revolutionary War general,
a single commander
commanding as if he were
a 16th‐century prince
representing the last
of the old wars.
Meanwhile, you have
Ulysses S. Grant,
representing the first
of the new.
Grant has been riding overland.
His boots are mud‐spattered.
He's the son of a tanner,
a poor, humble,
hardscrabble background.
He sits now at the top
of this meritocracy
surrounded by
a very capable staff.
And he has an American Indian
on his staff,
Eli Parker, a brigadier general,
a Seneca Indian
that's gonna write out
the terms of surrender.
‐ General Grant...
we should write terms now.
‐ General Parker.
‐ At least there's one
real American in this room.
‐ We're all Americans here, sir.
‐ Your terms are generous.
They'll have
a good effect on my men.
‐ Good.
And I must ask you in return
that you ask the rest
of your armies
lay down their arms.
They'll listen to you,
and this war can end quickly
without further suffering.
‐ That's not up to me.
That's up to my president.
‐ There's only
one president now.
‐ I felt like anything rather
than rejoicing at the downfall
of a foe who had fought
so long and valiantly
and had suffered so much
for a cause,
though that cause was,
I believe,
one of the worst for which
a people ever fought.
‐ Grant and Lincoln wanted,
at all costs,
to prevent a kind
of guerilla warfare,
which is why Grant
gave the terms
that he did to Lee
at Appomattox.
‐ The surrender terms
are relatively lenient.
Officers can keep
their sidearms.
Men with horses
can keep their horses
so that they might go back
and plant crops.
This is an idea of,
"How do we win the peace?"
‐ Grant really tried to honor
what Lincoln asked for.
Let him up easy.
Let these men go home.
Just lay down your guns,
and just go home.
‐ Grant actually went a little
bit further than Lincoln
might have wanted him to.
He paroled the Southern army,
Lee's army.
And that meant Lee himself
would be free from arrest.
‐ Very significantly,
Grant did not allow
his soldiers to in any way
gloat or celebrate.
He felt that that would simply
be rubbing salt into the wounds
of these defeated
Confederate soldiers.
And I think the fact
that Grant had experienced
so much failure in his own life
gave him a special sensitivity
and tact in dealing with these
defeated Confederate soldiers
at Appomattox.
So you can see
that there's this yearning
to be brothers again.
There were shared memories
and shared experiences
that these men had had,
and these are people
who had belonged
to the same nation
and that would again.
‐ When news of the surrender
of Lee's army
gets back to Washington,
Lincoln is so thrilled.
A crowd of well‐wishers comes
with bands to serenade him.
Lincoln comes out and gives
them an impromptu speech.
‐ Now, fellow citizens,
give three good, hearty cheers
for General Grant
and all under his command.
‐ Grant stands in the front rank
of great Americans of all time.
He was the man
who saved the Union.
‐ Grant is one of the greatest
military strategists
that the United States
has produced.
It is his strategy implemented
and pushed forward
to its conclusion
that wins the war.
‐ The news of Appomattox
is immediately reported
across the country.
There was a jubilant feeling,
at least in the‐‐in the North,
and a great feeling of relief.
‐ There's such this feeling
of celebration
throughout the North:
the fireworks
that are being set off,
people in the streets
celebrating,
the bunting that's being
put up all across
Washington and New York
and elsewhere,
and ministers across the North
begin preparing sermons
to talk about
the rebirth of the nation.
‐ I'm relieved we didn't
go to the theater tonight,
and the children will be
so happy to see you, finally.
‐ It's been a long time.
‐ Mm.
Do you know that man?
‐ I don't care for such looks.
Driver!
‐ On the night of April 14th,
the Lincolns had invited
the Grants
to attend Ford's Theatre
with them.
But they were instead planning
to visit their children.
While the Grants were
en route to the train,
a man on horseback galloped up,
tried to thrust his head in
as if to see who was there.
Always afterwards,
Julia Dent Grant believed
that man had been
John Wilkes Booth.
‐ General Grant.
‐ What is it?
‐ These are for you, sir.
‐ Excuse me, gentlemen.
‐ What is it, Ulys?
‐ I have to return
to Washington.
President Lincoln has been shot.
He won't survive.
‐ John Wilkes Booth
had gathered a small band
of conspirators
because Booth planned
not only to murder Lincoln
but to murder
Vice President Andrew Johnson,
Secretary of State Seward,
and General Ulysses S. Grant.
He planned to decapitate
the entire
United States government,
if he could do it.
‐ I did not know what it meant.
Here was the rebellion
put down in the field
and starting up in the gutters.
Now we had to fight it
as assassination.
‐ Grant gets back in Washington
by 10:00 the next day,
and Andrew Johnson
is already being sworn in
as president
of the United States.
What a different world
Ulysses Grant has returned to.
‐ The joy that I had witnessed
among the people in the street
and in public places
in Washington
had been turned to grief.
The city was in reality
a city of mourning.
‐ Lee surrenders to Grant
on April 9th,
and only a week later,
on Good Friday,
Lincoln is assassinated.
And a city that had been
so full of hope
and joy and messages of peace
is immediately
brought to mourning.
And the churches that had been
decorated for Easter Sunday,
full of their lilies
and other symbols of peace,
are now draped in mourning.
Only days after coming back
from Appomattox
and being this great,
victorious general,
now Grant is tasked
with planning the funeral
of a man who had been
not only his president
but also had become
a dear friend.
‐ To know Lincoln personally
was to love and respect him
for his great qualities
of heart and head.
His death was
the greatest possible
calamity to the country
and especially
to the people of the South.
‐ After the war,
the South is devastated.
What was all of their wealth
has largely been wiped out.
Lincoln gets killed.
Now who's gonna provide
that stability?
Who is gonna be the one man
who can provide that stable,
guiding hand on the nation?
‐ When the war ends,
Ulysses S. Grant
is still general in chief.
And this becomes
extremely significant
because there's nobody who has
a more comprehensive view
of what's going on in the South
in the years after
the Civil War than Grant.
‐ And so in 1865,
Grant's duties,
his responsibilities
as general of the armies,
was to run
the largest civil project
ever the federal government
had taken on,
known as Reconstruction.
Reconstruction, fundamentally,
was military occupation.
And it was organized around
five military districts
within the American South.
‐ Reconstruction
was three things.
It was to rebuild
infrastructure in the South.
It was to help transition
newly freed people
and what freedom
could look like for them,
most of whom
are completely illiterate,
who have no property,
who have no prospects,
but who have desire.
And it was to restructure
legal systems
to help protect
newly freed people
and to address this idea
of equality for everyone.
‐ But I don't think anyone
recognized the true magnitude
of what Reconstruction was
going to look like in America,
the level and number
of challenges
of problems that could
potentially emerge
from the end
of the American Civil War.
‐ The success of the Union army
doesn't mean a return
to the status quo.
It means the Union restored
without slavery.
And so the most egregious part
of Union victory
for former Confederates
is emancipation.
And so they push back on it
from the very beginning.
They push back in legal ways
called the Black Codes.
‐ They create a series
of actions
that will mirror
the conditions of slavery.
And so throughout the 1860s,
in major cities,
conflicts would erupt between
former Confederate soldiers
and free African‐Americans.
‐ You see this conflict
in New Orleans in 1866.
African‐Americans and a handful
of white Republicans
are trying to write a new
constitution for the state
that would recognize
African‐American voting
and civil rights.
What happens is, a local
newspaper whips up a frenzy.
Ex‐Confederates gather,
trying to stop them.
It was an absolute powder keg.
‐ We stand here today
as free men,
but that's just the beginning.
We have to stand up
for our rights.
We have to fight‐‐
‐ Come on!
Out the back!
‐ I just got a telegraph
from General Sheridan.
This outrage in New Orleans
must be punished.
I simply can't allow‐‐
‐ General, we don't know
if the freed men provoked this.
It was a riot.
‐ This is an atrocity.
Sheridan is there.
‐ They're gettin' away!
‐ And the way he tells it,
this is a massacre.
Don't let him get away!
Hold him, boys!
‐ It's my duty
to protect the people.
‐ Try telling that
to President Johnson.
‐ Instead, I wish
I could speak with Lincoln.
We could declare martial law.
‐ Sir‐‐ ‐ It won't be popular,
but I don't want another war.
We can't have another war.
‐ So in 1866,
Grant receives reports
from his commanders
throughout the South,
and it becomes quite evident
that there are hundreds
if not thousands of so‐called
outrages of African‐Americans
being killed in horrific,
barbarious ways.
‐ Grant is constantly
compiling statistics
for President Andrew Johnson
in terms of the scale
of violence
going on against the 4 million
former slaves in the South,
and Johnson refuses
to believe it.
‐ Andrew Johnson is able
to emerge as a figure
who is a friend
of the Confederacy
who will not
implement Reconstruction
with the great force
of the federal government.
‐ Grant is
increasingly frustrated
and furious that Johnson
is trying to impede
any sort of military
intervention in the South.
But I think we underestimate
how politically savvy Grant was.
‐ Grant is an interesting man
as a political figure.
He doesn't seek out
the nomination
for the presidency ever,
but he doesn't turn down
the nomination
for the presidency either.
‐ Because of the Civil War
and because of Grant's heroism‐‐
and at Appomattox,
Grant becomes the hero
not only in the North
but in the South
for his fairness
to the defeated
Confederate troops‐‐
Grant enjoyed a certain status
and sort of levitated
above the level
of American politics.
‐ And not unlike Washington,
that Washington was
the father of the country
and Grant was the savior
of the country
is something that is
on many people's minds.
‐ And of course, at that time,
it was considered unseemly
for a candidate to openly
campaign for president,
and that was
just fine with Grant.
And rather than campaigning,
he's kind of swept
into the presidency.
‐ Grant wins the 1868 election
in an electoral
college landslide,
but his presidency
would be the presidency
that had the responsibility
of securing political rights
for African‐Americans.
He had an enormous
responsibility
and an incredibly difficult one,
because there were
so many people,
both in the South
and in the North,
who were opposed to those ideas.
But he was given
the difficult task, not once,
but twice, of doing this,
winning the war
and then winning the peace.
‐ In here, Mr. President.
‐ The country having
just emerged
from a great rebellion, many
questions will come before it
for settlement
in the next four years
which preceding administrations
have never had to deal with.
In meeting these,
it is desirable
that they should be
approached calmly,
without prejudice, hate,
or sectional pride.
I ask patient forbearance,
one toward another,
throughout the land
and a determined effort
on the part of every citizen
to do his share towards
cementing a happy Union.
‐ I feel the responsibilities
of the position
but accept them without fear.
And I bring to it
a desire and determination
to fill it
to the best of my ability.
‐ When Ulysses Grant
is inaugurated as president,
he has what amounts to
a colossal mess on his hands.
He has not only Reconstruction,
but he has a botched attempt
at beginning Reconstruction
under Andrew Johnson
that he has to overcome.
And that's going to create
a formidable agenda
for him to deal with
as president.
Reconstruction meant
the reintroduction
of the Confederate states
back into the American Union,
which sounds pretty simple,
but you've got to have some way
of reintegrating
the Southern economy
with the rest
of the national economy.
Then you have to think about
what you're going to do
with the freed slaves.
The 13th Amendment
abolishes slavery,
but what does it do beyond that?
‐ When Grant becomes president
of the United States,
he is absolutely committed
to the aims of Reconstruction.
He is committed to making
America fully just,
fully equal for black people
and white people.
He is committed to this in his
own simple and elegant way.
‐ So it's very important
to remember that Grant
is the first American president
to govern after
the 14th Amendment
that guarantees equal rights
before the law
and, most importantly,
after the 15th Amendment,
which gives black men
the right to vote.
After the passage
of the 15th Amendment,
African‐American men began to
vote in extraordinary numbers.
‐ Americans are finally
who they say they are.
All men are truly created equal.
I think this utterly
is reflected of Grant
and what he believes
this nation is
and what it should aspire to be.
‐ So now we have 3.5 million
people from Mississippi
to Louisiana to South Carolina
voting themselves and the
candidates of their choosing.
‐ African‐Americans
in most Southern states
were elected for the first
time to Washington, D. C.,
as senators and as congressmen
but on a state level as well.
And all these things,
this incredible
biracial experiment,
was happening.
‐ And the changes that they
make are extraordinary.
They establish free public
education for every child.
They establish systems
that make it easier
for people to vote and to
be able to acquire land.
‐ It's a period of possibility
in American history.
It was not just
a political project.
It was also a social project.
And you see the building
of schools,
the building of banks.
You see more people
are learning to read
among African‐American
communities than ever before.
‐ You probably had more
political progress
for black people than you
actually had in the North.
You know, not just because
there were more black people
but because of what was
happening was so revolutionary.
‐ There is a profoundly
progressive agenda
moving the arc towards justice
for everybody.
And then it falls apart.
‐ The Ku Klux Klan
very quickly grows
to become a paramilitary
insurgency
in which armed
Confederate veterans
will turn to violent tactics.
‐ There were thousands of blacks
who were killed for registering
and daring to‐‐to vote,
and black voting
would drop off to near zero.
‐ In many counties throughout
the ex‐Confederate South,
the Ku Klux Klan
is really controlling
the levers of power,
and they are meting out their
brand of vigilante justice.
‐ Mr. President.
You're thinking like
a politician, not a general.
‐ Well, there's more than
one way to get things done.
‐ But these Ku Kluxers' minds
won't be changed by words.
You of all people know that.
‐ Yes, and I know the misery
that the use of force leads to.
‐ That misery is all on
my people's heads right now.
Should we just wait, be patient?
‐ No.
That wouldn't be fair.
You will see the general
in me soon enough.
‐ Frederick Douglass,
he understands
Grant's huge popularity
among the people,
and he wants to help Grant
be that next great
American leader
in the vein
of a George Washington.
‐ But the question is,
what exactly can he do
about the activities
of the Klan?
Because this is,
after all, a state matter.
What Congress does
is to equip Grant
with the Ku Klux Klan Act.
‐ Grant felt so strongly
about the KKK Act
that he actually marched up
to Capitol Hill
with his entire cabinet
to lobby for it.
This was a very powerful
and sweeping act.
‐ It allows Grant
to declare martial law
and send federal troops
in directly to intervene.
‐ I've been there,
seen it myself, Mr. President.
The Ku Kluxers
are all over those towns.
They're farmers,
sheriffs, politicians.
‐ You served in the war,
didn't you?
‐ Yes, sir.
Missouri.
‐ And you faced your share
of rebel guerillas there.
How'd you deal with them?
‐ Well, sir, we had to find
the enemy any way we could.
We used informants, spies.
‐ Exactly.
‐ We had to gather information,
identities, find out
who the leaders were.
‐ And that's what you're gonna
do now against the Klan.
After you learn who your
targets are, you'll strike.
And I don't care if they're
doctors or farmers or lawyers.
You arrest them and try them.
‐ Yes, sir.
‐ You're gonna root them out,
Merrill,
no matter what it takes.
‐ You can count on me,
Mr. President.
‐ And so in 1871,
several companies
of the Seventh Cavalry
are sent into South Carolina,
where, under
Major Lewis Merrill,
they actually go out and begin
arresting large numbers
of Klan members
to bring them to justice.
‐ It took a lot of
counterintelligence operations,
of getting to know who
the political leaders were,
getting to know who
the Klan leaders were‐‐
a difficult thing to do,
but ultimately, Grant
is going to be successful
at defeating the Klan.
‐ For all practical purposes,
by 1872,
the operations
of the Ku Klux Klan
had been pretty successfully
suppressed,
and it is one of
the significant achievements
of Grant's administration.
‐ I think fighting and defeating
the Klan is a big deal.
And so that Grant defeats
the first wave of the Klan is,
I think, something that people
have not paid
enough attention to.
‐ And so the 1871 Klan Acts
made it safe enough
for African‐Americans
to vote in the South.
But there was pushback,
and there was pushback
in large part
because many people believed
that Grant was overextending
his hand with the Klan Acts.
Many white Northerners,
including a fair number
of Union soldiers,
are never on board
with occupying the South.
They say, "If this can happen
in the South,
why can't it happen
in the North?"
‐ And the country's also aware
of the great cost
of this military occupation,
the great cost
of Reconstruction.
And quite frankly, they've
grown weary of Reconstruction.
‐ Grant is well aware
that public opinion
goes strongly against
the use of federal troops
just being sent in whenever
there's some kind of emergency
and martial law being declared.
In other words, he could wreck
the entire
Reconstruction project
if he reaches for the
martial law weapon too much.
‐ I thought I could
run the government
of the United States as I did
the staff of my army.
It was my mistake,
and it led me
into other mistakes.
‐ What's this?
‐ Requests, Mr. President.
Suggestions for
cabinet appointments.
Businessmen
want to meet with you.
Another report of violence
in the South.
Sherman wants troops in the
west to contain the Indians.
One of the Indians,
a chief named Red Cloud,
wants to come to Washington
to meet you.
‐ When Grant is president,
he's dealing with a host
of issues with the
Transcontinental Railroad,
certainly with Native Americans.
He makes a pledge of leniency
and goodwill
toward Native Americans
which ultimately
doesn't pan out.
And we're moving
into the period when industry
and capitalism
are coming to the forefront.
‐ The economy in the North,
in particular, had expanded
tremendously during the war.
So you have‐‐
during Grant's presidency,
you have the beginnings
of the rise of big business.
At the same time,
there's an enormous expansion
of the federal government,
and there is much more
opportunity
for government corruption
than before.
‐ Grant himself was not corrupt.
Ironically, his presidential
administration goes down as one
that is remembered
as being corrupt.
‐ Grant thinks everybody
has a good heart,
everybody has as good
a heart as he does.
‐ Grant has a blind loyalty
to people,
and some of the people that
he appointed were corrupt.
‐ You see that fierce loyalty
with his secretary,
Orville Babcock.
Babcock was involved
with the Whisky Ring,
which was government officials
working with
whiskey distributors
and dealers to embezzle money
to the tune
of $1 1/2 million a year,
and it was a major,
major scandal.
But Grant's loyalty
was so strong,
he vouched for Babcock.
‐ There was an innocence
about Grant,
and because he was not
deceitful himself,
he had a lot of difficulty
seeing that in other people.
And everyone who knew Grant was
mystified by his gullibility.
‐ Corruption increasingly
becomes a problem
as bribes become more evident.
And so there is a cultural
shift that's going on.
‐ Voters take their
frustrations to the polls
in the midterm elections
in 1874,
and they put
a Democratic majority,
for the first time
since the Civil War,
into the House
of Representatives.
Once there's
a Democratic majority
in the House of Representatives,
Grant finds himself crippled
in all of these
Reconstruction measures.
‐ The notion
that his administration
is full of corruption
leads people to doubt
and to pull back
from supporting him,
especially when it comes
to Reconstruction.
But Grant remained popular,
and he certainly remained
popular with Union veterans.
‐ Good to see you, sir.
‐ Thank you.
‐ You're too good
to your country.
Good men.
Good men and true.
‐ Thank you, sir.
‐ It's nice to meet you, sir.
‐ Pleased to meet you,
President Grant.
I fought with General Thomas
over in Chattanooga.
‐ I won't forget you, soldier.
‐ Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
‐ Excuse me, gentlemen.
‐ General.
‐ In September 1875,
Grant gets an appeal from
Governor Adelbert Ames
of Mississippi,
and Ames says that there's
already so much violence
ahead of the November elections.
And so he asks Grant
to send down federal troops.
‐ There's a real pushback
to any more intervention
in the South.
Many white Northerners
say enough is enough.
There's a notion
that corruption abounds
in the federal government,
and there's no longer
a real willingness
of white Northerners to say,
"More needs to be done
for African‐Americans."
‐ So now Grant has to weigh
what intervention in the South
will mean at the polls
in Northern states
for Republicans.
Do you sacrifice
the Republican Party,
and the only party
that's supporting
and defending African‐American
voting rights,
or do you capitulate
to this terrorism
on the ground in the South?
‐ It was duty on one side and
party obligation on the other.
Between the two, I hesitated.
If a mistake was made,
it was one of the head
and not of the heart.
Tell the governor of Mississippi
that I won't be sending troops.
I should not have yielded.
It requires no prophet
to foresee that the results
of the war would be
in large measure lost.
‐ And so after Grant
leaves office,
Reconstruction
is effectively over.
‐ Grant is not the one
who abandoned Reconstruction.
The American people
abandoned Reconstruction,
and he just couldn't
rally them back in
because of the swirl
of things around him.
And the abandonment
was also an abandonment
of the ideals behind it,
which was really equality
for everyone.
And when that was abandoned,
the remnants
of this white supremacy
was able to reemerge.
The subjugation of black people
was allowed
to reassert itself unchecked.
It will take another 100 years
of people pushing
against status quo
before we can even get to
a point where we get Congress
to actually enforce the
amendments of Reconstruction.
‐ But Grant's presidency,
in many ways,
was a heroic presidency.
All of these things
that he accomplished,
he didn't accomplish because
he was pursuing fame
or money or power.
All these things
that he accomplished
were just in the course
of doing his patriotic duty.
‐ He was probably
the most respected man
and maybe the only who could
have led at those times,
and look what he does.
He starts
the Justice Department.
Then he battles
the Ku Klux Klan.
He passes the 15th Amendment.
Under his watch,
the nation advances,
and he does not just one
but two terms.
And yet ultimately,
I don't really think
he was a political animal
in any sense.
‐ Personally,
I was weary of office.
I never wanted
to get out of a place
as much as I did the presidency.
‐ Grant felt, especially
in his second term,
he felt that was in jail
every single day.
In fact, he used that
in a letter:
"I'm breaking out of jail."
He couldn't wait to leave,
and he planned to travel.
He loved to travel.
He loved to be on the move.
And he and Julia spent two years
traveling around the world.
He went to India.
He went to China.
He went to Japan.
‐ And in every country
where he goes,
he's received
by tremendous crowds.
So routinely, 100,000,
200,000, 250,000 people
would pour into the streets.
So clearly,
after Abraham Lincoln,
the one name that the world
knew was Ulysses S. Grant.
‐ When Grant returns
to the United States
after his two‐year world tour,
he is looking for an income.
Presidents had no pension
at the time,
and his son Ulysses Jr.
Had gotten involved
in Wall Street.
So Grant and his son started
a partnership for a firm
with a man named Ferdinand Ward,
an up‐and‐coming phenom
in the Wall Street market.
The principal members
are given allowances
of $3,000 a month.
There's just money rolling in.
‐ Father...
we need to speak.
‐ What is it?
‐ Ward is gone.
He's taken the money.
Everything's lost...
everything.
‐ And it turned out
that Ferdinand Ward
was the Bernie Madoff
of his day.
The whole thing
was a big Ponzi scheme.
Grant woke up one morning
only to discover
that he was worth exactly $80
and Julia was worth
exactly $130.
He was wiped out.
All his children were wiped out.
‐ What's the matter, Ulys?
You look ill.
‐ I must speak with you.
‐ Of course.
What is it?
‐ This morning,
I was a wealthy man.
And now I've lost everything.
‐ So what brings the famous
Mark Twain to my parlor?
‐ General...
a reason for my visit.
I hear you've agreed
to write your memoirs
for "The Century" magazine.
‐ They've made me an offer.
‐ And what royalty
have they promised you?
‐ 10%.
‐ General, they are treating you
as if you were a private
in an army
nobody ever heard of.
Let me make you a better offer.
‐ But you're too late, Clemens.
I have committed
to "Century's" publisher,
and I can't go back on my word.
‐ Let me publish your memoirs.
I promise, you'll leave
your family well off
and the nation richer
for your story.
‐ In 1884, Ulysses S. Grant,
Civil War general
and two‐term president
of the United States,
was now faced with poverty.
And Sam Clemens,
better known as Mark Twain,
arrived at his home
to see if he could help Grant
by having him write his memoirs
and leave a lasting legacy
of how he saw the war
and how he saw one
of the most pivotal moments
in American history.
So eventually, Grant
did go with Twain's offer
to make money for his family
to save them from poverty.
‐ But during the summer
before he started writing,
he bites into a peach,
and he says that somehow
something stung him
from the peach in his throat
and he can't figure out
what it is.
He sees a doctor,
and at that point,
they realize that it's cancer
and that they can't operate.
So he realizes that it's fatal.
‐ What is to be my fate?
Will I have to lay awake again?
Making it a study
how to get a breath
is about as much
as I could stand
to go through another night.
‐ Grant wrote the memoirs
under horrific conditions.
He said that every time
he drank a glass of water,
it was like drinking
a glass of molten lead.
This was a truly heroic effort
of Grant in agonizing pain,
writing the memoirs.
And he literally willed
himself to stay alive.
‐ And it's the final battle
of his life,
the battle to outrace
his terminal cancer
in order to finish his memoirs
and rescue his family
from bankruptcy.
‐ But as everything else
in his life,
he did not let it defeat him.
In the end, he would prevail,
and he would finish the book.
‐ These volumes are dedicated
to the American soldier
and sailor,
U. S. Grant, 1885.
‐ He dies three days
after writing the last page,
and Twain realizes at once
that what Grant has written
is a monument
in American literature.
‐ My family is American
and has been for generations.
In all its branches, direct...
‐ This memoir
is hugely important
and hugely powerful.
It earns over half
a million dollars for Julia,
which, of course, in today's
money, would be much more.
It's very successful,
and people read it everywhere.
I think something people
tend to forget now
is that Grant, at his death,
was arguably the most famous
American in the world.
‐ The response to his death
was amazing.
The national funeral which
took place in New York City
that day began with bells
ringing all over the country,
North and South.
It was just a national
outpouring of grief for him.
‐ In 1900, Theodore Roosevelt
suggested that Grant, Lincoln,
and Washington
loomed as the three great
heroes of American history.
So even as late
as the turn of the century,
he's part
of this heroic firmament.
And then in the decades
that follow,
that diminishes rapidly.
‐ What happened was that
the history of the war
came to be written by a lot
of pro‐Southern historians
who exercise a powerful sway.
It's often called
the Lost Cause.
‐ The Lost Cause narrative
is really an effort
of the South to say,
"How did we sacrifice so much
for a cause so bad as slavery?"
So they changed the narrative.
"No, no, it was about state's
rights and independence."
And so that narrative
has become
the predominant narrative,
and I think a part of it
that gets buried in there
is the role of Grant.
‐ There were three separate
attacks on his legacy.
Grant is known by many
as the butcher.
Grant is known as the drunk.
Grant is known as the corrupt.
‐ Everything else
gets stripped away,
and you've got the guy
that won the Civil War
and he was an alcoholic
and a failed president.
‐ And the Lost Cause
casts Grant as the villain
and Lee as the hero.
So once the memory
of that generation
that venerated him passed on,
he was forgotten.
‐ And so Confederates
lost the Civil War,
but they certainly won
the war of myth.
And Grant was on the wrong side
of that myth.
‐ Shall I read one to you?
This one's from
a Confederate soldier.
Ulys?
"Dear General Grant,
I hope you will allow one who,
"when a boy, laid down his arms
at Appomattox
"and pledged allegiance
to the Union
to express his warmest
sympathy..."
‐ For you and your suffering.
I have watched your movements
from the hour you gave me
my horse and sword
and told me to go home
and assist in making a crop.
I have been proud to see
the nation do you honor.
And now, dear General,
in the hour of your pain,
I weep that so brave,
so magnanimous a soul
must suffer as you do.
‐ There's something, like,
really beautiful and American
in his whole story.
He just comes from nothing.
‐ From the
hardscrabble background
who's had a lot of hard times
and failures in his life,
who rises to the highest
level of power,
becomes the greatest general
of his time.
‐ Against all odds,
against incredible obstacles,
he became the winning general
of the Civil War.
‐ He was the commander
of the victorious army
that led to the emancipation
of 4 million people.
‐ Grant is the unheroic hero
of our greatest national epic,
the Civil War
and Reconstruction.
‐ He was committed
to making America
fully just, fully equal.
‐ Grant was the first
civil rights president.
‐ It's as improbable a rise
as any other figure
in American history.
‐ Indomitable will.
‐ Dogged determination.
‐ Moral vision.
‐ He's a fighter.
‐ It's truly an American story
of not only patriotism
to the nation
but for the values,
who we are
and who we aspire to be.
‐ One of my superstitions
has always been,
when I started to go anywhere
or to do anything,
never to turn back or stop
until the thing intended
was accomplished.
Watch free HD Movies and TV Shows at
StreamingSites.com