My name is Barry Allen, and
I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came
back from the future to help,
she changed the present.
And now our world is
more dangerous than ever,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
Save her.
Our life is a million times
better than what it was
and it's all because of you, Gracie.
Got you some groceries and some
meloxicam for your injuries.
We call it the cure.
It's a serum that suppresses
dark matter in meta-humans.
You're the first person
to take it.
I think we should offer
the cure to Cicada.
From the journal
of Nora West-Allen:
"Timeline is malleable."
Why is she hiding this interest?
Tell me you know
what you're doing.
I am the only speedster
who knows what he's doing!
Stick with the plan.
The cure is finished,
and it works.
Now we can use it on Dwyer,
and then his connection
to the dagger will be broken.
What's wrong?
The timeline.
I've charted this timeline
from Anthro the First Boy
to Kamandi the Last.
I know all of it.
I know its crests,
I know its valleys,
I know what we must do
to defeat Cicada.
Or rather, I knew.
This is a photo
of the last public sighting
of Flash and Cicada.
Their final confrontation.
Dad's last chance to use
the cure on Cicada.
I've been trying to engineer
a moment like this
the whole time I've been there.
Now, watch.
See this?
That is a new timeline
struggling to break through,
manifesting itself
right before our eyes.
Is it a good timeline,
or is it a bad timeline?
That doesn't matter.
What matters is it's new
and, as such, unpredictable,
and we may lose
our window of opportunity.
So we need to find Cicada
before the timeline changes.
Why did it change?
Did I screw something up?
No.
No, no.
You've done very well,
little runner.
But a new variable is coming,
something big is coming.
Or someone.
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
Well, it's interesting
that you say that, sir,
since it's your company
that's denying
the Robertson family's claim.
Yes, of course, I have the
contract right in front of me.
And it says that animal attacks
do not fall under Acts of God,
and that includes gorillas.
The Citizen looks forward
to your statement.
Thanks, babe.
Mmhmm.
Are you ready
to do this thing now?
Hell yeah,
we just got to find Nora.
It's her big day after all.
You don't think she's too busy,
do you?
Okay, people, think!
We haven't seen Cicada
since the rooftop fight,
which means the only way to
track him down is to figure out
who his next meta-human
target's gonna be.
Have we double checked
every bank robbery,
every lab break-in?
Yes, yes! We have looked
at all of that, all right?
And all the criminals
that are in custody
are simply mere mortals.
What about the ones
on the street?
Frost says that no new metas
have shown up
since Norvock went into witsec.
Are the satellites tracking
for dark matter
or meta-gene bursts
or Element X?
Yes, yes, and yes.
They're scanning for everything.
Congratulations,
you raised a menace.
Your daughter, so energetic.
This is pretty impressive.
Um, and I... and I know
with the cure working,
we're all ready
to put Cicada to rest,
but I'm sure
he'll resurface soon.
And then you're going
to give him the chance
to take the meta-human cure?
Yes, exactly.
Even Dwyer deserves a choice,
we just got to convince him
to do the right thing.
Are you ready?
This is gonna be one of
the biggest challenges
of your career as a hero.
Do you know what
you're going to say?
Oh, yeah... you know, yeah.
I've... I've got
some loose thoughts.
Oh, great.
Well, that instills all of us
with confidence, right?
Loose thoughts?
What are you going to say?
"Hey, most bloodthirsty enemy!
Stop."
Guys, it worked for Marlize.
Maybe not so much for
Savitar, but...
I will figure out
what to say to him, all right?
I got this.
I know you do, Dad.
Which is why we need to try
everything to try and find him.
Okay?
Maybe we should go on patrol?
Patrol, you say?
What this is, World War II?
Oh, wow.
Wow, this is crazy.
There is something nuts
going on at Jitters.
Do you think it's a meta-human?
Probably. You should...
- We should check it out.
- Yeah.
For sure.
Yeah.
- Mm-hmm. Y-yeah. Go!
- I'm... oh!
- You two did this.
- You made her.
You are responsible.
Well, well, well.
It is nice to see someone
back at his desk
Oh, hey, Foxy.
It's good to be back.
After three months of sipping
Wally's Tibetan butter tea,
I actually kind of missed
this break room coffee.
Ugh. Uh-uh.
Hey, you have any idea
where I can get my hands
on the Cicada task force file?
Babe, you're standing in it.
What?
I've been trying to catch up
on what I've been missing.
Oh.
Uh, speaking of which...
you ever seen this woman?
Uh, Dr. Vanessa Ambres.
Born and raised in Central City,
got her MD from McNider U.
Oh, that's interesting.
This says she treated
Orlin Dwyer and Grace Gibbons
on the night
of the Enlightenment.
Yes, and she has been
treating Grace ever since,
even though she's an ER doctor,
and the nurses report
a whole slew of drugs missing
from the coma ward.
You think
she's working with Dwyer?
The guy got stabbed,
struck by lightning.
He's got a hole in his chest.
Somebody has got
to be patching him up, right?
I think we should be asking
the doctor a few questions.
All right, let's do it.
Oh, you want to come with?
Yeah, I want to come with.
What?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah!
- All right, partner.
- Partner. I like that.
- Yeah.
Okay, I thought something big
was supposed to be
going on down here.
Oh, I don't know.
It's pretty big.
Feast your eyes on the newest
addition to the Jitters menu.
The XS-presso.
I got my own drink!
It's pretty schway, right?
Think of what could be next.
An XS action figure?
XS Day?
Guys, you are embarrassing me.
We're just really excited.
I mean, we still haven't
even gone on a trip together
or made Grandma Esther's famous
sweet potato pie recipe.
Did you put karaoke
on the list like I asked?
I think so, actually.
Just a sec... let me see this.
Okay, there are so many things
on this list.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, I mean, we've got time.
Okay, is that a real alert
or another fake one?
No, this one's real.
M-20 at CCU,
Chemistry Department.
- A meta attack.
- Yeah, let's go. Come on.
Been a while
since high school chem,
but that does not look like
proper lab safety.
I need this!
Leave me alone!
Sodium bicarbonate
neutralizes any acid.
You have the cuffs?
Let's go get him.
- We don't need to.
- What?
Look at this burn mark.
That acid guy, he...
He must've been there
when the photo was taken.
What are you talking about?
Dad, today's the day
you stop Cicada.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down. Say that again?
There's a photo,
it's in The Flash museum,
of Flash and Cicada... the last
time they were ever seen
confronting each other in public,
and in the photo, by Flash's feet,
the exact same burn mark left
by the meta that we just fought.
This acid meta was at
their final confrontation?
He must be
Cicada's final target.
His final target before I vanish
and he starts killing again.
Why is Nora just telling us
about this crucial meta now?
Because a lot of the stuff
from my timeline is unreliable.
You know, uh, different metas,
different victims, different circumstances.
But this time,
everything's exactly the same.
So far.
If Cicada goes
after this acid meta,
that means that today's
the last day
we're going to confront him.
And our last chance to stop him.
Yeah, all right, well, then,
I gotta figure out exactly
what I'm gonna say to him.
You'll find the words, Dad.
I'll help you.
And I am going to start
working on facial rec
for this Acid Master.
Yup, that's what I'm going with.
Always trust your gut, kids.
And we'll figure out a way
for you to talk to Cicada
without him killing you.
Well...
if it all works out, then...
looks like today could be
the end of our journey.
Yeah.
And I guess
everyone starts moving on.
Nora.
Oh, hey, Mom.
Um, look, I've really gotta
hurry and go help Dad.
Yeah, I know, it's just...
I guess you might be
going home tomorrow.
Yeah, I guess so.
Um, mission accomplished.
Well, if you two need
a break after a while,
Papa Joe taught me the famous
West family right hook.
I-I would love to teach you.
Nora?
Sorry, uh, sorry, Mom.
I just, uh, thought of something
that's going to help Dad...
I-I got to go.
Babe, this is a first!
We've worked together before.
We have, Detective,
but anytime we did anything
even close to this,
I didn't have my abilities.
Okay, here we go.
Uh, if I fiddle with my ring,
you know,
assume that means she's lying
and then you just get in there
and, mm, mm,
do your thing.
You cop it up.
Prednisone, sirolimus,
abatacept.
All drugs classified
as immunosuppressants.
They also happen to have
all been reported stolen
from this facility.
I'm aware of the report.
What I'm wondering
is why it warrants the interest
of the DA?
We believe
that the missing medications
are connected
to a much higher profile case.
Orlin Dwyer.
Grace Gibbons' uncle.
Is he still at large?
I don't really watch the news.
Yes, he's very much at large.
And we have reason to believe
that those exact medications
are the ones that Dwyer would
need to treat his injuries.
What are you saying exactly?
The records of the stolen meds
continued after Dwyer stopped
visiting the hospital.
Which means that someone here
may be still supplying them
to him.
Sounds like a good theory,
but I don't know
who that could be.
Everything I know
is in those reports.
Okay, okay.
That's enough for now.
Thank you very much
for your time.
Of course.
What are you doing?
You're just gonna let her
walk away like that?
I-I didn't want to scare her.
We don't have enough evidence.
We don't even have a motive.
So, then, let me
keep doing my thing!
I'm not used to going
into an interview
factoring in
your meta-abilities.
I-I'm used to going in
using my gut.
What about my gut?
All due respect,
this isn't about your gut.
Huh.
Look, Cecile,
what I meant to say was...
No, no, no, no, no, no, Joe.
You said exactly what you meant,
and you know what, right now,
I'm about to say
something that I mean.
Maybe we shouldn't be working
on this together after all.
Oh, man.
Okay, the clock's ticking,
and we have no clue
how to convince Cicada
to take the cure,
but we still have
our best weapon.
- Your journal.
- Your legacy.
One of the biggest things
history remembers
about The Flash is your ability
to change people's
hearts and minds,
especially your enemy's,
and I have dozens of entries
about those times.
Any chance you've got
the future words
I say to Cicada in there?
Nope,
but I have your past words.
Magenta, she wanted to drop
an oil tanker on a hospital,
but you convinced her
she was a good person.
You said, "Use that good
to beat the bad."
Magenta had split personalities.
She literally had a good side
and a bad side.
That's not gonna work
with Cicada.
Leonard Snart,
he said he didn't want
to be saved
and you still found a way to
convince him to save himself.
"There's a part of you
that knows
you don't have to let
your past define you."
Except Snart had already
worked with us at that point.
Killer Frost,
you dared her to kill you.
"Come on, live up to your name,
Killer Frost!"
And what did she do?
Nora.
Amunet, Plastique,
the list goes on and on.
Nora, all... all of these times
are... are different.
Cicada doesn't even care
if he lives when this is over.
What am I supposed to say
that he'll care about?
You'll know.
The Flash always knows.
So, when you think about it,
an anti-dampening array
is the way to stop him
in his tracks.
Sherloque, are you happy
to be going home soon?
Of course I'm happy to go back.
I just feel that...
somehow there's more work
to be done here.
I think he's, uh,
talking about his lady friend.
You know, I have a bit
of experience with these, uh,
long-distance relationships.
I got one word for you:
Holo-cube.
These things work wonders.
And I request that you stop
speaking possibly forever.
I can deduce from your
conversation when you came in
that you have indeed tracked
down Cicada's next target
but do need help
facilitating the conversation
between Cicada and The Flash.
Correct? Yes?
Oh, good.
Come with me and I will
give you the solution.
When did you figure it out?
I will miss you both very much.
But you will miss me more!
Allez!
Philip Master!
We good?
Yes, Philip Master is secure
in the pipeline.
Wait, Acid Master's real name
is Philip Master?
This is it.
Just like in the photo.
The last confrontation
between Flash and Cicada.
Oh, what's the matter?
You don't have one of these?
Bye-bye.
Cicada!
How long does he have?
He has to hold that dagger
for 60 seconds, maybe less.
Flash better figure out
what he's going to say fast.
He will. I know he will.
I don't want to fight.
We have a cure.
What are you talking about?
We have a way
to cure meta-humans.
We have a way to take
their powers away.
We want you to take it.
And why would I agree
to do that?
Your legacy.
I know how this ends.
You keep killing,
and you're remembered
as a monster, not a hero.
But we can change that together,
you can have a different legacy.
You just have to choose it.
I don't give a damn
about my legacy.
That was it.
That was our last chance.
We ran citywide
facial recognition scans
and scanned
for dark matter signals
from Cicada's dagger.
That was our last shot
at confronting Cicada.
We don't know that.
We're changing the timeline.
That photo that Nora saw
at the Flash museum,
it could be different now.
Maybe it doesn't even exist.
After all...
the timeline is malleable.
I just don't understand
why our plan didn't work.
Yeah, you guys
did everything right.
The only reason it didn't work
is because
I couldn't convince him.
Dad, you're the Flash.
When the Flash speaks honestly
from his heart, people listen.
Not all people.
Let's keep searching.
I'm gonna check
the Cicada files at CCPD.
See if I missed anything.
Nora.
We just... we just
need to create
another window
of opportunity, okay?
Dad couldn't convince Cicada
to take the cure.
He just... he just needs
to find the right words.
Bare.
What are you doing here so late?
We hit a wall at S.T.A.R.
Labs tracking Cicada.
Thought a change of scenery
would help, but...
Keep your head up, man.
We'll find him.
We always do.
Honestly, I'm more worried
about what happens when we do.
Our whole plan depends on me
being able to convince Dwyer
to just take the cure.
The last time I tried...
I don't think I've ever
struck out so hard.
Wow, that's saying a lot
considering your track record
at the plate.
Wait, what exactly
did you say to him?
That he was creating
a legacy of fear,
one that would go down
in history,
but that we could work together
to change that.
That sounds like
something the Flash would say.
Well, I am the Flash.
Look, that man's a zealot.
He sees you in that suit
and all he sees
is the thing he hates.
Meta-human, superpowers,
the thing that took his niece
away from him.
He can't see past the Flash,
but what he doesn't know...
There's a whole lot
more to you than that.
Be more Barry Allen.
Human.
Yeah, you're right.
Thanks.
I'm gonna dive back in.
I'll let you get back
to running down Ambres.
Actually...
me and Cecile ran
into a wall ourselves.
We are... uh, she... like,
working together.
I mean, ever since
she got her powers,
it's like she's
a human lie detector.
How is that a bad thing?
You know I've always
prided myself
on being able to read people,
right?
But Cecile and these powers,
I mean, she puts me to shame.
Well, you just got to remember
that you guys are a team.
That makes her strengths
your strengths
and yours hers.
So if you let her
do what she's great at,
it's only going to
create more room
for you to do more of what
you're great at too, right?
Well, damn.
You're getting real good
at these pep talks, Bare.
Well, I had
a pretty good teacher.
Hey, Nora.
Hi, Nora.
Yeah.
Do you want to turn
that down a little bit?
Hmm? Oh, sorry.
What are you listening to?
Sped-up archives
of the Flash's comm recordings.
I thought that if I listen
to his best appeals,
I could figure out
what exactly worked so well.
And did you?
No, not yet.
But if I run the transcripts
through the computer,
I can extrapolate
recurring key words
from his most successful appeals
and create a sort of
"best of speeches" speech.
Well, um,
why don't you let your dad
think about it
and we could go
to the rooftop of Jitters.
It's a great place
to clear your mind,
plus it's got the best views
of the city.
You want to go sightseeing?
Right now?
What... is this from
that list of yours?
Well, yeah, but...
All day I've been trying
to figure out a way
to stop Cicada
and all day you've been
trying to pull me away.
Why are you pushing this list?
I mean, it's just the last time
that we may get
to spend together.
Nora, I mean,
once we stop Cicada,
you'll go back to your time
and...
Us like this together will end.
Mom, it doesn't end.
We have our whole future
together.
Yeah, for you it'll feel
like no time has passed
but for me,
it'll be decades before I...
see you like this again.
Uh, no, it's okay.
Um, I will catch up
with you later.
Joe.
What's going on?
Why'd you want me
to meet you here?
Look, I know the last time
we tried to work together
went a bit south.
Oh, a bit?
You're right.
I'm sorry, Cecile.
I let my pride get in the way,
and I didn't lean
on your strengths
when I should have.
But you know me,
I'm not a man who makes
the same mistake twice.
So...
Would you do me the honor
of joining me
in this interrogation?
You do what you do best,
I'll take care of the rest.
Get 'em, girl.
Detective. DA.
This is starting to border
on harassment.
I have told you
everything I know.
That's not true.
We know that you've been
funneling meds to Orlin Dwyer.
Well, if you knew that,
then I'd be arrested
and not sitting here.
Let me correct myself.
We have a strong hunch,
but I bet if we were
to go through
the video camera footage
from the hospital,
we'll find proof
that you were assisting Dwyer.
I'm a doctor.
I mean, why would I condone
a vigilante murderer?
Because of what happened
to Darius.
Darius.
It hurts you
to even think about it.
My fiancé was killed
by meta-humans
during Zoom's rampage.
So, yes, it hurts
to think about him.
Hurt enough for you to help
Dwyer kill other meta-humans?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
you took an oath to do no harm,
right?
Can you truthfully say
you've upheld that oath?
That guilt that you feel
right now?
There's a way to make up for it.
All you have to do
is help us find Orlin.
What, so... so you can put him
in jail? Kill him?
No, so we can cure him.
It's not possible.
Maybe not with the medicine
you've been giving him,
but S.T.A.R. Labs
has created a treatment
that turns metas back
into normal human beings.
I can't take you to him.
Okay, okay,
then help us set up a meet.
Look, Dr. Ambres, it's clear.
You've come to truly care
for Dwyer.
So we're asking you now...
help us save his life.
I can make contact,
and I can share the location.
I have rounds in an hour
and patients
that I can save tonight.
So am I free to go, please?
I love my job.
I can stay here all night.
And we will, unless you tell us
what you're keeping hidden
right now.
Yo, yo. I got your text.
You talked to Ambres?
Cecile and I together
got through to her.
She's going to show us
where to find Dwyer.
Joe, that's amazing.
Yeah, Ambres told us
something else.
Dwyer's niece, Grace?
She's a meta.
So le petit Dwyer is a meta.
Wait, I thought we scanned
Grace for meta powers
when Nora entered her brain.
We did but that was back
when her DNA was 100% human.
Her powers must have activated
in just the last few weeks,
right?
Yeah, Ambres told Joe
that the wound in Grace's head
recently started glowing
and mutating.
Now all we need to do is get
Dwyer to listen to you, again.
Killer Frost can put him
on ice from the neck down.
Better yet, I can re-sequence
the Speed Force Bazooka
to overload him
with negative tachyons.
- Yes. Absolutely.
- So that he's stuck there...
Tachyon, shmack-yon.
No, no. La Machine à Mémoire!
We could go inside Dwyer's mind.
- Guys...
- No, La Machine à Mémoire!
Guys, hey!
I appreciate the enthusiasm,
but I think we need to take
a different approach.
No powers, no crazy plans.
The Flash can't convince
Cicada to stop this,
but... maybe...
I can.
- Hey.
Dad's back.
He says Papa Joe's
got news about Dwyer.
Okay, good. I guess we should
get over to the Cortex.
You know, I had a list too.
Your wedding,
Auntie Jenna's baby shower,
Jitters, The Enlightenment.
Those were all
the moments in time
you wanted to go back
and see us?
Yeah, so I could have
memories and experiences
with all of you.
I get it.
I should've been sensitive
and I-I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not.
I was so focused on making sure
Flash beat Cicada,
I forgot what I was supposed
to really be focused on.
You and Dad.
You're the reason
I came back to this time,
not fighting big bads
or getting my own XS-presso.
So that I could spend time
with my parents.
My family.
I don't know how much time
we have left together
or how much of your list
we're going to get done,
but from now on,
every moment we have left,
we're going to make it
a memorable one.
I promise.
Well, I guess we can cross off
"hugging while drinking tea"
off our list.
Yeah.
Hey, guys, sorry to interrupt.
No, it's fine.
We were just...
We were just talking about
Mom's list.
Um, so I heard Dad
has a lead on Dwyer?
We have a location.
I'm going to head there
any minute.
Does Flash know what
he's going to say this time?
Actually, I think
I'm just gonna talk to him,
father to father.
That's a really good idea, Dad.
Hey, Doc.
Dr. Ambres told us
where to find you.
I just want to talk.
There's no more talking.
Every time one of you metas
comes near the rest of us,
good people get hurt.
This is what you all deserve.
Does that include Grace?
Ambres hasn't told you.
Grace. She's a meta.
The night the satellite crashed,
she was hit
with a piece of shrapnel
inflected with dark matter.
That's... that's why
she's in a coma,
and now it's changing her.
That's a lie.
And that's why Ambres
told us where to find you.
She's afraid.
She's afraid you're going
to do the one thing
you can't come back from.
I know how much you care
about Grace.
You're trying to make the world
a better place for her.
She didn't choose to be a meta,
but she is.
Does that mean
she deserves to die?
No.
I would never hurt Grace.
Then you'd let her grow up
in a world of fear.
Where there's someone out there
hurting people like her.
The cure,
it will heal Grace and you.
And why should
I believe you, Flash?
Because I'm a father too.
My daughter,
I love her more than
I ever thought possible.
I would do anything to make the
world a better place for her.
And I think you would too.
So do it.
We made an arrangement.
We cure him and then Grace.
Okay.
Why are we here
and not at a hospital?
We have to be sure
that the cure is successful.
We created it.
We're the ones who know
how it works.
Once administered,
the cure will take 60 seconds
to eliminate the meta-human
powers in your system.
That means the wound
in your chest will then open.
You'll need me to suture it
shut so you don't bleed out.
- Why not Doc Ambres?
- She's being held for questioning.
No, it's Ambres, or we're done.
All right, we'll get her.
If anything goes wrong,
or if you're lying to me,
I'll kill every... last...
one of you.
And we're certain everything
in this room is sterile?
Of course.
Everything except that.
That thing's not negotiable.
That rage of his, it's...
Joe, I can't.
Are you going to stay?
Uh, yeah, just in case.
- Okay.
- All right, babe.
Good job today.
You too. Partner.
We never could have done this
without you guys.
Well, I'm glad it worked out,
but when this is over,
he's going to jail,
for a long time.
Okay, one fresh serving
of piping hot meta-human cure.
I'm just supposed to trust
that that thing works?
Has it gone through
any human testing?
It's gone through
giant shark testing.
It's a long story.
It's okay, Doc.
I wanted to tell you
the truth about Grace.
I just couldn't find the words.
You were just trying
to keep her safe.
I'll always be thankful
for that.
See you on the other side.
There we go.
Injecting the cure.
His vitals are spiking.
How can we tell
if the cure is even working?
Oh, it's working.
My powers are back.
Which means Dwyer's powers
must be gone.
Well...
It appears your sojourn into the
past was a success. Congratulations.
Thank you.
You as well.
It's your, uh, 38th Cicada?
That's right, yes.
38th Cicada.
Trente-huit Cicada.
Alley-oop!
But, of course,
there's some business here
that remains unfinished.
For instance, how did you know
before you saw the burn marks
in the photograph
that it was a meta-human
that would lead us to Cicada?
Uh, I...
You know, I just had
this feeling
that something big was coming.
They're working on him now.
I will be so happy
when this is all over with.
What's going on?
What happened to the power?
I have no idea.
I should check the Med Lab.
Someone's coming.
Who?
Cicada?
Where's that coming from?
Cisco!
- Hold on!
- Iris.
- Careful.
- I can't see anything.
Here.
Cisco, we need power.
We got a much bigger problem.
Cicada?
How the hell did that happen?
I don't know,
but he's coming here
and he looks pissed.
We have to move now.
I've got to keep
patching him up.
Stand back.
There.
- He's in the hallway.
- Get the hell out of here.
Iris! Get down!
Come on!
Who are you?
Please, whoever you are.
I only came here
to make him human again!
I helped him!
Please!
Please don't do this!
Nope. They're all toast.
Well, better the computers
than us.
- Joe.
- Are you okay?
I'm okay, I'm okay.
I'm a little bruised, but...
Everybody else?
Yeah, we're okay.
Guys...
Dr. Ambres didn't make it.
There's no sign of them
anywhere.
I don't understand
what happened.
I mean, we got Dwyer,
we gave him the cure.
If... if Cicada doesn't exist
anymore, who was that?
Someone worse.
I've missed you.
Uncle Orlin.