Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
"Tis in the blood, your
father would say.'
Mining, 'tis is in the blood.
'Like a vein of copper.
"Tis the bread of life.
'Eat, sleep, live and breathe it.
'She's your salvation...
'.. and your downfall.'
My Lord!
My Lord Basset!
'Make you reckless, make you bold...'
It isn't right,
this is all we have.
Many a friend did break
and many more will follow.
My Lord Basset!
There are bailiffs at Wheal Reath.
"Tis a fool's game...'
You can't do this!
Back!
'..it will end in tears.'
I admire your optimism.
Your father died afore his time.
In his bed.
It was mining did for him.
My Lord Basset!
'And he won't be the last neither.'
And if he were here today,
he'd tell you to not to
make the same mistake.
I wonder.
Judas, it's cold!
Argh! It's freezing!
Satisfied?
Shouldn't I be?
It ain't enough not a' stink.
A body must scrub herself raw as a
buttock of beef to please some folk!
What happened?
'Tis the mine, Ross.
They closed it.
They closed Wheal Reath.
Is it true,
about Lord Basset?
It would appear so.
Will we be blamed?
Did we furnish the pistol?
~ We called in his loans.
~ No,
we declined to extend them.
Does it not reflect poorly on us,
that we let his pleas
fall upon deaf ears?
Are we in the business
of sentiment or profit?
Will I be going now, Mr George?
Have you been dismissed?
No, but happen I have
other engagements.
None that reward you so well.
Return to my chamber.
And... in future,
you will address me as "sir".
Yes, sir.
These ancient families lack backbone.
I wonder they survive.
Why would they close it?
Believe me, this is the bank's
doing, not the owner's. Here.
It's now Grambler who has the
only mine left hereabouts.
Is my uncle taking on men?
Even if he were, my breathin'...
You'd welcome a few
months above grass?
I need to work, Ross, or...
my mother and sisters will starve.
Can you use a farmhand?
So, now we be home to all the
waifs and strays in the county?
Rags n' tatters of Wheal Reath
and their begging bowls!
Ross!
You still here, boy?
When do you leave for London?
I'm minded to stay
and take my chances here.
As I expected.
Stubborn as your father!
Little good it did him.
Well, I fancy you'll do better.
Better than his cousin?
You heard about Wheal Reath?
And the owner.
Lord Basset shot himself.
Bad business.
Very bad.
Does Grambler have loans
with the Warleggans?
Everyone has loans
with the Warleggans.
That doesn't alarm you?
George is like a brother to Francis.
You must visit me soon, Verity.
And neglect her duties here?
She has no time for gadding about.
Well...
.. I trust you've learnt
one lesson today?
The hazards of owning a mine.
Feeling tired, my dear?
A little.
Perhaps I should rest a while.
Shall I join you?
Oh, you blatherin' idiot!
Poldark, we have orders to take you
to Bodmin Jail for inciting a riot!
You have a new farmhand.
'Tis a fine thing you done for Jim.
Happen you could do
the same thing for we,
below ground?
You have pitches already,
at Grambler.
Ah, where it please your uncle
to pay us starvation wages.
The owners have we
by the throat, Ross.
We can't go on like this.
I can promise nothing.
Ah.
Father tells me you intend to remain.
Does that disappoint you?
Not at all.
We were always more
friends than cousins.
I would be sorry if that changed.
I've been wondering if this
mine was entirely worked out.
You don't think of reopening her?
I'll think of anything that
might help those poor devils
at Wheal Reath.
You consider them
your responsibility?
You don't?
My father doesn't trust
me with responsibility.
He likes to keep the mysteries
of mine-owning to himself.
Perhaps we should open
Leisure together.
Share the burden and the spoils.
What are you doing?
This is no task for you.
Let me or Mrs Tabb...
What may I do, then?
There is much you may do, Elizabeth.
You are the lady of the house.
You may go out when you choose,
pay calls, attend balls...
And may you not?
I'm 25. Unmarried.
I spin and I bake, pick preserves,
I dose the servants with
possets when they're ill.
My life is not your life.
Suppose I wished to open a mine?
I'd suppose you'd taken
leave of your senses.
What in the least would I require?
~ Capital?
~ I have none.
~ Expertise?
~ A smattering.
Allies?
None of means. My cousin
will lend his name.
So, you'd require investors.
Can you find me any?
In these uncertain times?
With no experience, no bona fides
and a reputation somewhat tarnished?
Are you speaking as my
banker or my friend?
Both.
Good day, my lord.
Are we acquainted, ma'am?
We could be.
I have neither time nor the
money to seek such diversions.
What do you seek, milord?
Better days ahead, I see.
A prosperous business.
Perhaps you should try
a different profession.
Sweetheart, perhaps?
I made the mistake of going to war.
And when you returned, she
was pledged to another.
Yet you still care for her.
Perhaps she loves you still.
Ross?
Verity?
You escaped, then?
Father's gone to the
mine for an hour.
I see you've not been idle!
I needed a distraction.
Demelza! This is my cousin, Verity.
Has she settled?
Still somewhat feral.
Does your wound still pain you?
Less than it did.
Then I wonder if I might ask
you the greatest of favours?
My dear, tonight's assembly,
will you not reconsider?
You know how I love to show
off my wife to the world.
Where's he going?
To the dance.
He don't look too glad about it.
Gentlefolks is strange.
I'm obliged to you, Ross.
For vanquishing my
loathing of a gavotte?
For persuading father to let me come.
As official escort, I'm
entirely at your service.
Don't be!
Look to your liberty, cousin.
Is it in danger?
From a great many girls who would be
glad to acquire the name of Poldark!
Those ruffians at Wheal Reath
made a nuisance of themselves.
You'd hardly expect them
to celebrate the closure.
They have no business to
have an opinion at all!
Some would say that view is outdated.
In America, for instance, they
have more liberal views.
All men created equal?
Preposterous! Distinctions
of rank must be preserved.
Especially when they're
so dearly bought.
To the Trade!
And the Captain Ross, for providing
for our ease and comfort!
This be the life!
Not dancing, Ross?
Will none of the ladies have you?
The whiff of soil is
hard to swill off,
but if one communes with peasants...
Do you prescribe perfume?
It covers a multitude of sins!
Like money.
Indeed!
For how else would a family
of blacksmiths become bankers?
One of these days,
you may come knocking.
I would need to be desperate.
I look forward to the prospect.
You know that lady?
Captain Poldark.
Miss Teague.
How do you find your first ball?
Exceeding all expectations, sir!
A sea captain? How... invigorating!
One is seldom idle.
And so much to remember.
The sails, the masts.
~ Are you interested in rigging, ma'am?
~ Oh, exceedingly!
Are you fond of dancing,
Captain Poldark?
I fear I possess few of the
refinements of polite society.
~ Ross Poldark!
~ Mr Treneglos.
I saw you sniffing round that
old strumpet the other day.
Wheal Leisure? You don't
mean to resurrect her?
It would take a brave
man to open a mine now.
~ Don't you agree, Henshawe?
~ Depends on the mine.
Mr Henshawe? You were mine captain
at Leisure in my father's day?
~ I was.
~ You worked her for tin?
~ Aye.
But in the last samples taken, there
were definite signs of copper.
A pity she closed before
we could dig further.
But if you know of anyone
who'd be willing to chance
a little speculation, Mr Pascoe...
I'll see what can be done.
I'd require discretion.
I fully comprehend you, sir.
~ Mizzenmast, you say?
~ Which is part square-rigged
and carries a gaff.
~ A gaff?
~ And a spanker boom.
~ So many names!
When may I see you again?
Oh! Captain Blamey,
that I couldn't say.
Judas!
What 'ee be doin' in there?
Jus' lookin'.
Jus' lookin'?
There's books, an' maps,
an' knives, an' 'arpicord...
Can 'ee read?
Can 'ee play?
Can try...
Be nothin' in there
for the likes of we.
~ Unless we be gettin' ideas
above us station? ~ No!
~ Go home.
~ What?
Back where 'ee come from.
'Ee don't belong 'ere.
Forgive me.
I do no wish to appear forward
but I'd dearly like us
to be better acquainted.
I, too.
I should not have said that!
What must you think of me?
Can you be unaware of that, ma'am?
Remind me, Captain Poldark, was I
engaged to you for this next dance?
Not that I recall.
Would you excuse me?
Ah, Ross, are you come to
take my wife off my hands?
If she's no objection.
Did you not promise me this dance?
The cotillion.
And I dare say Ross will return
you to me in one piece.
Your cousin is most attentive.
~ Hm?
~ To your wife.
Oh, I don't think he
cares for dancing.
He only came to please Verity.
Who is that man?
Captain Blamey, master
of the Lisbon packet.
A pretty catch.
~ And at her age...
~ She won't get many more chances?
But Father couldn't spare her.
And Elizabeth would miss her.
Though doubtless your wife would
find ways of distracting herself.
Ross.
May I introduce Captain
Andrew Blamey?
My cousin Ross Poldark, my
sister-in-law, Elizabeth Poldark.
Your servant, ma'am, sir.
I hope our boisterous spirits
don't offend you, sir.
Not in the least, ma'am. I've
every reason to be happy myself.
If I could dare to hope
that my interest would in the
smallest way be returned.
I think you might dare
to hope that, sir.
May I speak with your father?
You may think me presumptuous
but my attachment is sincere.
I would not wish to proceed
without his approval.
Forgive me, I must
speak with my cousin.
My dear, I believe Francis
is looking for you.
~ People love to gossip. ~ Isn't
that why they come to such evenings?
But to give them cause? To make
your attentions so pronounced?
Whatever was between you, trust
me, she has put it behind her.
So must you.
You'll take supper with us?
Thank you. I've no appetite.
Miss Verity, I cannot
go to your father
without your being in full
possession of the facts.
Ross Poldark in love?
Quite the spectacle.
Though, may I say,
an excellent choice.
Ruth Teague is unlikely to remind
one of a previous attachment.
May I be of service, me lord?
One service is all I require.
You don't say much, me lord.
But p'raps you don't pay
me for my conversation.
My apologies.
I was not in a talkative
mood last night.
A rare hand.
Knows what it wants but...
not always how to get it.
Is my nephew at home?>
Uncle, to what do I owe the pleasure?
Opening a mine?
Despite our conversation?
Exploring the idea.
Stubborn.
Rash.
~ Won't take no for an answer.
~ Well...
The curse of the Poldarks.
And our salvation! I salute you, boy.
Take Francis with you.
He needs to learn some
initiative. When do you meet?
Tomorrow, if Pascoe can
drum up any interest.
Francis will come.
He must learn to stand
on his own two feet.
~ You must help him.
~ I will, Uncle, of course.
But if you could urge discretion.
Especially with regard
to his good friend George?
He's ready for 'ee, sir.
~ Demelza.
~ Sir?
You look weary to the bone.
Have they been making
you a beast of burden?
No, sir, I be content, sir.
~ It be that Jud. 'Ee be sayin'
I got ideas? I an't got ideas!
~ No?
I do know me place.
Your place is where I say it is.
Fetch your cloak.
Sir?
Never 'ad no cloak.
This is an important day for us both.
Let's see who can strike
the better bargain.
Verity!
Oh, Ross.
~ Is Francis with you?
~ He's at the inn.
~ Could I be of service?
~ I believe I can manage.
No, allow me.
Did you enjoy the assembly?
Ruth Teague seemed
very taken with you.
I scarcely remember her.
How can that be?
There were distractions.
Perhaps you should pursue her.
Would that please you?
I have to go.
Verity will be looking for me.
~ Four pence, or I'll take them away.
~ Three pence.
~ Four pence!
Three pence? Four pence,
and you've got a sale.
I will leave you.
Ross.
Shall we go?
I'm in no mood to speculate.
May I ask why?
I need something I can depend on.
~ Are we expecting your cousin?
~ Francis has changed his mind.
~ A pity. He would've lent a certain...
~ Gravity?
Gentlemen, welcome.
You come here today
to decide one thing.
Whether to risk good gold
in the pursuit of copper.
The times could hardly
be less auspicious.
When Wheal Reath closes...
And Grambler's future
hangs in the balance.
.. when Welsh mines prosper
and Cornwall's on its knees,
what chance has this meagre venture?
Your cousin divides opinion.
Some think him arrogant.
Others observe a sense
of... entitlement.
~ To what?
~ Whatever takes his fancy.
But perhaps they misjudge him.
So, what do I hear
of his latest venture?
The venture is small, so
overheads will be low.
Without Reath, supply to
the markets will fall,
so the price of copper should rise.
And if it doesn't?
Is he seeking investment?
I really couldn't say.
So the question is
what will it cost us?
To begin with, I propose
to act as manager
and head purser without salary.
If Captain Henshawe would
oversee the works...
Also without salary?
At a favourable rate, until
we're up and running.
If Mr Renfrew would supply gear
and tackle at nominal cost.
The man has impudence!
Pascoe's Bank will honour
our drafts up to £300.
Pascoe's Bank?
~ Yes.
~ Not Warleggans?
Warleggans would be happy
to accommodate him.
Given the friendship
between our families.
Perhaps he doesn't value friendship.
Or family.
Warleggans will lend to a mine
for as long as it prospers,
but once it starts to struggle, they
withdraw credit and see it go under.
They could close Grambler tomorrow
as they closed Reath.
Business is business but should
profit be the be-all and end-all?
I'm inclined to agree. We
know Reath was struggling,
but closing it cost
the shareholders dear.
~ And the miners dearer.
~ And the owner his life.
We cannot choose our family.
But we can choose our friends.
And, as a friend, I say to you,
if ever you need my assistance...
~ What assistance might I need?
~ What any man needs.
Someone to alert him if he sees his
friend being played for a fool.
A fool?
In love, in business, at cards.
It's true, my losses have
been considerable of late.
Then let me prove our
friendship by advancing
whatever might defray them.
Gentlemen, I'll be straight with you.
The rewards could be considerable
but so are the risks.
But if you like a wager, and
which of us here doesn't,
then I'd sooner gamble
on a vein of copper
and the sweat of 50 men than
on the turn of a card.
50 guineas apiece will cover
the first three months.
There's mine.
And mine.
If I may take the liberty
of proposing a toast?
A toast.
To Wheal Leisure!
Wheal Leisure!
He tried to swizzle me
but I beat 'im down.
I expected no less.
A good day's work for us both.
What am I? A circus attraction?
A poorly-dressed one!
Come with me.
This cannot continue, she must
be brought to her senses.
She must indeed. But what of
him? Has he no sense of shame?
I hold her most to blame! She
must have encouraged him.
~ If you had seen her at the assembly.
~ But you were there!
~ Could you not have put a stop to it?
~ I should not have needed to!
She should be mistress
of her own behaviour!
Something must be done at once
before our family name is
dragged through the mud!
Jud?
Jud!
Prudie!
'Ee be lookin' fer Mr Ross?
I am.
Elizabeth.
Have you been offered
some refreshment?
Your maid has done her best.
You can go.
~ Oh, Ross...
~ What is it?
How to even begin to
put it into words...
Don't try.
You love Francis, I love Francis.
But this cannot be
allowed to continue!
Out.
Damn me, if a man can't get about
'is sacred an' profane duties
~ wi'out a blastin' from...
~ Out!
You must speak with Francis.
And your uncle, you must
speak with both of them.
I'll follow you directly.
Saddle my horse.
And remind me to thrash
you when I return.
In't no call for that, Mr Ross.
Tidn' just, tidn'
kind, tidn' civil...
.. tidn' friendly.
It's a bad business, Ross.
But we must make the best of it.
Verity has greatly disappointed us.
~ Verity?
~ You're aware that she formed
an attachment at the ball?
Who could fail to be aware?
She was all over the man!
~ The sea captain? Blamey?
~ He's been secretly paying court to her
~ ever since.
~ Hoping, no doubt,
to secure her before she became
aware of his appalling past.
~ The varmint! ~ He's a drunkard,
who beat his wife to death.
~ Is this certain?
~ Verity has confirmed it.
And forgiven him.
She's a plain girl, and
that makes her easy prey.
We must close ranks and protect her.
Of course, but how?
She will not leave this house until
she swears never to see him again.
Ross!
I heard what they told
you. It isn't true.
It was an accident. She
tried to strike him.
He pushed her away, she
fell and hit her head.
~ He told you this?
~ At the ball.
But there was never any
intent to harm her.
None in the world. And
he's paid for what he did.
He lost his rank and went to prison.
~ And I know he would never
lift a finger to hurt me.
~ But still,
~ how can you be sure he...
~ I'm sure.
He loves me. I love him.
You of all people know
what that feels like.
Yes.
What can I do?
Captain Poldark,
most generous, to allow
us to meet here
in view of your concerns.
Verity trusts you. I trust Verity.
She's my angel of redemption.
You'll have no cause to regret it.
I believe you, sir.
Sir.
Dammit! Tell our guests
to keep to the parlour.
Farming is such an engaging
hobby, is it not?
More than a hobby for me, ma'am.
But do you not hunt, Captain Poldark?
Would it not be a fine thing
to be mixing with people
~ of your own station?
~ I'm very well occupied here.
~ Of course, Ruth is an accomplished rider.
~ Of course.
Not that it's her
only accomplishment.
One has only to taste her syllabubs
to know their succulence.
Indeed.
Is Miss Verity still meeting that
blackguard in spite of her father?
~ I um...
~ Of course, you're so out of the way here,
~ you would not hear of it.
~ No, indeed.
This must be the young
person that you adopted?
I've adopted no-one.
I needed a kitchen wench, the girl
is old enough to know her own mind.
Of course, she looks as if
she would know her own mind.
But I must beg your
indulgence, ladies.
There is much I must attend to.
But you must take tea
with us at Teague House.
Perhaps we can show you what a
woman's touch can do to a home.
I thank you, ma'am, but I fear...
your efforts would be...
.. wasted.
Yes, of course. Yes.
~ My daughter, Esther, lives
with her governess in Plymouth.
~ Oh, indeed?
And my son, James, was
midshipman with the fleet.
~ A midshipman?
~ I miss them greatly.
And you, who are no less
attached to your family,
would surely be loathe to
quit them for my sake...>
Have you had word of your family?
No, sir, I don't expect none.
Without me to skivvy for them,
they'll have no love o' me.
Particularly your father.
Too busy in the kiddleys
or down the mine.
~ And your brothers?
~ Soon be followin' in 'is footsteps.
Seems we both have
mining in our blood.
Aye, sir. Though God knows if
that's a blessin' or a curse.
This is good timing. I was about
to ride to Wheal Leisure.
The investors meeting went well.
~ I hope I may yet to persuade
Francis to join us.
~ That will depend.
I take nothing for granted.
And I still ask for George
to be kept in the dark.
I doubt your friendship would
prevent him betraying you
if the need arose.
Any more than our kinship has
prevented you from betraying us?
Do you deny that Verity is meeting
that man at your house?
I think you misjudge him.
I think I've misjudged you!
~ Filthy skunk! Sneaking behind
our backs to debauch my sister!
~ Francis!
~ No...
~ Deceiving her family...
~ Francis, please!
If you and your father
refuse to meet me...
We do not deal with wife murderers!
I have a right to choose my own life!
Honour means nothing to your
sort. Perhaps a thrashing will.
Not in my house!
You have the impudence
to take his side?
I take no-one's side, but you won't
change the issue with this foolery.
I have no wish to quarrel,
but Verity is coming with me.
~ That she is not!
~ Please, Father!
~ There'll be no cleaning of your boots
~ on this family!
~ You insolent puppy!
~ Oh, "puppy", is it?
When will it be convenient for
you to meet me, Captain Blamey?
~ As soon as you like, sir.
~ Andrew, no! Francis, please?
~ Get me a pistol.
~ Get one yourself.
This fellow claims to be a gentleman.
~ Let him step outside and prove it!
~ Francis! No! Ross, stop them!
Stop him! He's out
of his depth, Charles!
Francis, I implore you...!
Andrew, please, for my
sake. Francis! Francis!
Francis, have no truck
with this scoundrel!
~ Verity will come home with us.
~ Yes, Father.
It's gone beyond that.
The skunk insulted me!
Fight it out with fists, then. He's
not worth the risk of a pistol!
Do you want this family
to be a laughing stock?
~ Francis, I urge you to consider...
~ Consider what?
That anyone may abuse our trust
and take advantage of us?
Francis, I beg you.
I will have satisfaction!
You, there! Act as referee.
Can you count?
Aye, sir. One, two, four, seven...
We'll do it ourselves.
One, two, three...
Stop them, please stop them.
.. four,
five,
six,
seven,
eight,
nine,
ten.
~ No!
~ Francis...
Prudie! Fetch me some water.
~ I know it was not your intention.
~ God forbid.
Help me stop the bleeding.
I can't, sir, I be
afeared of the blood.
Surely you must see how impossible
it would be for us
to be together now?
I do see.
I'll 'elp, sir. I b'ain't afeared.
Goodbye... Verity.
Where is he?
Oh, God, no, no, no! How
could you let this happen?
~ Elizabeth...
~ You let him die.
How could you let him die?
Speak to him.
Your cousin do owe 'ee 'is life.
Where'd 'ee learn to do such things?
On the battlefields of Virginia.
You are a disgrace to
the name of Poldark.
I'm sorry you think so.
I offer no thanks.
I feel no gratitude.
I hold you entirely to blame.
I understand.
I do not blame you.
I wouldn't for the
world wish him hurt.
I know that. And I'm grateful
for all you've done.
Come, Elizabeth!
The more so now since,
more than ever,
I need him well and at my side.
I'm with child.
Elizabeth!
Do I have "half-wit" branded
across my forehead?
No.
Yet I fell for it, again.
Built a castle out of winks and
smiles, and all the while...
I should be grateful.
What clearer proof is needed?
Fetch Jim and Jud and Prudie.
We have work to do.
You did well today.
I can see how valuable you
must be to your family.
~ Sir?
~ And if you miss them,
if you feel their need
is greater than mine...
~ 'Ee be wantin' rid of me?
~ What?
'Ee be wishin' me gone?
Sir, I'll work 'arder. I'll scrub
an' scour an' fettle an'...
~ Demelza, your work is
more than satisfactory.
~ Then why, sir?
I was merely offering you the
chance to return to your home.
If that's where you feel you belong.
I belong 'ere.
I declare the Wheal
Leisure mine open!
I wish you could forget him, my dear.
Is love so easy to forget?
Are the rumours true, do you think?
He's a damned fool if they're not!
Any man opening a mine must
be exceptionally brave
or extremely foolish.
'Tis a sign, mark my words.
Step down, Mr Poldark, or we'll have
you committed for contempt of court.
Confess what sin there
is 'twixt you an' Poldark!
You know what people say of us?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org