Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
~ Tidn't right.
~ Tidn't fair.
~ Tidn't fit.
~ Tidn't proper.
~ Won't last.
~ Won't work.
~ Who'd she think she is?
~ Who'd 'ee think she is?
'Chit of a girl.'
~ She'll be too grand t'skivvy.
~ Too common t' curtsey.
'Tis all cocky-eyed.
He's late t'night, Garrick.
Mm? Where can he be?
Sir!
Ross.
I was thinking 'ee might
stop over in town.
I have a home, do I not? And a wife?
I do sometimes forget.
~ That I live here?
~ That I'm your wife.
Let this be a reminder.
~ Why are you up so late?
~ I 'ave chores.
~ Suppose I have other plans for you?
~ Tell me.
Yes, Ross.
Folks'll wonder.
~ They'll not understand.
I don't rightly understand.
~ What?
How it came t'happen - this. We.
You're not required to understand.
You're required to accept
it as a fact of life.
So it's not t'be a secret?
Why should it?
Good day, ladies. Are
we expecting a storm?
~ Storm o'pilchards, God willin'!
~ They're late this year.
An we d'fear they miss'd us entire
an' swung away t'Ireland.
If that happens you'll have nothing
to see you through winter.
~ An' we'll starve.
~ Simple as that.
Let's hope it won't come to that.
I'm not a magician, sir! I cannot
conjure wages out of thin air!
The men must wait.
~ Did my father send you?
~ Why would he?
Read me the riot act, tell
me what I'm doing wrong?
Or was it my wife?
Does she think I'm falling
short of the mark?
Is she wrong to be concerned?
~ What she doesn't know, won't hurt her.
~ What she suspects, might.
Gaming? Whoring? What gentleman
doesn't occasionally indulge?
~ This one.
~ Since when?
~ Since my wedding.
'Your kitchen maid?'
But, Ross, surely you must see...
With such a wife you cannot hope
to have entry into any
respectable gathering.
You will cut yourself out of
society, consign yourself to...
A life of peace and seclusion?
I must try to bear it as best I can.
May I leave you to share the
glad tidings at Trenwith?
Demelza?
Damn me, he's done it now!
What the devil can he mean by it?
I never thought you
the marrying kind.
Is she wealthy?
~ Not at all.
~ 'Could've had his pick.'
Any number of eligible girls
from rising families.
Instead of which... he
marries his serving wench.
~ It beggars belief.
~ It may beggar him.
He must be deranged.
How else could he lower
his sights so abominably?
Is she beautiful?
In a way.
In spite of our assets, we Warleggans
struggle to pass muster.
How will he fare with a
scullery maid on his arm?
'His family with never forgive him.'
Society will never forgive him.
'Doors which were open will
be slammed in his face.'
His ventures will fail...
and you can enjoy the sight of him
in the gutter along with his slut.
So you love her?
We get on.
"My dear Ross, I am the last person
to criticise your attachment.
"But I would like to be the first
to write to you and wish you joy..."
".. I am presently taken
up with tending Father
"but I hope soon to call to offer
my felicitations in person."
There. We have at least one friend.
"Callin'"? Who 'as time to call?
What they mean by it - "callin'".
Callin'.
What?
'Ee bin givin' me squinny-eye ever
since I got back from church.
'Ow else we mun look? We don't
rightly know 'oo we lookin' at!
One minute she Miss Skivvily-
Scullery-Kitchen-Maid,
the next she be Mistress
'Igh n' Mighty!
Do 'ee think it's not as strange
to me as it is to you?
Do 'ee imagine I ever looked
for or 'spected it?
~ Come to think of it, 'tis
more your fault than mine!
~ 'Ow be that, then?
'Tis you 'ave raised me up
an' taught me all I know.
So if I'm fit for better
than I'd 'oped,
blame 'ee'selves for eddycatin' me!
~ We?
~ Eddycators?
~ We made 'er what she is.
~ She 'ave we a' thank ferrit.
~ She still do all her chores.
~ An' most o' yourn.
~ An' 'tis better'n
takin' orders from some fudgy-faced
baggage wi' drop-curls!
Damn this ironstone,
is there no end to it?
How long till we strike copper?
IF we strike copper
- it could be months.
~ Can we last?
~ With good will and good men.
~ And the power of luck beside.
~ We'll need a rise in the price of ore.
Else we're all wastin' our time.
~ This shareholders meetin'...
~ Not a prospect I relish.
We're no closer to copper, so I
must appeal for further investment
if we're to keep blasting.
But - are they not friends o' yourn?
If ever they were, they're
reconsidering the connection.
I would that I had nothing better
to do than admire the view!
They'd happily swap
places with you, sir.
You have means to last the winter.
Without the pilchards, they do not.
Those who cannot feed,
should not breed.
I believe felicitations are in order.
Your son John? Recently wed.
To Miss Ruth Teague.
A determined girl.
~ My best wishes to them both.
~ But are we not remiss
overlooking the presence of
a bridegroom in our midst?
Oh, yes - indeed, indeed.
Congratulations, Captain Poldark,
you have our best wishes for you
~ and your young bride.
~ I thank you, gentlemen.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I must consult Captain Henshawe
before our meeting.
I confess myself uneasy.
His early skirmishes with the law,
his contempt of court
at the last assizes...
and now this marriage
to his serving wench.
~ You think him foolish?
~ I think him reckless in the extreme.
Is a man that demonstrates such
spectacular lack of judgment
to be trusted? Is he fit to helm
a venture of such risk as a mine?
More to the point,
am I prepared to trust him
with more of my capital?
I am not, sir.
I can see no reason for pouring
good money after bad.
Come to me when you've struck
copper and I may reconsider.
Till then you'll see no
more of me or my guineas.
The rest of you share his opinion?
I do not.
Nor do I.
Gentlemen, thank you. I'm sorry we
could not bring you better reports.
You got the candles an' twine?
An' muslin for the cheese?
Open it.
A book for you.
To practise your letters.
And ribbons to tie
up that unruly mane.
I know little of these things.
If they don't suit,
give them to Prudie.
~ Did I mention I wrote to your father?
~ Oh, Ross, ye never!
He'll be that vexed, thinkin'
I'm never comin' 'ome.
I told him your duty lay here.
So it do, Ross. Nothin's changed.
Nothing?
I d'get less sleep!
~ That's your only complaint?
~ I 'ave no complaints.
I do, however.
~ Tell me.
~ You have yet to make an
official visit to the mine.
~ Oh, no, Ross - I couldn't.
'Ow would it look?
~ "Look"?
~ A kitchen maid givin' 'erself airs.
~ I see no kitchen maid.
I see a wife whose duty is to take
an interest in her husband's work.
~ I do take an interest!
~ Excellent. First thing tomorrow, then.
Harder, dammit. Push harder.
Is this wise, sir? Can Grambler
not wait till you're stronger?
~ Dr Choake ordered bed-rest.
~ Dr Choake doesn't have a failing mine
or a son who's neither
use nor ornament!
I'm touched by your faith, Father.
Not sufficiently touched to behave
like a man and the heir of Trenwith?
~ Father!
I never knew such ironstone.
It's impenetrable.
Our luck has deserted us.
Let's 'ope the pilchards
don't do likewise.
Mining and fishing is our lifeblood.
Surely both won't fail.
Captain Henshawe, you
know my wife Demelza?
~ A pleasure to see you, ma'am.
~ G'day to 'ee, sir.
~ No sight 'o th' shoals yet.
~ Demelza's of mining stock herself.
Her father's a tributer at Illuggan.
Perhaps you'd like him
to join us here, ma'am?
I'd as lief stick a fork in my eye!
Um...we d'get on better
from a distance, sir.
I must be gettin' back.
~ The pies'll be burnin'.
~ Right.
We hope to see you here often, ma'am.
~ I was that worried I'd show 'ee up!
~ Why would you?
~ I've no notion how to be.
~ As you are.
~ What am I?
~ A lady.
~ I'm not - an' I don't know 'ow.
You're a quick learner.
Nay, Ross, I came a'day at your behest,
but I shan't venture again.
Miners are my own kind - but I'd
not be so kindly received by yours.
Judas! I'll fetch
'im such a doostin'!
~ Demelza!
~ Oi! Guts!
Get back 'ere, you
good-fer-nothin' viper!
Thievin', connivin'...
'Alf a morn I labour'd
at that pie, y'lizard!
~ Demelza, leave him be!
~ Think to fox me, would 'ee?
'Ee'll 'ave to be quicker 'n that!
Damn me if a man can't take
a fair morsel now 'n then.
~ I told you to stop. Did you not hear me?
~ Yes, but...
I cannot have my wife wrestling
a manservant. It's unbecoming.
No, Ross.
I see it is not dignified.
~ I'll remember next time.
~ There'll be no next time.
There's only one way to remind
you you're no longer a servant.
~ But you'll do all th' arrangin'?
~ I will not.
You are mistress of Nampara. It's
for you to engage your own servants.
I'll serve 'ee gladly, ma'am.
When shall 'ee want me?
~ Tomorrow'd be quite convenient.
~ Yes, ma'am. Thank you, ma'am.
'She curtsey'd to me.'
Get used to it.
~ No, I never will.
~ I must visit my uncle.
~ Perhaps it's time for you to come with me.
~ No...
No, I cud'n't. There's
calves t'be meated,
~ an' pastry t'make...
~ From tomorrow, that excuse won't avail you!
How does the patient fare?
Lucky to have any blood left.
Progress is excellent.
If he continues with my treatment,
he can expect to eat a
hearty Christmas dinner!
But how will you manage, Ross,
without a kitchen-maid?
My wife has, this very
day, engaged another.
The cheek of the devil!
But your father was no different!
The Nampara Poldarks were renowned
for their disregard of convention.
Good day to you.
We're so delighted by the news, Ross.
~ Francis, especially, was
quick to see the advantage!
~ Father.
~ Of what?
~ A wife to divert you!
He feels it marginally less
likely that you'll ride over
and steal Elizabeth from him!
Father!
Compose yourself.
My heart! My heart!
~ Fetch the doctor.
~ Damn Choake promised me Christmas dinner!
He's asked to see you.
I've lost all faith
in this world of ours...
.. and my legacy.
~ We both know Francis is not the man you are.
~ Uncle...
Look after him for me.
~ Of course.
~ And our family.
And our good name.
You have my word.
He'll be missed.
Not by me.
Is it terrible to feel
nothing but relief?
~ Nothing I ever did pleased him.
~ Not even your choice of wife?
He always said she would make
a fine mistress of Trenwith.
And I, an indifferent master.
~ You can still prove him wrong.
~ Now I've come into my estate?
Half of it's mortgaged, the
other half soon will be.
But apparently now...
I'm one of the most important
men in the county.
How is it 'ee be not at the buryin'?
'Tis for fancy folks an' family
- not for the likes of me.
Are ye not family?
Ross might say so.
But I know 'tis not my place.
What is your place?
Betwixt an' between.
Neither one nor t'other.
You need more flour,
stops it from sticking.
See?
I warned Charles. Too many
capons and custards.
Look at me - poached
egg, a little broth -
fit as a fiddle!
Fitter than Francis
by the look of it.
Grambler must be taking its toll.
Not to mention a young morsel
by the name of Margaret.
Have you dined there yourself lately?
My tastes are more
refined these days.
Are you not coming down?
I really cannot face it.
Nor I, but one of us
must play the hostess.
She didn't come.
His wife.
This isn't the occasion.
~ Will you give him my good wishes?
~ Shouldn't you do that yourself?
I wouldn't know where to begin.
"Unwell"? And not even the thought
of a tete-a-tete with Ross
~ could persuade her?
~ Francis...
She'll have few opportunities with
Mistress Poldark to amuse him.
~ You must be relieved.
~ How?
You're not the only one
to disgrace the family
~ by an unsuitable attachment.
~ Francis!
Consider yourself fortunate.
See what you've missed.
~ Dr Choake.
~ Mm? Mm.
I've puzzled you out.
Was I so hard to fathom?
Well, I thought so, but your recent
nuptials have made everything clear.
It delights you to thumb
your nose at society,
because you consider yourself above
the niceties by which it operates.
Not above. Just indifferent.
~ Are you pleased with Wheal Leisure?
~ Pray do not mention it to me.
Mining's always a gamble.
And the gamester rarely
meets a Good Samaritan.
As in?
Oh, someone willing to take
a worthless bet off his hands.
But should I hear of anyone,
would you be interested?
What have I told you?
I don't require my wife
to crochet and sip tea,
but I do require her to remember
she's not a beast of burden.
~ Are you happy?
~ I am.
~ Then I hope you'll be even more so
when I tell you who's coming to stay.
Come on through.
It's so kind of you
to invite me, my dear.
Would you care for some refreshment?
Oh, no, please! Let me
take care of myself.
~ The last thing I want is
to give you any trouble.
~ No trouble at all.
We've been looking forward to
your visit. Haven't we, Demelza?
Yes, Ross.
It's a quiet house since father died.
Though Elizabeth plays the harp and
speaks French to Geoffrey Charles.
And I have my needlework.
Aunt Agatha her spinning.
~ And Francis?
~ Is...
.. often away.
This pie is delicious, my dear.
Did you bake it yourself?
Custard! I'll go an' see if it's set.
She thinks you a great
lady who will show me
~ what a mistake I made in marrying her.
~ What can I do?
I'm sure you'll think of something.
Ross! No! Where are you going?
You cannot just - Ross!
~ Blasted copper. It's
proving a devil to find.
~ Blasting is the word.
It seems to be our only hope.
Right, boys.
~ Some tea?
~ Oh! Thank you!
But no. It's a little early.
Oh. Yes, so it is.
Thank you, Jinny.
You know, Ross is very dear to me.
What woman should ever deserve
him, I couldn't imagine.
~ So when I heard he'd married you, I was...
~ Horrified.
~ .. relieved.
Before he met you he was...
.. broken. Lost.
So I was relieved to think he'd
found someone to console him,
to save him from his loneliness.
But now I see it's
more than consolation.
You've given him hope.
A life without hope is bleak.
~ And a life without love...
~ Oh, 'tis not that.
~ You do not...?
~ Love 'im?
Beyond anythin'.
But...
I could never hope that... that he...
That he would ever...
He's kind to me.
And when we're abed...
I 'ave reason to think
I do please 'im.
Oh, I'm sure you do.
But I'd never call it love.
Ee's never used that word t'me and...
I misdoubt 'ee ever shall.
It's life's greatest
treasure to love.
And be loved in return.
My dear, do you think I care
a jot where you come from,
or who your father is,
or how well you curtsey?
I of'en wished I could curtsey.
Will you teach me, Verity?
The left, left, left!
Well, make up yer blasted
blatherin' minds!
What in God's name are you doing?
We thought we should
move it into the parlour
so Demelza may learn to dance.
If you ladies would give us leave?
Dip. One, two, three...
Dip.
Dip. One, two, three.
On your tip-toes.
One, two, three. Dip...
Foot behind.
One, two, three. Step.
Slowly...
And dip... One, two, three.
That man who used
to meet Verity here?
~ Captain Blamey?
~ Has nothin' bin heard of 'im?
Thankfully, no.
~ Oh, Ross, the shame on you!
~ What do you mean?
~ How could you let 'em part like that?
~ What the devil could I do?
You should've stood up t'yer uncle.
Even now in 'er heart she
still hankers for 'im.
Then she must stop.
Why should she?
Must hope be buried?
An' love denied?
What do you know of love?
~ A little.
~ Is that all?
Then you must practice more.
Must you go home tomorrow?
Francis needs me.
But I'll come again soon.
~ Did you really hate it today?
~ Oh, no!
I'm just afeared we spent too much
money and 'twill all be wasted.
~ How could it?
~ Only that...
p'raps my measuring might
not be the same for long.
My dear, do you mean...?
~ Oh, Ross will be delighted!
~ Don' tell 'im! Not yet. See..
ee's not liked me fer long.
And when I get to waddlin'
about like an old duck,
~ he might forget he ever liked me at all.
~ Ross forgets nothing.
If we are to find copper
it's now or not at all.
Come to watch us set our final fuse?
Will one more blast get us through?
One more blast is all we can afford.
~ I heard the bell! What's amiss?
~ We must leave at once.
Quickly!
~ What is it?
~ Nothin', sir.
Ross. Just...
~ What's the matter?
~ Sometimes...
I d'think I displease you.
I'm used to giving orders and having
no-one to suit but myself,
but you are far from
displeasing to me.
~ See, how would I know that?
~ I'll endeavour to make it clearer.
We must go. Make haste!
Where are we going?
~ Good catch, eh, Mark?
~ 'Andsome, Ross.
More than a quarter of a million,
they reckon, afore they're done.
I'm very glad. It'll make
the difference this winter.
~ 'Twill indeed! Night, Ross. Night, ma'am.
~ Night, Mark.
Night, Ross. Night, ma'am.
~ Night, Ross. Night, ma'am.
~ Night.
Everyone's happy tonight.
They like you.
~ Nonsense.
~ 'Tis the truth. I should
know - I'm one of 'em.
You're a gent.
You don't despise 'em, you help 'em.
You give 'em food, an' work, an...
~ Marry you.
~ No, not that.
They don' know what t'make o'that.
But they like you jus' the same.
And you?
Do you like me?
I could learn to.
And I, you.
We're still not through.
~ I could swear we're almost there.
~ But we're out of gunpowder.
Capital. Investors. How
long can we continue?
An optimist would
say... three months?
~ And a realist?
~ Two.
I must find more investment.
It gives me no pleasure to tell
you this, but capital's short.
~ I understand.
~ Though I've kept my ear to the ground...
~ in case other speculators could be found.
~ And?
Tom Choake has done
you no favours, Ross.
~ His views on your marriage...
~ "Ross Poldark, the loose cannon.
"Too much of a risk for
the prudent investor."
~ I blame myself.
~ You couldn't foresee as we'd 'it such rock.
But I could foresee that
in marrying my kitchen maid,
I'd scandalise all I might
look to for capital.
Well, short of jilting her
and wedding a rich heiress...
Perhaps I was over-hasty.
But it's done now.
So how shall we order things?
We can last till the
week before Christmas.
Let it be the week after.
If I have to sell half my house,
I'll not ruin Christmas for them.
? The boar's head in my hand bear I
? Bedeck'd with bay and rosemary
? So pray my masters, be merree
? Quod estes in convivio
? Caput apri defero
? Redens laudes Domino
? Redens laudes Domino... ?
From Francis.
Inviting us to spend
Christmas at Trenwith.
Oh.
What's the matter?
I-I couldn't.
You go.
Naturally, we both
go or we both stay.
Ross, I aren't their sort.
They'll look down their noses and
send me t'eat wi' th' servants.
Do you think I ought
to be ashamed of you?
~ 'Tis not that but...
~ You think they are so much better than you?
I don't, but...
they'll think so.
Mebbe not Verity, but...
Elizabeth.
You do her an injustice.
~ And me.
~ You?
To think I could admire someone
who thought meanly of you.
Do you admire her?
Elizabeth was born to be admired.
An' I was born to pull turnips.
~ What you doin'?
~ Accepting the invitation.
What a sorry Christmas
I've handed them.
No. You've handed them near-on
twelve month o' work
they'd otherwise not 'ave.
Welcome.
My dear, it's so good
of you to come to us.
May I take you to meet Aunt Agatha?
Married, you say? To my nephew?
Why wasn't I told of this?
You were, Aunt. I told you myself.
They never tell me anything.
And you, where are you from?
'Luggan, ma'am.
Who do we know from Illuggan?
The Cardews?
You'll know Sir John, of course.
And the Perrins of Helston Hall?
No, no, ma'am.
Six generations of
Poldarks I've seen.
Now what do you think of that?
You think I don't look old
enough? Quite right, too.
Now, you go and sit by Elizabeth so
that I can see how you measure up.
~ Aunt Agatha.
~ Go on, child. Go. Off you go.
Hmm.
Pretty little thing.
A mite coarse beside Elizabeth
but doubtless she'll
polish up sufficient
when the need arises.
'I thought she'd hate me.'
I wouldn't blame 'er. I mean,
I probably should in 'er shoes.
Then you've less sense
than I credit you with.
You think I don't know
what you're about?
~ Taking her under your wing,
making her your friend.
~ Francis...
"Oh, Ross, see how kind
and generous I am!
"Look, what a pearl you've lost!"
~ You're being ridiculous.
~ Am I?
~ What's this?
~ Jus' something I ordered from town.
No, Ross! It's meant as a surprise!
It's just a family party.
No need to flig yourself up for it.
I asked Verity and she said it was
right t'change fer Christmas Eve.
Well, don't lace your stays too
tight - they feed you well here,
and I know your appetite.
You were very kind to Demelza.
Who wouldn't be? She looks
like a startled faun.
She's young. And this must
seem very daunting to her.
You don't despise my choice, then?
What right have I to despise anyone?
Besides, I've too much
to distract me here.
Grambler failing and Francis
gambling away his inheritance.
~ I'm sad to hear it.
~ Oh, and worse!
Rumours...
no, reports...
that he has another woman.
Has he?
If he has, he's an idiot.
I am ravenous! When do we dine?
'I can scarce stand up.'
Lord knows how I'll
keep my food down.
And then they'll think that
I'm that vulgar and simple...
Ross will be sorry he ever wed me.
Here, let me help you.
I shan't lace you too tightly.
Thank you.
Trust your husband. And yourself.
Visitors? At this hour?
Mm.
We were just passing, Francis.
Thought we'd come and offer
the compliments of the season.
If we're intruding,
we can easily depart.
Oh, damn me nostrils, though!
What do I scent?
Swan? Partridge?
Mrs Tabb, please lay four
more places for dinner.
Ross Poldark, the famed recluse!
For all we see of you, you
might be Robinson Crusoe.
Oh, but he has his Man Friday, dear.
Is she hereabout?
Or should we seek
her in the scullery?
An attempt on the King's life?
Ambushed for his waistcoat, no doubt.
I'm told it's worth more than
half the mines in Cornwall.
And the Royal Household servants
not paid for 12 months.
I'm amazed no-one's attempted
to sharpen a knife
on the King of France.
Give them time, sir. Give them time.
~ Dinner is served.
~ Excellent!
Demelza...
Let me introduce you.
Damn you, Ross, for keeping
this rosebud a secret.
Hardly secret, John.
All the county was talking
of her in June.
Yes, ma'am. People dearly
love to gossip, don't they?
Ha! Well answered, mistress.
A merry Christmas, and
damnation to all gossip.
~ She's on her mettle tonight.
~ Overdoing the manners a bit.
Look at her plate. She's
hardly touched a morsel.
Too busy making conquests.
What news of the mine, Ross?
Are we swimming in copper yet.
~ Not according to my father.
~ We have reason for optimism.
Glad to hear it, Ross. At least
one of us is prospering.
~ You believe him?
~ Each way, we win.
Enjoy his ruin, or the
fruits of his labours.
Our friend Choake saw
the wisdom of my offer
and sold me his shares
in Wheal Leisure.
How do you manage for
servants, Elizabeth?
Mama and I were only saying,
young girls these days
have such ideas.
Always trying to rise
above their station.
I haven't noticed that.
Perhaps you've been unlucky.
Well...
at least I have my own household.
My poor sisters all lack husbands.
And truly, beyond the age
of 23, what hope is there?
I don't believe there's ever
cause to give up hope.
'Tis sometimes just
a question of waiting.
And seizing the opportunity
when it comes?
I bow before your expertise, ma'am.
Mistress Poldark, now you
must play something for us.
No, no, I don't...
Not musical, ma'am? Did your
governess not teach you?
~ Demelza sings.
~ Oh? Then we must hear her.
We surely must!
? I'd pluck a fair rose for my love
? I'd pluck a red rose blowing
? Love's in my heart
? A-trying so to prove
? What your heart's knowing
? I'd pluck a finger on a thorn
? I'd pluck a finger bleeding
? Red is my heart
? Wounded and forlorn
? And your heart needing
? I'd hold a finger to my tongue
? I'd hold a finger waiting
? My heart is sore
? Until it joins in song
? Wi' your heart mating. ?
Good night.
It's a curious thing.
We envy a man for something he has.
Yet the truth may be, he
hasn't got it after all.
And we have.
Am I rambling?
Ignore me.
Merry Christmas, cousin.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, my love.
~ Thank you, Francis.
~ Merry Christmas.
That wasn't so bad.
I hope you won't live to regret
your choice of husband.
~ Why would I?
~ We may soon be destitute.
There are other kinds of treasure.
What is it? A rock fall?
What happened?
Copper! Copper's been struck.
A monstrous load.
There's masses of copper!
So, how did I do, Ross?
You were not too ashamed of me?
Why do you think I married you?
I don't rightly know.
To satisfy an appetite?
To save myself from being alone?
Because it was the right thing to do?
I had few expectations.
At best, you'd be a distraction.
A bandage to ease a wound.
But I was mistaken.
You've redeemed me.
I am your humble servant.
And I love you.
I hope you will have
a little love to spare.
For what?
Our child.
Did you hear of the
riots in Launceston?
People can only starve for so
long while the rich get fat.
My shares in Wheal Leisure... You
must take that as a compliment.
~ What of the other shareholders?
~ Two or three more wish to sell.
This is Dwight Enys. I have him
to thank for patching me up.
For months now, Grambler
has been failing.
She means Francis has been failing,
~ You barely know her.
~ Maybe so, Ross.
But truly, she's my heart's desire.
~ My name is Poldark.
~ Did Verity send you?
May I see her? How? When?
My husband's against me, stirring
up what should be left alone.
Some obstacles cannot be overcome.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org