You missed it, didn't ya?
You don't know
what happened last week.
You want me to tell you?
Give me 100 bucks.
Come on, 100 bucks,
I'll tell you what ha--
Okay, 50 bucks!
You make a good living!
Give me some fucking money!
You want to know
what happened or not?
Well then, fuck you.
I'm not telling you.
It's my goal to get you all
safely across the border
into Canada.
- Do you see anybody?
- No, I don't see--
Hello. Wrong side
of the border, boys, eh?
You can find your own
rich dude to control.
I am past
my prime whoring years.
Top ten places
to look for rich dudes.
High-end pubs.
We're taking you
sugar-daddy shopping.
I saw you took
the "For Rent" sign down.
It's about time I got
something of my own
for a change.
You're pretty damn intriguing.
How intriguing?
There was, uh, an accident
at my building,
one of the roofer guys
fell off the roof.
- Is he okay?
- I think he broke his ankle.
If there's anything that
I can do to help.
Thank you.
What, Youens still?
I can't stop picturing him
in an orange jumpsuit
for the rest of his life.
You're a good fucking friend,
but you can't fix everything.
You still on that Bible shit?
Yeah, I'm proving to
my online haters
that Jesus is a fag hag.
Another gaycorcism's going down.
Gotta gather the kids.
- Who are you?
- I'm his girlfriend.
- Check this out.
- Wow.
You're
yelling at me right now!
Because you're being crazy!
Yes, I'll marry you!
Fucking hell yes!
Oh, my God...
♪ Think of all
the luck you got ♪
♪ Know that
it's not for naught ♪
♪ You were beaming
once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so sure of? ♪
♪ Round up
the friends you got ♪
♪ Know that
they're not for naught ♪
♪ You were willing
once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so sure of? ♪
Ah, you're, uh,
still at it.
Yeah, I'm trying to figure out
where all the
gay-hating churches are.
There's like one
in every neighborhood.
Homophobia's back in style.
Not for long.
I've got more kids coming
for a meeting tonight.
- Youens still in jail?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm actually gonna
go check on him later today.
Oh.
Hey, they've got
a retirement calculator.
I fucking love the internet.
I'll roll over my 401K
from Lumber Lawn and Lighting.
And then I add
my estimated yearly earnings.
What are you doing, Frank?
Planning my retirement.
Time to reflect on
my accomplishments
and to bask in the spoils
of a life well-lived.
You mean leech off your kids
and drink booze
out of a backpack?
You guys, Farhad found me
a temp job that
pays 40 bucks an hour!
- Oh, yeah?
- Some nighttime welding gig.
I don't know, nighttime welding?
Sounds kind of sketchy, Debs.
Took me two weeks to make
300 bucks walking dogs.
I can handle sketchy.
Expenses? Alcohol and drugs
is non-negotiable.
Clothing? Yes,
the occasional golf shirt
or swimwear for leisurely
retirement pursuits.
Hola, hola, good morning.
No mortgage...
Hola, mi cielito.
Como estás?
No rent...
Are you ready to have a nice day
with your abuelita?
I'll change you.
- Good morning, boo.
- Did you make all this?
Yes.
For you, bae.
I am going to cook for you
every day,
and dinner too,
and then blow jobs for dessert.
I'm going to be
the best fucking wife.
The age
I'd like to retire,
based on my current age?
Well... they're identical, so.
I--
W--this makes no sense.
Let me see.
Come on.
All right, you need...
23 grand annually to retire.
And you are short by about...
22 grand.
Sounds right to me.
Oh, fuck that.
I've got engagement presents!
The vibrations
will lift up your follicles
so that the blades cut
below your skin.
Thank you.
And a Nintendo 3DS
for Liam.
Dope.
And a Zen garden
with a tiny, little sand rake
for you.
And, um, a Fitbit for Ian.
Sweet.
And... hot rollers for you.
Cool.
And for you, my sweet,
hot bitch...
I found it.
What is it?
Is that blood?
Is that your blood?
Yeah.
It's your blood now.
You possess me,
and vice versa.
Here.
Come here.
I'll try not to nick an artery.
Gross.
- Hi.
Nice color.
It's called "Dangerous Robot."
I'm doing the bathroom
in Liquid Kitty.
What happened to just "blue"?
Blue... is not badass.
Well, neither is Liquid Kitty;
it sounds like a dyke bar.
Why don't you just paint it
"Wet Pussy"?
Benjamin Moore
didn't have that one.
It took me forever to choose.
What is my taste, even?
Ghetto chic.
That's by necessity, not choice.
Well, you're asking
the wrong gal.
Mel handles this shit.
And her style's like...
resort meets brothel.
That's perfect for a nursery.
You guys start
picking out cribs?
Crib, singular.
We're down a fetus.
I miscarried.
Oh, shit.
It's okay.
I mean, yeah, it sucks, but
we hadn't figured
we'd both get pregnant.
Least now I can drink.
Got any beer?
Yeah, go help yourself.
Well, how's Mel taking it?
I haven't told her yet.
Maybe I'll eat smoked salmon
and raw eggs in front of her,
and see if she notices.
"Hey, stranger.
Picking up some chairs
for a client.
Wanna join and grab
some furniture for your flat?"
- Is that Ford?
- Mm-hmm.
Say yes.
He's like a furniture savant.
So the last time I saw him,
we kissed,
and then he threw me out.
Well, said he had to work.
I have never waited this long
for someone to bang me.
It's kind of fun, weirdly.
For now.
Guy better be an animal in bed.
I wouldn't know.
I closed my eyes and
pictured Scarlett Johansson.
But I've heard
glowing accounts.
Well, if I find out
before I'm 40,
I'll let you know.
Any bites yet?
Maybe we should change
her profile description.
What does it say now?
"Sassy Russian ex-prostitute
seeks single geriatric male
with piles of money
and a terminal illness."
Subtle.
Guy named Gerald
seems interested.
Luxury cigar importer.
Hey, guess what we're doing.
I can find my own rich husband.
We know that you can,
but if a wealthy cigar importer
comes into The Alibi tonight,
it won't kill you
to smile and have a drink.
What is the point of smiling?
Make other people feel good.
I make people feel good
other ways.
Yes, you do.
But there are some situations
where hand jobs
are not appropriate.
American mid-century modern.
Mm.
That's cool.
Reference to the Danish
design movement of the 1950s.
Try it.
- It's comfy.
- Mm-hmm.
- Not sure it's me though.
- Says who?
You get to choose that.
That's what design is for.
Decide who you want to be.
speaking Greek
- speaking Greek
speaks Greek
Thank you.
- What the fuck was that?
- Uh, Greek.
I lived in a monastery
in Macedonia for a while.
Of course you did.
And I just scored you
a $2,000 chair for 450,
which is insane.
I'm not gonna spend
$450 on a chair.
It's not a chair.
It's an investment
in your future self.
How much
that building cost you?
It was a lot more than I had.
Why'd you buy it then?
You're good.
- Hi.
- Hi. Inmate's name?
It's, uh, Clyde Youens.
Y-O-U-E-N-S.
I'm sorry, he's deceased.
What?
There was an incident.
He didn't survive.
W--when?
Tuesday.
Next of kin was contacted
and the body was claimed.
Next.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Here for Paddy, 4629...
They're kicking him out
of the hospital in the morning.
And how is
this my problem, huh?
He fell.
I didn't push him.
He worked six hours;
he'll get his 150 bucks
when the job is done
and I get paid.
That's how this works.
We're not leaving this spot
until we get out our money.
Whatever!
Sorry to bother you.
Do you mind if my kids
use your bathroom?
Sure.
We love you, Ian!
There he is.
Look, it's Ian.
- Ian! Ian!
- Can you come to our...
- What's up, guys?
- My boyfriend is gonna flip.
He can't stop talking about you.
Could you, uh,
record a message for him?
His name's Nico James.
Mr. Gallagher,
hi, I'm Reverend Murphy.
I'm a pastor at
Trinity and Life Evangelical--
Oh, we don't need
any more ministers,
but if you want to give money,
that'd be cool--
I'm not here for me.
Some folks from my church
wanted to meet you.
This is Alice.
Her parents put her through
conversion therapy twice.
She has something for you.
Go on, honey.
Wow.
That, uh, tha--
you drew this?
Thank you.
Can you, like, heal people?
I'm a paramedic, so...
Well, when are you gonna
perform your next miracle?
Oh, no, I don't
perform miracles.
Do you--I'm sorry,
I only saw the one video.
- What is your ministry, again?
- I don't have one.
I just kind of show up
to these conversion things
and argue with assholes.
I... lead meetings at this
youth center if you guys want--
My boyfriend needs help.
Could you talk to him?
Oh, well, lookee here,
Mr. Popularity.
- Mr. Viral Sensation.
- Okay.
Mr. King of the Queens.
Kind of hoping
they'll lose interest.
Yeah, well, there's more
and more of them every day.
They're blocking
the garage door.
I'm gonna have to
park the ambulance
outside by the curb
so I don't accidentally
run somebody over.
What do they even want?
Uh--
Guess they just want
to be seen by...
someone who sees 'em back.
Oh, please.
Looks to me like they want to
douse you in syrup
and slurp you up with a spoon.
Could be down for that.
That chair suits you.
Might be the first time
I bought something
I didn't actually need.
Beautiful, functional
everyday objects
should be affordable.
My idea of affordable is
looting the house
of the neighbor who just OD'd
so I don't gotta buy new shit.
I've got an old coffee maker
that needs a loving home.
Ooh.
Now you're talking.
Maybe I'll come by
your place later?
- Pick it up?
- I got plans tonight.
I'll drop it off tomorrow.
How long have they
been in there?
About 20 minutes.
Are they bathing?
I think they might be.
Why would they do that?
You think they're homeless?
Jesus, you startled me.
I didn't think
anybody else had keys.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Oh, I'm Lip.
Um.
Phillip Gallagher.
Who are you?
I'm--I'm Tabitha, his daughter.
I--um, are you a student?
No, I was.
I was helping him
after the accident.
Accident? I thought
he was arrested for a DUI.
You know what?
It's okay.
I don't even want to know.
Jesus Christ, this week.
You--you do know he's dead,
right?
What happened?
He had, uh, a seizure.
Alcohol withdrawal.
Hit his head.
- Jesus.
- Yeah.
There's a memorial service
tomorrow,
and the students are welcome
to say a few words if you like.
Oh, no one told me.
The school said
they sent out an email.
I-I-I'm sorry,
who are you again?
I picked up your dad...
from jail,
after the DUI.
I bought him groceries.
I--
Did he pay you?
No, he didn't pay me.
He...
covered the cost of my rehab.
And he got me an internship.
He-he tried to
convince the school
to revoke my expulsion.
He listened to me.
He...
listened to me about everything.
Well, glad you were
so well-parented by my dad.
Look, I-I have this covered.
You can leave your key
on the way out.
Thanks.
Sure.
Here you are, sir.
On the house.
- Oh, thank you.
- Of course.
Our elders are
a precious resource.
Thanks for staying alive.
I'll drink to that.
♪ 'Cause ♪
♪ You dance... ♪
My, my.
You must be Svetlana.
Wow.
What a knockout.
Good evening, ma'am.
May I procure you a cocktail?
Vodka.
Your profile was, uh,
quite provocative.
You were an escort
for a time, weren't you?
Hand whore.
Occasional
cocksucking and fucking.
What is your name?
- Gerald.
- "Gerald."
Sounds like bald man
drowning in hot soup.
Huh?
There you are, m'lady.
What would it run me if, uh,
you and I were to take
a walk out to my vehicle
and you were to
keep me company for 30 minutes?
$900,000.
Forty bucks.
And you take off your shoes
so I don't get any...
dirt on my seat.
Oh!
♪ You got hotness ♪
♪ To get your body... ♪
Could've gone worse.
Don't know how.
It sucks when people use God as
an excuse for their own hatred,
and when it's your family,
it's the worst.
Look,
I know you don't
want to hurt your parents,
but sometimes they forget.
God creates us all
in his own image.
We gotta jog their memory.
If they believe that God hates
the same people as they do,
well, they're creating God
in their image.
That's right. That's right.
We all have a Holy Spirit.
We're all holy.
We're all divine...
Jesus, listen to that.
Oh, I know.
He's like a prophet.
And he's super hot too.
Like hot gay Jesus.
"Hot gay Jesus."
Bet we can make money
off of that.
How?
Ring the right bell
for the right causes,
the guilt-ridden
pry open their wallets.
It's Pavlovian.
Righteousness
is very marketable.
What's that all about?
Uh, just a queer
religious rebellion
led by your gay brother.
No biggie.
We all have
the Trinity inside of us.
I'd like to read a passage
from Romans now.
- Who are we hiding from?
- The union workers.
We gotta wait till
they leave for the night.
- How do we get paid?
- Cash.
We meet tomorrow, location TBA,
and they'll text the address.
My God.
This is so exciting.
Everybody, let's go, let's go.
OMG.
That was amazing.
Your brother is,
like, everything.
And they all ate my popovers.
God, I am really fucking happy.
- Are you?
- Yeah.
But are you, like,
really fucking happy
or are you just, like, meh?
I'm really fuckin' happy.
Yay.
- Hey, what you writing?
- A list.
"Swiss Army knife, stun gun,
retractable night stick,"
what-what is this shit?
List for school.
Give it back.
Wait, military school?
You said that
you weren't going back.
We're engaged!
I never said
I wasn't going back.
I've been packing my duffel bag
all week.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I guess I've been just too busy
buying your fuckin' family shit
and-and making
a fucking life for us.
Meanwhile, you've just
been shitting all over it.
Why did we even bother
getting engaged?
Why did I fucking
cut myself for you?
We'll
make it work; you'll come visit.
- We'll scout motels.
- Motels?
What am I, a prostitute?
No, I never said that!
You are so
full of shit, Carl!
- You don't even love me!
- Of course I love you!
Well,
you don't love me enough!
Then how do I
prove it to you?
Um, you're not supposed to ask
how you prove to love somebody,
you should just prove it.
Well, obviously
it's not fuckin' enough.
Uh, yeah,
because your real goal is
to go back to military school.
Of course that doesn't
make me think that you love me!
I want you to stay here
and be my husband!
Reverend Murph,
this is my sister Fiona.
- Pleasure.
- Hi.
I'm super impressed, dude.
The only way I can
get that many people
is if I offer free pizza.
No, it's just
'cause of that video.
No.
You got something, man.
Bunch of folks
who couldn't make it
already messaged me
about the next one.
Oh, I definitely can't
fit more people in here
than I did tonight.
Would you feel weird
about using our parish hall?
No pressure.
Just shoot me a text
when you decide,
I'll send you the address.
Thanks for the beer.
How's the new place?
Small.
Quiet.
- I bought a chair.
- Oh.
Your, uh, fellowship thing
seems to be doing well.
First Gallagher
to become famous for something
other than larceny or assault.
Ha, yeah.
It's, uh...
it's getting pretty out of hand.
I got people showing up
at my home,
church place, work.
I had to shut down
my Facebook page.
So why not quit
if you hate it so much?
I don't.
Just...trying to manage it.
She's back to flipping
out again about military school.
Says I can't go
'cause we're engaged.
Wait, you're actually engaged?
- I thought that was a joke.
- Don't marry her.
I can't lose her.
She's fun, hot,
rich, hot.
She loves me.
No one's ever
loved me this hard.
Do not marry her, okay?
She is a fucking psycho.
Marry her.
Hear me and heed me.
Do not let that frothing piece
of lady meat out of your sight.
She has a trust fund.
Get joint checking.
And whatever you do,
do not sign a prenup.
Hey.
It's Gay Jesus.
Can I have this?
Hey!
Scabs!
- Go, go!
- Fuckin' run!
- Oh, fuck!
- Get back here!
Debbie!
Debbie, run!
Come here, you motherfucker!
Hey!
How ya feeling?
Like shit.
Sorry to hear that.
Your boss emailed me.
He finished the job,
sent me an invoice.
Probably want to track
him down so you can get paid.
Thanks for the heads up.
Okay.
You did really well last night.
However, we need
to tone down the rage a little.
You're not gonna get anywhere
if your date thinks
you want to murder him
the second he ties the knot.
- What if I do?
- Great question.
Which brings us to Part A
of our plan: etiquette.
Rich guys are old school.
They want a lady to be a lady.
A man wants to feel powerful.
Really powerful.
So let him dominate
the conversation.
Act like he's
totally fascinating.
I cannot do this.
Okay, this brings us
to Part B of our plan.
This is a tiny microphone.
Attach it to your shirt.
This is a tiny earpiece.
Put this in your ear.
Oh, come on, Svet.
You're Russian.
This is spy shit.
It's in your DNA.
Testing, testing.
Can you hear me?
You are right there.
I meant in the thingy.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Okay.
Do everything I say.
Scratch your nose.
Tuck your hair behind your ear.
Excellent.
Say, "Kevin Ball
has a sexy voice."
Why should I lie?
Say it.
Kevin Ball has a sexy voice.
Mmm.
What the fuck was that
last night?
I never said it was risk-free.
You also never said
we'd be running for our lives.
Why'd they hire us instead
of hiring their own guys?
Scabs are non-union.
Union guys get overtime,
pension, health.
So we're screwing over a union
we want to join someday?
If we don't take the work,
someone else will.
It's wrong and it's dangerous.
I'm never being a scab again.
Hey, just got a tip
for another gig.
Pays even more.
Five hundred.
I'm in.
Hi.
What you got there?
Free appliance.
Works great if you're patient.
Is that a shitty,
old percolator?
It's Italian.
It's art.
Hey.
What are you guys
still doing here?
We can't leave.
Rodney won't
fit in the car with his leg.
Plus, our AC is busted.
You know anybody with an SUV?
Or I can take you somewhere.
Where you headed?
Is there, uh, some family
you can stay with
or maybe an old neighbor?
Oh, we've been looking
into some charity housing,
but they all have a wait list.
I know someone
who works with local shelters.
I can ask him if he maybe knows
a place that could take you.
- Wow, you'd do that?
- Sure.
Hey.
What the fuck?
Hey, baby.
You cut up all my uniforms?
Well, I weighed out
the pros and cons,
and I made a decision
for our family.
I think that it's
better for everyone
that you don't
go back to school.
We have a wedding to plan.
Kassidi.
Don't say my name like that.
- Kassidi--
- Do not
say my name like that,
I mean it, Carl.
Kassidi, this is not a joke!
I am going back
to military school.
I hate you!
Hey!
Fuck. Wait!
You can't leave me! I'll die!
Hey, what the fuck!
You're not gonna die!
We're gonna see each other
like once a week!
- I can't!
- Open up the door!
- I need you!
- What the fuck? You kidding me?
This engagement
is bullshit!
What?
What the fuck?
I paid like 100 bucks for that!
- Fuck you!
- Come on!
Fuck you!
Oh, my God!
What do you want me to do?
Marry me before you leave,
dumbass.
You love me, right?
Then what's
the point in waiting?
Okay, fine.
- Today?
- Yeah, sure.
♪ I was in so deep ♪
But--do you have a fake ID?
Yeah.-
♪ My same ole story ♪
♪ And the weight is all ♪
♪ The weight is all on me ♪
- Hey.
Where's Ian?
I don't know.
I haven't seen him.
Fuck.
He was supposed to be here
like an hour ago to help set up.
Doing this thing about
careers in emergency services
for our Life Skills program.
Shit-ton of people signed
because of him, but...
whatever.
What's up?
Uh, one of the guys
who was working on my roof
got hurt.
He's gonna be out of work
for a few months,
and his family's
living out of a car.
I was wondering if you might
know any
family shelters
that could take him?
Um, I might, actually.
Follow me.
So, uh, what's your take
on this whole, uh,
Ian ambushing
all those ministers?
Uh,
not really sure
what to make of it.
Ah, yeah.
I mean, part of me is psyched
that he's helping people, but
another part is, I don't know,
kind of bummed that I have to
crowbar my way into his life
if I want to see him.
Oh.
This place is decent.
I'll call over and
get everything squared away
and let you know.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
And, hey, if you see Ian,
please...
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Will do.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
The fuck is this, Frank?
Son, I don't think
I've articulated
how impressed I am
with your recent endeavors.
I knew you were talented,
but, uh...
"The Church of Gay Jesus."
Is this a jumbo shirt?
To reach the masses,
you've got to
embrace merchandising
to take your brand
to the next level.
Uh, how about T-shirts
proudly displaying your message?
Well, I-I don't have a church.
And I'm not fuckin' Jesus.
Tongue in cheek, son.
When you repurpose
a-an iconic logo
for the-the sake of kitsch,
you present an ironic critique
of American consumerism.
And if that logo
just happens to resemble a...
giant, throbbing penis,
what could be
more counterculture?
It looks like a hot dog.
And the lettering sucks.
Revolutions don't come
wrapped in a cute ribbon.
You want to bring down
power structures?
You want to get
in the face of people
who are peddling
corroded ideals?
You need a uniform
that screams authenticity.
We didn't pay
Chinese factory orphans
three cents an hour
to make these.
No, this is our living room.
Our hands.
Our sweat.
Talk about grassroots.
I have a meeting tonight at
Trinity and Life Evangelical.
You can hawk
your shit there, but
everything you make
has to go to Trevor's kids.
Oh, come on!
This is my retirement fund.
Twenty percent.
Thirty?
Okay, 95 percent,
and we appreciate your business.
And this has been
a rough few years.
Needless to say,
it hasn't been that easy
being around my dad.
But my favorite memory of him
is this thing that he would do.
So he would be in his office,
hunched over paperwork,
and I'd knock.
And he'd look up, confused.
And then, boom.
It's the--the biggest,
warmest smile.
That is the version of my dad
that I'm going to remember.
And I'm grateful
for every moment
that I had with him
when he was just him.
You hear about these professors
who go the extra mile
to help a student.
But what Youens did for me
went above and beyond that.
Got me my first real job.
Listened to me
bitch about my family.
He was there for me.
He got me internships,
wrote dozens of letters
of recommendation,
personally called
the dean at Carnegie Mellon
to get me into the
robotics doctoral program.
Told me once,
he wished he'd been a poet.
And he showed me something
he'd written.
Said I was the only person
he trusted enough to show.
That poem was awful.
And no matter how busy he was,
Youens always
made time to talk to me.
He helped me with
whatever I needed,
listen, offer advice,
wise counsel.
Day or night,
it didn't matter,
when you called or
knocked on his door,
he always answered.
Always.
♪ You could ever
really love me... ♪
He was like a father to me.
I honestly don't know
where I'd be without him today.
♪ It's in your head... ♪
He invested his
time and energy to make sure
I didn't become a total fuck-up.
He didn't have to.
I'm still not sure why he did.
Okay.
My friend found you a place.
It's a family shelter.
They'll have a room for you
in two days.
Girls, we've got
a place to live.
They can take us
in two days, you said?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, we've got the tarp
if it rains again.
Why don't you just
stay here for two nights?
Really?
Yeah.
Not a problem.
I'll just, uh,
I'll crash at my old place.
Oh, my God, Fiona.
Thank you.
You're a lifesaver.
We should go get a blanket
and a bottle of champagne,
go in the park, and lay
in the grass as man and wife,
and let the moon and the stars
bless our union.
Cute!
103.
Oh!
Yay!
That's us.
Okay, come on.
All set.
Your marriage license is valid
for 60 days in Cook County only.
There's a one-day waiting period
before the license
becomes effective.
Wait.
So we can't get married today?
You can get married
at this exact time tomorrow.
What the fuck?
This sucks.
I look like a fucking
First Lady.
Here.
Go cross your legs
and pretend to be captivated.
Smokey to Bobcat.
Do you hear me?
Over.
What are you guys up to?
We're trying to get Svetlana
married off to a rich dude.
So...
you just gave 'em your place,
just like that?
What else was I supposed to do?
Man, I was really digging
my quiet mornings
away from Gallagher chaos.
And it's extra bad right now
'cause of Ian's
gay messiah shit.
He should read
Pope Leo the 13th's
encyclical on property rights.
I'll pass it on.
You know, whiskey is actually
clear when it
comes off the still.
It gets the caramel color
from the barrel--
You know, I'm just--
I'm just gonna say this.
Sometimes it feels like
it doesn't even matter
that I'm sitting here.
I know all the places
you've lived.
I know all the languages
you speak.
I've met your exes,
your baby mamas, your spawn.
And yet, you have never asked
one question about me.
Did you know that I became
legal guardian
of my siblings when I was 23?
Or that I dropped out
of high school,
but then I got back
and I got my GED?
Yes, actually, I did.
And I know you did it
to convince your genius brother
who's a recovering alcoholic
to stay in college.
I know you got left at
the altar by your junkie fiancé
with whom you were
very much in love.
- How?
- 'Cause I ask around.
There's some other stuff I know.
You're fiercely protective
of your family.
You're generous.
Like today, for example,
you gave your apartment
to a homeless family.
You are so very much yourself.
You don't even have to try.
And frankly, you scare
the fuckin' shit out of me.
It's him.
Svet, Svet.
The buzzard is in the tuba.
- The what?
- I have no idea.
I've never done this before.
What's she saying?
I can't hear anything.
We never tested the microphone.
All right, well,
she needs to relax.
Tell her to lean in a little.
Svetlana, lean in a little.
Too far.
Too Far.
Take a sip of your drink.
Sip, not gulp.
Tell her to-to ask him
about something.
All right.
All right, Svet.
Ask him about his mother.
No, not his mother.
Ask him about
his favorite sports teams.
Allergies--
what the hell
do people talk about on dates?
Did she just drop
her earpiece in her drink?
Oh, no.
She's gonna grab his cock,
isn't she?
Mm-hmm.
Called that one.
T-shirts!
Each garment has been worn
by the man himself.
- And blessed!
- T-shirts.
$50 suggested donation.
The white one?
Okay. Thank you.
T-shirts, T-shirts.
T-shirts,
get your T-shirts here!
Nice turnout.
Only half of them are regulars.
You did great.
I just sat there while
people talked about
how horribly
they'd been treated,
by family, co-workers...
Can you please sign this,
please?
- ...strangers.
- Thank you.
Sometimes that's all they need.
Tomorrow's our weekly service...
- Thanks so much.
- ...where we invite speakers
to come up
and discuss how to turn
personal pain into
positive action.
We call it
"A Night of Good Grief."
The name is silly,
but the idea isn't.
You up for it?
Well...
I don't...know what to say
that hasn't already been said.
You say it again.
It can't be said enough,
not until queer kids
stop being told there's
something wrong with them.
It was so worth it.
♪ Solid as a stone ♪
♪ All is almost lost ♪
♪ And it starts to show ♪
♪ And it's home
but it's gone ♪
Fuck!
♪ Tear down your ♪
♪ Suffering ♪
♪ Bolt ♪
♪ By ♪
Hey.
- Hm?
- Hey.
We need to talk.
What?
You gotta promise
not to freak out.
I promise.
Okay.
First of all.
You're, like, the best thing
that's ever happened to me
like, by like a bazillion.
But when we were
at the clerk's office,
and she said we had to wait...
I was relieved.
A little.
'Cause I feel like
we rushed into this.
And I totally want you
to be my wife,
my little sweetie boo.
Would you hate me
if we stayed engaged
a teeny bit longer?
Until we're both
no doubt, positively sure
we're ready?
I could never hate you.
- For real?
- Yeah.
And thank you
for being honest with me.
That's, like, super important
for a healthy marriage.
You are awesome.
I love you.
Mm, I love you too.
Mm.
Okay, okay.
Okay, now.
You're getting pretty good
at that.
Fourth time's the charm.
Well,
two left.
Better hope you tire out soon.
Do you think
I'm the only person on Earth
who doesn't want your babies?
I don't want my babies.
That's why I keep
letting other people have them.
I dig this
candid version of you.
Now...ask me something
about myself.
What's the one thing
about Fiona Gallagher
that might surprise me?
That's a tough one.
You seem to have me
all figured out.
That's my gift.
How about...
I think I might not
want to have kids.
But you're a woman.
How is that possible?
Well, my siblings are my kids.
It's Nessa.
Mm-hmm.
I'm supposed to be analyzing
your skills and reporting back.
And how am I doing so far?
Overall positive.
Happy to give you more data.
Hi.
Can I call you back later?
You're fucking kidding me.
- Thanks for the heads up.
- Any time.
FYI, they just dragged in two
sleeping bags and a pull-up bar.
Hello?
- ...uh-huh.
- Hi.
Now, everyone,
this is the lady
who has been helping us.
This is, uh, my sister,
my cousin, his wife,
and their son.
What's going on?
They're paying us to crash here
so we'll have some cash
for the shelter.
Oh, fuck!
My chair!
Ooh, sorry about that.
Good thing
it's an old chair, right?
Hey.
Sorry about last night.
Something came up last minute,
and I'm trying
to juggle everything
but it's snowballing and--
and I--
Hey.
- Yeah.
- It's snowballing.
I had like 40 people show up
to this meeting yesterday.
Yeah, and I had 50 kids show up
to a career symposium
about being a paramedic.
But...I guess since yours
is about God, you win, right?
- Hey, hey, Ian.
- One second, guys.
I'm helping people in need,
same as you.
Are you saying it's only cool
when it's your idea?
I don't ask a lot of you.
This was one thing
that was important to me.
You know, maybe
what you're doing is worth
pissing off the people
that care about you.
That's fine.
But don't insult me
by acting like
it's not happening.
Hi.
You didn't speak at the service.
Uh, I was gonna, but...
everything I was gonna say
was already said.
Sorry for your loss.
Yeah, I lost him
a long time ago.
Still doesn't make it easy.
He was a good dad,
just, um,
not to me.
I guess it's easier to be
kind to somebody
who looks up to you.
Hey, um,
I found this
going through his paperwork.
It's a draft
of a recommendation letter.
Thought you might want it.
You know, in all of
his years of teaching,
I never heard him
talk about a student like that.
He says he's amazed
by your mind.
You don't want to keep it?
Oh, I think I'm too angry
to keep it.
Kass?
Where you at?
♪ One, two, three, four,
blowing down my door ♪
- ♪ Five, six, seven, eight... ♪
- Babe?
Kass!
Oh!
You saved my life!
- You really do love me!
- Yeah.
What time is it?
Like 4:00?
The County Clerk's office
is open til 5:00.
♪ Nothing's gonna
stop me now ♪
That your new chair?
Why's it over here?
So that the pile of assholes who
are squatting in my apartment
won't destroy it.
Who aren't actually assholes.
They're just poor and broke
and taking advantage of the
situation.
Just like I've done
100 times.
And they aren't squatting.
I told them
that they could stay there.
Did you just get this pic
from Kassidi?
Yeah.
"Birth, marriage, death."
What the hell is that?
- I think they got hitched.
- What?
Yeah, I told him not to.
Not legally, right?
She's, like, 15.
Hey.
Can I get a ride
to this church?
Supposed to speak
at this thing, and I don't know.
Kinda scared shitless.
I mean...
I don't do speeches.
So don't do it.
Sorta feel like I have to.
Everyone thinks
that I have something to say.
What if I don't?
When they're gone, they're gone,
folks, so don't miss out.
All profits go to help
gays across the planet.
Can you give me just one second?
Are we really gonna give
all of our money to Ian?
No, of course not.
Thank you so much for waiting.
Gay Jesus loves and blesses you.
Get your T-shirts here!
Don't miss out, folks.
We're runnin' out.
T-shirts.
Oh, shit.
No wonder you're nervous.
Did you know that all these
people were gonna be here?
- No.
- Hey.
They all came for you.
Isn't this amazing?
So I just wanna start out
by saying that I'm no hero.
I'm just a guy
who keeps showing up
to these anti-gay churches
and hearing shit like,
"God created man and woman.
You either look
like a man or a woman.
Don't...bring us
any of your other shit."
So they're essentially saying,
"Don't make me work too hard
to see you on your own terms,"
right?
But we have the God-given right
to be who we are.
Not who others want us to be.
So when they say shit like,
"Don't use fake words
like 'nonbinary'
or 'gender-fluid,'
'cis-whatever,'" it's like...
Those are my terms, bitch.
Mm-hmm, yep.
Mm-hmm.
Which means we have to be
so big,
so noisy...
that there's nowhere else
to look.
And we do it in God's name
because...
Because God hates haters.
I spotted 12 safety violations.
No wonder they pay
so much.
I think I'm gonna bail.
I gotta stick it out.
I need the cash.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, could you grab me
a clip light?
Can barely see anything
I'm doing.
Okay.
Debbie!
Call 911!
Hi.
This fucking day, man.
Find Svetlana a man?
No, she grabbed
the guy's cock.
Is that a good thing
or a bad thing?
Not taking her home
to meet Mom.
Where you coming from?
Church.
Ian has a cult.
- A what?
- Yeah.
They think he's Gay Jesus.
Looking for Fiona Gallagher.
That's me.
You've been served.
"As a result of
one or more acts
by defendant L. Donner
and defendant F. Gallagher,
plaintiff R. Latham has been
injured,
damaged,
and incapacitated."
Who the fuck is R. Latham?
Rodney.
The dude that
fell off your roof?
He's suing you?
"Plaintiff demands judgment
against defendants
in the sum of $6 million."
Motherfucker.
Motherfucker!
♪ Whoa-oh ♪
♪ I'm the love
he left you with ♪
♪ You sound bent out of shape ♪
♪ No blood can try
to stop me now ♪
.srt Extracted, Synced and Corrected
by Dan4Jem, AD.I.MMXVIII