Nobody's saying
our neighborhood
is the Garden of Eden.
Hell, some people say God
avoids this place altogether,
but it's been a good home
to us...
to me and my kids,
who I'm proud of,
'cause every single one of them
reminds me a little bit of me.
Fiona, my rock, huge help.
Has all the best qualities
of her mother,
except she's not
a raging psycho bitch.
Blow.
Lip, smart as a whip.
Straight "A"s
and the honor roll.
Boy's definitely
going somewhere.
You, come back!
Stop!
Ian, industrious,
conscientious,
ambitious,
incredible work ethic.
Don't have a clue
where he got that from.
Wants to be a paratrooper.
Knows how
to disembowel an enemy
with a roll of dimes
and an old gym sock.
Carl.
Uh, I don't really know
that much about Carl.
Oh, loves animals.
Always dragging home
some poor stray he found,
taking them up to his room.
Ah, Debbie.
Sent by God, total angel.
Raises money for UNICEF
year-round,
some of which
she actually turns in.
Liam, going to be a star.
I'm no biologist,
but he looks a little bit
like my first sponsor.
He and the ex were close.
Kev and Veronica,
fantastic neighbors.
There's nothing they won't do
for each other.
Or to each other.
That didn't hurt half as much
as I thought it would.
I never realized how little sex
I was having
till V and Kev moved next door.
And me, Frank Gallagher,
father, teacher,
mentor,
captain of our little ship.
We may not have much,
but all of us, to a man,
knows the most important thing
in this life...
we know how to fucking party!
No!
♪ Here it come running,
here it come running again ♪
Fuck you, man!
♪ Ah, trouble
where the kids are ♪
♪ Here it come running ♪
♪ Ah, running... ♪
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
7:15, monkeys.
Come on.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Oh, no.
7:15.
I fell down.
First shower!
You had it yesterday.
Fuck!
Shit.
Electric.
Yeah.
Coming through.
Electric.
No. You've got a Happy Meal
on the front of that shirt.
Oh, um, field trip.
Need Dad's signature.
Okay.
Arms up.
Wow, Deb, that's
getting really good.
Who's got the phone?
I got it.
Any minutes left?
Uh, 14.
Hey, I need something
for show-and-tell.
How much are we short?
$18.30.
Oh, I'm tutoring after school.
I should be able to
kick in like ten more.
Hey, did, uh,
Carl put in any?
Mmm.
You're almost nine.
You're going to have
to start pulling your weight.
That's right, and
get a real job,
not just dipping into the
collection plate at St. Tim's.
I'm filling in for Candi.
I can cover the rest.
Extra kraut on mine.
Cheese on mine.
Somebody's got to take Liam.
Uh, I got a calculus test.
I'm working after school.
Show-and-tell?
Show them the birthmark
on his back.
It looks like Latvia.
♪ I want you to be true ♪
♪ 'Cause sometimes
I don't understand ♪
♪ The things you do ♪
♪ I won't save you ♪
♪ From the ways you so ♪
That's my fucking bike!
♪ So wrongly want to choose,
la, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, pay attention now ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ Pay attention now,
la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ Pay attention now. ♪
No Candi again?
Bobby's got a bail hearing.
That kid's going to
be the death of her.
What is it this time?
Tried tagging a cop car
with the cops still in it.
What?
Who's got the jumbo dog?
How'd you know?
X-ray vision.
Hey.
Would you tap that ass?
Once, if I
double-bagged it.
Project girls don't abort.
Uh, hi.
I'm here to help Karen study
for her midterm.
Okay.
You have to take your shoes off.
What?
I'll get you a plastic bag.
Here you go.
She's got this thing
about people bringing dirt
in the house.
Molysmophobia.
Oh.
Right.
Okay, so, um...
if you remember it like this,
the... the formula
is completely visible.
Um... okay.
Midget naked witch
is bending over,
and she's crying
'cause she lost one ear
and she can't find it.
How do you know all this?
Uh, just something I like
to fool around with.
Like a hobby?
Uh, no. More like a plan.
Physics?
Yeah, yeah.
Have you done Newton's first?
I've got a great one for that.
Um, "Everybody continues
"in a state of rest
or uniform motion
"unless acted upon
"by an external...
force."
Uh, hang on.
Karen, I'm, uh...
I'm still going to have
to charge you for this.
Charge me?
Yeah, this isn't charity.
I get paid for tutoring.
I know.
Science just turns me on.
Okay.
♪ ♪
Jesus.
Lip, you in there?
Lip. Can I borrow your deodorant?
Yeah?
I'm using Ian's.
If I stick this in the washer
Fiona, where are you?
before I go out, keep an eye on it?
Uh, do it tomorrow.
God, it stinks in here.
Oh, sorry.
There's a shirt I need.
Fiona!
We need to go if we're going
to get a ride to the club.
Hey, five minutes.
Look at me.
No, this has got
to go back tomorrow.
I'll put it back on later.
I have a tag gun at home.
What? From when I worked at T.
J.Maxx.
Let's go.
Hot dogs downstairs.
Nachos, too.
Have fun.
Bye, Lip!
Hey, Veronica.
Hey.
♪ She won't ever get enough ♪
♪ Once she gets a little touch ♪
♪ If I had it my way,
you know that I'd make her say ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ No more sailors,
and no more soldiers ♪
♪ With your name in a heart,
tattooed up on the shoulders ♪
♪ Your kiss is like whiskey,
it gets me drunk ♪
♪ And I wake up in the morning ♪
Hi.
My purse! Fuck!
My purse!
That guy just took my purse!
♪ She won't ever get enough ♪
♪ Once she gets
a little touch... ♪
Shit. Hey!
Hey! Assholes!
Ah, sorry.
That was fucking incredible.
Truly, honestly, one of the most
heroic things I've ever seen.
Did you see him?
Stupid, but, man, heroic.
Uh, Steve.
Uh, my name is Steve.
Uh, I was...
going to offer to buy
you a drink anyway.
Oh. She'll take a drink.
Hey, where do you
think you're going?
Uh...
Are you serious?
Where's his stamp?
Can you believe this joker?
If you were doing your job,
he wouldn't have had to.
No stamp, no reentry.
Is he for real?
Fat prick.
Fine. You're all barred.
For what?
Uh, drugs.
What?
He probably let them get away
'cause he knows them.
Shut up, skank.
Watch your mouth.
Or you're going to do what?
Okay. Okay, forget it.
Please, forget
it. Okay.
Come on, let's...
let's get a cab.
Thank you.
Come on.
Oh!
Oh, shit!
Watch it!
Hey, fucker!
Got a hummer today.
What's the law on sex with pets?
From Karen Jackson.
No way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She got a "C" in physics.
Needed a "B."
Or you, uh...
you wouldn't have waited
this long to tell me.
Oh, five hours.
Okay, you're full of shit.
Fuck you.
You ever have a knob job?
Once or twice.
Oh. Wow.
I didn't hear you
rushing to tell me.
Yeah, well.
I mean, I thought...
we tell each other everything.
Unless...
You got sucked off by a guy.
For instance.
No way. Lake Forest...
Lake Forest is not Chicago.
I'm not kidding, Steve.
You are dead if he ever lays
eyes on you. And I mean dead.
I nearly peed myself
when you hit him.
Well, I did a little.
Hey.
Hi.
Wait, how many of you guys
live here?
Not me, I'm one down.
But the old guy next door
died in March, which I guess
technically makes us
next-door neighbors.
So you're a nurse, Veronica?
Used to be.
Lying bitch.
She worked housekeeping
at Cook County,
bedpans and shit-sheets.
Fine. But I was offered
a place in the nursing school.
Fine. But it never happened.
They fired her for selling
medical supplies on eBay.
Will you shut up?
We don't even know him.
Steve.
Carl.
Lip.
Debbie.
How you doing, Debbie?
Nice watch.
Oh, thanks. Panerai.
What'd that set you back,
about six bills?
Plus, Ian.
Hey.
Hey, Debbie, why do
they call him "Lip"?
His real name's Philip.
Yo, Veronica!
You got my keys?
What's going on here?
This is Steve.
Decked the bouncer at
Purgatory to defend my honor.
My honor.
Yeah? Which bouncer?
Jimmy Clifton.
Jimmy Cli...
Well, Jesus, man,
put it there!
Respect!
Guy just stands there,
doesn't really do anything.
Yeah, you'll be his
third conviction.
Huh?
Third or fourth.
Fourth. Yeah.
I mean, after that much
practice, you would think
the man would have manslaughter
down by now.
No more fuck-ups like last time,
like leaving his dad
still breathing.
His dad.
Yeah. Five years,
over an '87 Monte Carlo with
200,000 miles on the odometer.
Fucking Monte Carlo!
Okay, come on, time for bed.
Up the wooden hill. Come on.
- It's not even midnight yet!
- Aw, man.
Come on, come on, go!
Already? Shut up.
Move, move, move, move, come on.
Yeah, let me take
one last look at you,
while you're still alive!
Here.
What, that's his?
Yeah. Well,
company car.
What kind of company?
Internet startup?
Earning what?
Couple mil a year.
High school dropout.
Got a job as a janitor
in this small tech firm.
Within a year, he owned it.
Made his first billion by 20.
Two Jags, controlling
interest in the Red Wings,
10,000 employees
kissing his ass.
"Yes, boss. No, boss."
Why shouldn't he
ride around in style?
Oh, you just made that up.
What...?
Why do you do that?
Your face!
How is that even funny?
It's not even funny...
How the fuck would I
know how much he earns,
you twisted dumb prick?
I'm not a dumb prick.
Kevin, I just met
the guy an hour ago.
Take back "dumb prick"!
Hi, nice to meet you.
I'm Veronica.
What's your pre-tax income?
Well, you sure didn't mind
watching him take his
shirt off, now, did you? Huh?
Not one bit.
In fact,
if you hadn't walked in,
Fiona and I were going to knock
him down and tag-team him.
Now I guess I'm stuck with you.
Hold on.
The Fiona tag-team,
is that an option?
'Cause you know, you can throw
that in the mix...
Anytime you like it, too...
I'll be doing it, all right...
All quiet up the "wooden hill"?
As quiet as it ever gets.
Straight answer: if I hadn't
busted my skull for you tonight,
would you have
looked at me twice?
Who's saying that
I looked twice?
Oh, you did, then.
I can't.
You know, 90% of the world's
problems are caused by
tiny words that come in pairs.
I mean, we're healthy and we're
happy, but when people ask,
we say...
"Not bad."
You know, the first time
that I saw you dancing,
about a month back at Crobar,
I was desperate
to buy you a drink.
You know, normally I'm shy,
so I told myself: I can't.
She won't. We wouldn't.
And then tonight
I see you there again.
All the indications
being that I'm getting...
...a second chance
to make a good impression.
Tell me to stop, and I'll stop.
Take it slower, slower,
slower, slower.
Slower.
Ah! Ah! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Almost... almost...
Fiona?
Shit. Shit, shit!
Fiona!
Shit.
Fiona, are you home?
Is Fiona in?
Uh... she's upstairs.
I'll go get her.
Hey.
Oh.
Yeah, uh, cops looking for you.
Stay here.
Liam.
Liam?
You... you...
I wouldn't put him
anywhere near a carpet
till his pants dry a bit.
Thanks, Tony.
See you, Fiona.
Who the hell is that?
My dad.
You just leave him
there all night?
He's never there when I get up.
So, uh, who's the little guy?
Liam?
Liam's my brother.
Rita.
Anne's school called.
She's sick.
Everything up to 204 is clean.
I should be back in
a couple of hours.
Raul won't care?
He smoked his lunch again.
He won't even know.
I'm making tamales tonight.
I'll drop off a dozen.
Okay.
Adios...
Oh, and take all the
toilet paper you need.
Okay.
You ready, big man?
Let's do it.
Come on. Here we go.
Kevin, did you miss me, dear?
A beer and a bump. And, uh...
Billy, you having one?
Have one!
Go away, Frank.
A pen, Mr. Beerkeep,
it is disability day.
Disability people haven't
caught up with you yet?
I thought they had some guy
following you around
with a camera.
They can follow me around
all they want to,
but they have to actually
catch me doing something.
What's with the crowd?
Layoff at the Chrysler plant.
You see?
That's the problem with working.
Too much instability. Stress!
What the fuck is this?
What's left, after I settled
out last month's bar tab.
Better start a new one, then.
Oh! And a round for all
my friends from the UAW.
Wow. Really?
Fuck no.
Hi.
Wondering what your schedule's
like on Friday.
Uh, I've got a...
I've got a party.
Want a chaperone?
You're not eligible.
Right. Chick thing?
You're not that desperate.
Wanting to see you again
is desperate?
No, feeling like you have
to... that's desperate.
Come on, you can
get laid anywhere.
Oh, so I'm only here for a fuck?
Never crossed your mind?
Just when you think
you've collared your dream girl,
her incontinent,
alcoholic father appears,
wrecks everything,
and she's blaming you?
Your dream girl?
We had drunken sex
on my kitchen floor.
Pretty sad.
Quit pretending
you don't even know me.
You weren't that drunk.
Hey, it's Phillip.
Hey, it's, uh,
Dead Man Walking.
Jimmy Clifton called today
looking for you.
No school?
Nah, I got some
teeth pulled today.
Wisdom teeth?
Sugar rot.
Ah.
You know, little known fact:
don't just chew your food
on one side,
'cause it can buckle your jaw,
which will buckle your hips
and affect your posture.
Oh, that's a fact?
Skeletal fact.
Lip.
Hey, um,
talk out of your ass
with that much conviction,
you end up needing
a much bigger toothbrush.
That's a anal fact.
Listen, thank you for trying
to get my purse back
and, uh, stuff.
But, uh...
Stuff?
I'm not looking.
Not right now.
Okay.
Is it all right if I leave
my number for when you might be?
Relax, okay?
No.
No, no, you're gonna like it.
What am I, what am I even
gonna say, all right?
You just got to keep
talking about science.
I don't know
anything about science.
Okay, so just read from
the table of elements.
Cerium, erbium, praseodymium.
Mrs. Jackson.
Oh!
Karen is thrilled with you.
She got an "A"
on her physics midterm!
Karen!
Honey, your little helper
is here.
This is my brother Ian.
Um, I'm out of plastic bags.
Why don't you leave your shoes
out here where they can breathe.
Sure.
Mix these two together...
Erbium, cerium,
praseodymium, magnesium...
You kids want some homemade
lime chicken chimichangas?
Um, no, no, thanks, Sheila.
I think we're fine.
No? All right.
Uh, praseodymium, uh,
magnesium, sulfur...
All right, I'm off to work.
Hey, fellas.
Where's Karen?
Uh, her room.
I think Google Earth
for a GPS reference
on where Isaac Newton was born.
Guess what I
made for your lunch.
Cornish game hen
with Asian pear.
No.
Wild salmon with baby carrots.
Kiss and I'll tell.
I'll find out what I got when
I open the damn box, all right?
All right, I'm late,
Karen, honey!
I guess I'll see you
in the morning.!
What's she hiding for?
What are you hiding...
...for?
Ah, sweet Jesus.
No...!
♪ I'm gonna get free,
I'm gonna get free ♪
♪ I'm gonna get free ♪
It's just a study group.
♪ She never loved me,
she never loved me ♪
♪ She never loved me ♪
He caught Lip!
♪ Come here, come here,
come here ♪
♪ I'll take your photo for you ♪
The farther you run,
the more I will kill you!
♪ Come here, come here,
come here ♪
♪ You know you really ought to ♪
♪ Come here, come here,
come here ♪
♪ Move out of California ♪
♪ Come here, come here,
come here ♪
♪ Move out of California! ♪
Really? An old lady
on the train?
Oh, yeah, yeah. The, um,
the doors were closing
on her walker, and Lip
barely got his foot in
in time to stop them from...
Ow!
Jesus, Fiona!
Can't remember whether
that's good or bad.
More likely, you two jumped
the turnstiles again
and he twisted it trying
to outrun the transit cops.
No, no! Always
elevate extremities!
Move before you give him
a fucking embolism.
You okay, Lip?
Sweetheart? Yeah, just please don't...
don't touch it.
Okay.
Wiggle your toes.
Go to my house,
top of the freezer.
Yeah.
Two ice packs.
Second cupboard above the sink.
Yeah.
Liquid ibuprofen,
freeze spray, ACE bandages.
Sure.
Shouldn't we get it X-rayed?
Fuck no.
He'll be in the E.R. forever,
and for what?
"Submetatarsal hematoma."
Thanks. Tell us something
we didn't know five hours ago.
Fuck off. My bedroom,
top of the TV.
Yeah.
Pack of smokes and a lighter.
Shit! I'm not here!
I'm not here!
What...?
You don't know us, Fiona!
Oh, what have you done?
What have you done?!
Can I get it through here,
is it better coming
around the back?
Samsung washer.
It's not me.
Gallagher, number 2119?
Yeah, but that's not ours.
Well, it's paid for.
You want me
to hook it up or not?
Where you going with those?
Uh, Veronica wants them.
Well, give me one.
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Everybody say oh, oh. ♪
Got it? Okay.
Ice and Advil.
And keep your weight off of it.
I thought you were broke.
That's what I said.
These were in the washer.
Steve?
Yeah.
No.
Uh-huh.
Who's Steve?
The other night.
No.
I know.
15 years!
I've done everything
in my control...
What did I say?!
What did I tell you?!
Sow and thou shall reap.
Well, she didn't
reap this from me,
I'll tell you that.
Reap what?
Wh-what are you reaping now?
Eddie, Eddie, Eddie.
Whatever it is, I'll try.
I'll-I'll...
I'll really try.
Mom, don't beg him.
If he can do this,
then the bastard's not worth it!
Hey, you honor thy father!
Get fucked!
Don't try blaming me for this!
You're your own worst enemy,
you two.
They say bad things happen
in three; they don't.
Twos! You two!
Insane.
Hello.
How much you pay for it?
I'm not telling you that.
It's a gift.
So you'd remember
the phone number,
which obviously worked.
Your washer's in the yard, okay?
We don't need it,
I don't want it.
So you got to come pick it up
before it starts rusting.
Oh, is it?
No.
Did the guy connect it?
Yes.
It's working okay?
It's not my favorite color.
Oh, so you've tried it.
Let me smell your breath.
Pork rinds?
No.
Um, those are mine.
See? Hey, since
when do pork rinds
actually come from a pig?
Ian, I am the one
that signs your check.
What's bad for him is
really bad for you.
If you are stupid enough
to start lying for him...
They're just corn chips
with fake hair,
fake corn even.
Last warning.
You get yourself to that mosque
so your dad stops
blaming me for the fact
that we're all going to hell.
And talk to your mother.
She won't talk to me.
I can't force her
to take her meds.
Well, I don't want
the cops dragging me
out of bed again at 4:00 a.m.
because she's out in the alley
yelling that the CIA
is stealing her trash.
But that happened, didn't it?
Once.
Four years ago, yes.
But now she's locked
in the basement,
making a helmet out of tinfoil.
Enough's enough!
Boys, come on, let's go.
Get in the car.
Now, I have to take
the boys to Cub Scouts
at the mosque before all
the carpets are taken.
She's your mother; get her
to take her Thorazine.
No, boys, no candy.
Come on, let's go.
We're gonna be late.
Let's go, go, go, go, go.
No more!
Come on, we're gonna be late.
Hurry up.
Just tell me you didn't go
and get some girl pregnant.
No worries.
He hates me.
You just,
you look more like mom
than any of the rest of us.
You probably scare him.
Yeah?
Yeah.
He ain't seen nothing yet.
Did he give you money
for the field trip?
I'll pay my own way, all right?
No, you won't.
You mustet sick of having
to think for everybody.
Well, at least I can.
Proves I'm wanted.
Jesus, Fiona, if all you want
is to be needed then,
congratulations.
You've got yourself
a job for life with is joker.
Hey. Get up.
Dad, get up.
Get up!
Good job, Fiona.
I don't know how I could
do this without you.
Thanks for all your hard work.
You're welcome, Dad.
My pleasure.
Hmm.
Good night, Daddy.
Hello.
If that wasn't bullshit,
what was I wearing?
Huh? First time you saw
me, if that wasn't a lie.
Black top with gold trim,
black shiny jeans,
thin shoes... straps...
Sandals.
With your hair pinned high.
Dangly gold earrings
that made me smile.
A big watch... too big,
so it slid up your arm.
But it looked great.
And you were dancing
next to red-haired girl
in a green dress.
Yeah, yeah, Jenna.
It was Jenna's birthday.
So you were...
you were watching her,
who's a lot better looking
than me.
You think so? Really?
Yeah, so how come you're
not stalking Jenna?
Because you... you think like
that and Jenna doesn't.
Jenna dances for an audience.
You dance like there's no one
else in the room.
Your life's not simple, Fiona,
and you can't stop it from
showing because you're no fake.
You're not lost,
you don't need finding.
This whole city belongs
to the Jennas,
but I'm sick of them.
I swear, Fiona, you're nothing
like anyone I've ever met.
You make me want to enjoy
my life again.
Are you there?
Fiona?
♪ ♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa
, whoa, whoa, wait.
What have I ever done to
anybody, never mind you,
that made me look unreliable?
Un... unreliable.
People like you are just way too
used to getting your own way.
And by people like me
you mean people like what?
Okay, wait, all right.
Yes-no. All you got to do
is agree or disagree.
He thinks the sun shines
out of his own ass.
Agree or disagree.
Agree.
He's overly generous
and that bugs me.
Agree.
Because I'm not used to get...
Actually very agree.
Because I'm not used
to getting spoiled.
Agree.
Okay.
So I lose respect
for guys like Steve
because people unlike Steve
or people diametrically
opposite to Steve
have always let me down.
So deciding that
he's overeducated
and has more money than sense
is somehow more socially
acceptable
than asking myself,
for instance,
why do the men I always date
treat me like shit?
Fuck you.
It's a question.
Either-or.
Agree.
He's had a easy life.
Definitely.
And you prefer a guy who's been
around the block a few times.
What if I do?
Say, D block
of a maximum security prison?
If he knew how to have fun,
yeah, sure.
Fiona, I can't help
my upbringing.
So how come it's me again
having to apologize for mine?
Who's asking you to?
We finished here, guys?
We're working on it.
You want to wait outside
while I pay the bill?
Sure.
He's on break?
Any second now.
All right.
♪ Well, I can't ♪
Good evening, sir.
Thanks.
♪ Outside of me, outside of me ♪
♪ No, I can't ♪
♪ Get the devil ♪
♪ Outside of me, outside of me ♪
♪ I don't get
all the good things ♪
I don't buy and sell cars.
I just sell them.
But the cars I sell
are mainly, uh, not mine.
♪ Outside of me, outside of me ♪
Still looking for fun, Fiona?
Go.
♪ Outside of me, outside of me ♪
♪ Outside of me,
outside of me ♪
♪ Outside of me, outside of me ♪
♪ Outside of me,
outside of me. ♪
Mom, we have to wear our shoes.
There's bits of glass
on the floor.
Maybe Lip could use a drink.
Oh, yes. Sorry, Lip.
That's okay.
I'm a-I'm a bit off today,
aren't I, Karen?
So, um, vodka?
I could do slow
comfortable screws.
Plenty of tequila.
I think I'm out of lime.
Um, definitely gin fizz.
Just a couple of Cokes, Mom.
And some beers.
Beers.
Great, Sheila. Thanks.
So what if your dad
comes back and sees me here?
He won't.
That's my fault?
He's been looking for
an excuse for months.
What kind of impression
did you get from my brother?
Ian?
Yeah.
He seems nice.
Right, but, uh...
did he pitch a tent?
Huh?
Did you make him hard?
Ever try to play
pool with a rope?
♪ Well, I have ♪
♪ Once or twice ♪
♪ Thought I left ♪
♪ My life... ♪
Yo, Kash?
♪ In a thousand years... ♪
♪ ♪
Yo, Kash!
All right, you stack the butter,
I'll do the snacks.
Oh, Jesus Christ, Lip.
Sorry, sorry, Kash.
Just, uh...
Thanks for the tools.
Any time.
Long as I get 'em back.
Right.
You must be joking.
What, y-you're fucking him?
Fuck.
He bought them for you,
didn't he?
Those shoes.
He's married!
With kids!
What else does he buy you, Ian?!
Stuff.
Now and again.
And you're happy with that?
What's that make you, huh?
A fucking kept boy at best.
Listen to me, stupid!
You think you know everything,
but you know shit!
Ask me what I've got him, huh?
Ask me!
CDs, dozens of CDs!
Stuff that he's never heard of,
stuff I think he might like,
'cause I want him to like
the same things that I do.
And a couple Sox tickets
for his birthday.
So what's that
make you, Lip, huh?
It makes you wrong, you
fucking smart asshole!
Now go back to Kash
and promise him
that you're not
gonna tell anybody
'cause he's done nothing
to be sorry for, nothing.
"Fake Muslim cheats on
white fundamentalist wife
with gutless gay boy."
Says more about White Sox fans
than it does for
the rest of us.
I think they're all asleep.
Gotcha!
Who's been eating my porridge?
Hey, Dad.
This is Steve.
Oh, no, no, no, we met before,
but you weren't exactly...
How much do you weigh?
Uh, I don't know.
That would fit me.
You can just ignore him.
And you? Move.
You know what?
I better let you get to bed.
Um, but thanks.
It was nice.
Yeah.
Nice, right?
Oh... no. Nah.
Who paid for this?
Hmm?
What the hell's he on?
Uh, he thinks
he bought Ecstasy,
but the only dealer he gets
credit from is a schizophrenic.
It's not a case
of whether or not
I agree.
It's a fact.
If I were a single
parent, we'd be on...
Aren't you a single parent?
"Yeah, but if I had tits..."
Yeah, but if I had tits, Steve,
they would double the money.
If you're a guy, they don't
want to fucking hear it.
I-I get it, Frank,
so it's,
"Prove you're looking
for work."
Oh, he's on disability.
Yeah? r what?
A tragedy really. I gave my life
to that company.
You worked there a week.
What happened?
Uh, slaughterhouse, poultry.
Dangerous work.
Doing my job, unsuspecting,
when out of nowhere
I am slammed in the ribs
by a headless flying chicken.
I was lucky... it
almost missed me.
And what do I get for my pain
and suffering?
Followed around
by a video camera!
Where's the trust, Steve?
The sacred bond
between employer and employee?
Gone, Steve.
It's gone.
How's a guy supposed to work,
hurt, with kids this age?
Hello? Thank you!
Yeah.
Exactly. Excellent!
Excellent.
And her mother, God rest
her soul, Dad, stop it!
'cause she better be dead, that bitch.
Cut it out!
Four... four-month-old baby.
14-year-old girl just
had her appendix out,
11-year-old Lip,
ten-year-old Ian,
a seven-year-old,
a five-year-old.
And, oh, and a Dodge Astro van!
No.
Calypso... Yes. Calypso blue.
What's the one thing
that we needed?
One word?
One thing?
Sterilization?
Continuity.
Con-tin-uity.
I... I... what could I...?
Oh, my God, I love this part.
♪ In the white room ♪
♪ You said no strings could... ♪
I... I...
what could I do, Steve?
I-I...
Disappear for three weeks?
I had a breakdown.
You went on a bender!
I-I had... fuck off...
nervous breakdown.
Dad, come on. Keys!
If this... Okay.
This is... Sorry.
I like him.
You got any idea Sorry.
What time it is?
It's Frank. He's...
Yo.
Frank, what did I tell you?!
Here we go.
Neighbors of Satan.
The day you start paying
rent around here, Frank,
like the rest of us, you can
play whatever shit you want.
But if you're gonna
pump up this time of night,
you're gonna pump out the
stuff that we like, okay?
♪ If you're not drunk,
ladies and gentlemen ♪
- ♪ Get ready to get fucked up! ♪
- Oh!
♪ Let's do it! ♪
Oh! Oh!
Uh. Uh.
♪ Lil' Jon ♪
♪ All the alcoholics,
where you? Let's go! ♪
Baby.
What? What? What?
♪ Hey! ♪
Uh, uh, uh.
Yep! Yep!
That's it.
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
Oh! Oh!
♪ Let's go, round two ♪
♪ Shots, shots, shots, shot. ♪
Watch it.
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Your dad made me follow you up.
Gave me a condom.
He must really like you.
He usually just gives
my boyfriends a dental dam.
Liam's in here somewhere.
Don't the kids wake up?
Would you?
Hey, Carl, you seen Ian?
Uh, gone when I woke up.
How can that be good for you?
Or-or-or... or that?
Yeah. You know what's
not funny, huh? Huh?
You.
Ever.
Anybody before Kash?
One.
Yeah? Who?
I'm not telling you, all right?
Name a single time
I've let you down.
It was a kid at school.
Yeah?
All right, I guess
it doesn't really matter
'cause, I mean,
he's long gone now anyways,
but, uh... Roger Spikey.
Roger Spikey?
Fucking donkey dick
The original beefmeister?
Or did he start that rumor?
Not a rumor.
Whoa, that was a bit gay.
What you just did there
with your eyebrows.
You want to watch that.
All right, fuck off, all right?
But seriously, like...
like up the ass?
Do you get used to that?
Can someone get used to that?
I mean... I mean,
the whole point
of the digestive system
is one-way traffic.
It just is.
What? What?!
"Just is."
Like, like, we're only given
our lungs
to freakin' smoke, right?
It's hot!
Don't drop it off.
Please don't drop it.
Please don't drop it!
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God.
The sausage is ready.
I haven't had
eggs in a while.
Somebody already
get the pancakes?
What's all this?
Debbie's the only person I know
wakes up earlier than I do,
and I told her
I never eat breakfast,
but she said
it's her favorite meal.
And I thought since
it's her birthday...
Whoa!
No, it's not!
It's not her birthday.
I never said it was.
I said, "I wished it was."
Ah, right, she said
she wished it was.
Sorry, Deb,
I totally misheard that.
Perforated eardrum
on the right.
15 minutes before school, tops.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ian, Lip, dishes soon
as you're done.
Debbie, Carl...
Yeah.
You've got to take
the trash out.
♪ We get high in back seats
of cars ♪
♪ We break into mobile homes ♪
♪ We go to sleep
to shake appeal ♪
♪ Never wake up on our own ♪
♪ We go out in stormy weather ♪
♪ We rarely practice discern ♪
♪ We make love
to "Some Weird Sin" ♪
♪ We seek out the taciturn ♪
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN