My name is Max William Easton.
I'm a British
intelligence officer.
You said it's done.
That whatever shady bullshit
you were involved in
in London is over.
Then you come running in
with a screwdriver
and you lock your children
in the bathroom!
Cooper and Toumi
have popped up in Beirut.
We need you to go in
and clean up the mess.
Find them. Deal with them.
Find Said.
Deal with him as well.
Ali Ardavan. Major financier of
the nuclear weapons program.
Our next target.
I found the source
of the breach.
Burnett Hanson.
Ardavan was a client there.
Harry is using Burnett Hanson
as a misdirect.
Burnett Hanson
is not the breach.
Harry is.
- How long have you been passing intelligence to Tehran?
- What, are you joking?
Where's Said?
Why did he kill Harry?
Said didn't kill Harry.
Harry's here. In Beirut.
Said, please!
We're giving you the
opportunity to make this right.
Isn't that what you'd want?
Why all of them?
Why not just Said?
It's what Langley wants.
Give me your hand.
Give me your fucking hand.
Slumped.
Two in the head.
Now get out of the car.
You're gonna disappear...
for good.
Anyone finds out you're alive,
we're both dead.
I was doing my job and now there's
a fucking kill order on me!
What did White tell you?
That I was the breach?
- And you believe that?
- You're alive, aren't you?
What are they covering up,
Said? You don't know, do you?
Find your way across the border
to Ashgabat. Lose yourself.
And you're just fine with this?
Don't make me regret
not killing you, Harry.
Said? Thank you.
Yes?
We've had
a complication in Tehran.
Care to expand?
One of our team has done
some digging on Ardavan.
He's followed the trail...
to Burnett Hanson.
- What?
- I've dealt with it.
Dealt with it, how?
He's down.
"He"?
Weren't there five of them
out there?
- Yes.
- How do you know they haven't talked to each other?
How do you know he hasn't
shared what he found out?
Are you willing
to take that risk, George...
stake your life on it?
No, I didn't think so.
They have to go.
All of them.
Do you have someone
who can clean up
or do you want me
to send one of mine?
No, no. I have someone.
- He's...
- I don't need to know.
Just make sure he's reliable
and you can control him.
You may find yourself
in another part of the world...
living in a beautiful house...
with a beautiful wife...
and you may ask yourself.
"How do I work this?"
"This is not
my beautiful house."
"This is not my beautiful wife."
You may ask yourself.
"Well..."
"how did I get here?"
Where's Harry? Is he alive?
Cooper!
Aargh!
My name is Max William Easton.
I'm a British
Intelligence officer.
My last ass...
- Max?
- Anna?
- It's not a good time now.
- I just wanted to hear your voice.
- How's your cold?
- What?
You said you were
coming down with a cold.
Erm... yeah,
it's... it's... it's fine.
I'm fine.
Well, you don't sound it.
- How's Beirut?
- Same as ever.
You've been there before?
Couple of times.
It's neutral ground
for old clients.
So did you find it... the money?
- Are you coming home?
- Soon. I promise.
Anna, what's up?
Nothing.
I have to go.
Lola just came down.
Can you put her on?
Lola?
She went to the bathroom.
I really have to go.
Okay.
I love you.
My last assignment was the
assassination of Dr. Marcus Reynolds...
the British government
scientist.
Four dead
Iranian nuclear scientists
in the last two weeks.
- Are you gonna tell me this was the Israelis?
- No, sir.
Since Stuxnet, we're more careful which
operations we share with them. This was us.
Sounds like mission creep.
Our brief was to contain Iran's
nuclear weapons program...
Your brief was to identify
and report back.
The administration's
current approach
is to safeguard
diplomatic stability with Iran.
Perhaps you'd like
to enlighten me
as to how
dead scientists turning up
on the streets of Iran
is furthering that aim?
Are we containing the regime,
or aren't we?
Excuse me?
I'm just not clear what the
objective is here, Mr. Chairman.
That makes two of us.
You're supposed to be
gathering credible intelligence
upon which this administration
can make an informed choice,
not wreaking havoc
in the Iranian capital.
We believed there to be
an active threat, sir.
Let me ask you, do you think the security
of the Republic should be underpinned
by something
more than your belief?
I'm minded to recommend
shutting this operation down.
Isn't Cyber Command a more effective way
of achieving our goals, in any case?
With respect, Mr. Chairman,
some of us believe in good
old-fashioned analogue tradecraft.
Boots on the ground.
Okay. If you wish us
to support further operations,
we need to move
beyond mere belief.
Is Tehran in breach of
the nuclear deal, or isn't it?
Cold hard facts,
not supposition,
are what is required here,
Ms. Jones.
Fucking suits.
Why do you always
have to antagonize them?
Do you think they would
talk to you like that?
They're a bunch of corpulent, flatulent
misogynists, John. Don't you dare defend them!
You heard what he said.
Go get more evidence.
Otherwise they're gonna
shut us down.
Give me some good news.
Cooper's off the table.
I knew you still had it in you.
Leyla?
She got picked up by police
in Petro Trad square.
Okay. We'll find out which
station she's been taken to.
I'll call the embassy and see
if we can get you in there.
What?
I want Harry's body repatriated.
That might be tricky, Max.
I'll do my best.
Well, if anyone can do it,
you can.
I think you've got more faith in me
than I have in myself these days.
Let's see how long that lasts.
Finish the job, Max.
And then go home, see your
family while you still can.
Olivia, if you're watching this,
you'll know what to do with it.
My name is Max William Easton.
News on Toumi?
Yes, we trawled police comms.
Leyla Toumi is being detained
at Tareek El-Tafilah Station,
the Mazraa quarter.
Alright, let's get Max in there.
I'll contact
his usual pickup point.
I want everybody on this.
Where's Walker?
I was under the command of
George White at The Section.
Not disturbing you, am I?
We need you out here.
What is it?
Nothing. Nothing.
Out here.
Since the Omar tip-off, Ardavan's
stepped up his security.
He flies to Beirut the third
Sunday of every month.
Hey, Said.
Salam, chetori?
Chetori? Salam.
- Where the hell have you been?
- Where's Harry?
Harry's dead.
London told us to pick up Omar,
interrogate him...
- And you didn't tell us?
- You're on Ardavan.
- We still need to know.
- You need to know what I decide to tell you.
We drove to Omar's apartment
and we waited for him.
Then he shows up and he walks
straight towards the car.
Pulls a gun.
And... shoots Harry in the head.
I'm sorry.
Alright, er...
did you get him?
Said, answer the fucking
question! Did you get Omar?
No. He got away.
I got out, I chased him...
but he had his exit planned.
- He's gone to ground.
- Well, then, we're screwed.
No, not yet.
We'll put the word out,
we'll find him.
Where's the body?
By the time
I returned to the car,
police were crawling
all over the place.
- So you just left it there?
- I didn't have a choice.
- I have to get it back.
- Leyla, he is gone!
His body is lying on some
fucking Tehran police slab!
Now, our orders are
we take out Omar and Ardavan
and then we get out of here.
Unless you're willing
to defy those orders?
- I should never have asked you to take...
- To what?
Spy on him?
Yeah, it wasn't like that.
Yeah?
So what was it like?
Why the constant questions?
- Special treatment?
- He was here because of me.
His father and I, we were friends,
and he walked out on him.
And you were a good substitute?
Apparently not.
I should have been there.
- This is not on you.
- No. No.
It's on you.
This whole fucking shambles
is on you.
- Leyla, if...
- Get...
Let's get this over with.?
And then I'm out.
And I never have to
look at you again.
Said turned on him.
He killed him.
Shukran.
As-Salamu Alaykum.
Alaykumu As-Salam.
Henry Adams.
Attaché to the British Embassy.
I'm here to collect Leyla Toumi. Can I
speak to your commanding officer, please?
- Yeah, have a seat.
- Thank you.
Sir.
I'm sorry, but there is
no one here by that name.
- She's here. I know she's here.
- No, sir, she's not.
- I literally just saw her...
- No... sir... you did not.
Do you have her?
She switched custody.
Handed over to the ISF.
Salim Baraket.
Baraket?
Baraket's no longer head of the ISF. He's
semi-retired. They're phasing out the old guard.
Except we never do
fucking retire, do we, George?
Baraket told me never to
set foot in Beirut again.
He knows I'm in town,
must have his dogs on me.
But now Baraket's got bait,
all he has to do is sit back
and wait for me to come to him.
That's a bad idea, Max.
You walk in there, with your history,
you know exactly what will happen.
Why, you got a better move?
Raid the vaults.
Find me something on him.
Make it good if you want me
to walk out again.
My name is Max William Easton.
I'm a British
Intelligence officer.
My last assignment was
the assassination of
Dr. Marcus Reynolds,
the British government scientist
and UN weapons inspector...
She just played the tape
for her brother.
What's the order?
Did you speak to White yet?
Just sit tight.
I'll call you back.
So we are looking into some compromising
intel on Baraket from 2005.
Did you find anything on
Baraket, anything we can use?
Good God, man, please tell me
you have something.
What the hell
have you been doing?
I'll get onto it right away,
sir.
Sorry.
I spoke to White.
This needs to be contained.
You're gonna need
a strong stomach for this one.
- Am I clear?
- And the children?
Nothing left behind.
For what it's worth, I don't think Dr.
Reynolds deserved to die...
if anyone ever does.
Max, Max, Max.
What are you doing here, Max?
I told you what would happen
if you ever came back.
The ISF's holding one of ours...
a British national, an asset.
The Section wants her back.
- How much?
- We both know you took her.
How much
are they prepared to pay?
Nothing.
Argh!
I warned you what would happen
if you returned.
If this was about me,
why did you take our asset?
Well, if you're after her,
means she's valuable.
A man's got a right
to make a living.?
So...
fish hooks, shark line,
gutting knives.
No reason we should
make this quick, right?
- I have a confession.
- I'm not a priest.
Left jacket pocket.
When I was stationed here,
I have to say,
you were a generous host.
You gave me access to your work,
maybe more than you knew.
Long time ago.
- Memory fades.
- Records remain.
21st July, 2005. The
government motorcade bombing.
Twenty people died,
including your Prime Minister.
Everyone pointed the finger
at Syria.
But you and I both know...
that couldn't have happened
without information
from insiders,
high up in
Lebanese intelligence.
What some people might call...
traitors.
The code is 1834. Take a look.
If the communiqués
don't bury you,
the Damascus meeting with Syrian intelligence
two days before the bomb certainly will.
If I don't
get out of here alive,
all of that gets leaked.
It's just a click of a button.
You once told me,
if you had to run,
you'd seek sanctuary in Syria.
Is that right?
Well, that doesn't seem like
such a safe haven now.
You're gonna take me
to Leyla Toumi.
It'll be returned to you
when you leave.
Sit down.
This man is here
to collect you. You are to be
released into his custody
and escorted back to the UK.
- This man?
- Yeah.
This man is here to kill me.
Leave me alone with him
and you'll be testifying
as to why a British citizen
was murdered on your watch.
I need to talk to you
about Harry.
Say what you like, I'm not
going anywhere with you.
"Love is a kind of warfare."
Your ring.
It's written on the inside.
It's Ovid. I know because
I had it engraved there.
I'm his father.
Would you give us a moment?
He obviously gave it to you.
His mother gave it to him.
And I gave it to her.
Long time ago.
So, take it back.
You're about to be processed
by the Ministry of the Int...
I heard what happened to Cooper.
Your doing?
So, who sent you?
White?
And you're to do
the same for me?
Maybe.
Or maybe things have changed.
White told me Harry was dead.
- Cooper told me he was alive.
- A dying man will say anything.
Is he alive?
I have every reason to tell you
what you want to hear...
it keeps me breathing.
But how can you know
I'm telling you the truth?
- Harry said you were dead.
- Yet here I am.
So, you might not be
who you say you are.
I guess you'll just have to
take that chance.
Because I suspect, like me,
you want answers too.
And because
maybe you love him too.
Leyla, you're on a list
no one has ever survived.
I am your one chance
to get off it.
Now, you can either trust me,
come with me,
or you trust them
and you stay here.
Your choice.
I'll be seeing you, Max.
Now, White told me
you all mutinied,
you all turned on each other.
That Said killed Harry.
Or had him killed.
- That's not what happened.
- No?
- Then, what happened?
- If I tell you, what then?
I don't know. The only thing
I'm absolutely certain of,
is what's gonna happen
if you don't.
What happened in Tehran, Leyla?
You with me, honey?
- Two blocks away.
- Fifty meters.
Omar's cab is passing me now.
- Lost him.
- I'm on it.
Why am I on the kill list?
What?
- I don't know, I swear!
- Why were you meeting Ardavan?
I went there to warn him.
He was never supposed to be
on the list.
But he was financing
the program.
That's what they told you.
- So what's the truth?
- Speak to Ardavan. He knows.
- Knows what?
- What they're really doing out here.
What you're really doing!
So where's Ardavan now?
I don't know.
I got him a passport.
And the name on the passport?
- Er... Darius... Darius Kazim!
- Where's he fucking gone, Omar?
We need to move!
So he is alive.
Where is he now?
He's after a man
called Ali Ardavan.
- So you don't know where he is?
- I know how to find him.
- How?
- Ardavan was on our list.
When Harry started looking into him,
he ended up with an order on himself.
- The Section ordered Harry dead?
- White.
Said couldn't carry it out.
- Does White know?
- No. Said lied to him. Took off.
If we find Ardavan,
we find Harry.
Will Daddy be home on Saturday?
I want him to take me
to the climbing wall.
He always takes me.
- Promise?
- Promis.
- Lola?
- Maman.
Walker...
Ssh. C'était un rêve.
Allez, viens. Shh-shh.
Viens avec moi. On y va.
I never sanctioned an op
in St. Michel.
I know you've got
an asset in play.
You start talking!
- She knows everything.
- Who knows what?
The wife. Max made a tape, an insurance
policy, about the Reynolds hit.
He named you.
The wife watched it.
- I was doing you a favor.
- What's the action?
- What's the fucking action?
- Wet work.
I sent Laurence in.
- You treacherous little prick.
- Because you keep me blind.
You always have, standing on
my fucking shoulders!
You're finished.
Get out of my sight.
Maman?
Laurence, this is George White.
Show's over. Abort.
I repeat, abort.
Who's furthest? No.
I've come to recognize the sound of a
single malt being poured 3,000 miles away.
I reactivated an old asset to
sort out this fiasco in Tehran.
I thought I had enough
leverage on him
and it turns out
he has the same on me.
On us, actually.
Go on.
The Marcus Reynolds job.
Tell me you have
this ring-fenced.
He made a confession, of sorts.
- It's a tape.
- Christ!
His wife has seen it.
So has her brother.
But they are contained?
Walker acted rashly,
without my authorization.
She got spooked.
She fled.
- I'm getting on a plane.
- No. You don't have to do that.
If this spreads,
I burn right along with you,
so forgive me if I don't trust
you to deal with it alone.
Subtitles by explosiveskull