(theme music playing)
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
(chimes ringing)
Andrea (voice echoing):
Do you have a girlfriend?
Nasir (voice echoing): No. Do you?
Andrea: Would that turn you on?
(both laugh)
Andrea: Now watch this.
(thuds)
Nasir: Whoa.
(Andrea laughs)
(metal clangs)
Nasir: What is that?
Andrea: This is the party you missed.
(inhales deeply)
(breathing heavily)
(thumping)
(creaking)
(both panting, moaning)
(panting, moaning)
(siren wailing)
Cass: We pulled him over on
65th Street driving a cab.
He was stone intox, like, crash-landed.
- You didn't administer?
- Didn't get the chance.
Call came in. We had to take him with us.
Couldn't have him driving
off in that condition.
I was running a check on
him when a call came in,
so we put him in the car and responded.
And then we found the girl.
Apparently, you vomited,
up there in the crime scene.
I was gagging, not puking.
That's nothing to be ashamed of.
No, no. I'm just saying, you know?
I just wanna be really clear about that,
'cause Bell's been going around
telling everybody I was puking.
At any point when you
had him in your custody,
did he say or do anything unusual?
No. He was as quiet as a mouse.
Let's go.
(handcuffs clicking)
All right. Let's go.
Don't worry, Pauline. I'll be there.
We'll settle up with the money after.
You're asthmatic, huh?
I used to have it when I was a kid.
I know it when I hear it.
You might grow out of it.
It's the same family as eczema,
only that just keeps getting worse.
But I'm not sure how it's gonna play.
- What?
- The asthma.
It might not be a bad thing.
Well, then again, a knife-wielding,
heavy-breathing sex brute
is not a pretty picture.
- Sex brute?
- Mm.
Okay. You need to understand
what happened here, all right?
We were at her place, we
were drinking. I don't drink.
And she started giving me all kinds...
I wanna tell you something,
and it's the most important thing
you'll ever hear in your entire life,
so don't not hear it.
Shut it!
They come up with their story,
we come up with ours.
The jury gets to decide
which they like best.
Now, the good news is
we get to hear what their story is first
before we have to tell them ours.
So we keep our mouths shut
until we know what they're doing.
You keep saying "story,"
like I'm making it up.
I want to tell you the truth.
You really, really don't. I don't
wanna be stuck with the truth.
Not until I have to be.
But you need to know what happened.
I need...
to be flexible.
I don't believe you're doing this now.
Safar: I'm not slowing anything down.
(horn honking)
Now you are.
I'm ready.
Oh, my purse.
Let's go.
(police radio chatter)
(line ringing)
- Man (on phone): Hello.
- Mr. Taylor?
Taylor: Who the fuck is this?
Detective Sergeant Dennis Box.
What'd she do now?
Excuse me?
Whatever it is, you can keep
her there. I'm not coming down.
Actually, that's exactly
what I need you to do.
I said no. I'm tired of it.
Mr. Taylor, I need to see you.
I'm gonna give you an address.
It's important.
You got a pen?
Thanks.
There's a cat around here somewhere.
If you're wondering why you're itching.
You reach next to kin?
Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
Stone: Box is the senior man here.
He got that way by
doing what he does well.
He rolls up his sleeves, delegates nothing,
takes all things personally.
He seemed okay to me.
You're a kid who's never set
foot in a police station, Naz.
How would you know that or anything?
Stone: I'm not saying
he's a... he's a bad cop.
On the contrary. He's very good.
And like all good cops,
he does you over just
inside the rules.
He's a talented oppressor...
a subtle beast.
♪ ♪
- What do you got, Dennis?
- Not yet.
- Off the record.
Word is, some Arab cabby is in custody.
What's his name?
Victim's name at least.
Okeydokey.
Eddie.
I don't wanna read anything
in the paper that's news to me.
And the dude that I called...
Oh, shit. I gotta go.
Where?
I have to be in court in half an hour,
or the judge will have my head.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Meanwhile, you just hang tight,
and... and what?
Don't talk to anybody.
Very good.
Wayne! Klein! Somebody let me out of here!
(bag unzipping)
(necklace tinkles)
(camera beeping)
(door opens)
(telephone ringing)
Hello?
No.
(telephone rings)
Hello?
Cornish.
Come.
Have a seat.
She's out there?
No.
Okay, I have two photos here that
might or might not be of your daughter.
Stepdaughter.
Stepdaughter. Fine.
I'd like you take a look at
these photos, and if they...
If it's her,
all you have to do is initial
the back, and we're done.
I don't have to look at the body?
No.
Okay.
I have to warn you,
pictures like this can
be kind of... gritty.
Gritty?
The subjects aren't
featured in their best light.
Would you like a glass of water?
Okay.
It's not her.
You sure?
Of course I'm sure. It's not her.
All right, Mr. Taylor. I understand.
Let's go take a look at the body itself.
Why?
Just to be sure. This way.
It's her.
Hey, Joey. How you doing?
(indistinct)
Excuse me, sir. I'm an attorney
and I'm late for my trial.
Excuse me. I'm an attorney
Yeah? Who is it? Get in line.
- Can I...
- No. Mm-mm.
Hi. We're here to see our son.
Is he a collar?
What? Yes. He called us.
Is he arrested, I'm asking.
Sorry, no... Yes, but it was a mistake.
Always is. Name?
Salim Khan.
(sighs)
No Salim Khan here.
No. My name is Salim, I'm sorry.
His is Nasir. He's our son.
Nasir. Nasir Khan.
Nope.
I don't understand. He called us.
He told us that he'd been arrested.
- Where?
- Here, in Manhattan.
Where in Manhattan?
Did he say?
No.
I don't know.
What did he do?
Someone was killed, and they think that...
It's crazy, but they think he did it.
Any homicides last night?
Some Muslim freak carved
up a girl in the 2-1.
You're in the wrong precinct.
This is the 1-2. You
gotta go to the 2-1.
Thank you.
All right. Good luck.
_
(alarm beeping)
You gotta be kidding me.
Arms out.
Shoes off.
I don't think you want me to do that.
- Is it contagious?
- No.
But still.
All right. Go on.
Next.
Woman: We'll notify you when
we're done with the decedent.
In the meantime, you need to choose
a state-licensed funeral home...
we are prohibited from recommending one...
and give us their contact information.
Since this is a criminal case,
the personal property of
the decedent will be held
until after trial and appeals, if any.
Sign here I've told you this
information and you understand it.
Box: Mr. Taylor?
I want to say I'm sorry.
I know it's hard coming down
here and doing what you just did.
I didn't want to see her.
Is that bad?
Completely understandable.
What happened?
That's what we're trying to figure out.
You can be helpful.
Maybe we could go sit somewhere
and talk, if that's all right.
Where's your tie?
I don't have a tie.
You cheated a lot of people, Mr. Gerwitz,
and you did it with a
smile and a handshake.
I'll never live it down, Judge.
And I'll never stop trying to make amends.
Eh, someone pass me a hankie.
I'm sentencing you to 18 months in
the Franklin Correctional Facility.
No, you will not be able to
work on your backhand there.
Eighteen months? That's all he get?
Gerwitz: I deserve it, Your Honor.
Judge: You bet you do. Next.
Talk to him.
Hi. We'd like to see our son.
His name is Nasir Khan.
The Khan kid, how old is he?
How should I know?
Twenty-three.
Can't do it then.
Why?
Five tokes over the line.
(indistinct)
Excuse me. What?
He's an adult.
We are not leaving.
Free country.
On the phone, you thought I was
calling to say she'd been arrested.
She's been in trouble before?
Mm-hmm.
What kind?
Drugs, mainly.
Which?
You name it.
Forgive me for asking this.
It's only because we're trying to
determine if she knew her attacker.
Was she involved in prostitution?
No.
When I say no, I think no.
You don't know for sure?
There's a lot I don't know about her.
Her mother and I weren't
married all that long.
Where's her mother?
She died last year, cancer.
Sorry to hear.
Her father?
Died when Andrea was like... 10.
He was quite a bit older than Evelyn...
my wife.
She go to school?
Not for a while.
Job?
Job? No.
Boyfriend?
Lots of those.
She ever mention the name Nasir Khan?
Goes by Naz.
Is that who did it?
- He's a suspect.
- In custody?
We're talking to him. Do you know him?
Naz?
No. Did she know him?
She may have just met him.
I'd like to show you some pictures.
I don't want to see those.
Not of her, of him.
In case you've seen him around.
He's an Arab?
No.
- He's not an Arab?
- No.
What are they?
Any of them look familiar?
No.
The house will be sealed for a while.
You got some place you can stay?
I don't live there.
It's Andrea's house, her mother's.
I live in Queens.
Three years to commence immediately
at the Cape Vincent Correctional Center.
You'll like it up there, Mr. G.
Right on the border with
Canada, no frets about humidity.
Next.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- Three years?
How come I can't get time like the Jew guy?
You want Jew time?
Do a Jew crime.
Next.
Thank you, Your Honor.
I think what he meant to say was...
- Next.
- Thank you. Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
♪ ♪
(indistinct conversation)
His parents?
Yeah. They wanted to see him.
I told them no dice, he's not a juvenile.
Who's that with him? Their attorney?
No. Stone. I have no idea who that is.
Stone?
- Can you believe it?
- How did that happen?
He was just here, as far
as I can tell, trolling.
Sergeant, they're his parents.
Where's the harm in
letting them see their son?
You want me to argue with you a
little, or just leave it at that?
Leave it at that.
♪ ♪
Your parents are here.
You don't want to see 'em?
♪ ♪
(door opens)
Sit down. No contact, please.
Can I give him this?
No.
This is all a mistake.
You have nothing to do
with what they're saying.
Listen, Baba, they're
not lying. I was there.
Where? How? Uh, doing what?
I was there with her,
and then I got... I got
sick, so I fell asleep.
When I woke up, she was dead.
So I ran away.
Why did you run away?
You didn't do anything.
- I was scared.
- Did you know this girl?
No, I only met her.
I... I didn't even know her name.
They said you had a knife
on you. You didn't, right?
I did.
Salim (over monitor): What knife?
Nasir: It was there. I took it.
Salim: Why?
Nasir: I don't know.
I don't know what
happened. I can't remember.
I... But I know I didn't
do anything to hurt her.
I swear.
Baba, it's me.
Okay, there you are, huh?
Did you tell them these
things that you're telling us?
(speaking in foreign language) _
_
Why isn't he here?
Well, he said he'd be right back.
Is our time up?
No.
I just wanted to make
sure you're okay in here.
Thank you for letting us see him.
May I please give him this?
Ammi.
I'm sorry, no.
Rules.
But a mother's prayers never hurt anyone.
He seems like a nice man.
He's a subtle beast.
A what?
Stone: Frappucino would be
nice if anyone's going out.
(Stone groans)
How's the feet?
Embarrassing. Thanks for asking.
How's the investigation?
Clearer by the minute.
Oh, I doubt that.
I wanna talk to the boy again.
And I wanna live forever.
I had to ask.
You did.
But did you before?
Box: Didn't have to before.
You hadn't swooped down on him yet.
"Swooped"?
That's a strong word.
I feel for him.
I'm sure you do.
I do. I let him talk to
his distraught parents.
Yeah? You tape it?
This is a little out of
your league, isn't it, John?
Bloomberg would've been
appalled by the snacks here.
You're not gonna get rich off of
it, if that's what you're thinking.
It's gonna be the
shortest trial in history.
Yeah? Is that why you haven't charged him?
Doesn't feel right for it, does he?
Something in your gut
isn't liking him for this,
and you can't bring
yourself to pull the switch.
Mr. and Mrs. Khan?
I'm John Stone, your son's attorney.
- Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
Would you like one?
No, thank you.
How about you?
Hmm.
Come on. We'll talk a little bit over here.
I don't know what they have
and what they don't have,
but if they had what they
needed, he'd be charged by now,
and he hasn't been.
Other than possession of the knife.
They can hold him on that.
But this is good. It means
they're not sure about the rest.
In any case, there's nothing
you can do sitting here waiting.
You should go home. I'll let you
know the minute something changes.
You understand what I just said?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Of course.
But he didn't do this.
Of course he didn't.
I...
will call you.
I told you not to talk to anybody.
I didn't, only to my parents.
I said anybody.
While you were talking to them,
you know who was listening in,
which he can do legally,
just not with me and you?
Box.
I... I didn't say anything.
Sure you did. You had a
conversation. You conversed.
And I won't know exactly what you
said until it shows up in court.
I... I said I didn't do it.
I don't understand how
the truth can hurt me.
Again with this. Christ!
Okay, Naz, you're the jury.
Run the truth by yourself.
Who killed this girl?
Someone else?
Or the guy with blood on him,
his fingerprints on everything,
and the murder weapon in his pocket?
The truth can go to hell
because it doesn't help you.
And if you can't get that
through your head, right now,
you can forget about the rest of your life.
You think I did it.
I don't think anything.
Man: Khan? What is that, Arabic?
Box: Pakistani.
- What is he saying?
- He didn't do it.
- Do what?
- Exactly.
You call the DA yet?
You're gonna have to soon.
And I will.
Well, this is a... This is a lock?
Prints, weapons, witnesses. We got it all.
- Nonetheless...
- I know.
A confession would be deadly.
(door slams)
(panting)
(siren wailing)
It's an ambulance siren, John.
If you hurry, you could probably catch it.
(chuckles) Hey.
How'd it work out with that
IAD investigation, Lucas?
You still carrying a gun?
Anybody say you could drink our coffee?
Is that what this is?
Hey, how's it going with that Arab kid?
You sure he's lowlife enough for you?
You know, Raymond, someday
when you got the time,
I'd love you to teach me that choke
hold you used on the Ortega kid.
Raymond: I can show you now if you want.
We can go outside.
(snoring)
Box: Your parents are nice people.
I'm gonna try and expedite,
get that cab back to your
father as soon as possible.
I know how important that is.
We're both working men.
Your lawyer tell you not
to talk to me anymore?
Not even casually?
He ask you how it happened?
He didn't?
It doesn't surprise me.
Makes no difference to him,
or to his job.
And you are a job to
him, Naz, make no mistake.
He's gonna make money off this,
your parents' money.
The longer it takes, the more he makes.
They can't afford that, can they?
You know where he is right now?
Downstairs drinking coffee with the
detectives, breaking each others' balls.
Because the fact is,
it's a big club, the
criminal justice system.
We can't exist without
each other, and we know it.
But I'm not a member of that club.
I don't like the idea of a double life.
My job is to get to the truth.
So I don't see why I should socialize
with anyone trying to
stop me from doing that.
That's why I'm up here with you...
instead of drinking
coffee down there with him.
You shouldn't be doing this, should you?
- What?
- Talking to me without him here.
You know, I really love what I do, Naz.
But every once in a
while, I get frustrated.
I abide by the rules, though, I do.
So, yeah,
that's right. You don't
have to talk to me...
unless you want to.
You know...
this is the most
open-and-shut case I have had
in a very long time.
Everything is pointing to you.
But there's something I'm just not getting.
Something I am struggling
with here because...
what I see before me is a nice kid
from a good, hardworking family,
loving mother and father...
on what has got to be
the worst day of his life.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What am I not seeing, Nasir?
(inhaler hisses)
Explain to me what I'm not understanding.
It looks like I killed her, I know that.
Yeah, that's how it looks.
But it's not that simple, is it?
Because we both know this isn't you.
You didn't get out of bed yesterday
saying to yourself, "I'm
gonna murder someone tonight."
What you were thinking was "I
hope I pass the economics test.
I hope my mother gets off my
back for this, that, the other."
And things just got out of hand.
Sex, drugs, alcohol.
Some girl. You didn't mean
to do it, things happen.
Please stop.
If I'm off, tell me how I'm off.
Help me, help you, Naz. We'll
never get another chance.
You know, there's something
any experienced detective knows,
and it's something I've personally
witnessed hundreds of times
in the last 30 years.
Christian, Jew, Muslim, what have you.
There's an immense sense of relief
when they finally just let
go and tell someone the truth.
It's like...
finding God.
I'm not talking to you anymore.
_
(rap music playing)
(telephone ringing)
2-1.
Okay.
Transport's here.
Here you go.
Now, put these on.
Stone: Just remember,
don't talk to anybody.
These people, these men and
women, this is their life.
This is what they do every single day.
You're at a massive disadvantage here.
Luckily, you have me.
(police radio chatter)
(distant siren wailing)
(engine starts)
(rap music playing)
(thunder rumbling)
(engine starts)
(opera music playing)
(rap music playing)
(Muzak playing over PA)
(muffled voices arguing)
- _
- (rap music playing)
(woman singing ballad in foreign language)
(rap music playing)
(police radio chatter)
Let's go.
Come on.
(thunder rumbling)
(door creaks, slams)
(keys jingling)
(distant prisoners shouting)
Man: And dispense with lighters,
matches, cigarettes in the trash.
Whatever else in your
pockets, in the trays.
Anybody still got some weed
or other substance on 'em,
put it in the donation
box. No foul, no harm.
You keep it, it's a new offense.
Is this okay?
You're good. Go.
Come on. Hands up, spread your legs.
All right, turn around.
How is things in Cambridge?
What?
This is not mine.
Go ahead.
Hands up. You know the routine.
Turn around. You're good.
Go. Next.
Face the wall. Hands up.
(wand squealing, beeping)
It's a pin in my leg, man.
Yeah, we'll see soon enough. The chair.
Next.
You want to take that cell phone
out of your ass, or you want me to?
Next.
Why don't you do it?
Pants down, bend over.
Turn around.
Step to your right. Next.
Face against the wall.
Hands up, spread your legs.
Turn around.
Disposable.
Yeah, I'll say.
Step to your right. Next.
What are you looking at?
Woman: You are waiting arraignment.
I'm here every day,
So this is my place, and I like it neat.
You throw up on my floor, you clean it up.
Sweet dreams.
(retching)
I need a doctor.
(whimpering)
Man: I'm sick.
Somebody...
Shut up.
I'm dying. (cries)
I need help.
(shouts) Shut the fuck up!
(retching)
Man: Please,
somebody.
I'm sick.
Shut the fuck up!
(sobbing loudly)
(thudding)
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
(thudding)
(sobbing loudly)
(woman singing ballad in foreign language)
(sighs)
East Side is much busier
than the Upper West Side,
at least for now.
(broadcast continues indistinctly)
(sighs)
- Can I get some coffee?
- No.
Fine. I'll get it by school.
How's, uh, Thurgood Marshall?
I'm not doing my report on him.
I changed my mind.
Why?
I don't know.
It's boring.
Really?
(doorbell rings)
Yeah.
I'm doing Jamie Foxx instead.
(chuckles)
- Hey.
You ready?
Yeah. I'll get my stuff.
Is that coffee?
No.
It's getting worse.
Yeah, I'm gonna go see, uh, someone else.
What's up with the tie?
You hear about that zing on 87th Street?
A girl was murdered.
They made an arrest...
and...
You're kidding me.
No.
How'd you do that?
Right time, right place.
You sure you can handle
something like that?
I'm just saying. That's...
you know, big.
Hey.
See you, man.
Okay, see you.
Johnny, I didn't mean that
to sound like it sounded.
Yeah, I know.
Bye, Dad.
Can you at least do Denzel?
He's taken.
Jamie Foxx.
♪ ♪
(snoring)
(thunder rumbling)
(sniffles)
♪ ♪
Anyone in custody yet?
Yeah, but I don't know anything about him.
What's the scene like?
I don't know. I haven't been out there.
We just got the call.
This is making no sense.
'Cause it's Detective Box.
Oh.
Mrs. Weiss, jury's back in five.
Tell Dennis, I'd like to see him.
When?
Yesterday.
(opera music playing)
So, what do we got?
Beer bottle, water bottle, gas
station receipt, parking ticket.
I got blood above the
driver's door and handle,
more here on the front
seat and the steering wheel.
The cab's a guilty picture postcard.
Check this guy out.
Box: This would be Ali,
the first Imam of Islam.
Yeah? Where's he now?
Nowhere.
He was assassinated in the 7th century.
The Shias see him as the
rightful heir of Muhammad,
the Sunnis don't, and therein lies the...
you know?
What were you, Box, in counter-terrorism?
I like to read.
Yeah, but that shit?
_
Do you see "arraignment"?
(knocking on door)
Mr. Khan, how are you?
I'm going crazy.
I understand. I'm a father myself.
And I'm sorry to intrude.
This is a court order allowing
us to search the house.
For what?
May we come in?
(door opens)
Mrs. Khan, nice to see you.
Sorry to disturb.
(floorboards creaking)
(chandelier glass rattling)
What were you doing up there?
Laundry.
We're going to have to take that one, too.
That one is not Nasir's.
That... That one is Nasir's.
This is ours. We need it.
We need them all, sorry.
Rodriguez.
(cell door opens)
Stone: Mr. Khan, this is John.
Your son's attorney.
His arraignment's gonna be at
the next session later today.
100 Center Street, Court
2 on the ground floor.
Hang on a second.
Or you can have it in trade.
Let me tell you something
about me, Pauline.
I have the strength of ten.
You know why?
Because my heart is pure.
Yeah, just not your feet.
I know a remedy for that.
I've heard them all before.
- Thank you.
- Any time.
Good luck to you.
You still there?
Because they can.
Well, you just have to get a new computer.
Just hang on a second.
What is it, your remedy?
A machete.
(chuckles) This fucking guy over here.
Yeah.
Box: Prints put them in the cab.
Parking ticket puts the cab at the scene.
Prints, witnesses, and his own
statements put him in the scene.
Harry's got the blade
to within half an inch,
the same as the knife in
his jacket pocket, bloodied.
And all this without a phone call.
I called. Hence, I'm here.
Today. Not the night of.
I didn't want some kid two years out
of John Jay fucking up my crime scene.
I'll be happy to lead
throughout. May we proceed?
Of course.
What's he like?
College kid, no record,
but hey, it's murder.
You don't have to have
done it before to do it.
What else?
For what it's worth, he's Muslim.
Nation of Islam or...
Real one. As in, from Queens. Pakistani.
I wanna wait on the blood.
I want a house in Montauk. Come on, Helen.
You sure he did it?
No question.
You blinked.
I did not blink.
Dennis, honey, you did.
I've been up 56 hours.
So how am I gonna lose it?
You're not.
Woman: If I call your name, line up.
Jackson.
Ortiz, F.
Ortiz, W.
Khan.
Hightower.
Cruz.
Williams.
Bail set at 500.
That's a 100 an 8-ball. Sound fair?
Jimmy, next time, tell your client
to leave his tomahawk at home.
Where'd you have to go for this one?
Paris.
You're kidding me.
Toccoa fucking Georgia.
(indistinct conversation)
Judge: Next.
43562, Nasir Khan.
Which one of you is him?
Mm-hmm.
(scanner beeps)
Hey.
You waived the reading of the
rights, but not the rights themselves.
Ah. So waived.
You're Mr. Khan?
Yes, sir.
Well, according to the complaint,
you're charged with possession of a weapon,
possession of a weapon for deadly purpose,
resisting arrest,
aggravated sexual assault,
and murder in the first degree.
Fuck me.
How do you plead?
I didn't do it.
Mr. Khan, this court is
kind of like "Jeopardy."
I ask a question,
the answer has to be in the right phrasing.
He means to say "not guilty," Your Honor.
Is that what you mean to say, Mr. Khan?
Yes.
Can you say it?
Not guilty.
Thank you.
Your Honor, if we can be heard on bail.
The defendant has extensive
family roots in Pakistan,
and given the fact he's charged with
murder based on overwhelming evidence,
and facing a sentence of life,
we consider him a serious
flight risk and request remand.
John?
Your Honor, my client
was born in this country.
Whatever so-called
roots he has in Pakistan,
he's got far deeper roots in
his community here in Queens.
In fact, he's never been to Pakistan
or anywhere else outside
New York State in his life.
He's a young man from a
solid working-class family.
A college student, no priors.
He's not a danger to himself
or others, and is, in fact,
desperate to prove his
innocence in a courtroom,
and so not a flight risk.
And despite the DA's
confidence in the evidence,
there are no witnesses to the actual crime.
Which is to say, the evidence
against him is purely circumstantial.
It's not purely circumstantial, Your Honor,
All of which is to say, we request a bail
commensurate with his
family's ability to raise it.
Your Honor, this was a
particularly vicious crime.
CJA, Your Honor, recommends ROR.
I don't care what CJA says.
It's a waste of taxpayer's money, honestly.
Now you both know I usually like
to split the baby in terms of bail,
but I'm going with Mr. McPherson on this
one due to the severity of the charges.
That's all they are, Your
Honor, charges. Not facts.
You can take it up at a later
date if the circumstances change,
but I'm denying bail.
Your client's hereby
remanded to await prosecution.
Don't talk to anybody.
Where am I going?
John.
Just curious. Friend of the
family, or right place, right time?
Right place, right time.
Right place, right time. Good for you.
Yeah.
Next.
Bailiff: 43563, Hightower.
That's what I expected, okay?
Judge: Mr. Hightower, we meet again.
(door buzzing)
♪ ♪
_
Man: Let's go!
(door slams)
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
♪ ♪