Harbormaster, summer bay.
Is there a place for us
to come in and try to tie up?
All right. Thank you.
Back in 60.
We come in to offload some
of this crab and finish the
season up here, I hope.
It's looking pretty
gnarly out.
We've got some big seas here,
but I don't think I've ever...
Had more desire to finish
the season than I do
this season.
♪ legendary
I'll be legendary ♪
it's been a rough year
for a lot of us.
♪ necessary, yeah
saw my death, it's scary ♪
we have had
just the worst weather.
♪ nah, tell the reaper
I ain't ready ♪
♪ I'ma fight him
he ain't scary ♪
♪ I'm a beast
and in the belly ♪
being pushed by the ice
coming down on the gear.
♪ I can see my death
from here ♪
we had two of the major
canneries
completely shut down.
♪ the end is near
offend your fears ♪
and we lost some great guys.
I cannot wait for this season
to be over.
♪ legendary
I'll be legendary ♪
♪ necessary, yeah
saw my death, it's scary ♪
♪ ancestors dead already ♪
I wanna pray that we get
the gear back.
Let it go.
♪ yeah, death hereditary
won't stop unless I'm buried ♪
♪ and I ain't ever ready, uh ♪
[man] watch out!
Oh *bleep*.
Hang on! *bleep*
[screaming]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
we're getting close
to the finish line.
Kind of down to the wire.
Two of the plants
were already shut down.
If the main one closes down,
we're in big trouble.
[narrator] ten weeks
into the 2021 winter season.
[female reporter] in our top
story of the week,
another plant
in alaska shut down.
[narrator] half of all major
opilio crab canaries
suspend operations
following outbreaks
of covid-19, leaving
just two remaining.
It's kind of weird.
I'm starting to see all sorts
of funky marks on the radar
here, josh.
Oh *bleep* is that?
Ice?
[narrator] but now an old foe
descends from the north.
Those aren't boats.
-None of this is boats.
-I'm pretty sure
that's ice, pal.
[narrator] a 275,000
square mile arctic ice pack
surges south at an alarming
30 miles per day,
threatening to engulf
the crab grounds.
-Is this a risk?
-Oh, my god, yeah.
This is a huge risk.
Going over. Going over.
Every day that ice is getting
more and more...
Pots will be underneath
the ice floe, we won't be able
to get to them and
we lose them.
[narrator] with a frozen
menace capable of severing
or dragging pot lines
rendering everything
it touches unfishable...
I want to take these pots
all the way up north.
We've got everything
on the line.
[narrator] the fleet must
bring home their supersized
$250 million quota.
[man] I came back out
to help him out
so they succeed.
We all gotta work together.
[narrator] before the last
canneries close, or
the ice freezes them out.
Thing about this ice fog,
it looks like it's right there
and then it's not.
It seems like it's just
getting further and
further away,
then all of a sudden,
you're in it.
[narrator] thirteen miles
south of the russian line,
on the wizard.
[hammering]
and the other thing is
you know, these white caps,
it looks like you start seeing
like an ice mirage.
You know, every white cap
looks like a floe of ice.
Oh, you know what?
I don't think that's
a ice mirage there.
No, that's no ice mirage.
That's ice.
Yes.
[narrator] approaching the
southern edge of the ice pack,
captains keith
and monte colburn search
for their northern gear
before the floes
freeze them out.
Look at this ice, man.
Wow.
Come on buoy. Show up.
This is pretty gnarly.
That's like eight-inch thick
ice right there.
I'm not seeing *bleep*.
Dead ahead.
[man speaking indistinctly]
all right, guys, remember,
you gotta pull it off
the bottom slow, man.
Roger.
Now I wonder if there's
any critters in this.
Yeah. Good question.
I hope so.
Steady!
That's got crab in it.
That's got a *bleep* load
of crab in it.
Okay, right on.
Count it up. Count it up.
Four three zero.
Four three zero, I'm guessing
like 99% going in
the tank, right?
Yeah, roger. That was
nice stuff.
Yeah, roger that.
That's *bleep* gone.
*bleep*
damn it.
Yeah, he started
full speed. It broke off.
Roger.
Not only have we lost
at least one pot to
the ice so far but then
that happens.
-*bleep* could be anywhere.
-Yeah.
Let's just get them back, man.
No pots left behind.
It's only gonna get worse.
[narrator]
twenty miles southwest...
On the cornelia marie.
Right now, two options
to deliver.
Saint paul and king cove.
So only eight miles
from the russian border,
right here.
Close to the ice pack. We're
playing the ice age game now,
it'll be interesting to see
if we still have
crab here or not.
Don't know how it's going
to play out. We'll see
with the first pot.
[narrator] looking to plunder
their hotspot in the cold
of the north,
captains josh harris
and casey mcmanus
try to fill their final
60,000 pounds
before the frozen threat
can wreak havoc on their gear.
*bleep* did they go?
-Is that your side?
-I'm not seeing anything.
Trying to find
our first pot here.
So far, it ain't going
so well.
It's not right here
where it should be.
Oh!
-No.
-No. I don't see *bleep*.
*bleep*
ice.
Got down this far.
We have a real
problem on our hands.
That ice will freeze into
the buoys.
And it'll pull that pot
along the bottom.
And then at some point,
the ice will go back
and it'll let go.
So sometimes you're searching
for something could be 10, 15,
20 miles away
depending on how far
the ice moved.
Yeah, we'll start running
north over and over
two tenths to quarter mile.
Turn and go south,
run down the full length
and the strings and then some.
The whole time you got two
guys scanning
the wheelhouse.
We need to find these
real bad.
Real, real bad.
Gonna be a long night.
Long night.
A lot of eyeballs.
[water splashing]
[narrator]
twenty eight miles south...
On the northwestern.
Yeah, man.
We didn't come all the way up
here just to get hundreds.
[sighs]
oh boy, oh, boy, oh boy.
I'm trying to stay
optimistic, but
the numbers aren't here.
You know, if we don't have
a plant to deliver to,
then we're putting crab on
and we got no place to go.
So, we're gonna hit
the nitrous oxide,
end it with a banger.
I think they're moving,
they're bumping up and over,
northeast.
We want to try
to get on something
and get busy.
Although we did spread
this gear out to the west.
But we don't know
if there is crab there.
[narrator] with the clock
ticking, captain sig hansen
and daughter mandy
weigh two options.
Follow the best sign of life
and head to the northeast
or check their prospect pots
to the northwest.
[water splashing]
I'm worried about that ice
that's looming overhead.
You're limited in time
when you're fishing
this far north.
[narrator] and with 65,000
pounds still to catch,
the captain must choose.
West or east.
[captain sig] uh...
Jake is in the area.
South of us here.
I mean, realistically
if we can work together
we can cut down our time
and we can find the crab
that much faster.
[narrator] 48 miles south.
[waves splashing]
-[captain sig] you got me?
-Sig.
How goes it?
Um, down here, um,
[exclaiming]
well, we got some
prospect gear,
by the time you get up here,
it'll have a little soak.
No guarantee but it's worth
a look, so,
you want to pull those?
I mean that'll buy me
a little time too.
[jake] I've had rough history
with sig.
He makes me run around for him
to do his bidding
and he's been doing that to me
my whole *bleep* career.
I'm worried about
history repeating itself.
[captain sig] jake? Hello?
Where, where you at?
[narrator] on the saga.
[captain sig] well, we got
some prospect gear.
No guarantee
but it's worth a look,
so, you want to pull those?
I mean that'll buy me
a little time too.
Jake? Hello?
Where, where you at?
-What is going on?
-[thuds]
[captain sig] yeah, hello.
Yeah, there's nothing
down here,
I'm just going backwards.
I'm in.
I know it's a long way up here
but it'll be worth your risk.
So, I'll get you
those positions.
Okay. I'll be around.
[captain sig] well,
that might work,
don't you think?
Goes to show, see, guys know
how to work together
when we have to.
Up a little farther,
northeast.
- Set her when you're ready.
-Oh, yeah.
[thuds]
[jake] I don't want to work
with anybody else.
- But I don't have
any other choice.
-[thuds]
just praying to god it works.
I need the season to be over.
[narrator] 44 miles northwest,
on the time bandit.
Andy.
Just tell me.
Am I screwed
or is he gonna come get me?
That sucks.
I'll be able to fish
a few more days
and then retreat.
Okay, thank you so much.
We're out.
We've got trouble coming.
We're gonna be busy boys.
-Are we ready, guys?
-[worker] yeah.
Roger.
[narrator] his tanks
already stuffed
with northern opilio crab...
I'mma go down
in pervanence canyon.
The ice just doesn't
like the canyons.
The currents too strong there.
It's hard for it to freeze
'cause it's too deep.
I'm hoping.
[narrator] captain jonathan
hillstrand counts on one last
deep water set,
before the clock runs out
and the ice pack
chases him south.
Yeah baby.
We've got about 72 hours to
get as many crabs we can
and stack up
and get out of here.
Yeah.
[clattering]
aww, what the *bleep*?
Yeah, you never stick
nothing in that *bleep* hopper
except bait.
Jeepers. That
could've been bad.
We know you're gonna
*bleep* up that one,
you're gonna *bleep* chop
that *bleep* up by hand.
- Oh, yeah.
-All right?
Let's go.
I need to harvest some crab
as quick as I can.
We can't stop now. I mean,
ice is like a big bully
in high school,
you remember the guy
that stole your lunch money
that ate your lunch.
I kicked the bully
right in the nuts.
I don't think
there is much
I can do to the ice.
[narrator] 74 miles northeast.
[bill] last trip.
Be interesting to see
what we end up with.
I hope it's a bunch.
[narrator] on the summer bay.
[bill] b ack out
on the grounds.
We had better fishing
at this end.
Right where this red mark is,
it's got seven,
eight days on it.
[narrator] racing the ice to
the north and cannery closures
to the south.
Captain wild bill wichrowski
bets that his town soak will
be the ticket to full tanks
and a quick offload.
I'm hopin' there's still
enough of them little devils
down there
to fill up the pot.
Look at these damn things.
It's solid.
Solid effort.
[landon] hold on.
*bleep*
not what we're looking for.
When they first came up
over the rail, I thought
we're in them,
this is gonna be it.
Too small.
Not many keepers at all.
We just gotta start
from square one.
Female.
That sucks.
[bill] this one looks
even worse.
Not so good.
[bill] looks good
for the future.
I'd rather live in the present
right now.
-Hey...
-Woah, what the *bleep*
what's that?
-Nice and easy. Nice and easy,
nice and easy.
-Take it slow.
It looks like when we were
setting one of those shots
got wrapped up.
[grunting]
do not hurt yourself,
I can't afford somebody
*bleep* losing a hand.
Back it out a little.
Back it out a little, now,
cut that cord, yeah.
Woah, woah, woah.
Hang on, hang on.
Woah, what, who,
why would you cut something?
This line back here.
I'm gonna need a little help.
Watch your feet.
Take it off, take it off.
Oh, my god, don't...
You're losing it,
whatever is in there,
you're losing it.
Watch out.
Woah, woah, watch out.
Out of the block,
out of the block.
Everybody stay clear
- of the *bleep* line.
-[screams]
[narrator] on the summer bay.
Watch out, woah, woah,
woah, watch out.
Out of the block,
out of the block.
Everybody stay clear
- of the *bleep* line.
-[screams]
*bleep*
we're lucky nobody
got hurt right there,
went over the side.
Another high stress situation.
We had them.
They were right there
for the taking.
Man.
[narrator] a rookie mistake
by experienced deck hands
cost wild bill $4000.
In equipment and crab.
*bleep*
they wash down, they're gone.
[landon] we gotta start over.
Yeah. This trip's starting up
*bleep* awesome.
[landon] what next?
[narrator] forty-five
miles west,
on the saga.
Tell me the spots, jake.
Six pots.
If there is crab
I can set some pots in.
He's helping me get situated
and then in return,
he is getting any information
that I get.
[narrator] recruited by sig
to determine
if there is enough crab
in the northwest
for the two boat team,
captain jake prepares to haul
three of his former men
towards prospect pots.
All right. Here it goes.
Yeah, baby. Oh, yeah.
Kinda nerve-racking
partnering with my mentor but,
much as sig at times,
has been an enemy.
He's the only one I trust.
[man] coming up.
[man] wow!
Okay. Okay... Right.
That pot is not bad.
-[man 1] roll it up, buddy.
-[man 2] roll it up!
[man 2] whoo!
[man] come on, crab! Going up!
-[man 1] here we go!
-[man 2] yeah!
[jake] whoo-hoo. *bleep*
[all cheering]
[man] whoo-hoo!
These things are gonna be
*bleep* loaded!
[all cheering]
we're gonna set.
We'll drop as many as we can
off right here.
Oh, my god! 435.
[sig laughs]
[narrator] just
1000 feet away,
the second prospect pot,
nets over three times
the crab.
[jake] right now this is
102 fathoms.
These areas right here
are real touchy.
We could be
1200 feet that way,
and it'll be 1000 crab.
And if you go
another 1200 feet
there is nothing.
[man screaming]
[narrator] twelve miles east,
on the northwestern.
This is where
we were setting those ones
one to the north. Northeast.
I'm anxious to see
what's out here.
[sig] here we go.
[indistinct shouting]
-[man 1] no!
-[man 2] bad one.
Does not look good,
whatsoever.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
[man] man.
Where is our crab at?
[sig] damn it.
I think I really made
a mistake here.
[phone dialing]
-[jake] hello?
-Hello?
You got me.
Roger.
I mean,
that was a morale boost.
Yeah, dude.
You're doing me a solid.
This area is gonna be
really touchy.
So, you can't go
too far north,
too far south.
Too far east or west.
That's what's the problem
up there.
You can go half a mile
to the left or right
to get crab,
you just don't go.
I'm not gonna tell you
how to set.
Just be really careful.
[jake] fair enough.
Okay, later.
[sig] I don't mind
sharing with jake.
It will work for me
and I hope it works for him.
As long as he doesn't step
on my toes,
I'll be all right.
[narrator] forty-four
miles north,
just below the russian line,
on the wizard.
This area here
is completely under
full pack ice.
Right now we should have been
through our gear. We
got all of about, what,
12 pots up here in the ice.
[narrator] only a quarter
of his gear recovered,
captain keith hunts
his remaining pots
amid the thickening ice pack.
[exhaling] I can only pray
that we get the gear back
that's up here.
They're not just small junk.
[man] no, it's not looking
good at all.
[narrator] but,
with the individual floes,
now the size of automobiles
and growing by the hour.
Not a thing out here.
Just a bunch of ice.
Ice as far as the eye can see.
[narrator] the skipper's
window to recover his
$72,000 equipment
is rapidly shutting.
The floe goes this way
a long way.
-Do you see a weak spot?
-No, the worst of it's
ahead of us.
[keith] titanic sinkers
is what they are.
Better watch your speed.
It's going down the rail,
you know?
Pretty good flip here.
Split that in *bleep* in half.
[keith] I could feel it
up here.
There is another one
on the nose.
[keith] oh, god, I forgot
how much I hated
being in that white stuff.
It just took us 45 minutes
to get through it.
Three quarters of a mile. Ooh.
Bumped it and it tipped up
on the side.
Underneaath the bottom
of the boat.
Yikes.
[keith] yeah.
That's the stuff that
can get scary
when it's back here.
Back towards the runner, yes.
[narrator] as keith navigates
through the birds,
chunks of ice
threaten the hull
and crucial
steering equipment.
[keith] hopefully
it doesn't go on the rudder.
Okay. I'm gonna go
look at this side
and make sure.
[narrator] on the wizard.
[keith] hopefully
it doesn't go on the rudder.
Holy *bleep* man.
-Good riddance, man.
-[monte] put it straight.
[keith] it's moving
at a glacial pace.
[keith] one headache after
another.
Ice floes.
Recovering a bunch of gear.
1500 out of the pot.
At the same time
we can't stay up here
and be doing this.
[narrator] weighing the cost
of lost rigging
against the risk
of severely damaging
his $2,000,000 boat...
[keith] you know what,
let's leave 'em.
I'm gonna point it
right down here.
Little bit further south
where it's safe.
[narrator] captain keith
puts his rescue mission
on hold,
until the threat retreats.
[keith] weather and currents
permitting,
as the stuff rolls through,
hopefully, we will get
some open water
because at this point
you can't get into it.
I don't want to do it,
but you know what?
We can't afford to lose
any more pots.
I'm gonna point at open water.
Try to avoid the minefield.
I've got to catch my crab.
If I don't catch it,
we're not gonna get paid
for it.
[narrator] eighty-four
miles southwest.
[man] okay, guys. Coming up.
[narrator] on the time bandit.
I'll be able to hopefully
pounce on the crab
one more time,
and get a pick
before this ice comes down...
Eats are our lunch.
[narrator] only 72 hours
before the ice is forecast
to overrun his chosen grounds,
captain jonathan looks
to bring his season
to a close,
with his 110 fathom deep set.
I'm going for the gamble.
We're gonna work the canyon.
[laughs]
knock on wood.
[man] wow!
[man] welcome aboard, boys.
Welcome aboard.
[laughs]
that's the real deal there.
That's a solid crossbar.
[indistinct conversation]
yeah! I like it.
[man] it might be working out.
[shouting]
[jonathan] yeah, baby!
[beat boxing]
[jonathan] that's the way
you load a boat.
[man screaming]
[man] oh, there you are.
[man] oh, yeah baby.
Holy moly.
[jonathan] I can't afford
to hurt nobody.
'cause this could send
us home
really easy here.
Just gotta keep fishing.
Out of the block.
Outta the block.
Watch out! Watch out!
Out of the block.
Men. Careful, careful.
Help him.
Watch out!
-*bleep*
-uh-oh. Here goes the coiler.
[man 1] holy *bleep*.
Good job saving that thing.
Holy moly.
*bleep*
when it's flat come out,
our block's been fine.
We're coming off a big wave...
The line started popping
out of the block.
[narrator] as the boat rolls,
a 12,000 pound pot slips out
of the hydraulics grasp,
sinking unfettered,
ripping the coiler
clean off the deck.
That was close.
[chuckles] wow!
Let's get that thing back up.
- Let's keep working.
-[whirring]
get what?
Say that again.
All right.
That's *bleep* bad.
[jonathan] I just need
to harvest those crabs
as quick as I can up here.
We don't have time to stop.
Ice is gonna
shut this fishery right down.
Let's, uh...
Everyone help out.
[narrator] with just hours
until the ice
is forecast to arrive...
Back in 1982,
I did 10,000 pots.
By hand.
Life ain't fair,
get used to it.
[narrator] jon tasks his crew
with coiling
the old-fashioned way.
[jonathan speaking]
that's a tough son of a bitch.
He used to be
as tough as freddy.
Let's see how it goes.
[narrator] seventy-three miles
northeast,
on the cornelia marie...
Couple of holes
in the backside.
They ain't got shoved around.
Fifty-five.
Five, five.
Take a while to fill a
boat with that.
I really thought we were
coming out here, we were just
going to tear it all apart.
Kick ass and take names.
Came out to devastation, ice
came down further than
we anticipated.
Take the stuff from
the outside, buddy.
So, on retrieval mode right
now. Slow process.
We're gonna be on a constant
pot rescue mission until we
get them all picked back up.
The search grid is paying off.
[narrator] finding buoys
over three miles
off their mark,
captains josh and casey
scramble to locate
the final 30 pots
before the ice edge returns
with a vengence.
Next bag's sittin'
right up the bow.
[man] roger.
Been out here
for three months.
Just getting the *bleep*
kicked out of us
in everywhich way.
Been through storms,
been through injuries,
been through ice.
We're due for a little love.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey!
It's out of the box.
Uh-oh.
Hey, watch out. Watch it.
Keep your eyes on the prize
and get the line
back in the block.
Is everybody all right?
Go ahead, hit it a little bit.
There you go.
Hooks are flying out here.
Was a hatchet from hell.
[sighs]
[narrator] the line pops out
of a block.
Sending the metal cage and its
leg-snagging nylon
racing back to the sea floor.
Simultaneously untethering
the picking hook.
Acting fast, deck boss
matt simpson
wrangles the line.
While greenhorn kawai cho
secures the fifteen
pounds of steel.
Pot that's hanging,
it's no good.
That's why I jumped on that
and left the hook. The hook,
someone could grab.
A pot, you can't hang on to.
A pot'll rip someone over the
side if you're not paying
attention.
*bleep* that could have
went so south, so quick.
Bring another out.
*bleep*
[men shouting]
hey,
what's going on
down there?
It's frozen, boy.
Watch out.
[exclaiming]
*bleep*
whoa, whoa, whoa.
[narrator] on the
cornelia marie...
It's frozen, boy.
Watch out.
Oh!
[grunts]
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't let go.
Just got sucked
all the way down the rail.
He wouldn't
let go of the line.
That's called having a grip!
Yeah, man, it was interesting
to watch you ride the white
lightning down there.
I ain't letting go!
Perhaps should have let go
a while ago. He's too fat to
fly and he can't dance, so.
-It's like, you know.
-[laughing]
yeah, I went for
a little ride there.
It happens. [laughs]
rock and roll.
The great pot hunt
of 2021 is over.
We found pretty much
all of our pots.
You need to stay away
from the crowd.
You get into that
90 fathom range,
a lot of guys can reach at
112 or 114 fathoms.
Most guys can't get in there.
[narrator] with all their
pots recouped,
the skippers eye
the southern depths.
Their plan,
stay safe from both the ice
and swarms of smaller boats
more suited to the shallows.
Set all these pots
we just found off
and hopefully
we put it on some crabs.
All right.
Lock these puppies up
and, uh,
get the *bleep* out of here.
[man] yeah!
That's what we want.
[narrator] thirty-six miles
southeast,
on the summer bay.
We're gonna raise
a pot up here.
If we ever need
a change of luck,
it's now,
because that
sorting last night
just about killed these guys
and it's killing me
watching 'em do it.
[narrator] after landing
on a pile of small
and female crabs,
captain wild bill
targets the large males,
typically located
on the leading edge
of the school.
I'm looking for a band,
looking for a depth where
they're hanging out.
This'll be the furthest
north we've set.
Sounds kinda crazy but...
The ice is coming down,
we're going north.
Let's go!
Hands on!
[all exclaiming]
when the ice edge is down,
it does seem like right along
the edge, fishing changes.
I've... Seen it.
[narrator] drawing
on his 40 years of experience,
the skipper sets
15 miles from the ice pack,
playing russian roulette
with the floes.
It may backfire, you never
know. Could be eating snow
cones by the time it's over.
[cell phone ringing]
31, 3-1.
Hey, landon, patty lee's
got a medevac. We don't know
who it is.
I don't know...
Oh, *bleep* yeah.
What?
Coast guard helicopter
to 041 channel 16, over.
I just got word that
patrica lee heading,
someone got hurt really bad.
Landon knows a bunch
of people on board.
We had todd working there
with us a couple of
seasons ago.
Youre replacing a guy who wore
pretty big boots.
-Well, I'm gonna do my best,
that's what I'm here to do.
-Right on, man.
The kid turned out to
be an exceptional deckhand.
Since he's been out here,
his name comes up all
the time.
I hope it's not him.
Any available
launch channel 16.
This has got to be at
the limit for those
helicopters, I bet.
[narrator] six hundred
miles away,
in cold bay, alaska,
[woman speaking over radio]
right guys, plan,
short notice.
Ready to medevac,
so we've trained for this.
[narrator] the coast guard
responds to an urgent
distress call
from the fishing vessel
patricia lee.
[man] my main concern
is whether or not
he is alert and awake.
[narrator] where a deckhand
sustained
life-threatning injuries.
[man] yeah we don't have
a lot to go on,
find out when we get there.
[woman]
call the flight surgeon
to see what the urgency is.
If it increases
his chance of survival
or if it's, uh,
he's going to die.
Roger.
[woman on radio]
who's the flight nurse?
Sounds like
you got hit by a pot.
If you got hit
by one of those, man.
That's a scary,
scary thought.
[man over radio]
so the patient
is in a lot of pain.
It doesn't take much
for one of those
big, heavy steel pots
of 788 pounds to fall over.
Break an arm,
break a leg, break a back.
They're more dangerous for you
than the waves.
[indistinct radio chatter]
there's just so many things
that can go wrong
when you're under the gun
and you're trying
to save the gear
and get out of harm's way
when that ice starts
coming down on you.
[man chattering on radio]
[keith] now I don't know
if anybody knows anybody
on that crew or not.
And I don't know who
the crewman was.
Whether its todd or one of the
other deckhands. This is
*bleep* terrible, you know.
Maybe try
giving him a message.
See what's going on.
[landon] yeah,
I'll message him.
Can't keep losing friends.
[narrator] cold bay, alaska.
[woman on radio]
super, ready to taxi.
[man on radio]
it's taxi.
[narrator] the coast guard
gears up for a rescue
on a bering sea
fishing vessel...
What do we, uh,
hear about the patient?
[man on radio] uh,
he's in a lot of pain.
[narrator]
where a crewman battles
life threatening injuries.
[man on radio]
...6041 taxiing onto runway 33
and section charlie
for departure to the north.
6041, cold bay hanger.
[man on radio]
hanger, four-one, go ahead.
[woman on radio] four-one,
hanger. Stand down.
Over.
Hanger, four-one,
roger. Stand down.
[cell phone vibrating,
ringing]
yup?
-[man 1] going over.
-[man 2] roger.
We don't know who it was
on the, uh, boat.
But whatever it was,
he didn't make it.
He got crushed.
-Oh, my god.
-[bill] trying to get a name,
I don't know.
But whoever was on the boat
didn't make it.
My good friend
todd's on there.
He worked on here.
Unfortunately, that's happened
out here every year,
but that's usually
not like that.
There's only
so much you can do
when we're this far away.
I don't know what I'd do
if something happened
to one of you guys,
I really don't.
I don't know if I'd be able
to fish again.
[exhales]
[sig] it hits home every time.
And this is a small circle
of guys doing this,
just through one...
One way or another
you kind of know somebody
on all these boats, you know.
[man] bill!
Bill, it was todd.
His aunt just posted that...
Her only living nephew,
todd just passed away.
Yeah, that's
his profile picture.
Me, him and nick.
Yeah.
*bleep*
seems like ever quarter
we're losing somebody.
Nothing you can do.
[narrator]
twenty-one miles southwest...
[keith] banging through
the ice, stuff happens.
There's nothing safe
about this job.
[narrator] ...On the wizard.
[keith] this has been
as brutal a trip
as I can remember.
The thing is, we've got
our crab to catch.
I've got to catch my crab.
Coming up.
We didn't come this far
to come up short.
[narrator] after turning
his back on gear in the north,
captain keith colburn
looks to his southern set
to make up the loss.
If we don't hit
on this final set,
we're gonna have to go in
on this trip short.
I know the ice is coming.
I know we're gonna see it,
and this gear's gotta hit.
[metal creaking]
[man] get it, get it, get it.
[keith] that pot
looks pretty decent.
Give me a real good count
on this one, guys.
Give me a good count.
Three-seven-oh. 370.
Three-seven-oh, right on.
Right. That's how
I like to start.
[man] yeah, baby.
Loaded.
Whoo!
[cheering]
yeah!
Whoo!
That's the best sound
on this boat.
The sound of those guys
shaking those hoppers
trying to get
the crab to go down.
Well, this sucker's loaded.
We can get this boat
headed to town.
Get the hell out of here.
[man] hold! Hold on.
[laughs]
yes!
[grunts]
bang!
We're choking.
[cheering]
right on!
[grunts]
[narrator] taking the worst
mother nature can dish out
on the chin...
[laughing]
[narrator] captain keith
finally tanks the last
of his $9.7 million quota.
Huge season the bank.
That's the biggest season
we've had
in... Over a decade.
Just got to get
this offload done.
After we go in, hopefully,
we get our gear back,
or most of it, without getting
into the ice pack.
It's all we can do.
[narrator]
sixty-four miles southwest.
Aboard the time bandit.
[jonathan] I was just seeing
if you guys have
any spare motors
or anything for a king coiler.
Okay, buddy.
Keep up the good work
and keep in touch.
Thanks.
It's painful and brutal
and slow.
We really need to fix
this king coiler thing.
[narrator] with his coiler
out of commission,
captain jonathan's crew
must create each 800 foot shot
by hand.
[jonathan] this is
the best crab we've seen
so far in this trip.
The problem is,
in two and a half days,
the ice is coming.
[narrator] but after
eight hours of slow
back-breaking work,
the skipper is running
out of time,
and his crew is running
out of gas.
[jonathan] I don't know
what to do.
You see that, one guy.
The tempo sea set.
It just happens to be
about six miles away from us.
This driver behind us,
he might have a motor
on his boat.
Hey, jo, 116.
Time bandit.
Hello.
[man on radio]
how are we doing today?
You don't have to have
a king coiler motor, do you?
'cause we're hand coiling
and it sucks.
[joe on radio] oh, yuck.
Yeah, we do have one.
Whoo! Yeah.
[joe on radio] you want
to meet up later or what?
Hey, I got something better.
I'll just head right at you.
You know, just transfer.
[joe on radio] I'll get
the guys to set it up.
Okay, yeah. I appreciate this.
Dude, we might be back
in business.
Business might be good.
Okay. Just the last one here
and we'll stack it.
And they got
a coiler motor for us.
Wow!
[jonathan] everyone
helps everyone out here.
Even if you don't
like him in town.
Hopefully I can get
something working.
Salvage this trip
'cause it'll be heartbreaker
to lose some gear.
[narrator] thirty-eight miles
northeast...
[beeping]
[sig] three miles.
[narrator]
...On the northwestern.
[sig] we're just coming up on
our prospect pots that we set.
Jake, uh, I let him pull
a couple three of those pots.
We're looking for
some more real estate,
you know, wider area
and ice packs nearby,
so we need a shot in
the arm so to speak.
[narrator] within intel
from the saga,
captain sig arrives at
the alleged hotspot
eager to tank his final
50,000 pounds...
Before the ice closes in.
[sig] it's not a lot of area.
And they just got to be
in the right spots.
And that's what we're doing.
See if we get a couple
of whacks out of this area,
than I think, you know,
might get us out of here.
[man] whoa.
No. What is this crap?
Dad. Are you not seeing this?
You're tangled up
with jake's pot.
That's not... That's not good.
He's all over you.
[sighs]
be careful.
He's-- it's been
"jake-onized."
[sig] that's what you get
for being nice.
[man 1] no.
[man 2] yeah.
[sig] it's not bad
but it's not impressive.
What a dumb *bleep*.
[man speaking]
he can fish
where the hell he wants.
Just stay away
from my *bleep* pots.
[narrator] setting gear
too close together,
jake divides the biomass
making it nearly impossible
to accurately read the school.
Why would you do that?
You check my *bleep*,
you set right through it.
How am I supposed
to get a read on my pot now
when he's got a pot there
and a pot there?
And you got
four freaking shots
all over the place.
[sig] I don't care
how desperate you are.
What the *bleep*.
[line ringing]
I'm gonna give jake
a call here.
[jake speaking indistinctly]
so, I got some good news.
Well, it moved up north.
I spot checked just now.
All right. Stop talking.
[line ringing]
[jake speaking indistinctly]
so, I got some good news.
Well, it moved up north.
I spot checked just now.
All right, stop talking.
[sig] you said--
look, I don't understand
why you pulled my gear.
Like, you know,
but then you set
right through...
Those very pots.
Like, I wanted to be able
to check so that I could get
a decent number
on what's there.
I don't understand
why you set right through 'em.
Why would you do that?
Oh, yeah.
Well, a lot of reason
why it stayed close
is because I know this area
in here is really touchy.
I can't go too far
to the north, east,
or the west.
[sig] I know you're hungry.
And I know you are, you know,
had a rough go
on this last one.
And you're freaking out.
I get it.
I've been there.
I know what you're feeling.
But I don't understand
why you just, you know--
I just--
I want you to understand,
you want that to breathe.
That's all I'm saying.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna do exactly
what I think is best.
I gotta go.
I gotta get busy.
Good luck. Do well.
All right. Bye-bye.
[men cheering]
[jake] he's getting nervous
because now
ice is possibly coming.
And he wants to get
as much crab as he can.
And he's probably
kicking himself
because he let me
haul those prospectors.
[sig] this is not the way
to fish.
You can't be that close.
Just plain and simple.
You know,
it is what it is right now.
He can take my spot.
We're gonna go north.
We need to.
Two-tenths of a mile.
So, we're gonna stay
in the same vein,
but farther north
there is more real estate.
[narrator] with jake
setting through
the 100 fathom range,
sig resolves to follow
the same depth,
farther north
away from the saga,
but closer to the ice.
With the start we had
and the clock ticking,
we don't have a choice.
Right? He didn't go out there.
It hasn't been touched.
[intercom beeps] you ready?
Set it when you're ready.
There's always risk involved,
but we'll keep leapfrogging.
Keep mowing the lawn.
We gotta get out of here
before the ice comes down.
[mandy] these pots
better be loaded.
[man] going over!
If they don't hit,
we got a problem.
[narrator] thirty-seven miles
southwest...
On the "time bandit."
trying to fix that
damn king coiler.
[jonathan speaking
indistinctly]
hope it works.
[narrator] operating
at half-speed
without a crucial piece
of equipment,
captain jonathan's season
rides on a successful
at sea transfer.
We're running out of time.
The clocks are ticking.
[narrator] t o get his pots
on board along with
the thousands of pounds
he needs to cover his quota.
[siren blaring]
[man speaking]
yeah, go ahead any time.
okay, I got it.
I see it there.
[man cheers]
[jonathan]
you're making our day.
Thank you.
[man speaking]
[man] we got a new motor.
And we'll see if
we can put it together.
Hopefully this works out
for everybody.
For all these--
everybody involved out there.
[machine whirring]
[man] pow, pow!
[man speaking]
you want me to try--
why don't you
try it out, freddy?
[grunts]
[jonathan] I'm talking
next to the money pot.
We might have ourselves
a king coiler.
[machine whirring]
[cheering]
[jonathan] all right, man.
We just got
another crew member.
I just wanna fill
these tanks up.
And I gotta get back
to my pots
before the ice gets it...
Before all hell breaks loose.
[narrator] seventy-seven miles
northeast
on the summer bay.
We're further north
than I've ever fished
for crab.
Obviously, to the east of us
there is ice because,
uh, we're starting to see
some big chunks.
[bill] I am starting
to see that...
Pancaky stuff here.
But...
We're still
in wide open water here.
[narrator] after gambling
over 100 pots in the path
of the oncoming freeze,
captain wild bill
looks to turn his trip around
and wrap up
a season to forget.
You know we're talking about
everything that's happened
this year and...
In a period of seven months,
I lost three guys
who worked for me.
Mahlon and nick
and then
just the other day...
We had this kid, todd.
You know, he was a good kid.
Apparently, he got crushed
by a pot.
-[man] thirty-eight.
-Total accident.
Tragic.
Todd had been dealt
a pretty rough hand
in his own life.
And you know what?
He just shook it off,
worked hard
and did a hell of a job.
[man speaking]
[bill] all right,
first one's coming up.
It's coming down to the wire.
The thinking
and looking part is over.
It's just dialing in on
the best you can just find
and hope you soak some up.
With any luck,
we'll get twos and threes.
Time to get out of here.
[speaking indistinctly]
um...
[man] oh yeah!
Yeah!
It looks pretty good,
actually. It looks like nice,
clean crab.
[man speaking]
[man cheering]
that's real money, honey.
That is amazing.
Yeah, baby.
-Really big, clean crab.
-[man] yeah.
[bill] big boy fishing.
What you got, manny?
[man] three seventeen.
Three-one-seven.
[bill] three hundred
and seventeen crab.
It warms my heart.
Let's see
what this looks like.
[man] yeah.
And this one looks
even bigger.
[man speaking]
I think, all in all,
for all intents and purposes,
we made the right choice
going north.
[man speaking]
cha-ching. [laughs]
[cheering]
[bill] I'm sure you guys
are ready for this.
I know I am.
Thank you so much.
It's been hell of a year,
and be careful.
Get it aboard,
get the crab down.
Let's wrap this thing up.
[man] take your delivery.
This is probably
25 on the wind.
This is gonna come up tonight
and it's gonna make getting
into that harbour hard.
There's still a lot of stuff
that can go wrong.
[narrator]
five hundred and ten miles
northwest of dutch harbor...
On the "cornelia marie."
yeah.
First pot of
our southern stuff.
[josh] everything
is pretty much stacked,
all concentrated
right in this region.
We'll see
what happens here.
[casey] we're watching
the radar and guys
are coming down
right to the 90 fathom mark
they won't come past it.
[narrator]
to keep the competition down
and the crabs counts up,
captains josh and casey
bet on the southern depths
before the ice moves in
yet again.
Anything over 300
is gonna be mint.
We got crab!
-Wow, that's a nice pot.
-You can do it.
Nice job!
Dandy, right there.
One hell of a way
to start the morning out.
Five eight zero.
Yeah, all right.
Now we're cooking with gas.
-Wowie.
-Yeah.
Six three five.
All right!
Fill the tank, go to the bank!
Kicking ass and taking names.
See, the old man's helping,
channeling right through.
Now it's just all about
getting as much crab on
the boat as fast as we can.
Try to bang the
season out while
there's still enough crab
on the grounds to be caught.
[narrator]
77 miles north-west
on the north western.
First pot's coming up.
[sig] we're up to the
northern area here.
Up above the pots
that jake set back.
Hopefully we end this
with a big finale.
Where's the ice pack
at right now?
Is that gonna affect us?
It's close enough,
that's the problem.
Wow, come on.
-Here we go.
-More crab.
Wow, this is it!
Yeah, come on!
There we go!
How's that for a first pot?
-Five hundred.
-500, that works.
They're screaming, move,
get out of my way.
Yeah, that's 118.
Oh yeah!
Yeah!
Those are hot.
Oh, wow!
This is nice big clean crab.
I'm not so worried about that
as much as that ice
that's up ahead.
The ice edge is literally
20 miles away from me,
not even that.
I really need to get out
of here before it's too late.
Gonna be another ice party.
[narrator]
317 miles south-east
off saint paul island...
Harbormaster, summer bay.
[man speaking over radio]
is there a place for us
to come in and try to tie up?
All right, thank you.
Back in 60.
We come in to offload this
crab and finish
the season up here I hope.
[narrator]
captain wild bill races
to make his final delivery
at one of only two canneries
still open for business.
It's looking pretty
gnarly out.
Seas are building,
it's getting ugly.
There are some breakers
right inside of here, so.
No fun right now.
[narrator]
but roiling between the
summer bay and the dock
is the notorious
harbor entrance.
All I see right now in front
of me is breakers.
And then you look behind me
there aint nothing but
green and white water.
Yeah we got some
big seas here.
But I don't think I've ever
had more desire to finish
this season,
than I do this season.
I cannot wait for
this season to be over.
So we'll be sucking
it up right now.
All right better go through
one more set than go for it.
Okay, roger!
Well, here we go.
Trying to get in the harbor
between these gigantic swells
that are...
That are monstrous.
I'm just gonna ride one in.
And have it break just
at the entrance
and have that little lull
behind it and power through.
Will the one you ride in let
you go when it's time, that's
the only problem.
There's a big one.
Watch out!
Hold on!
You need to get down.
You need to get down,
let's go!
Go, go, go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Look out!
[alarms blaring]
that's forward bilge,
high level
what the *bleep* am I doing?
That's too big,
I have no control over that.
Come on, turn *bleep*.
Hang on.
[narrator] after weeks at sea,
chasing the deadliest catch.
The wizard crew celebrates
with the gentlest catch.
A number of our
driver bags went flat so...
Top of the buoy conveniently
is shaped just like a frisbee.
Doesn't take much to keep
these guys entertained
out here.
Kind of just kids.
It's all in the wrist.
Well, I guess all good things
come to an end huh.
Monte and the wizard,
finish at the top of the heap.
While wild bill and the
summer bay fight for survival
near saint paul harbor
bring out the storm.
Go, go, go.
Wow, wow.
Look out, look out.
Come on, turn *bleep*.
Hang on.
*bleep*
is everybody on board?
Everybody is on board?
[man over radio] yeah.
Whoa... *bleep*
*bleep* ...Everywhere.
*bleep*
[man speaking over radio]
[captain bill speaking]
[producer] hey, man. Hey!
We're still alive, buddy.
Good job. You... *bleep*
brought that
thing around, man.
I didn't think
we were gonna make it.
Thank you for... [chuckles]
just staying on it, dude.
Staying at the wheel.
That was not easy.
[bill]
I was okay on the first one.
When the second one hit
I thought,
"this might be it.
We might not
come back up on this one."
I got a lot of faith
in this boat,
more than I did before.
Windows were in the water.
I thought that was it.
Yeah, we got...
I hope you guys
aren't too traumatized,
but, yeah, we'll
put everything back together,
offload and finish the...
Finish the season up here,
I hope.
I'm gonna go ahead
and wait for this...
Weather to subside
before we head in.
Nowhere in my plans
is drowning here,
the boat being my coffin.
[producer] you know it's bad
when there's water
on the ceiling, man.
-That was... *bleep*
-[water dripping]
...Gnarly,
we're inside the boat.
It's one of them ones
you'll talk about for years.
[chuckles softly]
"I remember that
op season in '21
when you thought
things couldn't get
much worse."
guess what,
it just did.
Should have been a cowboy.
[narrator]
316 miles north-west...
On the time bandit.
[whooping]
[man] I'm excited
about that one.
Woo-hoo! Sometimes...
Sometimes I'd rather
be lucky than good!
Look at that table,
oh, my god!
That's more than
we needed...
To get home.
[narrator] after feasting
on the bio mass
just below the icepack,
captain jonathan
closes in
on his 350,000 pound quota.
Eight pots left.
I mean...
We're this close.
[narrator] the final push...
[deckhand] heads up!
[narrator] a 20 mile run north
to recover his final string.
This whole season, man,
everything tried to work
against us.
-[deckhand] woo-hoo!
-Right here.
[deckhand] nice job.
We see the light
at the end of the tunnel.
Ain't that bad-ass.
[laughing]
[all cheering]
hello.
How's it goin', man?
Yeah, I did about
10 miles above that.
The ice is right there?
[captain jonathan] wow.
Yeah, thanks, thanks.
All right, man.
All right. *bleep*
I lost lots
of my last string.
[captain jonathan speaking]
the ice is like
4-5 foot thick up there,
and they can't even
get to their gear,
and...
Our gear is gone.
I'm almost gonna cry,
like, my crew.
They've been with me
for 31 years,
these are my soldiers.
Kay,
I just found out
from another boat that
our gear is gone.
Save the pots.
We're gonna have
a little memorial.
Let's change that flag up.
And be really careful.
[deckhand] roger, cap.
[deckhand] grab that thing.
[captain jonathan]
pretty sentimental
about my pots.
Been out here a long time,
maybe I've just been
on the water too long.
I'm getting weird.
Watch your feet!
Okay, you guys ready?
[deckhand] roger!
[captain jonathan]
this is in memory...
Of pr.
Pot number pr.
Woo! Pr!
Thank you
for your service, pr!
[captain jonathan over radio]
that was our
damn best pots.
This is for all u2.
Uniform 2.
I wanna tear up.
Ck19.
[laughing]
*bleep* son of a bitch.
This sucks.
Last one.
[sig]
we're gonna do
a flaming hook.
-Yeah!
-[howling]
[laughing]
[sig]
this season, from day one,
has just been, uh,
one catastrophe after another,
it feels like to me.
It's been really tough.
There is no guarantee
out here.
[captain keith]
I just want to confirm
that the trident dock...
Is open for us
to come tie up to.
[man over radio]
wizard. Harbormaster.
Yeah, we copy.
[captain keith]
we had processors
in facilities
that were shut down.
But we managed
to get the crab in.
[captain josh over radio]
last one, guys. Nice job.
This is all...
Yeah, that's what we want!
Been a hell of a ride.
Caught more crab
than we ever caught before.
Yeah, made more money
than we ever made before.
I like that one.
-[laughs]
-it's the money.
[captain josh] what's funny is
we're gonna get home,
we're gonna have
a couple of days off,
then it's back to work
in hawaii. [chuckles]
at least it'll be in hawaii.
[captain josh laughs]
yeah, that's true.
[captain casey]
you don't have to worry
about ice.
[sig]
at the end of the day,
this is a small circle of...
Guys doing this.
Just getting ready
to haul the last pot.
Oh, thank god,
it's over.
Kay, you wanna see
some fireworks?
Yeah.
Ready?
[explosion]
yeah. Baby! Woo!
[mandy]
good job, guys! Good job!
[laughing loftily]
did you see that, kay?
[sig]
I'm coming home.
We have to be there
for each other
and continue to support
each other.
[captain jonathan]
this year,
so many industries failed,
and somehow,
some way,
the crab industry
got it together,
and completed
the opilio season this year.
[captain bill]
you know, the fishery
was on the line,
you know,
everybody came together,
and we got it done.
God bless!
[captain jonathan]
we fought hard for this crab,
and no one ever fought harder.
And I'll kick... *bleep*
of somebody if they say that.
It's not true.
But, uh, I don't know
if I'm coming back.
You know, but...
I always say that. [laughs]
[sig]
but, we still made out
all right, though.
Yeah.
But, honestly,
I'm glad it's over.
I wanna go home.
We can come back next year
with our heads held high.
Time to move forward.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/8u2xz
Help other users to choose the best subtitles