Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
A NEW FRIEND
Laura was my best friend,
my friend forever.
Since we met
it was like a crush.
Because she was and I was.
We had seven years ...
and it sure would be for
life to death.
I present to your
new partner,
Laura.
Well, we were in
the grammar lesson,
with verbs of the first group.
Who can give me examples
verbs of the first group?
All life to death.
All they look.
Hi Laura.
Are you okay?
What's up?
May the Lord confirm
this decision ...
and give them his Spirit to
I serve as a common agreement,
and that your union be blessed
in the name of the Father and of the Son ...
and the Holy Spirit, Amen.
United by the bonds
marriage
with from now on,
as a guarantee of your alliance,
these rings.
In the name of the Father ...
and of the Son ...
and the Holy Spirit.
Laura ...
And as in our childhood ...
We made a pact.
I made a promise.
This promise, Laura,
I'll keep it for you.
I will be all my life ...
ensuring your daughter Lucie ...
and his father, David.
For the Father, his son
and the Holy Spirit.
It's time, Claire.
Come on, get up.
I do not want to go.
Yes, make an effort.
You work, you
think of something else.
You agree?
See you tonight.
Until tonight.
Sorry.
It is done!
Bravo.
Do not you feel good?
Yes, but I wanted to tell you ...
I took a week's leave.
- Oh yeah?
- Yes.
I can not work,
not concentrate.
Do not apologize dear,
I understand you.
You called David?
No.
You could take this
week to go see him.
Help you with your daughter.
I'm afraid of ...
to see Lucie.
It reminds both Laura.
Thanks for dinner.
Barely touched your plate.
- It was very good.
- Thank You.
- Do you want to do it?
- But yes.
- Are you sure?
- Sure, why ask?
Hi, is David,
I'm away, but ...
Is there someone?
Good morning lady I ...
Sorry, just passing by,
I do not want to bother.
Wait, Claire ...
Stay, I must explain.
There is nothing to explain,
You do what you want.
Please, you must listen.
I'm going to bed the girl
and I'll be back.
Sit, drink something,
I'll be right back.
PARENTS
NEWSPAPER OF THE HOUSE
101 recipes to delight
And I went to bed.
I'm going to have a drink.
First of all,
I want you to know ...
Laura knew.
- Oh yeah?
- Yes
I know you had everything,
but this kept secret.
Before we got married ...
I confessed that ...
sometimes I liked
dressed as a woman.
Only that, as a game.
For pleasure.
He accepted it very well.
All he asked me ...
It was not to do it in public.
Then now
she's dead ...
Claire ...
I never left this house
dressed as a woman.
Nobody saw me as well.
Unless you today.
It was an accident.
In all this time
with Laura ...
He did not feel the need.
Her presence, her femininity,
I sated.
He loved her so much.
It was after his death
he returned ...
as evidence.
started a week later
Laura's funeral.
was alone with Lucie
in my room ...
trying to give him his bottle ...
but I would not stop screaming.
For two days
barely fed.
In that moment I understood
I missed Laura.
How I missed her.
This shirt is from Mom.
And suddenly ...
the pain of his absence ...
his fault, disappeared.
The scent of Laura ...
his clothes ...
a feeling of fullness
I was overwhelmed ...
like I was there.
She spoke to me ...
Lucie.
was inside me.
Wait.
Being alone with a child
to raise is very hard.
I think that ...
I could give you a
maternal presence.
Every child needs a mother.
And a father.
I do both.
It is temporal.
Only a less brutal form
leaving Laura.
To get used to his absence.
You do not do for Lucie.
It's for your own pleasure.
you are a pervert.
Maybe you're right.
Please, Claire.
Do not tell anyone, not to Gilles.
Just between us.
I do not know ...
If Laura's parents find out,
I care Lucie removed.
- You know how much I love her.
- Yes, I know ...
I want you to understand
as always he understood me Laura.
No goals Laura in all this!
Transvestite
Crossdressing. As become
more feminine!
- Goodnight My Love.
- Are you okay?
You smell nice!
Y? What did you do today?
- Nothing special.
- Do not you get out?
Yes ...
- To a friend.
- Yes? Who?
You do not know her,
a fellow high school.
- Did you know Laura?
- Yes, a little.
What you how did it go?
There was more.
- Not to get orders.
- Best.
- I did not tell you.
- What?
I called David.
- David ...
- As there beckoned, I did.
I suggested going to dinner
together on Saturday.
So we distendemos a little.
What did he say?
Which in principle would be fine,
You should only get a babysitter.
He told me that since the death
Laura he never left.
- When did you call?
- A while ago.
It is for you.
You do not answer?
Yes.
Good morning, Claire.
How are you?
Why are you calling from
that phone? You are crazy?
Sorry, I wanted to be
sure answer.
What's up?
Why do you call me?
I need to see you.
It did me good to talk to you
and that you share with me.
I go, dear.
- We turn to speak.
- I beg you, Claire.
Then I'll see.
Who is it?
That childhood friend of
I told you, it's heavy.
- Do not sit well ...
- What happens?
- Having trouble with her husband.
- What's it called?
Virginia.
Well, see you at night.
Until tonight.
Good job.
Thank You.
Who is it?
Me, Claire.
Enters.
Thanks for coming.
- Did you get the scent of Laura?
- Yes.
- That dress was Laura?
- Sure, the I retouched.
You like it?
Is to show me that dress
I did come?
Yes, among other things.
I think it's time
of the bottle.
Make yourself comfortable,
I will look to Lucie.
I love your lipstick.
It fits you well.
Thank You.
I'm coming, Lucie.
Yes my love.
But yes ...
Look Who's here.
Your godmother, Claire.
Smile at.
It's amazing how
Laura looks like.
The same eyes.
- And the mouth.
- Take it.
I'll get her bottle.
It's nothing, it's nothing ...
Mom turns away.
- What happens to you?
- It's ridiculous.
This can not last forever.
it's crazy.
I know, but found
Nothing better.
- And your work?
- Paternity leave.
Laura's father told me
I take my time.
Why not take someone?
A full-time nanny.
Lucie would have a
female presence and ...
No, Laura promised care
it myself.
I also.
And watch over you.
It's what you're doing today.
Do you think you told him to Fuiste
Gilles to call me?
- Did you tell him?
- Of course not.
I have a lot of sewing to do
and I ordered dresses online.
My dream would be to go
boutiques women,
do shopping and
buy large sizes.
But I never dared.
Laura had tons of clothes.
You can take whatever you want.
- Will not you stay with anything?
- Yes, but kids sizes.
I gain nothing.
- Are not you going to put this?
- I would love to.
But in here
it's a little hot.
You should touch the shoulders.
But I look good, right?
Yes, rather.
I personally am
against the skin.
It's an old animal.
It was my mother.
Did you keep a coat
of your mother?
If, as I recall.
I loved my mother.
This dress also.
- Is it because of it?
- Because of it, what?
- That you dress as a woman.
- No, I think not.
As a child I loved to dress up.
Especially not with her clothes.
Yes ... with your clothes
sometimes inside.
He would have liked
having a girl.
No, I was delighted
of having a boy.
My father too.
- Shit!
- Who is it?
My mother in law.
- Claire!
- Good morning, Liz.
- What a nice surprise!
- Yes.
I came to take care
a little Lucie.
How good of you
come to lend a hand.
- I brought a gift to Lucie.
- How nice.
I will give later,
It is napping.
- David is best?
- Yes.
- Are you resting?
- No, you're showering.
A shower at this hour?
Yes, I believe. It will not delay.
I'm not sure
I have made.
You're fine?
it's difficult.
You should come to the parish.
I'm sure you would
While talking, praying.
It helps me a lot.
Maybe.
What a beautiful couple did!
With Robert, we decided to let
the house and Laura savings
so you can raise the child
in good conditions.
it's okay.
No money and their parents
They did not have much.
- David!
- Good morning, Liz. Sorry.
- How are you?
- Yes ...
I'm so glad to see them.
- They are fine?
- Yes.
The lipstick.
What happens?
- David! What happens?
- Excuse me.
What happens?
You must have eaten
anything wrong.
The poor is not good!
Sorry.
Take a good hot tea.
No, I think I need
something stronger.
How is Lucie?
It is fine, thanks to Claire
that helps me a lot.
Laura always knew he could
trust your best friend.
Thank You.
Well ... I'm going, I have
to do some shopping.
- Already?
- I have to have lunch with Gilles.
Goodbye dear.
Give a kiss
your lovely husband.
Agree.
I'll walk.
Thanks, Claire.
- I forgot to tell you something.
- What?
Do not call me again with the
Phone Laura, removed it.
- Did you get a dress?
- You do not like?
Yes, but while ...
I try as we left.
- What?
- Looks Good.
- Wait.
What are you doing?
You like it?
I look like an old whore.
No, you exalted.
Did you get a nanny?
Better yet, let Lucie
with my inlaws.
For one week.
He will do well to take
a little time for me.
It is exactly what
I tell Claire.
- Time is very important.
- But I'm scared.
Why?
Care of Lucie
not let me think a lot,
but I'll be alone ...
single without Laura.
What you achieve, you'll see.
We will support.
Claire Is not it true?
Yes, of course.
- Have they chosen?
- Yes, I want the menu.
- How do you want the beef?
- On the brink.
- I do the same, but juicy.
- Very good.
And you, dear?
I want the bass, please.
I wanted the same thing,
instead of meat.
Will you continue with the same wine?
- Yes, it is perfect.
Thank You.
Lovely is not it?
What? Is not it pretty?
- For, Gilles!
- What's up?
It has a nice dress,
It is true.
- Sorry?
- Yes?
- Services, please?
- Going down to the right.
I will later.
- When did you start working?
- Tuesday.
We can meet
Monday, then.
It does not think it's a good idea.
Please.
I want you to come with me
to do shopping.
Will you go to Virginia?
- How to Virginia?
- I mean ... as a woman.
It would be nice as Virginia.
Now comes, shut up.
Come with your car at 14 pm.
I'll open the garage.
I love him to David,
He's a good guy.
No?
- What's up?
- Nothing.
- Yes, I see ...
- You were odious to the waitress.
What?
David comes from losing his wife
and incite to flirt.
I just wanted to defuse the atmosphere.
He did not take it badly.
Anyway ...
He saw that he was not interested.
I always thought
I was a little ...
A little what?
He has something. is very ...
- Female. it feels ...
- Oh, good.
Yes. I'm sure Laura
and he wanted but ...
I have the impression that
men are like him.
- Did you finish?
- No ...
No, but never mind.
Dave, are you here?
I'm coming.
Hi ...
Do you think go well?
Why?
Not well?
Try out with you,
but discreetly.
I do not want to look at me walking
1m with a transvestite, 80.
Then what do we do?
Why do not you wear pants?
No, for the first exit
I want to show my legs.
- Where is the dress the other day?
- Which?
- The one retocaste.
- It's dirty.
- Go get it.
- It's all wrinkled.
It's not a fashion show.
Let alone to go shopping
and not to attract attention.
Agree.
I'll board a little.
- Here it is.
- Very good.
Did I leave the middle?
I do not know ...
- You should Otherwise, shave.
- No, let them.
I do not want to
wait two hours.
You must help me, because
I have hairs on the back
and I can not take them off myself.
- What a mess in this dress!
- Wait.
- It is done.
- Thank You.
Beware, it was not
well lit.
It is that I do do
anything.
We do not do anything wrong.
Wait.
Do not you have another
more discreet wig?
I amounts.
It is done!
That's great!
I peinaste as Laura.
- Is not it too much?
- Do you think I can recognize?
Better not.
- Where we go?
- To the city.
But where?
A shopping center,
It is full of boutiques.
Claire.
Yes?
Does the wig okay?
Yes Yes.
Lovely.
Come on.
Then you call me Virginia.
OK
My first outing in shape.
Should not you also
change your voice a little bit?
- Good day.
Have the keys
Car, Virginia?
- Did you become silent?
- But no.
- The put in your bag.
- What a fool I am!
You're still not ready.
You'll see what I can do.
- They realize?
- I think not.
He could have let me
the other dressed.
But no, it's fine.
You mean you're credible.
It is the same color, look.
Smells.
How nice!
Look.
- Is it too dark?
- It does not look good on you.
Virginia.
You like it?
- Can I fit?
- Check it out!
- It's going very well.
- Thank You.
- It is not my style.
- Yes, it matches your hair.
- It makes you thinner.
- It is true?
And for the price, honestly ...
Goodbye, have a nice day.
- Shall we?
- Today I do not feel ready.
Why?
I already told you. I do not Epilate
legs and chest.
Yes.
It will be for next time.
- You'd go out with me again?
- Yes, why not?
- And Gilles?
- What about Gilles?
- I do not know ...
- No incumbent and ...
not understand.
We're going to start the movie!
Wait, do not run it
that I have tacos.
Look at this actress!
- Would you let me?
- Yeah right.
- Changing of place.
- Yes.
Tell me the truth.
You like men.
But no!
Man in cinema
I was excited right?
Oh yeah!
Yes, but not as we understand.
I was happy I
He takes over a woman.
And you touch her.
Claire, may seem
strange but no.
I never attracted men.
Now, women do, always.
Maybe it's because I want
be like them.
Have you tried with a man?
Never.
As a teenager I masturbated
with friends in the catechism ...
But nothing more.
Virginia How would you like?
I never thought.
But this is the first time I go
as a woman, watching me ...
so you never know.
You have to try.
Not to die idiot.
It's all so new to me,
thank you.
It's like a rebirth.
You should not hold my hand,
There is a guy who is watching us.
Do not worry, women
often they hold hands.
Certain types of women.
I would like this evening
it never ends.
Ten.
- I think you were right.
- About what?
It is not just by Lucie
I dressed as a woman.
What's up?
I spotted.
Wait.
It is done.
Gilles and not suspect anything.
- Bye-Bye.
This is what will happen in
little or longer.
I have an urgent call.
- David?
- No, Virginia.
See you for lunch.
I'm not good at all.
Yes, but not before 13 and 30.
See you at your office?
In the coffee shop across the street.
Thank you Claire.
Until then.
Do you come dressed as?
No, I said it was Virginia.
- Sorry, it can not be.
- Why?
It is close to the office.
I can not take chances.
What are the risks?
The other time was all right.
Well, see you at 13 and 45
in the lounge of the Mall.
There you are!
Hello.
Sorry for the delay,
I have a lot of work.
Do you let the glasses?
- You asked me to be discreet.
- I think that's fine.
I have only half an hour. I'll take
a sandwich, do you want anything?
No, I'm not hungry.
- Insurance?
- Yes.
Good day, one of these
sandwiches, please.
I like your skirt.
It Looks Good.
Thank You.
Do not you shaved?
- Noticeable?
- Yes, a little.
Shit!
He employs a woman.
- What medication are you taking?
- Nothing ...
antidepressants.
You know, our access to the center
Trade was like a trigger.
I never felt so happy ...
blissful.
We repeat that ...
I'm overwhelmed with work,
this week is difficult.
Claire, you can not leave me like this.
I need you.
Laura's parents stay
with Lucie until Sunday.
We could go to his house.
It is not impossible.
What would you say to Gilles?
The truth.
- All right?
- I end this mess.
This scarf is mine.
I found there.
My throat hurts.
Charming.
- I spoke on the phone with my mother.
- Oh yeah?
- Not well.
- What happens?
I think it's something missing.
We could go see it
weekend.
I can not, with these
office problems.
But you can go.
You do not need me.
I wish it
we were together.
On another occasion
we'll go together.
I promise.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
What come loaded
for a weekend!
Suit material.
- What did you say to Gilles?
- I was going to see my mother.
Would you lie often?
No.
I know only from
you dress as a woman.
I will never lie to Laura.
Here I am!
- You made quickly.
- I just changed me,
I maquillarי in the car.
You help me?
- No one saw you?
- Yes, a truck driver.
He saw me out of the men's room.
You must have liked my dress.
- You want me to teach you a trick?
- Yes, what?
For eye makeup ...
right eye, right hand,
left eye, left hand.
Great!
It works!
I remember. It was in the summer
our 16 years.
Yes, I know.
Well ...
What room you take?
As you like.
I parents because
there is a beautiful wardrobe
and a large mirror.
- I'll take Laura.
- Does your childhood?
- Yes, it gives me pleasure.
- But the bed is small.
It does not bother me.
You feel good?
Yes Yes.
At seeing these pictures,
Table, it gives me something.
Were moments of happiness?
Yes ...
That is important,
no sadness, only happiness.
Okay,
Are we going to walk?
Would you push you?
You see there?
All up.
We used to spend hours
making things.
We talked and played.
I can not find it.
- Are you sure it's here?
- Of course.
Here, look!
It was not erased.
its beautiful.
I remember what you told us
when we were kids:
"The boys are born in a cabbage
and girls in a flower "
I ...
I was born in a cauliflower.
- What happens to you?
- Sorry, I did not recognize you.
I switched to fetch firewood.
It is more practical as a man.
Yes, of course.
This evening, you prefer to dine
with David or Virginia?
Whatever, I do not care.
Gilles, better than
either with Virginia.
Yes?
- I have a problem.
- Which?
You know.
Not much, it's worth?
You promised me.
Agree.
Is it too hot?
Yes, but the pores
They should expand.
- How much time is left?
- I do not know, 10 seconds.
1 ... 2 ... 3 ...
- 4. 5 ...
- Come on, pluck it out!
Are you okay?
You have to suffer to be beautiful.
Show me!
We should have done
some shopping.
No, it's delicious.
I feel good here.
I always dreamed of living
close to nature.
Have a calm life,
less stressful.
I should go away ...
I do not know where ...
and where it can restart
a new life ...
as a woman.
What is a woman's life?
A life ...
where you can do everything
I was forbidden to do as a man.
Did you think really?
Yes.
With Lucie, you know
it is impossible.
Yes, I know it's complicated.
But while there is love,
everything is possible.
You're dreaming.
it is only a game. You should stop
and return to reality.
But you also,
you like to play with me.
Before we were not very close,
but Virginia approached us.
No.
It was the death of Laura
that approached us.
So our
dear Laura.
By Laura.
Good evening ladies,
ladies and gentlemen!
As an exclusivity
Amazone, I present
divine ...
the mischievous ...
Wicked ...
Eva Carlton!
I used to relate
something strange men,
as light as the
ash their cigarettes.
evenings in Daban
Palace of Versailles.
They were just straw castles
and wasting my time
gold in the desert.
She was alone when I met you.
The others were buried ...
you were alive.
sings sang as a child.
You were happy as an Italian
when he knows that will
love and wine.
And for the first time
finally felt ...
woman ...
a woman
you.
You had the air of a little old
where galloping
white horses.
Your face was serious
and clear your smile.
I walked right
to your glow.
Today, no matter what we do,
we love close to you
time seems so short.
Because you're a man
and you are tender
and you can do beautiful
our lives
you happy as an Italian
when you know
you will love and wine.
It's always like the first time
when he finally did me ...
woman ...
a woman with you.
A woman ...
you.
Women ...
O woman ...!
A woman ...
you ...
Are you okay?
Yes.
Are you tired?
No.
There's something I did not tell.
What?
When Laura died ...
at the funeral I was asked ...
what clothes I wanted
it was buried.
I proposed to
her wedding dress.
And I asked them out
I who dressed.
are usually
them to do,
but I insisted ...
and accepted.
I was left alone with Laura ...
in the middle of a huge piece.
He was cold and fear.
Then I remembered her smile
the day we met,
their eyes excited,
the day of our wedding,
wedding night.
He gave me courage.
I started to put his socks.
It's slipped ...
delicately ...
on her thighs.
Then ...
I put her blouse ...
I buttoned her dress,
I put her jewelry,
their shoes ...
and I pressed gently
his wreath
in her blonde hair.
It was there, I think ...
that my desire to get
women's clothing ...
reappeared ...
as evidence.
- Good day.
- Hi.
Are you okay?
Did you sleep well?
Not very well.
I told you that bed
it was too small.
It's not that, it's Gilles.
What happened?
I left my cell phone in the bag
and I forgot to call.
He called my mother and she
He said he was not there.
Shit!
You spoke with him?
No. I left many messages,
I'm calling now.
- Are you going to say?
- What?
You're in Crיancy with me.
And why should
to hide it?
You have nothing to reproach.
That's what's important.
I'll be right back.
- It's getting dangerous.
- What?
We must end.
Finish?
- Stop meeting?
- No.
To dress as a woman.
I thought you understood me.
You're sick, David.
You should treat yourself.
You're sleeping with David, is that it?
Of course not.
What are you saying?
So why do I hide
exiting the weekend together?
- He asked me not to tell you anything.
- Why?
Because you were right.
Wait ...
Any reason for what?
David found that ...
who likes men.
And so?
What's it to you?
Y ...
He needed to talk to me,
he feels guilty.
Why they were to Crיancy
to tell you this?
Because there ... it feels good.
Near Laura.
It's not easy, you know?
It is especially difficult to assume
after his death.
I feel good for David.
I know.
Why did you say that?
I had to say something.
If not, sorry.
it's ridiculous.
I'll look like a fool.
Is less severe look like
homosexual and transvestite.
These lies tired me.
To dramatize
You should come home.
What for?
To see that Gilles
there is nothing between us.
There is something between us, Claire.
Yes, but not what you think.
Are you free on Friday night?
Are you your friend Virginia?
- Did not I tell you?
- What?
- Not Free.
- Oh no?
- We will be only three.
- Well yes.
- Good night!
- Hi.
- Between David. I'll help.
- Thank You.
Claire!
David arrived!
With your daughter.
- Are you okay?
- Yes .
Hello small.
Are you okay?
- Goodnight.
- Hello, Claire.
How are you?
I still slept.
He did your bottle?
No, I'll give you sleep well
and we will be quiet.
She is very pretty.
How old are you?
6 months.
Let's sit down.
Are you going to get a bottle?
Yes, come in.
- You want to heat?
- No, it's warm.
I should have been
as Virginia.
- Why do you say that?
- It would be more honest.
I was hungry.
Yes, it is gluttonous.
Are not you looking forward to?
But suddenly you came?
Yes. Anyway ...
I always
I attracted men.
Who knows.
Still before Laura?
While we were together
I never felt like.
He returned after his death.
As evidence.
Today is not a problem.
They come from all sides.
I see it at work. Quarter
types is homosexual.
A lesbians
the note less.
- What will you do with Lucie?
- It is true ...
deceased mother
homosexual father.
It will be complicated.
No, I think not.
I also decided to go back to work.
- Oh yeah?
- Yes.
I need to return to normal life.
My mother got a babysitter
which is responsible for Lucie.
I also see someone.
- Did you meet anyone?
- Yes.
I see a psychologist.
- A psychologist?
- Yes.
A woman, very sweet.
It helps me talk to her,
Laura ...
my future with Lucie.
She understands me, without judgment.
it's okay.
You can not do wrong.
It's late, I must go.
I think I drank one too many.
Do you mind taking me?
I order,
Gilles prefer it.
It does not bother you?
No, no, of course.
I'll get to Lucie.
- Y?
- What?
- There's a guy.
- Because what you say?
No?
He has adventures.
As I pregתntaselo.
David.
What it is this story
a psychologist?
Thou counseled me.
- Did you tell?
- Yes.
What did he say?
Each must find their way
to grieve.
Claire, do we see the
next week?
No.
It ended.
Claire see much better.
Almost no talk about Laura.
Oh yeah?
it is funny.
When I met Claire was
jealous of his relationship with Laura.
They were so close.
I even thought I had
something between them.
No, Laura always
Men liked.
Of course, Claire too.
- In any case it gave us ideas.
- Any ideas?
Yes.
We decided to have a child.
- Do you want me to help you?
- No thanks, it's fine.
Well ...
You have a good day.
Good day.
Shit!
Sorry!
- I'm a mess today.
- No, play well.
No, I'm not in shape.
Look.
- What is he doing here?
- I proposed a double.
- How are you David?
- Completely.
I was waiting for you.
- Hello, Claire.
- Hi David.
- Play the two.
- No, let's make a double.
we are three.
Play the two against me.
Come on.
Let's undo, Claire.
- Are you okay?
- Very stressed.
I like you more than skirt.
Come on.
Bravo!
I drink.
Why do not you call me anymore?
I do not want to bother.
You said it was
all it finished.
- No, I told you ...
- I was scared.
- Of what?
- From start over.
- Did you stop it?
- Yes,
- Since we stopped seeing each other.
- We Play?
DRESS FOR MEN
- Well ...
- Sure.
Sharapova prefer.
- Would you like a ride?
- Thanks, I came with my car.
And Claire?
You did not expect?
Always expected to
women who shower.
Shit!
I forgot my racket!
Are not you well?
I miss Virginia.
Claire!
Wait.
Come with me.
We can not do this to Laura!
How took you!
- Did you see David?
- Yes.
- Is coming?
- He said he did not expect it.
Apology for tennis.
13:30 am-Hotel Virginia
Good morning, Claire.
Good morning, Virginia.
Sorry, I lingered.
I moved into a room.
Here are ladies.
I ordered champagne.
For our reunion.
- Thank You.
You made me fall.
Sorry.
It was during the dinner
home I realized ...
I was falling for you.
You were right. it would have been
better to stop, right?
And in tennis ...
when you told me ...
"I miss Virginia"
all awoke.
I also missed.
I can not waste my life.
It's in me.
Only you can help
to assume.
What do you want to do?
Going shopping with your friend?
Let's lie ...
as eager as I have.
What are we doing here?
Do not say anything.
What's up?
- Sorry, but it can not be.
- Why?
You are a man.
What are you doing?
You are crazy?
No, I am woman.
There are Liz and Robert.
- Good day.
It's horrible, my children,
horrible.
What happened to him?
He was hit by a car
when he crossing the street.
How is it going?
This unconscious, in a coma,
They say it may be as well.
It is atrocious!
Laura left us six months ago
and now David.
He is still alive,
not buried.
You're right, but I think Lucie
which may be an orphan.
- Where is Lucie?
- With the nanny,
we can not take care.
Can you see David?
Yes ...
but ...
- We should say something before.
- What?
Tell them.
is that ...
David, do not know why ...
It was found ...
... Dressed as a woman.
- What woman?
- Yes.
She wore a skirt and a wig.
Oh yeah?
I do not understand why
I was dressed like that.
I think it would
a costume party.
- It was early afternoon, Robert.
- It is true.
Of course, that
Just between you.
- No one must know.
- Keep us confidence, Liz.
David.
Did you you know that besides
fucking he dressed as a woman?
Yes.
It is incredible!
Why did not you tell me?
Excuse Me.
Are you sure the little one?
Yes, I am her godmother.
How are we going to do?
We can not improvise.
I will take leave and
I'll take care of it.
I promised to Laura.
Thank You.
Do not forget to give the bottle
in an hour.
- Yes, good night.
- Goodbye.
Lucie, how are you?
We came to get you.
You'll sleep at home.
Lucie.
I you open.
It is done.
There, that's it.
It is done ...
David.
David, I am.
I came with Lucie.
Do you hear me?
David?
You are right to be
come with the child.
Do you think?
The more you are
present and discuss it ...
more will help you wake up.
¿Virginia?
Virginia, I am.
You are with him?
Do you hear me?
Virginia!
David!
Lady!
- What's up?
- He opened his eyes!
Sir?
Can you hear me sir?
- I swear he opened his eyes.
- I think.
It happens, but not to
said to have left the dream.
His presence makes him well.
David.
Hi!
Do not talk very loud,
Lucie is sleeping.
It's okay?
Yes, just he fell asleep.
I have good news.
What?
Max called me this afternoon ...
and he decided to promote me ...
and raise my.
Great.
You could rejoice.
But, I'm glad.
Well ...
What happened?
Nothing.
David still in a coma ...
It will take time.
Do not worry.
I have the impression of being
living as with Laura.
In the same hospital.
It is horrible.
It's horrible, but leaves
looking back.
Forget about Laura.
Now it's David.
If you're right.
I used to relate
something strange men,
as light as the
ash of his cigarette.
Evenings in Daban
Palace of Versailles.
It was only straw castles
and wasting my time
gold in the desert.
She was alone when I met you.
The others were buried ...
you were alive.
You sang as a child singing.
You were happy as an Italian
when you know you will
Love and wine.
And for the first time
I finally felt ...
woman ...
a woman
you.
Woman ...
woman ...
a woman ...
you.
You had a little the air of yesteryear
where galloping
white horses.
Your face was serious
and your clear smile.
I walked right
to your glow.
Today, no matter what
We do, make love,
near you time
It seems so short.
Because you're a man
and tender are
and you know make beautiful
our lives.
You're happy as an Italian
when you know you will
Love and wine.
It is always like
the first time when ...
when I finally did it ...
woman ...
a ...
She has fun ...
We are here!
Who is it?
- Good night, Gilles.
- Goodnight.
I want you to meet a friend.
But ...
you, David.
No, my friend Virginia.
She is the mother of Lucie.
Lucie's mother.
I'll explain.
I'll be back.
7 YEARS LATER
Translated and synchronized by Vaimac
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/yurf
Help other users to choose the best subtitles