Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Max, come on! Max!
You couldn't just invent
a narrative about me.
You're doing it to yourself as well.
Annie.
Annie, is Max okay?
I know you're probably mad.
But seriously, is he okay?
-We were only trying to...
-We? Okay.
Uh, where are your injuries?
Oh, you don't have any.
Great. I told you you could leave.
You gotta listen to me.
Alex stole a ton of money from Lionfish
and from his own clients.
Miranda's picture was on their computer,
but it said that her name was Elena...
Then maybe it wasn't her. Can you hear
yourself right now, Cassie?
You've totally lost it.
No, listen to me. Max literally saved my
life. He pushed me out of the way of...
So I just got a call
from a friend at the local precinct,
and he told me
that they're holding a 17-year-old girl
who just learned a pretty
fucked-up lesson in driving while high.
So no one was chasing you,
and there's no conspiracy.
No, that's impossible...
Really? Because
that's the part that sounds insane!
Annie, please. This is way bigger
than any of us even thought.
So, in the entire history
of our friendship...
-Are we calling it a friendship?
-What?
Anyway, in all that time,
you've never seen me mad.
So I'd back the fuck off if I were you.
Did they find a flash drive?
It's a "Hello Kitty" flash drive.
Max had it in his pocket.
It was really small.
But it has all the information you need.
There is proof on there, I swear.
As long as you swear, Cassie.
Annie.
Annie!
Wait. Where is Max?
Surgery. Do you understand
the severity of this situation?
Yes. I'm sorry.
I didn't seem them wheel him out, okay?
But where are his clothes? He put
the flash drive in his back pocket.
I watched him do it,
so can you check...
Yeah, okay.
-There's nothing. See?
-He did. He put it in...
No, you don't have any proof, Cassie.
All you have are impossible stories
about stalkers and women on trains
and rich parents with guns.
You're the one that told me
about the Sokolovs, okay?
And the proof you need is on that...
Don't you dare say fucking
"Hello Kitty" to me one more time,
I swear to God.
There is no drive, Cassie.
We were trying to help you, okay?
We were trying to get information
that didn't come from you...
-Oh, you were concerned about me!
-Yes!
Oh, my God. Okay. That's great.
Ask me about my day.
So I can tell you about the fucking hell
that I went through for you
-before I even found out about Max.
-What?
-Ask me.
-What are you talking about?
-Just shut up! Shut up!
-You just told me to ask you!
Okay...
So Max is very injured.
-And all you can talk about is you.
-That's not true.
-I did CPR. I called 911.
-Oh, my God.
Congratulations, Cassie, for being
a human and doing the right thing.
-That's amazing.
-What else was I supposed to do?
I am sorry.
I did not mean for him to get hurt.
I'm done.
Annie.
Get your shit out of my house.
I'm done.
Cassie? It's pretty late.
Oh, God. Sorry.
I didn't even realize how late it was.
So I just thought we should,
like, connect more.
I'm sorry. Are you asking me
to, like, hang out with you?
We should do something, you know?
Yeah, I'll see you on the Rome flight.
Wait. The Rome flight? What?
In two days?
Girl, you are such a mess.
God.
You got Shane.
Leave a message.
-Hi, Cassie.
-Hey, Megan. Whatcha doing?
Are you gonna call
every person you know?
Are you pathologically incapable
of being alone?
Are you?
I do not wanna be in this room, okay?
I wanna be in the real world
with my real friends.
Good luck with that.
You've alienated everyone in your life.
Yeah, you're crazy.
My friends love me.
Do you wanna go get oysters?
Just me and you,
like a little girl's oyster night.
-You okay?
-Yes. I'm totally fine.
In fact, I'm really good. I'm sorry.
This is, like, super last minute.
But you always say we
don't hang out enough.
So I thought,
let's hang out, right?
Okay, Cassie. We're both adults.
And I can tell the difference
between real excited and fake excited.
-So what do you need?
-Why do you always think
-something is wrong?
-Maybe it's because it feels like you
only call me when you need something.
Does it really? That's interesting.
Because I thought you wanted me
to call you more.
You know, the way you call me all the
time, leaving me so many messages.
Cassie, I already apologized
for calling so often.
You even left me a message in Korean.
Yeah. So you're leaving me messages
in other languages,
but I just wanna simply call
you but I guess I can't do that, so...
Korean message? How?
Yeah. You and some guy. Talking.
I don't...
You know what?
It was actually Bill and I. Yes.
Yes, we had this weird sex thing.
And it's just totally embarrassing.
So could you just delete that for me?
Nah. I think I'm gonna keep it.
I'm gonna keep it for fun.
Gonna translate it later
when I feel like it.
No, no. No. You know what? Where
are you? I'll meet you for that drink.
You know what? Nope. I'm over it.
Vibe ruined. You ruined it.
-I should've fucking known.
-Cassie? Cassie!
I need. I need you. I need...
Hi.
Well, that was a quick answer.
Are you lonely?
Do you wanna see me?
Yes, and absolutely yes.
-All right. See you at my place.
-Okay.
No, no, no, no, no.
I do not wanna be in this room.
I am leaving!
That's never happened before.
Cassie, you gotta stop
lying to yourself.
No! No, no, no, no.
You stay in there.
-And I'm gonna stay out here.
-So here's what we're gonna do.
We're just gonna talk this through
like rational adults.
You can't ignore me, Cassie.
I'm hungry.
Do you wanna get breakfast?
Excuse me. Hi. Can we get
some more bottomless mimosas please?
-Yeah.
-No, no, no, no, no, no.
Can we keep those?
You know what? I can't see the bottom
of this. This is, in fact, bottomless.
-You know what's also bottomless?
-What?
What are you doing?
Oh, my God.
Hi, everyone.
Oh, she didn't like what she saw.
-Come here.
-Yes.
So, we have this weird policy where
we require people to stay fully clothed.
You need to pay and go.
So Cassie went to Alex's apartment,
then came here.
That's right. I saw the guy she was with
pick the lock to get in.
Why is an empty warehouse so important?
Maybe they stole all the stuff.
If they had access to a big truck maybe.
If they had a big truck, you would've
seen it when you were following her.
Isn't it time for your next shift?
-What?
-What's with the federal raid
-of Lionfish?
-Well, thanks to the blonde woman,
they had to clean everything out
overnight.
Hold on.
How the fuck do you know about that?
-Because I'm watching it happen.
-God damn it.
You told Victor you were back in London.
Why are you in New York?
And why does everyone have to
listen to him except for you?
I just need to clean things up before
Victor realizes I'm not in London. Kay?
Good luck with that.
Oh, come on.
Outside of this, we're friends.
Jesus, I even let you
take care of my cat.
For two years.
It's not your cat anymore.
It's my cat that I never wanted
just like these fuckin' phone calls.
Yeah, okay. Listen.
If Victor asks, I just need you to tell
him that you've seen me in London.
Okay?
Would you do that for me?
I'll pay you. Cash.
Fine. A few more days.
But that is it.
Feed my cat.
-Ooh, hey, girl!
-Hi, Mick! Hey, babe.
-Hey, can we get two please?
-You a regular or?
Uh, you know, just a little.
-You know I love this song.
-I know you do, Cassie.
It's my favorite.
-What song is this?
-Here you come again
You know the words too. Sing it.
To get myself together
You waltz right through the door
Just like you've done before
And I wrap my heart
Around your little finger
Cassie...
This is not funny.
What the hell are you doing?
Cassie!
-Hey. Let's go sit over there.
-Okay.
We never go into the city
on our weekly dates. This is fun, huh?
-Mom, where are we going?
-I gotta make a quick stop.
But I thought that we could
go to Big Gay Ice Cream. Sound fun?
Yeah, I guess. Stop where though?
Cassie has something of mine
that I need to pick up.
And she's not answering
any of texts, so...
Oh, my God. Can't this wait until,
I don't know, I'm not involved?
Sorry. I need this right now
so please get over it.
Cassie. Cassie is the absolute worst.
Why do you even like her?
'Cause she's my best friend.
Thank you.
It's kind of sad how you think this
party monster girl is your best friend.
You know what?
I like her, okay?
She does whatever she wants
and revels in it, and people love her.
And Eli, that is...
I just hope
that you never have to experience
feeling unseen or unwanted
in your life, okay?
'Cause if someone was to make you feel
that way, it's just terrible.
Are you even listening to me?
-I found Cassie.
-What?
Here she is. At a bar singing
Dolly Parton songs 28 minutes ago.
That is genius.
How did you do that?
So we're going to a bar. Cool.
No. I'm going to a bar.
You are going to wait
in the car, young man.
Oh, come on.
Cassie?
Cassie!
Behind you, do you see
that guy over there?
-Yeah. The one with the checkered tie?
-Okay. You can see him too?
-Yeah.
-Okay, good,
'cause he's been following me.
-This is not the first time.
-So you've got a stalker?
Brag.
Thing is... Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I think he's an assassin.
Wait. Is this some sort of fantasy
role play thing or something?
Okay.
Fuck it. I'm gonna go. I'm gonna
ask him. I can't take this anymore.
Wait, ask to see his passport.
Or his license to kill.
Hey, hey. Are you stalking me?
Are you trying to kill me?
Because I know all about Lionfish.
And I know you've been following me,
so what's up with that?
Wait a minute. Are you FBI?
Just tell me you're FBI,
and then I'll leave you alone.
I would love that because
that would mean I was safe!
Okay. This is good.
Wink.
Just give me a wink and then I'll know.
Then I'll know.
It's like a sign.
Okay. That was not a wink
but it was something.
-You're FBI.
-Nah, I'm just...
Yeah. I knew it.
You're nuts, lady.
-Drinks?
-Fresh drinks!
-Okay. Move it over, buddy.
-Hey. Come on in.
Okay.
-So?
-What?
-How'd it go with your stalker?
-Oh, no, no. Everything's totally fine.
It's no big deal. It's the FBI.
They're watching me.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
I mean, I didn't know I was dating
someone who was so important.
Are we dating now?
Is that what we're doing?
Yeah. Okay, okay. What if I say
we should just run away together?
Just run away
from everything right now?
What would you say?
Um, that's...
It's a good question.
I'm gonna think about that answer.
And I'm gonna come back...
-Okay.
-And I'm gonna tell you.
I'll tell you my answer
when you get back.
Oh, my God.
This is such bullshit!
You can't run away from me.
I'm in your head.
-It's just me and the mess.
-Fine, that's fine. You can be here.
But I don't wanna be in this room.
I thought I made that pretty clear
when I ran out the door.
I don't know, but unlike everyone else,
you can't seem to get rid of me.
Well, you said no one would
wanna spend time with me.
-You were wrong.
-Sure.
It's been a great night and day
with dead cat guy.
I was talking
about people who know you.
Oh, great. Please.
Share your wisdom please.
I'm not telling you anything
you don't know. You get it?
I'm telling you that even
though your life is in real danger,
your only wish is that anybody,
literally anybody,
had answered your call
because Annie cut you off.
That's just sad.
It's not... Annie and I...
We'll make up. We'll be fine.
-We're always fine.
-She's done. I saw it. I was there.
No. No. I'll prove you wrong.
Hasn't happened yet.
You're the worst.
Hey, hey. Sorry I had you wait out here,
but I found Cassie, got what I wanted...
Cool. Whatever, Mom.
Well, thank you for your help.
Hey. I gotta go fix things with
my girlfriend, Annie, like, right now.
-Oh, yeah. She's your lawyer friend.
-Yeah. Come on. We're leaving.
-Where's my phone?
-Okay.
-Are you sitting on it?
-No.
Where is it?
It's on the fucking floor.
-I mean...
-Wait. Where are you taking me?
Do you really care where
I'm taking you?
No.
I would go anywhere with you.
Good. That's what I thought.
Let's go.
You didn't mention Bowden brought up
Lionfish when you interviewed.
-Are those my notes?
-It's your field report.
-It didn't really register.
-Is it completely lost on you
that the warehouse we were standing
in earlier is leased to Lionfish?
How was I to know that one of the crazy
things she's said could be relevant?
Bowden was in that warehouse.
And at Unisphere and at the Sokolov's.
And all those things, she's
linking in her statement.
Try this. Bowden and Sokolov
knew each other in New York.
So they were flirting on the plane
because they were already involved.
Something went bad in Bangkok
during their marathon love fest.
She snapped. She killed him. Everything
she's been doing since that moment
has been cleaning up any proof that
they knew each other before the flight.
What about everything she said outside
of Sabrina Oznowich's apartment?
If you wanna look into her crazy
statement, then great!
That sounds like a really fun project
for you. I'm staying focused on Bowden.
Being your partner is really
infuriating sometimes.
Come on.
So, do you always hang out
in your friends' apartments
when they're not home?
No.
They gotta come home sometime, right?
-Here. You take that one.
-Thanks.
You're welcome.
She's home.
-Holy fuck. Are you for real?
-Hi.
We need to talk. I had to come here.
-Who's this?
-Yes.
This is Buckley.
He is a guy that I am...
-Buckley.
-No, you're right. You gotta go.
-But we just got here.
-I know. He's gonna leave.
Nice to meet you.
-He's leaving.
-I'll be right here.
Yeah. You should leave.
Annie, I am so truly sorry
about what happened.
You have to know that.
Yeah, no. You said that already.
And I got it. And I want you to leave.
Any time you and I get bad,
we always... we fix this.
Okay, so the man
that I love... fucking fuck.
Yep, okay.
The man that I love is laying in
a hospital bed and it's your fault so...
-You love him?
-No, no. This is not a sharing moment.
I'm really sick of having
to excuse you and forgive you
'cause I'm not the answer, Cass,
to whatever crazy thing it is
that you're trying to drown out with,
like, partying and booze and Buckleys.
And what the fuck kind
of name is Buckley?
-It's a family name.
-Okay. Can you go away?
Hold on.
Let me get this straight.
-You're sick of forgiving me?
-Yeah.
How about me having to forgive you?
I'm sorry. What?
I have forgiven you for so much shit.
I mean, let's think.
Oh, yes! Our trip in Cabo
when I fell asleep in the bar,
and you left me there!
Yes? Yeah. That was...
How about the trip to Palm Springs?
That bed... you broke the bed
and then you blamed it on me?
And I paid for it.
Like, what was that?
Okay, so, Cassie,
you got Max hit by a car.
I know.
I feel horrible about it.
I'd never... But friends, we mess up,
and then we forgive each other.
-And I am only asking for...
-Cassie, let's just be honest.
Our friendship just doesn't work, so...
You want honesty?
So I come to you as a friend, right?
And you want me to tell you things.
And I tell you someone's stalking me.
And you didn't believe me.
What do I do with that?
What about your honesty, Annie?
I still don't know
what you do for work
and why you have a creepy
third cell phone from 2004.
And I didn't even know Max existed!
-Yeah, you're right.
-Yeah.
What?
You're right.
Maybe... our friendship only works
because... we don't show each other
the messy bits.
You never had to call me a liar
and I never had to call you a drunk
but that's what we are, Cass.
-I am not a drunk.
-You can barely stand up straight.
If you wanna call me names and not
believe what I tell you, that's fine.
But you are not better than me.
I didn't say that I...
I just called myself a liar.
God...
Okay. You know what?
So I don't have the emotional bandwidth
to fight with you today,
'cause I'm a little tapped out.
So I'm done.
And I'm gonna need you to get your
puppy from the hallway and leave please.
Kay.
You know what, Annie?
You know what?
I did not think this would go like this.
Did your plan go wrong?
I'm so sorry.
My heart breaks for you, Cass.
Grow the fuck up, okay?
You know, you're gonna feel
really bad when I wind up dead.
-Come on. Let's go do something crazy.
-Yeah! Crazy.
What the hell is this?
They think this is funny?
This pony is completely chained up here.
It's fucking animal abuse.
It's not a real pony.
Symbolism? Ever heard of it?
I don't like what this represents.
The world is a messed up place.
Hey. But what if we set him free?
And we're back!
Look, I get that you're in denial
but do you realize what you are about
to do in broad daylight?
Do you know why Buckley is
so much better than you?
Because he wants me
to be me, you know?
He doesn't, like, judge me or he doesn't
question every fucking move I make!
-What do you mean?
-You wanted to do something crazy.
-Let's set him free!
-What do you mean?
Just help me, help me, come on.
If we get bogged down in logistics,
we'll never do it. Just do it.
Wait, wait, wait, hold on.
Too hard.
You're about to steal a ride
that's designed for children!
Okay. You know what?
I'm gonna tell you a thing.
-You ready to hear a thing?
-Yes.
Here it is. I am not gonna
always think about you. Okay?
I feel like I should
but I'm not going to because I can't.
Because if I keep thinking about you,
I'm gonna go insane.
Do you want me to go insane?
Let's go.
-Let's go. Let's go.
-Wait...
-Just go!
-Oh, my God.
-Hurry up!
-Wait, wait, hold on.
Oh, my God. Oh, fuck.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
-What the...
-Look at his dumb face.
-I am so sorry. I didn't mean to...
-It was...
-Hey. They stole my horse!
-No.
Fuck! Fuck.
-We are justice!
-Hell yeah!
Annie? How's Max?
Jessica...
He's fine.
He's fine. You got my message.
Thanks for coming.
I just didn't wanna be gone for too
long in case... in case I don't know.
I brought you something you can't kill.
I mean, something that won't die.
Oh, my God. I just didn't think
you'd want flowers...
It's fine.
Thank you, Jessica. It's fine.
Please take this to give to Diana.
It's my letter of resignation
from Davis & Carlisle.
Oh, wow. Why?
Sorry, I mean,
shouldn't you give it to her yourself?
No. Yeah, no.
If I go in there, she'll convince me
to stay because I... want to.
But I realize that I can't, so...
I don't understand. Is it the firm?
I mean, you're so good.
This is cute.
Your name isn't Jessica, is it?
It's Jennifer, actually.
Right. That's...
Cassie was right.
Wow, I fucking hate that.
Why would you let me call you Jessica?
You know what? Don't answer that.
Just, you shouldn't let people
tell you who you are.
Like, for instance, my name's actually
pronounced Ah-nie. It's Armenian.
But when I was little,
kids just started calling me Annie
and so my name just kind of changed.
Do you not like Annie?
Look, what people call you
is important, okay?
Like, I don't know.
Say they call you an ace lawyer.
And one day, you just fucking
withhold discovery.
Or start meeting with clients
in meat lockers.
And then suddenly a woman eating
a rare steak
is just, like, asking you
to murder a man. And that happens.
-Oh, my God.
-What?
Wow, sorry. That...
Please just don't let people like Diana
or like me tell you who you are. Okay?
I don't think
I can just become a Jessica,
but I'll miss working for you.
And I'll give this to Diana.
Breathing is so important.
We can forget to be present and just
experience this moment. This now.
-Oh, shit.
-It's happening to you.
-It can seem elusive...
-Fuck you.
You have to let go of the worries
that are beyond your control.
Every breath becomes a wave of comfort
washing over you,
washing over
your present circumstances.
You have the power to stop...
You're doing it right now, you know?
You don't even realize it.
-Why is it changing?
-Let's go. He's not coming.
-Yes, he is.
-He's probably getting drunk somewhere.
-Shut up, Davey.
-If he cared, he'd be here.
He just doesn't care about you
because all you do is complain!
In fact, he hates you. And so do I.
Stop!
Hand cake.
Stop. Don't do that.
-What's going on with your memory?
-No, you're doing this to me.
Whatever this is, you're doing it.
-Double fist!
-Dad, you're gonna ruin it.
-Let go of me.
-Dad...
-What's wrong with you?
-Come on! We were playing around.
It was an accident.
You two are so uptight.
And you're too full of beer to know
what you're doing, Hank. Jesus.
Get up. You're not hurt.
Get the hell up.
-Why did that change?
-This is what really happened.
No. This is not what happened.
We were having fun.
That was my fault. I started that.
I don't wanna see this!
What the hell is that noise?
No.
This is what really happened.
She's just a child.
You act like she's your drinking buddy.
I'd drink with my son
if he wasn't such a little fag.
God!
No, no, no.
Hello?
This is a collect call
from the 120th Street Correctional
Facility in New York.
To accept, say "Accept."
I'll accept.
Cassie?
Uh, hey.
This is my one phone call. So...
I'm your phone call?
Yeah.
Wait, isn't there someone closer
that you could... like Annie?
No. I'm just...I just need to talk
to you real quick. Don't worry.
Well, I wish I could, like, I wish
I didn't have to... Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Cassie, you're not fine.
This is not a fine phone call.
So here's the thing...
All these years,
I thought you were so crazy.
Like, I treated you
like you were crazy, you know?
Your version of our childhood
was just so unreal.
Like it was not real to me.
And I can't change what Dad did,
you know, and how he acted
but I think I was part of it.
And I was so wrong.
I am so, so, so sorry, you know?
I'm starting to think
that it was kind of my fault.
-No.
-And I'm so sorry.
No. I never... I never thought that.
I just remember Dad being so good.
I really wanted him to be good.
I know. We all do what we can...
Listen. Do you wanna
tell me what's going on?
Because I know something is going on.
-Maybe I can help.
-No.
Just, you know,
ruining my life one person a time.
-I can't drag you into that.
-You can. You can, yes.
You can drag me into this 'cause what's
the point of having a big brother if...
You know,
gotta be good for something.
I just have to figure some stuff out.
Really.
It's gonna be okay.
Right. Cassie...
You know I love you.
It's not okay how Dad treated you.
I know.
But it's not okay
how he treated you either.
Yeah... Okay. I gotta go now.
I love you. I gotta go now.
You know, I didn't realize
when you joined the swim team,
it meant that I would be
waking up with you.
Thank you for that.
-Here. I made this for you.
-Thanks.
And don't chug it all at once or else
you'll be bouncing off the walls, okay?
Ma, for what it's worth,
I actually had fun playing detective
with you yesterday.
You can be pretty cool.
Sometimes.
-Good luck today.
-Thanks.
-No.
-What are you doing up so early?
There's some computer issue at work.
They need me now.
-Right now?
-Yes, right now.
-What comp...
-I don't know.
-I'll call you later.
-Okay.
-I love you, baby.
-Love you too.
Hey, Bowden. Wake up.
You posted bail.
I... Really?
Who posted it? Was it Buckley,
that guy I came in with?
-I don't even know his last name.
-No. He's still being held.
Get up. Let's go.
Whole world's waiting.
We need to talk.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org