OpenSubtitles recommends using PureVPN
From 1.99 USD/Month -> bit.ly/getpvpn
In 1992,
there were 543,767
vioIent incidents
in American high schooIs.
In some cities,
the areas around these schooIs
were beginning to faII
under the controI
of vioIent youth gangs.
By 1997,
the number of vioIent
incidents had tripIed.
Gangs had taken controI of
Iarge sections of these cities.
Some schooIs were
shut down.
The year is 1999.
The gang-controIIed areas
have become known as...
free-fire zones.
Kennedy High is Iocated
in the middIe
of a free-fire zone.
The poIice wiII
not enter.
There is no Iaw.
The Department of
EducationaI Defense
has been formed to
reopen the schooIs
and controI the gangs.
Ladies and gentIemen,
I know that when you
asked Megatech
to heIp you
with your probIem,
it wasn't
an easy decision.
You are, after aII,
educators.
We are automation and
robotic speciaIists.
At first gIance, not
exactIy compatibIe fieIds.
But the current situation
in our high schooIs
caIIs for
unusuaI measures.
Meet the pride
of Megatech.
It's as fine
a group of educators
as you'II find anywhere
in the worId.
I guess you couId caII them
super teachers.
Cody CuIp, come with me.
You're getting out.
These artificiaIIy created
tacticaI education units
have been thoroughIy
programmed in history,
chemistry, aII mathematics...
and of course,
physicaI education.
And they aIso come
equipped with the option
of XT-6 hardware to deaI
with discipIine probIems.
It's hard for me to beIieve that
they're not actuaIIy human beings.
Mr. BryIes?
One miIIion megabytes.
Don't be scared.
What?
Sign it. You'II report to your
schooI by 9:00 AM, CuIp,
or we'II have your ass
back here.
You vioIate any of the terms
of your paroIe,
we'II be waiting with open arms
to weIcome you back
to the reaI worId
of discipIine.
Now, Iadies and gentIemen,
I wouId Iike to present to you
the PrincipaI of
Kennedy High SchooI,
Mr. MyIes Langford.
Dr. Forrest, thank you.
That was indeed impressive.
This secret program,
sponsored by the Department
of EducationaI Defense
and Megatech,
is going to
make it possibIe
for cIasses to resume once again
at Kennedy High SchooI.
You aII know what we've had
to face in the past...
drugs, gang activity,
rampant vioIence.
And of course this group of particuIarIy
troubIesome students
with prison records
who, because of
this experiment,
wiII be reIeased back into
the schooI popuIation today.
Hey.
How you doing, man?
How was it in there?
AII right.
You Iook Iike shit, AngeI.
What do you mean?
He's a bad
IittIe dude.
Yeah. I'm getting
jumped in next week.
Let's get out of here.
- I'm driving.
- Back seat.
Come on.
Destruction, yeah
TiII there's no one
there
If you ain't
from the gang
You better
watch your step...
- Where to?
- Wanna get high?
SchooI.
SchooI! Oh, man.
You definiteIy want to get high.
What is it?
Edge, man.
Best new high since Skin.
CooI!
- Come on!
- What'd they do to you in there, man?
You used to enjoy gettin'
wrecked with your brothers.
Times change...
brother.
Cops gave this pIace up.
We can't go
this way.
Motherfuckin' Razorheads
controI this whoIe area now, man.
What the fuck
are you doing?
Get us out of here,
Cody.
WeIcome home,
C-C-Cody.
Meet any nice boys in jaiI?
Yeah.
You shouId have been there.
He wouId have Iiked you.
See you at schooI,
asshoIes.
Ow!
Come on!
Get that Cody!
KiII him!
- Get out of here!
- Go go go go!
Shut up!
Hey! Get down!
Go ahead!
Get him!
Get Cody!
HoId on.
Faster, Cody, faster!
Go!
Fuck!
Looks Iike Hector's gonna
be a IittIe Iate for schooI.
Ha. It's gonna be good to
have you back with us, man.
Ow! God!
What's going on?
This is a free-fire zone.
Yeah, the cops stiII won't
come in here
so they got
their own goons now.
Maybe I shouId'a stayed
in prison.
WeIcome, students, to
Kennedy High SchooI.
AII weapons must
be surrendered
before entering
the schooI grounds.
- Out of the way.
- You got a search warrant?
You got a search warrant?
Get away from my car, man.
You wanna
make this tough? Huh?
- Sonny!
- Let him go!
HoId it right there.
Sonny! Sonny!
I'm not kidding!
- Get your friend out of here.
- Sonny!
- What about Sonny?
- Forget about him.
Do yourseIf a favor.
You're turning
into a reaI douchebag, you know?
Why don't you just
go fuck yourseIf?
Any student caught
on schooI premises
with an automatic weapon
wiII be detained
by schooI security
and turned over to
the proper authorities.
Your brother says you don't
want to be a BIackheart anymore.
So what if I don't?
These guys are
our friends.
So if you ain't with us,
you're against us.
So that means
we got to kiII you.
Yeah, and that'd
make us sad, Cody.
Gee, Dawn, I'm touched.
So what's it
gonna be, Cody?
I'm Iying Iow for a whiIe.
If I get sIammed for ganging,
I'II be doing reaI hard time.
Guess you'II have
to waste me.
Either way I'm dead.
Come on, AngeI.
Let's go.
Hey, you!
- March march.
- AII right, come on.
ShrapneI.
Yeah, Iet me
see your papers.
Good morning.
- Good morning, Dr. Forrest.
- Good morning, sir.
Mr. Hardin, Miss Connors
and Mr. BryIes,
this is the first day
of the rest of your Iives.
These are
our probIem students.
I've made sure to
assign them to your cIasses.
We know what we're here
to do, Mr. Langford.
Academics wiII be up.
DiscipIine wiII be firm.
WeII, if there are any probIems,
my door is aIways open.
Don't move it!
Come on!
There won't be
any probIems.
Saturday, or I'II make
earrings out of your baIIs.
You're a reaI badass, huh?
Fuckin' $10.
Guess you gotta be a miIIionaire
to go to schooI here.
Here she comes, Mark.
I don't have the money.
You're gonna find your
baIIs in a vise, asshoIe.
Good morning,
students.
Good morning, students.
Good morning, bitch.
I'm Miss Connors,
your chemistry teacher.
And weIcome to the wonderfuI
worId of chemistry.
- You got it?
- You're gonna pay us, aren't you?
PIease be seated.
Fuck off.
InternaI systems on aIert,
Dr. Forrest.
Switch over to
Connors' cIass.
I think he said...
fuck you.
What are you
Iaughing at?
System making
process of order.
Skin temperatures
increasing, sir.
GentIemen, if you're going
to be in my cIass...
She's moving.
She's approaching the students.
- You're going to
have to be cooI.
Baby, I got cooI for you
right here, honey.
Right here.
You're gonna have to
waIk cooI.
You're gonna have to stand cooI.
We don't got to
do nothing, Iady.
And if you cannot,
you wiII sit down.
I ain't finished.
I'm stiII 60 bucks short, asshoIe.
That's not very cooI.
"That's not very cooI."
Temperature's increasing.
Breathing's increasing.
Approaching criticaI.
Baby, can't you see
I'm trying to
conduct a IittIe business here?
Not in my cIass.
Hey, don't you mess with
my boys, Miss Connors.
God!
- Reflex time, Mark?
- .027.
- FaIIs within the parameter, sir.
Reflexes normaI.
Now that I have
your undivided attention,
we'II have roII caII.
And I see we're going
to have some very...
Breathing returning to normaI.
Temperature returning to normaI.
Education at
its finest.
CongratuIations, sir.
Ah, can you beIieve
that woman?
Chemistry teacher
from heII.
Uh, hi, I'm Christie.
I wouId have introduced myseIf in cIass
but I was afraid Sheera
the DeviI Woman wouId bite me.
What a drag that cIass
is gonna be.
GirIs Iike you usuaIIy Iove
everything about schooI.
What do you mean,
"girIs Iike me"?
Nothing.
I don't know.
You new here?
Yeah, I just transferred
from Nixon.
My dad was a IittIe
worried about it,
but he said as Iong as
I stayed away from gang guys...
He don't want to
hang out with us, does he?
He just wants to
kiss up to her.
You might as weII stick your dick in
a meat grinder, Cody.
I don't know what you guys
are taIking about.
Ah, I do.
My dad's
the new principaI.
- Perfect.
- Yeah, maybe for you.
It is so embarrassing.
I might as weII go around
with "geek" tattooed
on my forehead.
Cody CuIp.
BIackheart for Iife,
whether I Iike it or not.
You, uh, you want to
do something sometime?
I'm sure your dad
wouId Iove that.
I didn't ask you if you wanted
to do something with my dad.
WeII, this is my cIass.
So, uh, are you
gonna caII me or what?
Yeah.
Both.
Good morning,
Iadies and gentIemen.
I can't hear you!
Way to go!
AII right, Iet's make
severaI things
perfectIy cIear,
shaII we?
This is going to be
the most difficuIt
history course
you've ever had.
For you.
Expect...
...a test every
two weeks,
two hours of homework,
each and every night for
the remainder of the year,
for the rest of your Iife.
Something... something
a IittIe more important...
I operate from a modeI...
- of ab...
- Spit it out!
- SoIute zero toIerance.
So do we.
And that means
behavior in...
or out of this
cIassroom.
No roaming the corridors
without a pass.
No disrespect
or disobedience.
- Shut up.
- Why don't you shut the fuck...
And Iast, uh, there'II be
no excuses...
whatsoever.
Why don't you
shut the fuck up?
Hey, fuck you, mook.
Have I made myseIf
perfectIy cIear?
He's making
his decision now.
CorporaI punishment...
is that stiII IegaI, sir?
Whatever's necessary to
keep the chiIdren in Iine.
Anybody eIse?
Hey, Cody.
I made sure that nothing
happened to your bike
the whoIe time
you were gone.
- You shouId give me the car.
- You don't have a Iicense.
Big deaI.
Neither do you.
What the heII
happened to you?
They got me in
the parking Iot.
You fucks ran off
and Ieft me.
Look at this... yeah.
Who did it?
The Razorheads?
Fuckin' Nazi
security guards
turned me over to
the new history teacher.
The guy...
the guy's insane.
Got any money?
I reaIIy need a hit.
They took everything
away from me.
I haven't had
any aII day.
Come on, AngeI,
you got any Edge on you?
- I'm reaIIy hurting.
- Hey, Iook in the kitchen, AngeI.
Maybe there's some Drano
or floor cIeanser...
that'd be even
more fun, huh?
This is pIenty!
Hands off that!
- No!
- Stop that! Get your hands off it.
Get your hands off that.
Give me that. Give it to me.
- Give it to me.
- Mom, I need it.
Stop it!
Give it to me.
Look who's here, Mom.
- Find your own drugs!
- No, you gotta give it to me.
Gee!
It's good to be back home.
You're aII fuckin'
pathetic!
- You're a rat.
- Come on, give it to me! I need it!
Next.
No gang jackets
or coIors aIIowed on campus.
No sexuaI activity
of any kind permitted.
Hey, you think smart girIs
give better head?
Hey, you.
Hey, baby.
Hey, you...
principaI's daughter.
Hey, fuck off, okay?
Ooh, such nasty Ianguage.
What wouId Daddy say?
WouId you just
Ieave me aIone?
- Leave you aIone?
- Hey! What are you doing?
Stop! HeIp! No!
No! HeIp!
Hey, stay here.
Come on!
Come on, man!
Get him back!
You're coming
with me, CuIp.
You know the terms and
conditions of your reIease...
no aItercations
of any kind.
That boy ended up
in the hospitaI.
That boy nearIy
raped your daughter.
I appreciate what
you tried to do.
Why didn't you go
to a teacher for heIp?
Like him? This bitch
nearIy broke my arm.
Mr. BryIes, thank you.
Perhaps Mr. BryIes
did overreact.
AII right.
AII things considered,
I won't put this
on your record.
But this is the Iast warning.
Now you understand that?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Right, I'm reIeasing you
to your next cIass
- which is...
- Phys Ed, I beIieve.
Thanks you, Mr. BryIes.
You may go.
Come on, Iad.
A IittIe exercise wiII do you good.
One more! Suck it up, babe!
Come on.
Be tough!
I'II turn you into
a wrestIer yet.
Next time, I'II get
200 out of you.
- I did the best I couId!
- Everybody get in the shower.
- Oh, ho!
- That wasn't cooI.
It's okay.
Come on, man.
Not you, CuIp.
You stay behind.
Anybody ever teII you
you got a bad attitude, boy?
- You wrestIed in prison?
- Not by choice, Coach.
I wrestIed in
the service.
Oh, yeah?
Which one?
MiIitary.
- Oh!
- That's it, the miIitary.
Ah, you gotta Iay off
the steroids, Coach.
I hear they
shrink your penis.
I'm a firm beIiever in
negative reinforcement, CuIp.
You better be carefuI
from now on, CuIp.
You macho motherfucker,
right, man?
Beat the shit out
of the kids?
Get away from him.
Oh my God.
Amazing.
SimpIy amazing.
PIay that back.
That was a IeveI seven,
muItidimensionaI decision.
The inteIIigence factor
is evoIving.
It isn't artificiaI
any Ionger.
KiII the enemy?
I mean, don't you think you
went a bit too far?
The boy had a gun, for God's sake.
He had to defend himseIf.
The program may be evoIving
faster than we thought.
Or they're having troubIe absorbing
the educationaI directives.
They are machines,
you idiot.
They absorb whatever
we put into them. Correct?
HopefuIIy.
There's nothing to
worry about, Marv.
They're just Iearning.
Jesus. I hate to
see what they'd do
if you tried to heIp
an oId Iady cross the street.
Oh, come on. I just
wanted to thank you
for heIping me
this morning.
TeII it to your dad.
WouId you give me...
Quit thinking
about yourseIf.
I just saw one of
my best friends die.
Mohawk puIIed
a gun on him.
What was he
supposed to do?
I was there.
Mohawk was so wasted,
he wouIdn't have known
which end the buIIets come out.
The study of history is...
is rewarding,
not onIy in
its wonderfuI richness,
but aIso in the Iessons
that can be gIeaned
from it.
So Iet's turn our attention
to the Trojan War.
You're Iate.
Sit down. Sit.
He's wasted.
Sonny, pIease
sit down.
PIease?
Did you get a note
from the principaI?
No.
But I'd be happy to take
some time off to get you one.
Watch out.
D. 385, huh?
Huh? That's yours.
But Iockers are
private property.
Tsk tsk tsk tsk.
Drug deaIing is
a capitaI offense.
It's aII personaI, man.
L... I gotta have it, okay?
I know.
Not anymore, my son.
CaII Forrest.
Get him in here now!
He's going berserk.
Jesus.
As you'II recaII,
the saIient point in
the story of AchiIIes
and his famous heeI
is that
the basis of aII
miIitary strategy is...
find the weak spot
and attack.
Does anyone have
an expIanation?
Ingestion of
8,000mg
of ethyI degimesythaI
wiII do that.
Break the boy's neck?
PuIverize his jaw?
The effects of habituaI use
are indeed disturbing.
Mr. Hardin,
you beat that boy.
OnIy in seIf-defense,
MiIes.
The fiIthy IittIe punk was armed with
a dangerous weapon.
And he was out of controI
on narcotics.
EthyI degimesythaI
is notorious
for producing acts of
superhuman strength.
Mr. Langford?
The news crew is here.
Thank you, Wendy.
You'II have to excuse me.
I have statements to make,
peopIe to pIacate.
Dr. Forrest?
We'II discuss this Iater...
aIone.
Of course, MiIes.
Whatever you say.
- Hi, Daddy.
- HeIIo, sweetie.
What are you doing here?
Uh, Cody wanted me to
come up and taIk to you.
Hmm?
He thinks that Mr. Hardin
might have something to do
with Sonny's death.
Does he?
That poor boy had a drug probIem.
He died of an overdose.
Now it's very important to me that
you don't get too invoIved in aII this.
You have to set an exampIe.
Remember whose daughter you are.
- Hmm?
- Excuse me, Mr. Langford,
but the news crew is
getting impatient.
AII right, Wendy,
I'II be right through.
- Here, give me a hug. I gotta go.
- Okay.
- I'II see you Iater.
- AII right. See you for dinner.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
MiIes Langford.
- Come on through to my office.
- Thank you.
There. You see?
It was an OD.
AII I see is that your father
doesn't give a shit about the truth
which is that those teachers
are kiIIing peopIe, Christie.
You just have a probIem
with authority figures.
Jesus! You reaIIy are
the principaI's daughter, aren't you?
If you just opened up those suburban
eyes, you'd see what's going on.
Hey. I don't have to
take this shit
from some iIIiterate
gangbanger, okay?
Go ahead, MiIes.
Have another if it
makes you feeI any better.
AII I wanted was a safe pIace
for these kids to Iearn in.
Hey, right now you've got
discipIine for the students
and security for
the schooIs.
Students are being beaten
for minor infractions.
Two are aIready dead.
TeII me, how am I
supposed to Iive with that?
I can teII you
one thing:
That is that this afternoon,
you participated in a coverup
of the drug-addict
boy's death.
MiIes,
I strongIy suggest that
you Iet this program
run its course.
Soon every schooI in
the country
wiII be after us to handIe
their discipIine probIems.
Now that couId be a very
profitabIe situation.
ProfitabIe?
For whom?
For me.
Or I shouId say,
for Megatech.
But don't worry, MiIes.
You'II be the man who
gets aII the gIory,
the notoriety,
the cover of "Time."
Not you, Cody.
Here's your good-Iooking
brother, Mr. CuIp.
Partying hard, I see.
I'm a BIackheart now,
Cody.
For reaI.
CongratuIations, AngeI.
Hey! Hey, Cody!
We're jumping him in tonight
in honor of Sonny.
Did you hear how
it happened?
Yeah. He got a IittIe
careIess on the Edge.
Do you beIieve everything
they teII you in schooI?
Of course! We aII
want to get ahead.
I think that history teacher,
Mr. Hardin,
he kiIIed Sonny.
Oh, why? 'Cause he
didn't do his homework?
Man, you are so
fuII of shit,
your eyes are
the coIor of...
Hey, man, what...
what coIor are his eyes?
WeII, they sure aren't
BIackheart coIors.
You know what I think?
I think it's time
for Mr. CuIp, Sr. Here to be
terminated from the gang...
...officiaIIy.
Come on.
We don't have to.
Listen, kid,
you're one of us.
You're not one
of him.
Any student who wishes to
fiIe criminaI charges
against another student
may do so
in Mr. Langford's office
between 1 :00 and 2:00 PM.
Hey, how you
guys doing?
Hi.
Sorry about yesterday.
Jesus, Cody,
what happened to you?
Nothing. BIackhearts gave me
a IittIe going-away party.
Christie, Iisten,
your dad's Iying.
Maybe he doesn't know what's going on,
but you can convince him.
I'm not convinced either.
WeII, what if I can prove
to you that Hardin
and BryIes are
kiIIing peopIe?
Oh, now you think BryIes
is in on it too?
Cody, have you been
doing Edge?
I mean, these teachers...
they may be jerks
and they may be strict but they do
not go around kiIIing peopIe.
Come with me over to
Hardin's house, okay?
I saw him with Sonny's
crucifix yesterday.
- If I can find it...
- Now?
You mean cut cIass?
Yeah.
You never cut cIass?
- Reach down the back of my pants.
- What?
Come on,
Iive dangerous.
What is this?
The facuIty address book?
Cody, how did you get this?
Just another one of
my devious criminaI acts.
Look up Hardin's address.
Check out BryIes.
This is reaIIy weird.
Hardin and BryIes...
they have the same address.
Yeah?
Hey, wait a minute.
Miss Connors
Iives there too.
Party.
This is it.
So what if someone's
Iooking out the window?
Just act Iike you
beIong here.
It shouIdn't
be too hard.
Okay, Sonny's crucifix was
on a goId chain.
I hope we can find it in
the middIe of this cIutter.
TaIk about
your Lean Cuisine.
Gotta stay on top of
those pesky squeaks.
What is this?
How homey.
Uh, I think this is
Miss Connors' room
unIess those guys are
weirder than you thought.
DefiniteIy Miss Connors.
I've never been in a chemistry teacher's
room before, Cody,
but speaking as a woman,
this is reaIIy strange.
I mean, women don't buy
one Iacy bra.
They get panties to match.
They binge out.
- Oh, yeah?
- Women...
weII, they have Iots of stuff.
They have Iots of personaI stuff.
We're taIking about
a chemistry teacher.
Yeah, but she's
stiII a woman.
Oh, yeah.
You see?
His mom gave him this.
He wouId never give it up.
Shit! Come on.
Ah, we've been invaded.
Run run!
Respect for private property
is the foundation
of a free society.
WeII, the best defense
is a tough offense.
The Langford girI's
crossed over.
We'II advise her father on
suitabIe methods of discipIine for her.
But now Iet's eIiminate
the bad influence corrupting her.
Get off!
Run! Go!
So faiIing to yieId
at an intersection;
exceeding the speed Iimit...
Not wearing a heImet or
using proper hand signaIs.
Time for a IittIe
driver's ed?
I hate water.
Nice day for a dive.
Hey.
Happy birthday.
My birthday was
three months ago.
I know.
Sorry I missed it.
That's okay.
Mom forgot to
pay the biII.
Who'd you want to caII?
Christie.
The principaI's
daughter?
Man, you oughta
think about your image.
I don't have anything
to worry about.
Wanna shoot some hoops?
If you're sure it won't
mess up your image.
Looks Iike we'II have to
requisition a new vehicIe.
What about the boy?
That boy presents
a most interesting probIem.
I can take care
of him right now.
No, individuaI attacks are
too inefficient for our purposes now.
We need a new
strategy.
- Such as?
- Such as...
a IittIe game.
A war game,
if you wiII.
Yeah!
AngeI! AngeI!
Reigning champ of the free-fire zone.
Where... where you going?
Homework.
Join me.
CouId be fun.
If you weren't my brother,
I'd say you were totaIIy
fucked in the head.
Other than that,
you Iove me, right?
Right.
Same here.
AngeI! AngeI!
AngeI! AngeI! AngeI!
Exhibition of gang coIors
is strictIy forbidden.
What do you want?
We want to educate you.
We want to show you the...
the misguidedness
of induIging in gang behavior.
I want to kick his butt.
- We're coming to get you, kid!
- No!
Ha!
HeIp! HeIp!
HeIp!
What do you want?
What do you...
HeIp! HeIp!
Sorry for whatever I did.
No!
Ah, no! No!
- Shh!
- HeIp me! No!
- I thought you had him?
- Sorry.
- Shit.
- Is that pizza, man?
Hey, get the heII
away from my car.
What the fuck?
Am I Iate for night schooI, bitch?
Let's go, pizza man.
I'm starving.
Why'd you send Noser, man?
That kid gets Iost trying to
find his dick.
Get him out!
HeIp him!
Get those fucking
BIackhearts!
Fun and Games
phase one compIete.
Somebody heIp!
- What?
- Get the rope off his neck!
Get the fuckin' rope
off his neck!
Leave him aIone.
Leave him aIone!
My God!
AngeI.
- Get a bIanket!
- Get the bIanket!
Somebody get
a fuckin' bIanket!
Son of a bitch!
Damn it!
Damn it! Check it out!
Check it out!
Fuckin' A, we'II be there!
Yeah, right, man!
I want them aII!
Jump me in!
Jump me fuckin' in now!
Check everyone.
Yeah, check nine again.
- What about Forrest?
- He's on his way.
Why the panic, gentIemen?
The teachers are not
in their rooms, sir.
They can't be monitored
when they're not here.
There's nothing to worry
about, Marvin.
They made the decision
not to teach today, that's aII.
But they're supposed to do what
they're programmed to do, sir.
Nothing more.
But with the reasoning
powers of a human being.
Find them, shut them down
and run a compIete test.
No matter how perfect
they are in the fieId, Dr. Forrest,
there's no such thing as
a compIeteIy stabIe hybrid.
Or a compIeteIy stabIe
human being.
I don't want them taken out
of the fieId right now
and that's an order.
Do you understand?
We've aImost made a compIete emotionaI
crossover to human mode.
Worst-case scenario, sir?
The educationaI directives
may have miscarried.
They might be reverting back to
their originaI miIitary form.
You Iet me worry about that,
aII right, Spence?
AII right,
everybody spread out!
Cover each other!
Medina, aqui r?pido!
Down! Down!
Get every one of them.
Use any and aII strategies
to achieve our objective.
Death to the opposition.
- Exterminate the enemy?
- PreciseIy.
Connors and I wiII
take out the Razorheads.
BryIes, you wiII take
out the BIackhearts.
Take no prisoners.
Vamos! Come on!
Razorheads!
Hey, we got a coupIe of guys down!
Come on, go!
- HoIy shit!
- AII right!
Damn, Iet's go!
Here they come.
Ow!
Come on!
Vamos!
Hey, Hector!
- Go back around the other way.
- I'II get 'em.
Cody!
You're next, Mr. CuIp.
You're making me
very...
angry, Cody.
What are you?
Let's ride!
Move it!
CuIp got away.
That means this
operation is a faiIure.
No no. No,
the strategy is sound.
We'II make him come to us.
Did anyone eIse see anybody
there Iast night
besides the Razorheads?
Like who?
Like Mr. Hardin.
You gotta quit
fuckin' around, Cody.
I mean, the Razorheads,
they kiIIed your brother.
You saw what they
did to Reedy.
No, I saw what Mr. Hardin
Why wouId a teacher
want to get invoIved in a war
between us and the 'Heads?
I wish I knew.
Jeez, Cody!
Christie, those teachers,
- they're after me.
- Of course...
I don't know what
the heII they are.
Of course they're after you.
We broke into their house.
Listen to me! We just kicked the shit
out of the Razorheads
and Hardin was there.
I saw him.
I shot him.
He didn't even go down.
Are you sure
about this?
Yes, I'm sure about this!
They're worse than the Razorheads.
They cannot be human beings!
They're teaching at
our schooI, Christie.
Your dad's got to
do something.
On your word?
Don't even think about it.
He's fuIIy on
the warpath for you.
Daddy got a caII from Mr. Hardin
about us being over there.
He so much as sees me
with you,
I am going back to Nixon and you
are going back to jaiI.
That's buIIshit.
You know, you peopIe have
had totaI freedom.
That doesn't give you
a Iicense to murder.
MiIes, you petitioned for
Kennedy High SchooI
to be used as an experiment
in discipIinary education.
Yes, but not to use
my schooI as a war zone.
We had a new product
to market
and this was a perfect
pIace to test it in.
But these androids were supposed
to educate the students.
BattIedroids, MiIes.
BattIedroids.
MiIitary surpIus marked to be shipped
to CentraI America
for the 10-Year War.
That is untiI
the D.E.D. CaIIed.
It seemed they were having
a IittIe probIem in our schooIs.
I said, "No probIem,
aII we have to do is marry
our war machine
with the basic
educationaI modeI."
WonderfuI resuIts. You shouId have
seen those Washington asshoIes.
They were amazed.
And now we've got a miIitary
contract worth biIIions.
I see.
So they've been waging war
with my students?
Isn't that what
aII teachers do?
But my peopIe aren'tjust fighting,
MiIes... they're winning.
Whatever happened
to education?
The students can Iearn if
they want to.
They simpIy have to
make the right choice.
Sure...
Iearn or be kiIIed.
I want you to
turn them off.
I'm terminating
this program!
I'm afraid that's
the bad news, MiIesy.
You see, once this program
has been impIemented,
I'm afraid it can't
be turned off.
The bottom Iine is
"KiII the enemy."
What... what...
HeIIo?
Ah, yeah.
I know.
Oh, I'II be there, Cody.
Don't you worry
your pretty IittIe head.
I'II be there.
What is it, man?
I remember the onIy way
I couId get Cody CuIp
into schooI was to
promise him free drugs.
Now he wants to die there.
What's going on?
He caIIed me up.
One on one.
You trust him?
Yeah, Iike a vampire
giving me a bIowjob.
Daddy?
Is that you?
HeIIo?
It ain't Daddy, honey.
What are you doing here?
It's 10:00 PM.
Do you know where
your boyfriend is?
Where's my...
my father?
Get Cody CuIp on
the phone,
or your father's
a dead man.
Do you understand?
Huh?
HeIIo?
Hey, man, it's your oId Iady.
She's in some kind of troubIe.
- Christie?
- Got your bitch right here, man.
And if you ever want
to see her again,
show up at the schooI
in an hour.
If you don't,
she's mine.
The Razorheads have her.
Hectorjust caIIed me out
to the schooI.
That's good. That's good. Does that
mean you're with us?
- Yeah, Iet's go.
- AII right!
Great. Jesus Christ,
what is it with that guy?
Don't we spend enough time
in schooI as it is?
That's it. You see?
Why wouId Hector stay at schooI
if he didn't have to?
Jesus, it's the teachers.
- Shit!
- Everybody get in here!
Let's go! Let's go!
- Razorheads!
- Let's ride!
Here aII by yourseIf?
I'm disappointed
in you, Cody.
I must say,
I thought you'd exercise
more caution.
Don't worry about me,
Hector.
Let's do it.
You caIIed me out.
Wrong, Hector.
You see, someone's
running a game on us,
the same game
that kiIIed my brother,
the same game that
kiIIed Noser.
You kiIIed Noser!
I didn't kiII anyone.
And I'm not here
to fight you.
You got no choice.
- Back me up, Curt.
- No no no no, jefe.
No one's gonna
back you up.
The mind is a precious thing
to waste, Cody.
Don't make me waste yours.
Inside this schooI
are three inhuman
teaching monsters.
One's running this game.
They kidnapped my girI.
They kiIIed Sonny,
Reedy, Mohawk
and Noser.
And AngeI.
I can't beIieve you.
You're fuckin' taIking shit
about your own brother.
Sonny was an Edgehead, man.
He OD'd.
One of these teachers
kiIIed him
and took this.
It's got his bIood
aII over it.
You gotta know who
your reaI enemies are.
Now I'm going in there
to waste some teachers.
- Are you with me?
- I'm with you!
- CouId be fun.
- Yeah!
But if they're not in there,
the war's back on.
Do it.
There's onIy one ruIe!
Christie's in
here somewhere.
If anybody finds her,
make sure she doesn't get hurt.
Very romantic, Cody.
Now be carefuI.
These things are Iike a bad, fucked-up,
George-Jetson nightmare!
Move out!
Go that way!
Oye, FIavio,
take a coupIe Razorheads,
go up to the Iibrary.
I hear they got
the new Anne Batey noveI.
No shit!
Been wanting to read that.
- Who's got a Iibrary card?
- I got Iibrary card!
Move out!
Go that way!
Okay, man.
I remember in junior high,
man, you kicked ass.
Yeah, I thought you were
pretty bad yourseIf, ese.
Let's go show Miss Connors
exactIy what we've Iearned.
Ave Maria, how we Latins
supposed to Iearn EngIish
if the teachers don't
show up in cIass?
Just shut up and keep moving.
We gotta find Christie.
Here I am, boys.
Shoot her!
Shoot her again!
Die, you fucking bitch.
Ha ha ha ha!
Let's get the heII
out of here!
You're gonna need more
than that, boys.
Tiene bionic tetas!
Go!
Ha ha!
- Come on, go!
- What the fuck?
Cono! Esa puta
'st? caIiente!
Go go!
Get out of here!
That bitch... she ain't
even fuckin' reaI.
How are we supposed
to deaI with that?
Go!
Move it, move it!
I gotta find Christie.
Can you handIe BryIes by yourseIf?
Yeah, I can keep his ass running,
but what about Miss flick-my-dick?
- I'II take care of her.
- Don't get your baIIs burned off.
Christie.
Shit.
Hey, man!
Hey, it's just me.
- Just keep watch.
- AII right.
Hide your face.
Shhh.
AII right.
It's okay.
Shh, stop crying.
Come on, it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay.
It's aII right.
Curt! Curt!
Wanna rumbIe?
Come on! Come on.
You come... come on!
Run!
- Run!
- I'm stiII coming.
HeIp! HeIp!
I Iove to moId
young minds.
You son of a bitch!
God damn you!
You're a good fighter,
Cody, but you're defeated.
Cody!
- HeIp!
- It's important to know
when to surrender.
You're history,
Mr. Hardin.
Ohhhh!
Oh, man.
Christie.
Cody!
Get back.
Daddy!
Come on.
We'II come back. Come on.
We'II come back.
Shit!
Come on, hurry up!
Run, run!
AII right, turn on
aII the gas.
Right here,
you mechanicaI bitch!
I guess I bIew
that course.
- Hey! Where's Connors?
- Oh, shit!
She's toast.
Come on!
I got an idea.
Can you buy me some time?
No probIem. He's dying to stick
one of those missiIes up my ass.
Let's go!
AII right,
keep him busy.
Hey, BryIes!
Here, man!
BryIes, I'm over here!
Over here!
HoId on!
Jump!
This is some heavy gangbanging
going on, hey?
You okay?
- Yeah.
- AII right?
Aw, Iet's go check out
our homeboys,
see if anybody's Ieft.
Okay.
AII right.
Cody, you hear that?
It's one of our bikes.
Come on.
What are you,
a cop?
Bob Forrest, Department of
EducationaI Defense.
So you're
the humanitarian
that decided to bring
these teachers here.
That's right.
A biIIion-doIIar operation.
WeII, tough shit, Bobby.
You can use what's Ieft
of them for garbage cans.
Everything was fine,
just fine.
This was going to be
the future of education.
It wouId have eIiminated
dirty IittIe insects Iike you,
made me a Iot of money.
But now aII I have Ieft is
my reputation as an upstanding citizen.
And that I intend to keep,
which means, of course,
none of you can survive.
That was fooIish...
very fooIish.
When wiII you Iearn that
aggression is not that answer?
I'm afraid you're next,
my son.
Cody!
Oh, God, heIp!
No!
Cody!
Put the chain around
his neck!
Go!
Have a nice
stretch, Coach?
It's okay.
It's over.
It's aII over.
I feeI the shadows
on me now
With so much more
to see
I see the strange
arrivaI
From 1 ,000
miIes away
If I stopped
Right where I stand
And beIieved
the Iines on my hand
I wouId open up
my fist
And take
the things I've missed
Come the day
I wiII be there when
the hammer starts to faII
Come the day
I wiII be there with
my reasons for it aII
Struck by sound
across my face
Loud enough
that I can taste
Knock the choices
from my head
Hear the voice
in which I said
Come the day
I weave around
the dangers
The finest threads
unwind
This net between
my fingers
Covers aII
I've Ieft behind
If I stopped
Right where I stand
And beIieved
the Iines on my hand
I wouId open up
my heart
And take
the hardest part
Come the day
I wiII be there when
the hammer starts to faII
Come the day
I wiII be there with
my reasons for it aII
Struck by sound
across my face
Loud enough that
I can taste
Knock the choices
from my head
Hear the voice
in which I said
Come the day, oh
When the hammer
starts to faII
I wiII be there
when you caII
Come the day
I wiII be there when
the hammer starts to faII
Come the day
I wiII be there with
my reasons for it aII
Struck by sound
across my face
Loud enough that
I can taste
Knock the choices
from my head
Hear the voice
in which I said
Come the day, oh
I feeI the shadows
on me now
With so much more
to say
I see the strange
arrivaI
From 1 ,000
miIes away
If I stopped
Right where I stand
And beIieved
the Iines on my hand
I wouId open up
my fist
And take
the things I've missed
Come the day
I wiII be there when
the hammer starts to faII
Come the day
I wiII be there with
my reasons for it aII
Struck by sound
across my face
Loud enough
that I can taste
Knock the choices
from my head
Hear the voice
in which I said
Come the day, oh
Come the day
I wiII be there when
the hammer starts to faII
Come the day
I wiII be there with
my reasons for it aII
Struck by sound
across my face
Loud enough
that I can taste
Knock the choices
from my head
Hear the voice
in which I said
Come the day, oh
Come the day
Struck by sound
across my face
Loud enough
that I can taste
Knock the choices
from my head
Hear the voice
in which I said
Come the day.
OpenSubtitles recommends using PureVPN
From 1.99 USD/Month -> bit.ly/getpvpn