(SHOP BELL RINGS)
("LOST WOMAN" PLAYING)
VANYA: "My name is Vanya Hargreeves,
and this is my story."
♪ Don't know where to run to ♪
♪ Don't know where to hide ♪
♪ Seen my future comin' ♪
♪ Like the rising of the tide ♪
♪ But I lost you ♪
♪ Lonely woman ♪
VANYA: "We were never a real family.
We were our father's creation,
family in name...
And smile.
But not in fact."
VANYA: "In the end,
after our brother Ben had died,
there was really nothing connecting us.
We were just strangers
living under the same roof..."
"...destined to be alone..."
(PANTING)
VANYA: "...starved for attention..."
Oh.
VANYA: "...damaged by our upbringing..."
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Oh, my God.
She wrote that?
I can't believe she would do that.
Shh!
VANYA: "...and haunted
by what might have been."
"We all wanted to be loved
by a man incapable of giving love."
"Our father never missed an opportunity
to remind me that I was ordinary.
A hard thing for a little girl to hear."
VANYA: "If you're raised to believe
nothing about you is special,
if the benchmark is extraordinary,
what do you do if you're not?"
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
(PANTING) Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
(CHAMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
Shit.
(VIOLIN CASE CLATTERING)
(MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY)
Um... I'm so sorry I'm late.
I hadn't noticed. (CLEARS THROAT)
(TAPS BATON)
CONDUCTOR: From the top.
(MUSIC RESUMES)
(LUTHER SIGHS)Play it again.
ALLISON: We've watched it over and over,
Luther.
It's the same every time.
(LUTHER SIGHS)
(VCR WHIRS)
Er... (STAMMERS) What is she doing?
The tea. Did she poison him?
ALLISON: Uh... (SIGHS) I don't know.
(LUTHER SIGHS)
Where did you find this?
I was looking
at old footage of us as kids,
and I saw the tape just sitting there.
Yeah, Dad must have started using
the security system again.
He was getting more and more paranoid.
He thought people were out to get him.
Well...
I guess maybe he was right.
But Mom?
I mean, she's not capable of...
(SIGHS) Is she?
(MOM HUMMING)
(SIZZLING)
LUTHER: Mom?
We need to ask you some questions
about the night that Dad died.
Do you remember anything?
Of course. Sunset, 7:33 p.m.
Moon was waxing crescent,
dinner was Cornish hen,
wild rice, and carrots.
No. No, uh... later that night.
In his bedroom.
Did you go and see him?
(CHUCKLES) I don't recall.
(HUMMING)
Were you ever...
I don't know, angry with Dad?
(SCRAPING ON PAN)
Your father was a good man.
A kind man.
He was very good to me.
Yes, but after we all left,
it must have been difficult.
Oh, there were days.
You kids kept me oh so busy, and then...
What?
What were you gonna say?
Eggs are ready!
Breakfast is the most important meal
of the day.
Now, eat up.
Both of you.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
PATCH: Do you seriously
still not understand the chain of custody?
If you touch it, I can't use it.
Let me save you some time
running ballistics.
These nine-millimeters
haven't been manufactured
since 19...
1963. Odd, I know.
Matching casings were found
at a murder scene last night.
Ishmael's Towing.
DIEGO: The driver?
PATCH: Found him hanging
from the ceiling.
Looks like he must have known something
after all.
It's a shame nobody told you
to go talk to him.
(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
In the span of 24 hours, I've had attacks
in three different places across town.
Whatever this is, whoever this is,
they're not slowing down.
So, if you really give a shit
and you've got any fresh ideas,
I'm all ears.
The guy's kid, in the doughnut shop?
I've got units tracking
the extended family
in case anyone goes after him.
Well, this place must have
surveillance footage.
PATCH: No, it doesn't exist.
The first unit on the scene
clocked two shooters fleeing the premises,
wearing, get this,
creepy kids' masks.
The city is really going to shit, huh?
Coming from the guy dressed in spandex?
It's not spandex, it's leather.
And you used to like it.
A lot, if I recall.
God, please un-remember that.
Etched into the data bank, Eudora.
And we're done.
Yeah, well, you go fill out your forms
while I go hunt these animals down.
And, Detective,
I do give a shit.
(SIGHS) I still can't get over the fact
that you two used to...
Not another word, Beeman.
Not another damn word.
(WATER RUNS)
(VIOLINS PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(WATER RUNS)
Helen...
You were great today.
Really, really great.
Thanks.
It's those runs in the Stravinsky.
I've been hacking at them for weeks,
and you just make...
Make them look easy?
What's your name again?
Vanya.
And how many years have you been stuck
at third chair?
At a certain point,
it's not about practice.
It's whether you've got something special.
And maybe you just... don't.
You can put in your 10,000 hours,
or... you can go find something
you're actually passionate about
and stop slogging away at Stravinsky
like a scared 13-year-old.
Think it over.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIZZLING)
(MAN ON TV) ...at an RV park.
But they can have generators on them,
they can have their own tanks for waste,
everything.
All these materials, this is
what I'd use on a normal house...
I don't understand
how you can watch this crap.
You don't find it interesting,
how ordinary people live their lives?
They're agonizing over kitchen cabinets
as if the entire fate of the universe
rests on whether they choose azure blue
or asparagus green.
And your point is?
Sometimes there's beauty in the mundane,
you know?
Well, then, this is
the most beautiful room I've ever seen.
(WHOOSHING SOUND)
(CLANK)
Seven percent reduction in payment
due to job delay.
Further reduction every 24 hours
until job completion.
That is just... I mean...
It's only been one lousy day.
Let's see 'em get out
from behind their desks,
get their hands dirty for once.
Damn lazy bastards.
(WHOOSHING)
Are you done?
Yeah.
Well, let's get back out there
and kill this little shit.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
KLAUS: Damn it, where's Dad's stuff?
BEN: Can we go see a movie or something?
Or the ocean?
Shut up!
I'm trying to find whatever...
priceless crap was in that priceless box
so that Pogo will get off my ass!
I'd ask what you're up to, Klaus,
but then it occurred to me...
I don't care.
Hey! (LAUGHS)
You know there are easier ways
out of the house, buddy?
This one involved
the least amount of talking.
Or so I thought.
Hey, hey, hey, so...
You need any more company today?
I could, uh... clear my schedule.
Looks like you've got your hands full.
Oh, this? No, no. I can do this whenever.
I'm just...
(CLATTERING)
KLAUS: I just misplaced something.
That's all.
Oh!
Found it! Thank God! (SIGHS)
(GULPS) Delicious.
I'm done funding your drug habit.
KLAUS: Come on! You don't...
Maybe I just wanna hang out
with my brother.
Not you.
¡Mi hermano!
I love you!
Even if you can't love yourself!
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
Oh, shit.
Hey. (SIGHS)
Sorry you were in there for so long,
Delores.
No, I'm not drunk.
I'm working.
Yes, it's about the eye thing.
This is the place it was made.
Or... will be made.
(SIGHS) We just have to wait.
I don't like this any more than you do,
but she's hiding something.
Hiding? To me, she just sounded confused.
Well, uh... You saw the tape.
Grace knew what she was doing.
Grace?
This morning, she was Mom.
She's a machine, Allison.
Who read to us and cleaned up after us
and put us to bed.
And then we left her here, alone,
in this house for 13 years.
(SCOFFS) I mean,
no wonder she lost her mind.
To be away from your kids?
Hey, what happened with... Claire?
With Patrick?
You never told me.
Yeah, I don't wanna talk about it.
It's just... when we were kids,
we used to sit in here
and tell each other everything.
Yeah, and then we grew up.
(SIGHS)
Things got ugly between Patrick and me.
Now the court says I have to do
this mandatory therapy thing
before I can have visitation.
What for?
You used your power on her.
I mean, there were days
where she'd have these epic meltdowns.
And no matter what I said,
she wouldn't stop.
She was three then, and I...
I know that's what three-year-olds
are supposed to do.
So I said I would do it that one time.
Only it wasn't just that one time.
I told myself any... parent
with my power would do the same.
(SCOFFS) That it wasn't wrong.
I just had an advantage.
I mean, from the time I was little,
I used it to get everything I wanted.
Mm-hmm.
With Dad, with my career...
(SIGHS)
But now, I know nothing
in my life was real.
So I'm starting over.
(SIGHS)
I just didn't think it would be so hard.
It'll get easier.
Some things just take time.
Yeah.
And some things just stay broken.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You're still lookin' for Mr. Puddles.
I... I got out of rehearsal and was
in the neighborhood, so I thought...
I...
Came all the way to Bricktown?
Well, since you're here,
you might as well come in.
(KEYS JINGLE)
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
VANYA: These are beautiful.
LEONARD: Ah, thank you.
Restoration antiques.
It's my bread and butter.
But I do play around with other things.
Like what?
Oh...
I don't know.
It's kind of embarrassing.
Come on.
VANYA: You made all these?
When I was a kid,
my imagination was my escape.
And, clearly, I never grew up.
No, it's amazing.
Which one is your favorite?
Ballerina is kind of my best.
Or maybe the duck.
Or the other duck.
(CHUCKLES)
But there is one you should see.
Is that...?
LEONARD: Okay, so I might have...
stayed up last night making this.
Wow.
It's beautiful.
Thank you. Take it.
Oh, no. I...
I insist. Please.
I made it for you.
You inspired me.
This is so bizarre.
We've known each other for... two days?
I feel like you know me better
than anyone in my family.
(CHUCKLES) Hey.
This might be a little inappropriate,
seeing as I'm your...
impressionable young student, but...
would you want to have dinner
with me tonight?
You don't have to if you don't want to.
Yeah.
LEONARD: It's fast...
No, I...
I know, but...
I'd like that.
Yeah?
VANYA: Allison?
Hey.
Leonard, this is my sister, Allison.
Wait a second, I know you.
You were in that movie.
You're in the movie, the...
You were the lawyer.
The tough one in the wheelchair, right?
Yeah. (CHUCKLES) Yeah, that was me.
You didn't tell me your sister
was a movie star.
Wow!
You were in that Umbrella thing, too,
weren't you?
But you weren't in that, were you?
No, uh... I was sort of the fifth Beatle
of the family, so...
I never really did like the Beatles.
More of a Stones guy, myself.
Um, I'm sorry to interrupt, but,
uh... could you come back to the house?
We're having a family meeting.
And you guys want me there?
Of course.
It's about Mom.
I'm so sorry. I...
Oh, don't be.
We'll do a rain check on dinner.
Bye.
Thanks.
LEONARD: Yeah.
Who's the guy?
VANYA: He's a... just a friend.
Friend?
No, it's not...
Maybe I'm just trying
to not separate myself
from everything and everyone.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said
those things to you yesterday.
I was angry with Patrick, and I...
I took it out on you.
I'm really sorry.
I'm, uh...
I'm not good at this whole sister thing.
I hadn't noticed.
Ouch.
Tell me how you really feel.
Maybe I will.
(ALLISON LAUGHS) Okay!
(SIGHS)
BOY: Kick it over here!
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
(BOY ECHOING) Whoa!
(ECHOING) No!
LUTHER: Five.
Five!
Hey, Five.
(KNOCKING)
No!
LUTHER: Five!
What are you... (MUTTERING)
Oh, my God... (GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
You okay?
You shouldn't be...
How did you find me?
LUTHER: Um...
Hey, baby...
Hey, a little privacy, guys.
We're really hitting it off back here.
(SCREAMS)
Get out! You can't be here!
I'm in the middle of something.
Any luck finding your one-eyed man?
(WHISPERS) No.
What's he talkin' about?
Does it matter? It's Klaus.
(FIVE SIGHS)
What do you want, Luther?
Um...
So, Grace may have had something to do
with Dad's death.
So I need you to come back to the academy,
all right? It's important.
"It's important."
You have no concept of what's important.
Hey!
Did I ever tell you guys about the time
I waxed my ass with chocolate pudding?
(LAUGHS)
It was so painful.
What are you still doing here?
Ay, ay, ay...
What?
I... What? I need an excuse to hang out
with my family?
We're trying to have
a serious conversation.
What, and I'm incapable of being serious?
Is that what you're saying?
Luther's got a point, you should get out.
What?
Fine!
LUTHER: What the hell are you up to?
FIVE: You wouldn't understand.
Try me. Last I checked,
I'm still the leader of this family.
Well, last I checked,
I'm 28 years older than you.
You know what your problem is?
Really hoping you'll tell me.
You think you're better than us.
You always have. Even when we were kids.
(SIGHS)
But the truth is, you're just as messed up
as the rest of us.
We're all you have.
And you know it.
I don't think that I'm better than you,
Number One.
I know I am.
(CHUCKLES)
I've done unimaginable things,
things you couldn't even comprehend.
Right.
Just to get back here and save you all.
(SHOP BELL RINGS)
Whoo!
NAN: Stop!
(GRUNTS)
Hey! Stop right now!
KLAUS: Hey, bitches!
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
NAN: You, get back here!
(TIRES SCREECH)
KLAUS: Out of the way, asshole!
Now I'm starting to wonder
if that was the wisest decision.
(TIRES SQUEAL)
AGNES: You really love doughnuts,
don't you?
Is there anything better in this world?
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I suppose not.
Though I guess I'm kind of biased,
seeing as how I make them all day,
every day.
(CHUCKLES)
All day, every day.
Elaborate.
Well, um...
I get here before the sun's up.
I measure out the dry ingredients,
I mix in the slurry real slow,
and load 'em all into the extruder.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) Extruder.
Yep.
That's what makes them
into the doughnut shapes.
The real trick is, um...
I let 'em rise for about half an hour
before I fry 'em up.
That's what makes them so...
light and fluffy.
How come you're so light and fluffy?
(LAUGHS) Well,
I guess you are what you eat.
(CHUCKLES)
Uh, might I try a raspberry jelly?
Oh. Sure.
(WHISPERS) The secret's in the jelly.
Agnes.
Beautiful name.
Well, thanks.
It means "pure."
(TOILET FLUSHES)
Of course it does.
(DOOR OPENS)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(CLEARS THROAT) So, uh...
is there anything
that you might be able to tell us
about the night that this place
got shot up?
Um... Well, I... I mean,
I already told the police
everything I know.
Twice, actually. (CHUCKLES)
Do you remember the boy from that night?
I didn't really notice him, to be honest.
Uh, him and his father sat
right over there.
(BELL RINGS)
That most definitely was not his father.
HAZEL: We're just concerned for his...
safety, is all.
It's a dangerous world out there.
Wouldn't want anything bad
to happen to him.
Are you with the police?
We were hired by his family
to help get to the bottom of things.
So if there's anything you could tell us,
we'd really appreciate it.
I'd really... appreciate it.
I'd... I'd really like to help,
but I wouldn't know anything about that.
Although, come to think of it,
there was one thing.
He had a... um, a tattoo on his wrist.
I mean, who lets a kid get a tattoo?
Unbelievable.
(SIGHS)
You mind drawing that tattoo?
Sure, I... Yeah, I can...
(WHISPERS) It was a circle... and...
Good. And there was... Ah, yeah.
VANYA: I mean, do you really think
Mom would hurt Dad?
You haven't been home
in a long time, Vanya.
Maybe you don't know Grace anymore.
If he was poisoned, it would have shown
in the coroner's report.
Well, I don't need a report
to tell me what I can see
with my own eyes.
Maybe all that low gravity
in space messed with your vision.
(BUTTON CLICKS)
Look closer.
Dad has his monocle. Mom stands up.
Monocle's gone.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, yeah!
She wasn't poisoning him.
She was... taking it.
To clean it.
LUTHER: Then where is it?
No, I've searched the house,
including her things. She doesn't have it.
She doesn't have it.
That's because I took it from her.
After the funeral.
You've had the monocle this whole time?
What the hell, Diego?
Give it to me.
I threw it away.
You what?
(SCOFFS)
Look, I knew that if you found it on Mom,
you'd lose your shit,
just like you're doing right now.
Diego, you son of a bitch.
VANYA: Hey. No. Calm down.
Look, I know Dad wasn't exactly
an open book.
But I do remember one thing he said.
Mom was, well, designed to be a caretaker,
but... also as a protector.
What does that mean?
VANYA: She was programmed to intervene
if someone's life was in jeopardy.
Well, if her hardware is degrading,
then...
We need to turn her off.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
She's not just a vacuum cleaner
you can throw in a closet.
She feels things, I've seen it!
She just stood there, Diego,
and watched our father die.
I'm with Luther.
Surprise, surprise.
Shut up.
I... I don't...
Yeah, she shouldn't get a vote.
LUTHER: Wh...
I was gonna say that I agree with you.
DIEGO: Okay. She should get a vote.
What about you, stoner boy?
What do you got?
Oh, so, what? You need my help now?
Oh, "Get out of the van, Klaus!"
"Well, welcome back to the van."
What van?
(SCOFFS) What's it gonna be, Klaus?
I'm with Diego, because screw you!
And if Ben were here,
he'd agree with me.
No, I don't.
(HISSES)
DIEGO: So that's three?
Wait.
To two.
ALLISON: Vote's not final yet.
What?
Five's not here.
The whole family has to vote.
We owe each other that.
Right.
No, we should wait.
Hey.
How long you been here?
You all seem upset. I'll make cookies.
Do you ever wonder...
All those moments with Mom,
the things she said.
Like, was it her, or was it really Dad?
What are you talking about?
Well, he built her.
And he programmed her to be a mom,
to be our mom.
Sometimes when I look at her,
I just see him.
Maybe that was true at first.
But she evolved.
Well, how do you know?
Because Dad only loved himself.
(ALARMS BLARING)
(ALLISON SIGHS) Coming through!
Come on, Luther!
How will the Umbrella Academy
ever become an effective crime deterrent
if we can't even leave the house
on time for missions?
LUTHER: Behind you!
Come along, children! Come along!
(ALLISON PANTING)
I can't find my domino mask.
It needed a little bit of TLC
after the last mission.
Thanks, Mom.
Ready to go?
(GRUNTS) Yeah.
DIEGO: Where's my knives?
(VIOLIN PLAYING)
Sounds beautiful, Vanya.
Thanks, Mom.
(LAUGHING)
GRACE: Oh! Klaus!
Thank you, Mother.
Boys will be boys.
Oh, Ben.
It... It's stuck.
BEN: Guys, wait for me.
DIEGO: D... Don't mmm...
(STUTTERING) Don't mm... mm... mm...
(SIGHS) Don't muh... muh...
Remember, Diego,
just picture the word in your mind.
(SIGHS)
D-Don't mm... muh...
D-Don't mmm...
Don't mo-move.
(GASPS) You did it! I'm so proud of you!
(REGINALD CLEARS THROAT)
(GRACE HUMMING)
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Mom, we need to talk.
GRACE: Okay, but only for a minute.
I need to finish this cross-stitch.
Everything you did for us
when we were kids...
for me...
why'd you do it?
Because being your mother
is the greatest gift of my life.
Is that you saying that?
I'm not sure what you mean, Diego.
I mean, our father, he...
made you.
When you think something,
is it like he's telling you what to say?
Your father isn't here, silly.
Did I do something wrong?
No, it's... it's not...
Look.
It's okay...
if you hated him.
He was terrible to you,
to all of us.
Don't say that.
Why not?
We were just tools in an experiment
to him. Nothing more.
So I'm saying, I would understand if...
you know, if... if you wanted to hurt him.
Now, now.
Mr. Hargreeves was a great man.
Industrialist, inventor,
Olympic gold medalist.
He made the world a better place.
Stop it!
Do you hear me? Stop trying to defend him!
Mom, you gotta feel something.
Look, he treated you worse than anyone.
You worked for him for 30 years.
He didn't even give you
a room to sleep in.
But I've got such beautiful views here.
DIEGO: Mom, those are just paintings.
Of course they are. (SIGHS)
What a wonderful world she lives in.
Sometimes I wonder if she's lonely.
You know, you don't have to tell me that.
I know there are only six days left.
Yeah, you got a better idea?
(SCOFFS) Okay, then.
FIVE: There's our guy.
(CAR APPROACHING)
FIVE: What the hell is he up to?
(GROANS)
(AIR HISSING)
(AIR HISSES LOUDLY)
Cha-Cha.
CHA-CHA: That's our kid.
(HUSHED FEMALE VOICE ECHOING) Klaus!
(OVERLAPPING WHISPERING VOICES)
(ALL SCREAMING) Klaus!
Klaus!
(OVERLAPPING WHISPERS)
(ALL SCREAM) Klaus!
FEMALE VOICE: Klaus.
(SCREAMS) Klaus!
(ALL SHRIEKING) Klaus! Klaus!
(GASPING)
Oh...
(SIGHS DEEPLY) Oh!
Oh.
("WE'RE THROUGH" PLAYING OVER HEADPHONES)
(EXHALES)
♪ I should be better off without you ♪
♪ You take a pride in making me blue ♪
♪ I'm tellin' you, my friend ♪
♪ It's got to be the end ♪
♪ We're through ♪
♪ I told you time and time again ♪
♪ You told me he was just a friend ♪
♪ But I found out some way ♪
♪ I've seen him every day ♪
♪ With you ♪
♪ 'Cause you never treat me tenderly ♪
♪ You got no reason for leavin' me ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't leave you... ♪
Somebody's been eating his Wheaties.
♪ Alone ♪
♪ 'Cause I knew from the start ♪
♪ You'd be tearin' me apart ♪
♪ Sooner or later ♪
♪ 'Cause I knew from the start ♪
♪ You'd be tearin' me apart ♪
♪ Sooner or later ♪
Wow, look at that.
LUTHER: Mm.
Home sweet home.
I'll tell ya,
things are a lot simpler up there.
What's it like?
Quiet.
(CHUCKLES)
Cold.
And, uh...
lonely.
Although,
every now and then...
when the sun came rolling over the horizon
just right, and the light hits it,
everything would turn to white glass.
It's...
It's beautiful.
You know, whatever you told Claire,
I didn't really feel like a superhero
up there, but...
those few moments
when my whole world was glowing,
I felt like maybe I was meant to be there.
You know?
I wish I'd been there with you.
You were.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(METAL SWISHES)
(GUN COCKS)
(GUNFIRE)
Is that...?
It's coming from our bedrooms.
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
HAZEL: Cha-Cha, shoot him.
CHA-CHA: Get out of the way, dumbass.
(GRUNTS)
(GUNFIRE)
CHA-CHA: Come on.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(HUMMING)
(GRUNTS)
(ALLISON YELLS)
(CHOKING)
(DIEGO GRUNTS) Let her go!
(LUTHER YELLS)
(ALL GRUNT)
(HAZEL SCREAMS)
Who the hell are these guys?
Who the hell are these people?
I don't know,
but at least we know who owns the shoe.
You're welcome.
I was doing fine.
Oh, yeah, you really had them...
DIEGO: Ever hear of a rope-a-dope?
LUTHER: Get out of here now! Go!
DIEGO: Luther, go!
HAZEL: I lost my gun.
CHA-CHA: I'm going after them.
VANYA: Hello?
Guys? Is everyone okay?
Hello?
Guys?
(YELPS, GRUNTS)
LUTHER: Hey, asshole.
("SINNERMAN" PLAYING)
♪ Oh, sinnerman, where you gonna run to? ♪
♪ Sinnerman, where you gonna run to? ♪
(LUTHER GROANS)
♪ Where you gonna run to? ♪
(BOTH MEN GRUNTING)
♪ All on that day ♪
♪ I said rock ♪
(PANTING)
♪ What's the matter with you, rock? ♪
♪ Don't you see I need you, rock? ♪
♪ Good Lord, Lord ♪
♪ All on that day ♪
(GASPS)
♪ I said rock ♪
(CHA-CHA GRUNTS)
♪ What's the matter with you, rock? ♪
♪ Don't you see I need you, rock? ♪
♪ Good Lord, Lord ♪
♪ All on that day... ♪
You wanna rumor this psycho?
I don't need to,
because this bitch just pissed me off.
CHA-CHA: We just want the boy.
Oh, well, in that case...
♪ It was bleedin', I run to the sea ♪
♪ It was bleedin' ♪
(BOTH GRUNTING)
♪ All on that day ♪
(ALLISON SCREAMS)
♪ So I run to the river ♪
♪ It was boilin' ♪
(DIEGO WHISTLES)
♪ I run to the sea ♪
♪ It was boilin', I run to the sea ♪
(GRUNTING)
♪ It was boilin' ♪
♪ All on that day ♪
♪ So I run to the Lord ♪
♪ Please hide me, Lord ♪
♪ Don't you see me prayin'? ♪
(DIEGO AND CHA-CHA GRUNTING)
♪ Don't you see me down here prayin'? ♪
ALLISON: Get her.
♪ But the Lord said ♪
(CHA-CHA GRUNTS)
♪ Run to the Devil, the Lord said ♪
Come on.
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING OVER HEADPHONES)
Klaus! Klaus!
♪ He said ♪
♪ Go to the Devil ♪
♪ All on that day ♪
(LUTHER AND HAZEL GRUNTING)
♪ So I ran to the Devil ♪
LUTHER: Vanya, get out of here!
♪ Ran to the Devil ♪
♪ He was waitin', ran to the Devil ♪
♪ He was waitin' ♪
♪ All on that day ♪
♪ I cried power ♪
♪ Power, power ♪
♪ Power ♪
Vanya?
HAZEL: Come here!
♪ Power ♪
(YELLS)
♪ Power, power ♪
(BOTH GRUNT)
(HAZEL SIGHS)
(LUTHER GROANS)
(HAZEL CLEARS THROAT)
Phew.
(SIGHS)
(CHA-CHA GRUNTS)
ALLISON: Luther!
(GROANING)
Come on, Luther, get up.
Ah, you gotta cut down on that fast food,
soldier.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(CLANGING)
Out of the way!
Luther!
♪ Power ♪
♪ Power, power ♪
(PANTING)
♪ Power ♪
(CHANDELIER RATTLING AND CLINKING)
(LUTHER GASPING)
Holy shit.
(SIGHS)
(FOOTSTEPS ECHOING)
Did you know?
No.
(GRACE HUMMING)
Shit. Mom.
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
Mom.
You okay?
Of course I am.
You didn't hear the noises?
The guys in the masks
that just shot up the house?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
What are you talking about, silly?
(CONTINUES HUMMING)
(DIEGO BREATHING SHAKILY)
Diego?
What are you doing?
(FAINT BEEPING)
(WHIRRING)
It's gonna be o... (CRYING SOFTLY)
Remember what we worked on.
Just picture the word in your mind.
It's gonna be okay... (STUTTERS)...Mom.
(WHIRRING FADES)
(BEEPING SOFTLY)
(SLURRED) Di-e-go...
Re... mem... ber.
Who were those people?
I don't know.
But we are lucky to be alive.
You sure you're okay?
(DIEGO BREATHING SHAKILY)
ALLISON: Diego?
What are you still doing here?
I'm just trying to help.
No, you could've been killed.
Or gotten any of us killed.
She is a liability.
Allison?
I think what he's trying to say
is that this kind of stuff is dangerous.
You're just...
Not like you.
No, that's not what I...
Vanya, wait.
Let her go.
DIEGO: It's for the best.
(PANTING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(KNOCKING)
Vanya!
Oh, my God, you're bleeding.
What happened?
Sorry, I...
I didn't know where else to go.
It's okay.
Come in.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(MAN ON TV)
structure of a haunted house.
(BED WHIRRING)
With the main structure in place,
we are launching into the creepy corridor,
and, without even having
to shake a floor plate,
it's already starting to feel spooky.
(MAN ON TV GASPS)
(WOMAN ON TV LAUGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
NAN: I'm still...
Where the hell were you?
When you didn't come out,
I figured we'd just regroup here.
And you stopped...
to get a jelly doughnut?
Maybe.
After everything we just went through?
Well, I needed some comfort food
after that disaster.
Well, tonight's a total loss.
Well, I'm not so sure about that.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(ROCK VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING)