Previously on "Billions"...
You know those poison-tip arrows
that go through one
guy and kill another?
As long as it doesn't
come from you.
You get someone else to ask her.
Won't track back to me.
You come through for me,
I'll pay off your house.
People are getting
sick on Ice Juice.
Freezing the assets?
Now, that's an Ivan Koloff bear
hug you're putting on the man.
You're squeezing the
breath out of him.
But now you owe me.
A favor to be named later.
Back channeling, patronage.
I lost my taste for it.
Just don't forget, it was the
back channels and deal-making
that put you in that position.
Remind me again, and it's
the last meal we share.
It is still Axe Capital,
no matter who's making the
day-to-day decisions.
Are you sure?
I know it's Axe's faith
that confers value on me
until I have a track
record of my own.
Unless it becomes necessary,
I will not leave.
I'm holding in my hand
Robert Axelrod's signature
relinquishing his ability
to trade securities.
Well...
ol' Samson got a real buzz cut.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Counting Crows "Round Here" ♪
♪ Step out the front door
like a ghost into a fog ♪
♪ Where no one notices
the contrast ♪
♪ Of white on white ♪
♪ In between the moon and you,
the angels get a better view ♪
♪ Of the crumbling difference
between wrong and right ♪
♪ Well, I walk in the air ♪
- Hold on.
- ♪ Between the rain ♪
♪ Through myself
and back again ♪
♪ Where? ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ Maria says she's dying ♪
Bobby. Are you okay?
I went down to the crossroads.
What?
I made a mistake.
The deal. I can't do it...
not trade.
I've worked my entire life
putting myself in a position
where I would be truly free...
No limits, nothing
I couldn't do.
And with one signature,
I've stripped myself
of all of that.
It wasn't the signature
that did it.
It was the living like
there were no rules.
That's what made the
signature necessary.
Wendy.
Yeah. Don't wake up the kids.
I'll be right up.
I can't do this now.
Realize that limits,
constraints, they can be useful.
Letting someone else run
Axe Capital gives you
a chance to realign who you are.
To get good at letting go.
Which is a different
kind of freedom. A more
powerful kind of freedom.
Now go to sleep.
Even if it were a good
idea, which it's not,
there is nothing you can do to
regain control at this hour.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
We need to meet.
These fuckers can take
away my ability to trade
but not my ability to see.
Insightful guy like you,
how you gonna turn it off?
I'm not. I can't.
I don't want to.
If you can't trade on
the insights, who can?
Only those who I have
reason to trust absolutely.
- And that's me.
- It better be.
Because no one can know I'm
behind any of these trades.
Well, our doors wouldn't be
open if it wasn't for your,
um, let's say goodwill.
And when we're done, those
doors are gonna open
on to a much bigger shop.
Been hoping to hear from you.
I've been wanting to expand,
but I've never been
great at the raise.
That'll no longer be a problem
for Old Oaks Investments.
Your money is always good here.
You can't direct funds,
so how's this work?
Let's dive the fuck in.
I'll be in touch.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
So, this is the way it's done?
Yeah.
And there's really
nothing we can do but...
Hope the wheel of
fate favors us.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
Welcome to old New York,
where judicial assignment's
still determined by
the spin of a wheel.
Hey, it beats having
Chief Judge Morgenstern
make 'em after a long night
of gin at the goulash joint.
- Both.
For the United States v.
Robert Axelrod...
Judge Leonard Funt.
Do I have to say it?
You really don't.
You just got Funted.
Ha!
[laughing continues in distance]
How bad is this?
Funt is a true believer in
the power of a free market.
Old school Libertarian.
He's the best friend
Bobby Axelrod
could have on the bench.
Well, if Connerty
builds the case right,
the judge doesn't matter.
Wrong.
You need to find a way to
get Funt off the case.
So the wheel spits
out another name?
No. Only one spin,
then it's up to Chief
Judge Morgenstern.
The other judges lobby him,
depending on if they want
on or off. So you need
to stunt that process.
That is tampering twice over.
No. It's finesse.
I don't break promises, so
our unappetizing deal holds.
- Mm.
- But it will not expand.
Fate has dealt our hand.
Now we play it.
♪♪♪
Chuck.
What couldn't be talked
about on the phone?
We got judge-fucked
in the Axelrod case.
And, uh, I don't mean "We,
the people," I mean...
We. Our family.
- Fuck.
- Yeah.
We need a judge who
believes that the rich
have gotten away with
too much for too long.
And one who won't allow Axelrod
to create a distraction
by alleging I set up a roach
motel and lured him in.
Axe can't do that without
essentially admitting his guilt.
I know.
That's one of the things
keeping me up at night.
You know what I risked...
What I gave up... to get him.
What would he give to get me?
Everything.
Well, the judge we drew
is Leonard Edward Funt.
Isn't that good news?
Doesn't he owe you...
Yes, there is a debt.
I once did him a kindness. But
back then, during a case,
I tried to allude to the
favor in conference,
and that man hammered me
for even hinting at it.
Seemed to grow
larger as he talked,
the way some men can when
they're not pretending
to dignity and honor but they're
actually made of the stuff.
You withdrew the request?
I did.
And I fear it would
be even worse today.
See, if he wouldn't return a
favor back when it was fresh,
why would he do so now?
But that's not what
happened, is it?
He didn't actually refuse.
He didn't say no.
Not in so many words.
What he did was: Spare
himself the question
by putting a tougher one to you.
It's about will, Chuck.
Impose your will on him
until he does what
he needs to and repays the debt.
Why, you are a marvel.
Go.
Do what you have to do.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
I've recently invested nine
billion of Axe Cap's money
back into the market. In phases.
And now when it's time
for the next phase,
another two billion...
You can't.
Why?
There's a velvet rope around it.
So to speak.
What's actually around it?
A directive from Axe that
the money remain untouched.
Is he considering
moving the funds
or deploying them elsewhere?
Never mind. You don't know.
Don't I?
Maybe Axe is hedging.
Against the main fund?
Against you.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
Ah. The two billion.
I told them: Velvet rope.
Spoken like a man who's still
mad he never got into Xenon.
I'm on it, Taylor.
This is clean. And it
does what you need,
how you need. Tracks
it all in real time.
We've also swept the apartment.
There are no listening devices,
no visual recording devices,
no compromising
devices of any kind.
But guests leave eyes and ears,
so we should sweep often.
- The women.
Wand them.
He will.
So, this is the Counter
Intel team, the new Halls.
I don't think they
care for that.
Why should I trust you to
do anything other than
point me to the nearest
avocado toast?
For whom have you worked?
Is this just a walk
on the wild side
to spice up the b.
How much you doing
this for the money?
You can answer him.
In re bona fides, John
built the code for
four successful startups in
high school then Stanford,
then was asked to travel
to 71 countries for DARPA
and Other Government Agency,
all which he did
without complaint.
And Timmy Dones has a
military background.
What fucking war were you in?
Mr. Hall fought the
wars you've heard of.
I fought the ones you haven't.
As for your other questions.
It's none of your business,
smashed spring pea toast
is the new avocado toast,
and 70 percent.
Are we clear to talk to Mr.
Wagner going forward?
Discuss anything except
women you care about.
Yeah, so, the two billion.
Ah, and here I was thinking
you came to keep me company.
Look, I know you're giving
it to outside funds,
not on the surface.
It'll get routed around
the world first,
but then it will land
in certain funds,
and suddenly they'll get hot
as Farrah Fawcett in '76.
Don't do it. One errant e-mail,
one recorded call, one
trade that tracks back
to you... and it's Hassan chop!
We're done. All of us.
There's no need for it, bwana.
Satisfy your urges
some other way.
Buy yourself something.
I bought it all already.
Probably thrown it out.
What about that vintage Cheetah
you've been eyeballing?
Look, this is not a message
I'm born to carry.
It goes against everything
I've built my life on.
But for you, holding back
is essential right now.
You're right about
hiding the money.
That's too dangerous.
What if I didn't?
- I could have Taylor move it,
on-the-books, perfectly legal
disbursements to outside shops.
Bobby... that's right, I'm not
calling you "Mr. President,"
I'm calling you "Bobby"
because I've never used
your first name and
I want to underline
how serious this moment is.
You've called me Bobby before.
Strategic mistake, but
not nearly as big
as the one you're making if
you ask Taylor to do this.
They have nothing to
gain by going along.
They get to keep their
princely fucking job.
If you fire them, it will
look like what it is.
And you can't have it appear
you're illegally meddling.
Especially when you're
illegally meddling.
- My point...
- I get your point.
So you won't take
the two billion?
I get your point.
Let's leave it at that.
Ah!
If it isn't George and Edward.
Which one of you will give
up the throne for love?
That seems like a stupid reason.
You must be George.
Are you coming to our
game later, Uncle Wags?
Is it official Little League?
- Yeah.
- Can't. Banned for life.
Well, here we are on the
Axelrod case together,
so, you know, we got our
fairy tale ending after all.
You been working out? You look
like you've been working out.
There's no good way to
answer that question.
Is it ping pong? You
back at the tables?
Uh, can I get a lawyer?
Excuse me, Ms. Gonzalez...
Special Agent Terri McCue, FBI.
Uh, me llamo Bryan Connerty,
uh, Federal prosecutor.
He's also second alternate
at the World Table
Tennis Championships.
I'm really not... that good.
Ms. Gonzalez, we don't care
about your immigration status.
That's not what we do.
We may even be able to help
you if you cooperate with us.
We want to speak to you about
your boss, Victor Mateo.
Mr. Victor, he's very good.
He and his wife,
they sponsor me for
the green card, so
I don't need help.
You're not eligible
for a green card
if you've committed a crime.
A crime? No. No, no, no.
Let's put it up
on the colortini.
That couple near you snapping
selfies were undercover agents.
Mr. Victor made me do it.
Did Mr. Victor
give you the vial.
It was someone else. A woman.
But I know that it was for him.
Him and his wife, son monstruos.
One time I drop a glass licorera...
Baccarat.
Then Missus, she break the tail
light to my car to punish.
I had to drive home afraid
that I get pulled over
and sent back to Guatemala.
Now I take the bus.
I want to know how it worked.
When and where...
The way that Mr. Victor and his wife are...
I can't be late.
Or do I have to tell them...
No, no, no. Don't...
don't say anything.
After work, you'll
come to my office
and give a statement.
Lo prometo.
Yeah, what is it?
My maid was late today.
She's never late.
We have a real problem.
We need to meet.
Group of guys who own this car,
it's a smaller club than the
one that owns NBA teams,
only 29 ever built.
Which is exactly
why I'm buying it.
Which is why I'm gonna
let you outbid me.
Thanks.
Sounds like you want something.
I do.
I want in on the new shit.
You're raising money for
new ventures, count me in.
Thanks, but I'm not looking
to give up any more equity.
You're saying no to money?
Look, Axe, let me answer the
question you didn't ask,
and this pains me to say...
I don't want your money.
I've got too many eyes
on me, and I can't be
anywhere near the shit show
you're in the middle of
right now.
Noted.
♪♪♪
Michael Panay.
You haven't gone home
with a car this year.
Is it the one you had your
heart set on all along?
If Bill Thomas built a toaster,
I'd skip work to buy that.
But you won't actually
buy this car, will you?
Because you've been downsizing,
hoping no one would see.
We're not downsizing.
I was on the other side
of the Alperin trade.
I know how much you lost.
Well, I know you're
not exactly trending
in the right direction, either.
Maybe we help each other.
I lead the early bidding,
knock out the dabblers,
then you swoop in at
your desired price.
What's your number?
Mike, I'd pedal the
fucking Flintstones car
before I went in
on this with you.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
You sure?
I know my people.
She's been approached.
I'll handle it.
You know what this
means, don't you?
They'll be coming
for the others.
If that bursts into flame,
I'm denouncing you to
Governor Danforth.
It's a focus exercise.
And Danforth is
just in the play.
At the real Salem trials, the
judge was William Stoughton.
Careful, that sounds like
something a witch would know.
Also: We're looking good
on the two billion.
Now that got you focused.
I'm here to break the glass.
In case of emergency, you know?
Breathe, then talk.
We're getting hit by a tsunami.
Shit. Did the Fed hike...
No. Actual tsunami. In Brazil.
No way. Brazil doesn't
have tsunamis.
The worst they get
is ressacas do mar.
"Sea hangover."
Am I the only person here who's
loved a Portuguese woman?
Brazil does not
normally have tsunamis.
Black swan event.
How heavy are we in Brazil?
Jim Morrison at the end.
Our newly redeployed funds
are affected in dozens
of different ways, among
the most notable,
- Brazilian sugar and shipping.
- So we buy sugar futures.
Impending shortage
means prices go up.
Everyone will do that, but sure.
A few of the moves
I'm already making.
Shorting Brazil's
largest debt holder,
buying long-dated VIX calls.
Also buying solar, wind,
and every alternative
energy play
not dependent on
government subsidy.
Um, is no one worried
about the people, you
know, in Brazil?
If you want to pretend
you're concerned, see Wendy.
He's not pretending, Wags.
If you really care,
start a walk-a-thon.
Tough Mudders are the
new walk-a-thons.
But don't bring that shit to me.
Our own foundation was set
up for just these situations
as a kind of emotional
and fiscal catch-all
for you to use as a
tool for you to get
your conscience out of the way.
I wondered why you
showed at this meeting,
you fucking vulture.
What would salve my conscience
and my wallet is if I was
a fucking contractor in Brazil.
Too bad their leading
construction company's
a scandal factory.
Can't get into bed with a
firm that's had almost
100 executives indicted.
Our principal has been indicted.
If it's a money-maker, we do it.
Legal trouble does not
mean you can't fulfill
your teleological purpose.
We're on the clock, people.
Now's the time to
earn your paychecks.
There's something I
always wondered:
Why aren't you Charlie?
- Feels like you would have
- been a great Charlie.
- No, I agree.
Oh, Charlie Rhoades, yeah,
that guy's yer best friend.
- Yeah.
Sure. Call ol' Charlie, see
if he can fill in, uh,
as a fourth for tennis
or on a double date
or just ride around
smashing mailboxes.
Yeah. Charlie. The best.
But in our household,
my father was Charles.
And every now and then someone,
business associate, the guy who
managed one of his buildings,
who would get just
a little casual,
accidentally let a Charlie fly.
The world would stop dead.
"Do I look like a fucking
'Charlie' to you?"
And that was that.
The guy would piss himself,
and the day would continue.
So, he was Charles,
and you were Chuck.
And Good Time Charlie
was somewhere else
out on the town having
all the laughs.
Christ, man.
Don't I know it.
And how 'bout now?
You just show up in my
chambers for the laughs.
No. No.
I am here in your chambers
to put myself in your debt.
In my debt.
That's right.
I was thinking back to
our last meal together,
wherein you told me I
ought never mention
the favor I had done you again.
And I promised then,
and I intend to
keep that promise.
And so I am here to
ask of you a favor,
not as repayment to
me but the opposite.
Oh, this must be big.
Judge Funt is stepping
off the Axelrod case.
No one knows.
And when he does, Morgenstern
will make a special appointment
of the judge who convinces
him he most wants the case.
As often as not, that's
the first judge to ask.
And you need that to be me.
We'll time it out so it will be.
Now, there are those
that would frame this
as a favor for you, because
it's a marquee case.
But I won't.
You would be doing me a service.
And all you're asking
is that I be the judge,
not that I rule in Dake's favor,
not that I'd be
slanted in any way.
That's right. It's
that straightforward.
Win. Lose. Draw.
I want you on that bench because
I know you can't be bought.
You can't be bent.
You can't be worked.
Dake has a strong case.
I want it heard fairly
and without prejudice.
And if I grant this request...
There is nothing you can ask me
that I'll refuse you for
the rest of our days.
If I agree, I would take
those words as gospel,
Chuck. And I would not
be bashful to collect,
should the need arise.
I'd be honor bound to deliver.
That's too small a play.
It won't save us.
Keep looking.
Axe would be out on that
floor screaming at them
like Gordon Ramsay
until they delivered.
Hm. You're more Alton Brown.
The ideas they're bringing...
Some deployable,
some useful as a benchmark
of what other firms
will be thinking and how
we need to do better,
but none platonically good.
Your first round of
investments coinciding
with your first crisis.
That would be a lot for anybody.
Axe was already considering
sidecarring two billion.
And you think today will
make the decision for him.
I am acutely aware of the
way people look at me.
I have cultivated, through
achievement and discipline,
a mystique that compensates
for my lack of track record.
A loss shatters that,
and with it the confidence
of everyone who works here.
In their eyes... in Axe's eyes...
I become simply inexperienced.
I can't let that happen.
That's why I need to get
through today unscathed.
The way you think Axe would.
It's important in your job that
you face unpleasant realities.
Axe Capital may
lose money today,
probably will.
You know that, right?
No.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
Wags, I'm coming in.
The place is getting
crushed without me.
♪♪♪
Can I stop you?
No.
You sure I can't stop you?
You know that painting
of Washington crossing
the Delaware. In the boat
with all his troops?
I forget what it's called.
I think it's called Washington
Crossing The Delaware...
- You didn't forget.
- No.
And do you know why
it's called that?
Because at the moment that
his troops were facing
the sting of battle,
Washington was right there
with them, leaning
into the wind.
Not back at home jerking off.
I'll admit, Washington Crossing
the Delaware would look pretty
fucking strange without
George Washington.
Then how can you ask me not to
be with my troops right now?
Well, Washington was allowed
to talk to his men.
He was allowed to lead.
When we walk out
of this elevator,
you're gonna see it is quite
a different situation.
But it is what's required
under your deal.
This is Ari Spyros,
Director of Compliance
and Risk Management
for Axe Capital.
It's 12:09 p.m. I am
here with Robert Axelrod
and will stay with him anywhere
he goes inside these walls,
ensuring compliance with his
preclusion from the secur...
I'm looking at small
sugar companies in Asia.
We pick one... invest in
it, grow it, help it.
Not a big fan of...
Oh, shit.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
What do you think
he'd say about that?
Bobby Axelrod doesn't
grow mom-and-pop shops.
He buys 'em out, turns 'em out.
That can't happen with this one.
Hmm.
Well, then it sounds like your
idea doesn't fucking work.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
Whoo.
Um...
Oh, I don't like nothing
between me and the water.
We called first. You
knew we were coming.
Yeah, doc says I gotta swim.
Right.
We need to talk to you about...
About some unexplained
coincidences.
If I can sort you out...
In the last year, your
house was paid off.
Yeah, my wife came
into some money.
Mm.
And your kids, they stopped
taking student loans.
Marcie's dorm room business,
it's really taking off.
I'm sorry, do you... do
you want a towel, or...
- I'm good.
- You're fair.
So, you got sick from Ice Juice.
The person behind its
poisoning was Bobby Axelrod,
the same man you tried
to cooperate against.
You think he targeted
me deliberately?
Wow, that's a long road
to travel for revenge.
But if he did it, I
hope you nail him.
That juice made me puke
so hard I bust a lung.
Hence the swimming.
Anything else?
Okay. Drop by any time.
Guy flashes a little brain,
and you turn into Dudley Do
I thought under
the circumstances
I acquitted myself admirably.
A lot of people think
you can't get a good
flat white outside of Australia.
They forget, there's
no such thing
as a good store-bought
flat white.
It's the tongue temperature.
Oh, please, I'd
love to hear more
of your expertise
on flat whites.
So I just had a fun
little poolside chat
with some friends who are
very curious about you,
me, and beverages.
Thanks.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
Oh, shit, he's leaving.
Hey, Mafee.
You sure a lunch break's
the thing right now?
Nothing urgent that you
should be getting...
Are you testing me?
Like that waiter in 'Club?
I'm not allowed to talk
to you about this. Right.
Or do you want me to, because...
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
Hey.
Got any summer plans?
No.
Guess Lara and I will need
to talk about it. The kids.
I don't like to go far.
We got a spot in Mystic.
While the family's looking
at the boats and shit,
I can play a little pai gow.
I was planning to go
back and climb Kili.
How much vacay time is it
culturally appropriate
to take here?
Ah, maybe I'll
just do base camp.
- Korst.
- Scandinavian shipping company.
While the South American
companies are down for
the count, these guys will
have a shot at a monopoly.
- We should buy in two days.
- Four days, when it bottoms.
But this is going to help
dig us out a little more.
Good work.
Will you make sure Axe
knows it came from me?
Why would you think we're
communicating about trades?
What?
That would be illegal.
I know. But...
What are you saying about me?
What are you saying about
the place you work?
Actually, if he hates it,
that would be worse.
Don't say anything.
It is now 1:47 on
the 9th day of...
I'm sitting in my office,
which I paid for,
seeing how things
run without me.
Won't work.
People are afraid
to take chances
with you here. To be wrong.
Or they want a slap on the ass from you.
Which you can't give.
Move over, Zapruder. I got this.
Actually, I think this
falls within my dominion,
and the stick can be
really tricky for noobs...
Hmm. Guess it was tricky.
Why didn't you
anticipate the tsunami?
Maybe I should have when that
underground earthquake
hit off Mozambique.
Strange conditions
bring strange results.
That's what brought this on.
You knew right then
but you couldn't act.
Maybe you would have
used your experience
to think more globally.
Maybe you would have been cautious.
De-risked.
The mature move.
Is that a dig?
It's not.
You have more experience.
You connect points I don't
even know to look for.
I understand how hard it is
to have things inside you
that you can't communicate.
I can't imagine how hard it
must be to know how to say them
and still not be allowed to.
And yet, you are not allowed to.
Have you heard me
direct any trades?
The people out there don't
know who they're looking to.
Since it can't be you,
it needs to be me.
If you can't live with that,
I can be the one who leaves.
You'll probably make up the
losses but get yourself
banned for life or worse.
I'm leaving,
and I'm taking the two billion.
I'll send instructions shortly
about what to do with it.
And at 1:53 p.m.,
Robert Axelrod...
has left the building.
I'm glad I caught you.
You wouldn't have if
my fucking car guy
could time his job right.
Yeah, George Washington had the
same problem leaving Trenton.
Wags told you?
Texted me while you were
rampaging through the office.
I wasn't rampaging.
I was inspiring.
You know Washington
didn't actually.
- Of course.
Structurally unsound, and he'd
have made himself a target.
Yet you worry about neither.
It's hard to shut it off, Wend.
I know.
But if you can't, you will
lose the battle and the war.
Do you want me to come with you?
Stay here with Taylor.
They need some senior
officer for back up.
You're fired.
Find out when Judge Funt's
court is in recess.
Yep.
A Mr. Allerd is here for you.
I'm Karl Allerd, your new AUSA.
I think I'd remember if I
hired a new line prosecutor.
Remember when Dake said there'd
be a favor to be named?
Ah.
You're the favor.
You don't trust me.
Hell, I wouldn't
from your chair.
A Spy In the House Of
Lords and so forth. Yes.
So I'll earn your trust.
Will you?
I look forward to
seeing that trick.
That'll be a neat trick.
Ms. Sacker, our Head of Crim,
will get you situated.
- Mm.
Mm, I will.
Hey, I've been revising my idea.
There's a division of
a struggling company
in Thailand, that I think...
Wait, is this the sugar company?
Is it, is this the
same damn deal?
No... It's just one
facet of the company
that I think could be
promising to look into.
It started out as a
family business, and...
- So this is... This
is the same deal.
- Not really...
- Kimmy,
this piece of shit
ain't Axe Cap.
What are you working on?
Nothing.
I want to see all Ben Kim's
search results for the day.
You mean, like, browser
results, or...
Everything he did today.
Hey, you on your way home?
Nope.
Chief. You got to
get on your way
if you want to make
it in time to take
the princelings
to Little League.
Have Bruce take 'em.
You got it.
He's been home three
weekends this year.
I'm almost positive one of them
was his assistant's mistake.
And he assumes I never
say anything about him
fucking his way through
the entire New York pool.
But if you can leave Axe...
You give me courage, Lara.
You're smart, Lilly.
You had a career for a second.
You know your shopper
isn't your friend,
personal trainer doesn't think
you're actually making progress,
and all the charities you
give money to don't actually
honor you when they honor you.
But on some level, you
believe every bit of it.
You think the attention
you receive is deserved.
But when that fades,
when every relationship
in your life reveals itself to
be a trade on your husband's
net worth, you may say
"Fuck false friends,"
but you'll be hiring a
PR rep the first time
your Halloween costume isn't
mentioned in Page Six.
So keep your own courage, Lilly.
And while you're at it,
consider keeping that husband.
Because while he may not give
you what you think you want,
he lets you keep on being Mrs.
Keith Currier Smith,
and I'm pretty sure
that's what you need.
Now you're trying
to decide whether
to be pissed or grateful.
Definitely grateful.
Whoa!
Here you go.
Have fun.
Thanks, Bruce.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
We got your latest request.
It's a big lift. Hard transfer.
International withdrawals
and deposits like this
do not get done same day.
- It's not the sort of thing
most clients ask for. Especially
not when they're drawing heat.
These are my needs.
Either you meet
them or you can't.
We can get it done. But this
isn't a reusable pipeline.
Fine by me.
♪♪♪
She's supposed to
be here by 5:30.
- It's already...
- I know what time it is.
Call it in.
I'd like to have a
person of interest
picked up. Gonzalez, Maria.
No Social.
Yeah.
D.O.B. 1/22/79.
You think she got cold feet?
I think that's best case.
You have her already.
That's great news. Where?
Hold her. She's mine.
She got picked up
in an ICE sweep.
She's currently at the Varick
Street Detention Center.
Are you gonna bring Maria?
She's right there.
Who is that?
Maria Gonzalez.
That may be a Maria Gonzalez,
but that is not our
Maria Gonzalez.
That is the wrong
Do you have someone else
here with that name?
We did until she was put
on a goodbye charter
from Newark Liberty.
It's got to be some
bureaucratic screw-up.
No, it doesn't.
Somebody knew she was
gonna be picked up
before we did and
got to her info.
This has Axe written
all over it.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
They deported the
wrong Maria Gonzalez.
Our witness is on a plane
that lands in 90 minutes.
We need her met on the ground
in Guatemala and returned.
There are a lot of, uh,
high-level, deeply uncomfortable
calls required to make that happen.
DOJ. DHS. State.
And they all start
with your boss.
I really don't want to call the
Attorney General about this.
He's publicly stated this
case matters to him.
Ollie, you're a bit of a
rara avis, aren't you?
You got no "hat," no one
looking out for you,
and yet you have risen.
Maybe it's because you
have an immaculate record.
Some guys don't trust
immaculate record.
I do. I have an
Thank you, General.
That was from a movie.
You don't watch movies,
do you, Ollie?
I re-watch The
Decalogue every year.
Uh, well, I read
what you sent me.
Just to make sure I have it
straight: We got the wrong Guad?
That is indeed the case.
Say it.
We got the wrong Guad.
But Maria Gonzalez,
our Maria Gonzalez,
is a key cooperator.
We need her back.
And since this is
an extraordinary situation...
Well, in one respect.
In another, it's just the way
things are supposed to go.
The right Maria Gonzalez came
into this country illegally,
she stayed illegally, and
she committed a fraud
on the stockholders of that
snake-bit juice company.
She is three times illegal.
That makes her removable,
and she was removed.
Um...
Next time...
instead of asking me
to undo your fuck-up,
maybe just see to it that
the situation remains like
our holy Mother of Mercy,
blessedly un-fucked.
How'd that go?
Does Axe ever hesitate?
Why?
I'm hesitating. Can't
pull the trigger.
Markets are closed.
Overseas play?
Ben Kim found a big
opportunity in Thailand.
A troubled public company with
a promising sugar division.
He spotted a good target
but just couldn't quite
figure out how to hit it...
Or didn't have the courage
to shoot at it.
We need to keep working
with him on that.
But you see the play?
Yes. A PIPE. Private
investment in public equity.
Basically, we take
ownership of a spin-off,
and a commission from
brokering its sale.
So, why the hesitation?
It will be the single largest
investment I've made as CIO,
and a type Axe Cap has
never made before.
If you make this move, where
do you end up for the day?
Unscathed?
This would lock in a loss.
Yes. The high-reward
plays are all high-risk.
It's good you can't
run it by Axe.
Forces you to hear your
own voice and trust it.
You'll probably do
the right thing.
And when the day comes you get
one wrong, that'll be good, too.
Because I'll realize I'm
mortal and it's not so bad?
Because it'll be
fucking horrible
and you'll do anything you can
to avoid that feeling again.
Hey.
You know what, Bobby?
I'm gonna do you a favor:
You're off the hook.
If you don't want 50-50 custody,
you don't need to have it.
I can tell other
people it's 50-50,
and I can come up with something
to tell the boys, too.
Why the fuck do you think
I don't want the kids?
You had them for one day,
at a time when you don't
have to go to work,
and you ditched them.
You let them be airlifted
into Little League.
I mean, it was mortifying.
I didn't mean to embarrass them.
They weren't embarrassed.
They didn't know to be, which
is a whole other thing.
You know, I don't know if you
need to work on your case
or go on a trip
or become a fucking cobbler,
but it doesn't seem like you
are where you need to be.
And I'd offer to help,
but my help doesn't seem
to be what you want, either.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
I have everything
positioned and ready,
and yet...
Judge Funt still has the
case on his docket.
My bag is packed, but I can't
seem to walk out the door.
If I fail at this,
everything is dashed.
For then I will
have ruined myself
in his eyes
and exposed my position.
Only a fool doesn't
look at the downside.
But only a coward allows
it to dissuade him
from that which he
knows he must do.
I know you're not a coward.
I don't like the sound of that
word coming out of your mouth.
Neither do I.
I'll see you at home. After.
Chuck?
No one takes this
shortcut anymore.
This isn't your courthouse.
Are you lost?
Oh, right where I need
to be, Judge Funt,
which is, unfortunately,
in your way.
Ah.
The Axelrod case.
You had to know a day
like this would come.
I never asked you...
You didn't have to.
Your son's doing well, I hope,
made the most of his
medical career.
Yeah, he's a good doctor.
That's what I wanted for him.
If he hadn't have supplied those
future sons of Hippocrates
with Adderall, some other
med student would have.
I won't let you
dictate my rulings.
The bench cannot be tainted
by personal debts.
Name another favor.
I know that this is the biggest
case that you've ever drawn.
Well, that's something that you
would think about in my shoes,
but I don't.
No, you wouldn't.
And you wouldn't hide
in a hallway waiting
to pounce when I walked by.
But I am not the man you are.
Oh.
You're not here to ask
me to shade my rulings.
You're here to ask
me to step off it.
It's a hard laydown. And I'm
asking you to lay it down.
Ask yourself
who you really are, Chuck.
Are you the man that's
reduced to collecting debts
of the soul like... Like old Mr.
Scratch?
Well, as with all stories
about that being,
the debt is due, even
if, especially if,
it is not fair or even
right to collect it.
Believe me, my... my insides
hurt making this request.
Oh, I don't believe
that even a little.
You like your insides
just as they are.
You want to be right here,
making these moves.
You need that feeling in your
stomach to know you're alive.
I really think I am sorry.
Fuck you, Chuck!
I'll recuse myself.
My tab is clear.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
May I?
Do you want me to call the
Secretary of the Treasury
and ask for a personal loan?
I just heard DeGiulio is the
new judge on the Axelrod case.
Not our dream judge,
but fair-minded,
likely to hew closely to
the law, rule narrowly.
That'll favor us a
lot more than Funt.
Well, then,
I guess it's a gift.
Chuck.
I know his fingerprints.
Are you gonna do
something about this?
I'm not in the habit
of rejecting gifts.
Do you know about
White Day in Japan?
Over there on Valentine's
Day, women buy presents
for their salarymen bosses, and
those presents are displayed
for all to see, so the most
important thing is the size.
That's how others know that
the recipient is valued.
A month later, on White Day,
the men give a return gift
of two to three times the value.
So if there's a salaryman
you don't respect,
you get him something
small but expensive.
Chuck just gave you
diamond cufflinks,
and when White Day comes,
you're gonna have to give him
something that costs a lot more.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ Counting Crows "Round Here" ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Step out the front door
like a ghost into a fog ♪
♪ Where no one notices
the contrast ♪
♪ Of white on white ♪
♪ In between the moon and you ♪
♪ Angels get a better view ♪
I didn't like you
kicking me out.
I apologize if I was rude.
I don't give a fuck about rude.
It showed you were distracted.
How did we do today?
Just executed a huge PIPE.
We're going to arb a Southeast
Asian sugar company.
Fun.
If all my projections hold,
we're still down five
percent overall.
Anyone else would have lost 12
or done something
stupid to get even.
Booking the loss
was the only way.
I'm not pulling the two billion.
It's yours to invest.
I really thought you
didn't trust me.
That's why you
were in the office
looking over
everyone's shoulder.
I was in the office,
because as of now,
I don't know what else
to do with myself.
And...
as much as I can trust
anyone with my name
and my money...
I trust you.
I am irrelevant.
You want the money because you
want the stake, the control.
You need the game to
remember who you are.
I've decided how I'm going
to invest that two billion.
I'm going to diversify,
invest in outside funds.
I'll hear pitches, among them
your hand-picked favorites.
And after I give them the money,
I'm going to be a
passive investor.
Thank you.
You're not doing this
'cause I need it.
You need it.
You're giving me a place to
play so I stay off your field.
And you want the benefit of
my moves on our bottom line
in case there's
another disaster.
I'm your hedge.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Maria says she's dying ♪
♪ Through the door,
I hear her crying ♪
♪ Why? ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ 'Round here ♪
♪ We always stand up straight ♪
♪ Something radiates ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Maria came from Nashville ♪
♪ With a suitcase in her hand ♪
♪ She said she'd like to meet
a boy who looks like Elvis ♪
♪ And she walks along the edge ♪
♪ Of where the ocean
meets the land ♪
♪ Just like she's walking ♪
♪ On a wire in a circus ♪
♪ She parks her car
outside of my house ♪
♪ And takes her clothes off ♪
♪ Says she's close to
understanding Jesus ♪
♪ And she knows she's
more than just a little ♪
♪ Misunderstood ♪
♪ She has trouble acting
normal when she's nervous ♪
♪ 'Round here ♪