[Grigor] Previously
on Billions...
You want an unprecedented
raise in record time.
So how are you going to help me
get the first ten stacks?
We need Grigor Andolov.
I just want to see you work
a little bit harder for it.
You breached my threshold
and threatened me.
Just wait a second...
Drop your credentials
at the guard's desk.
And GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE!
What the fuck?!
What, exactly, did you do?
How do I get you to break
your letter of intent
with Oscar Langstraat?
It basically solves our problem.
[Taylor] You sold out my
relationship in order to do it.
He said I was
off the raise team.
I won't stagnate.
Not for Axe.
Not for anybody.
I'll talk to him.
With someone like Taylor, what
they need is forward momentum,
above all things.
Where the fuck did Jeffcoat
get all this money?
TexasSouthCable.
I want you to launch
an investigation
into Jock Jeffcoat's brother
and TexasSouthCable.
Nothing makes me feel so alive
as putting my head
in a tiger's mouth.
We're gonna get Jock
on trying to stop it.
Obstruction of justice.
I'm putting you
on the raise team.
Fuckin' A.
Onward and upward.
There's gonna be
30 bil on the table,
get ready to help me
haul it outta there.
It looks like you're ready
to get into business.
I need a meeting with
your boss, Grigor Andolov.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ ♪
[Frank Sinatra's
"Come Fly With Me" playing]
[announcer] The Sands
is proud to present
a wonderful new show,
a man and his music.
The music of Count Basie
and his great band.
♪ ♪
And the man is Frank Sinatra.
You smell that?
That's money, son...
People who have never been
near money will say:
"I smell money,"
when entering a casino
or showing up
at a sales conference.
They, of course, can't
because they don't know
how to recognize the scent.
But you?
Like a shorthaired pointer
on a dabbling duck.
And I am telling you, Sef,
I smell money.
[Sinatra] How did all these
people get in my room?
[laughter]
♪ Come fly with me,
we'll fly, we'll fly away ♪
Gentlemen, today's the day!
- How much is on the table?
- By the close of the event,
30 billion will be earmarked,
invested, captured.
If we don't walk out of here
with at least a third
of the available capital...
I've teed this whole thing up
so that you will.
♪ Come fly with me ♪
Should I give you
"napalm in the morning"...
I already got a version...
Then "no vice but beggary"?
How 'bout Nick Saban?
[Southern accent]
Roll Tide... Roll!
That's fucking impressive.
I count on it.
Where's Taylor?
I have a text.
They say: "Soon.
Organizing some
last-minute things."
Pitch doesn't work
without Taylor.
They better make it.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ ♪
I was just asking myself
if I would.
And you know what?
I would!
Wow.
Every day you live this life
you learn something
about yourself.
Delightful!
If you're delighted, just
imagine how it makes me feel.
That's good.
You didn't even flinch.
Like the titan, Lee lacocca.
That's important.
To business then.
I read your approach
in the materials you sent.
What's your market outlook?
I could tell you
that interest rates
have topped out
for the near term,
that the tax and regulatory
climate are favorable,
that growth is looking
somewhat robust...
I could also
read your tea leaves
or the creases in your palm
or divine the future
by cleromancy...
Cleromancy?
Casting bones.
But I'm no gypsy.
So instead I'll tell you that
my anticipation and my reaction
to moment by moment changes
in market conditions
are lightning quick.
And cutting edge tech:
A quant piece that wasn't even
in place during the past year
that reflects my
already positive results.
Sure. But it's all words.
And words have very little to do
with how I decide things.
What then?
Internal process.
Like your casting bones.
But inside.
Last question...
Why are you leaving Axe?
After all, he made you.
We can debate that statement
some other time.
As for your question:
The same reason
you leave a house
that has a furnace
leaking carbon monoxide:
It's the only way to survive.
I like this image.
They say you can't
taste it or smell it
or even know that
it's putting you to sleep.
But I always think I would:
Most people are
already sleepwalking
through their lives.
So they don't even notice.
How could they,
it's only a matter of degree.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ ♪
You crushed it.
I'm glad I brokered
this meeting.
I have to talk to him,
but I imagine
money will be flowing shortly.
♪ ♪
So your suite
is the largest one.
Because there is more demand
for you than we can fit.
- Hey, Sara.
- Hey, Axe.
I didn't see you
down on the list.
Yeah, I'm not here to invest,
so I didn't want to take a spot.
I know you've said you'll
never take Spanx public...
And I won't.
Yeah, but when you do,
let me know.
[chuckles]
See ya, Axe.
Oh, ho, ho, I thought
the velociraptor was extinct.
And yet it walks amongst us.
A velociraptor doesn't walk.
It stalks, hunts, kills,
with great stealth and speed,
and if you want him
to prove that to you,
- keep fucking talking.
- [Axe] Easy, pal.
They're just jealous
'cause we got a waiting list.
Because you're the freak show,
the ten-in-one.
Everyone wants to take a look.
But after they stare at the
bearded lady for five minutes,
they'll walk down to my suite,
hand me the grisbi.
After today, everyone will know
that Axe Capital
is just like Atlantis,
this once great land,
now totally underwater
and feels like a figment
of someone's imagination.
[indistinct conversations]
[siren wails in distance]
[door closes, bell dings]
Sorry to interrupt
the rebalancing
of your lower body meridians.
- Will you excuse us, please?
- Uh-huh.
Target letter
announcing the investigation
into Zeb Jeffcoat.
Once it's signed
and the hard copy is sent
along with the PDF,
there's no turning back.
No. The proverbial Rubicon.
We cross it and Jock
goes on the offensive.
And even though
that's what we want...
Intimidating nevertheless.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ ♪
We are in the chute...
We can expect Zeb to call
his big brother immediately...
[Chuck] And for him
to go batshit.
♪ ♪
Or...
Or he's cool as can be.
[Chuck] But there's no way
he's cool enough
[Chuck] to simply let this
play out in court.
[Epstein] Since it would
lead back to him.
[Epstein] He'll confer
with his lawyers.
[Chuck] But not in a way
that will leave a trail.
[Chuck] Ultimately he will
fall back and make his move
[Chuck] to derail the case.
[Chuck] And that attack will
come on one of two fronts.
He will either ruin,
threaten, pressure
or otherwise discredit
and destroy you,
since you'll be
bringing the case.
Or he will try to compromise
[Chuck] who he surmises
to be the star witness.
♪ ♪
Now, if we can leak to him
that Ashley Cutler is the key
and is in our neck of the woods,
Jock will likely
head to New York.
But the question is:
Which move will he make first?
If he digs on me, he'll come up
with a bouquet of begonias.
Yes. Yes. I did as hard a vet
on you as one could do.
I knew to get
where I needed to get
I'd have to be
Jackie Robinson clean.
Then I want that witness.
Which means he can
either try his luck
with the head
of the State Police...
Over whom he has no sway...
Or he can call me,
and implore me
to use my particular set
of powers to aid in his cause.
My phone has to be
the one that rings.
Yes, we need that to happen.
But what if it doesn't?
You and I know
Cutler is a weak witness.
But Jock might figure that too.
And if he's patient enough,
he might just wait it out.
Then you do the thing:
Impanel a grand jury,
and schedule Cutler.
It invariably leaks and Jock
knows we're going forward.
But if, but when
that call does come,
and we know we've got him
following along,
you can't just offer him help.
No, he'll sniff it out,
of course.
Ask for something, big.
For yourself.
So he believes you're in it
for your own reasons.
And then it's time
for The Prestige.
♪ ♪
Put your shoes on and get ready.
[indistinct conversations]
♪ ♪
Only Ricky Roma
gets to show up late.
Well, I am at the top
of the board.
What the fuck?
Uber...
If you're gonna go around,
go like a rich person.
Take a chopper.
I'm here now.
Let's do this thing.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
Remember: They are
not buying
your proprietary
trading platform,
they are not buying
your strategies,
they are buying you.
Remind them that
we have the answers.
That they are safe
in your loving arms.
Like Barry White.
Oh, he'd have had them
hands in the air,
weeping and singing along.
So, yes, exactly
like Barry White.
♪ Suspenseful music ♪
There are only two things
these allocators
really want to know,
but they'll never directly ask:
Can we be trusted?
And are we special?
We nail those.
We nail this entire thing.
♪ ♪
Welcome, everybody. Welcome.
Thanks for coming.
Now, you've read all our stuff.
You know my Sortino ratio proves
that we get a higher rate of
return with less downside vol.
How we avoided
the XIV liquidation
by selling our VIX positions
two weeks before
everybody else did.
And you know who
made sure we did that?
Taylor Mason!
[applause]
♪ ♪
Over the past year, we've seen
the lowest market correlation
of any fund in the business.
You will, of course,
want to know why and how.
So come sit in
and shadow me for a day,
because it's like
asking a magician
how they do their tricks.
We all know it's not magic.
It's the opposite of magic.
It's grinding, focused work,
it's sitting on their bed
for weeks, months at a time,
working slip cuts, perfecting
the Elmsley Count...
So that the audience never sees
where the cards really are.
No. It's not magic.
But when the effect
is presented,
it sure feels like a miracle.
[Taylor] And if you
invest with us, you will be
behind the curtain
with Axe. And me.
All the mysteries revealed.
Nothing kept secret from you.
Nothing held back.
Fully transparent work.
I could go on but...
But there are bars
in New York City
some of you want to hit
before they close tonight.
[laughter]
Look, Taylor is the single most
effective manager of money
I have ever come across.
They are the future
of Axe Capital.
And I'm just thrilled
that you're all gonna
get the opportunity
to work with them directly
alongside me and the team.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
[door closes]
[mid-tempo music plays
on speakers]
I've got him.
Dramatic. Who you got?
Beer tonight? No, you need
something stronger.
Chuck. Pulling shit again.
What shit?
He's using FBI to hide a witness
who's bad for Jock Jeffcoat.
What do you think you know?
That Chuck is helping his boss's
legal troubles go away.
And you're helping him...
♪ dramatic music ♪
Me?
[Connerty] You're on
the text transcripts, Kate.
[Connerty] Getting
favors from the FBI.
♪ ♪
How did you, uh...
Administrative subpoenas.
Blessed from on high.
So either you can help me.
Or go down with Chuck.
[glasses clink]
Well, you're right about me
needing that stronger drink...
- Mm.
- Um, can we...?
- Boilermakers?
- Mm-hmm.
[Dave the Bartender]
Two coming up.
You got the rest of it
backwards, though.
- Do I?
- Yeah.
You can't mix in here
and try to take Chuck down.
Not on this one.
He's finally doing it,
Bryan. The right thing.
He is not helping Jock
by hiding the witness...
Jock has been telling us
which cases to pursue
and which ones to drop.
Like the Lugo nightmare.
So us having to look
the other way,
stuffing all the bullshit down.
It finally got to be
too much for Chuck.
He is going after him.
He's doing that Chuck thing...
But for the right fucking
reasons this time, all the way.
[Michael McDermott's "Never
Going Down Again" playing]
Fuck!
Yeah.
So let us drink our boilermakers
and let him finish...
You can take him down
over something else
if you still feel
that you have to.
And if you do, I promise
I'll stay out of it
and leave it between
the two of you.
♪ ♪
[glasses clink]
We. Fucking. Did it!
[cheers and applause]
Six billion dollars committed.
In one morning.
[cheering]
We are back!
All the fucking way back!
[cheering]
Wendy, Wags
and Taylor.
[cheering]
[Axe] They all came through
for us huge.
Let's have a big shout out
for all three of them!
[cheering]
The Hold Steady!
[The Hold Steady plays
"Entitlement Crew"]
♪ ♪
♪ Tequila take off,
Tecate landing ♪
♪ Sorry about the centerpiece,
thanks for understanding ♪
♪ Hard branding, soft salesmen,
Campari commissions ♪
♪ I was sitting in the kitchen ♪
♪ Trying to guess
where she was living now ♪
[cheering]
♪ ♪
[door creaks, closes]
[inhales deeply]
[groans]
It's not exactly
like we thought.
[keys jingle]
Then what is it?
We have it flipped.
Chuck's going after Jock,
not covering for him?
Sorry to drag you up here...
There's an Acela back to
Washington tomorrow at 8:00.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ ♪
This is new.
What? I come over
all the time.
Not without an agenda.
A man can't want
to see his own father?
A man can.
Not this man.
[crunches]
[sighs]
This is big game, you're after.
Big fucking game.
The only problem is:
No call yet.
Make your man do
what you want him to do,
not what's good for him...
The object of
any worthwhile contest.
Well, there is one move
we've been holding in abeyance,
because it might bring him
along too quickly...
To a fatal mistake
or walking away free.
Better to play
fast and aggressive
with inferior matériel,
than let them be exposed later.
Rommel?
Me.
If the end game is coming
sooner or later...
Even if it might crush you,
I say: Bring it on.
Shift the pressure of the
decision from you, to him.
Let him have to
avoid the mistake.
Or see the one move
that might get him through.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ ♪
Epstein.
Do it. Pull the trigger
on the grand jury.
Let's see how patient Jock is.
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
[indistinct conversations]
- Hair of the dog?
- No.
[door closes]
It was, indeed,
some party last night.
But I fear it might be over.
Meaning?
I've been making follow up calls
to book the money
that was pledged at the race.
I'm having problems
locking it in.
What fucking problems?
Problems reaching people.
They're dodging.
I'm feeling like somebody
slipped us a Cosby.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
Where the fuck is Taylor?
They're here before me
most of the time.
Not sure.
Sent a text this morning,
didn't hear back.
Huh...
♪ ♪
["Entitlement Crew" playing]
♪ I feel I've been abandoned ♪
♪ Never got to say
goodbye to you ♪
♪ Give my best
to the Entitlement Crew ♪
♪ ♪
[Axe] And no Mafee today.
I figured it was
the whiskey flu.
Fuck.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ ♪
[Taylor] ...A new kind
of organization.
Top down but not imperious
or impetuous. Integrated.
And you can make more
than you do now.
With a partnership stake.
Goddamnit... When?
Now.
Taylor's making a move.
They've played
the Elmsley Count on us.
So we wouldn't see
their real cards.
Fuck.
Pretended to be one of us...
For just long enough to take
our personnel and our capital.
All of it.
♪ ♪
Wendy. Now.
Tell me she's fucking here.
She is. I saw her.
♪ ♪
Is there anything I can do
to stop Taylor
from officially opening?
You could file, and we will,
for intellectual property theft,
for tortious interference
for both the investor piece
and any employees
they enticed away,
and these suits will
have to be defended, but...
But we won't win.
We won't win fast enough
to injunct them from opening.
♪ ♪
File anyway.
Let's get Taylor distracted
from the bottom line.
Let's see how they do
with split focus.
Now, who's actually gone?
And who's on the fence?
So far, it appears
that other than Mafee,
only Ben Kim
sleeps with the fishes.
As for the cash:
500 million came on board,
three and a half billion
went with Taylor,
the other two billion
pulled back, went elsewhere...
Didn't want to be involved
in a family fight.
I'm gonna quarantine a few
traders I have my doubts about
before this thing
spreads like black death.
- [door opens]
- [Helena] Ben Kim is here.
He just got off the elevator
and went to his station.
The important thing
is: I said no.
So you're not a spy?
'Cause you showed up late
on this particular day.
So you can see how I'd wonder.
I can. But I'm not.
I said no.
Walk us through how
Taylor approached you.
♪ Mid-tempo music ♪
♪ ♪
[car horn honks]
Where did you come from?
Wrong question.
Where are we going
is the right one.
Is it?
Come work for me.
I already do.
At Mase Cap.
♪ ♪
You're leaving.
Left.
But Axe has been loyal...
He promoted me.
In title, yes,
after I told him to.
But what kind of money bump
did he give you?
♪ ♪
He gave you a paper title
as a way to keep you
running in place.
But I will give you an entire
field to sprint down.
♪ ♪
[Axe] Ben.
Ben, I'm sorry to
have to tell you, but...
Oh, no... Taylor told you
not to give me the raise.
So that I would be
dissatisfied and go with them.
That's pretty sound from
a game theory perspective.
Yeah. Well.
This ain't no game.
But Taylor treated it like
it was, and you fell for it...
I don't mean that.
No. I was suckered.
And now I will have my turn.
So now that we know
why you didn't
give me more money,
do I get the...
Finish that sentence
at your own peril, Ben Kim.
Though you do have
a future here.
And one that'll have you
getting as rich as a feudal lord
if you keep performing.
Are you in?
I am.
[footsteps depart]
[door opens]
Fuck.
[door closes]
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ ♪
At a time like this,
I suggest looking within.
To see what you... what we...
May have done to cause this.
We rebuild our business
as we rebuild our selves.
Or, don't look inside.
Do what I do instead.
Go drinks, dinners, parties,
funny massage joints
with every fucking whale
in the Street
and poison that
bitch's name to them.
For starters.
♪ ♪
[cellphone buzzes]
[cellphone clicks]
General!
I'd like to see you.
Something I can
help with now, here?
Come on over to the hotel.
Better to talk there.
And I'm on my way, sir.
[cellphone clicks]
Here we go.
♪ ♪
[cellphone buzzes]
[cellphone clicks]
Grigor.
We must meet. Now.
♪ Suspenseful music ♪
♪ ♪
Nice place.
Yeah.
Once I own every townhouse
on the block,
I'll put them all together.
Make a real home, you know?
Quilts on the beds,
needlepoints on the walls,
healing crystals
in every window.
Until then, this one is a place
for special conversations.
They can hear it?
They hear everything,
but they know
exactly what happens
when someone speaks out of turn.
As, I imagine, your man does.
I do.
So, you know
you have a problem, yes?
Yes.
Because you don't
have pest control.
So the pests are running
all around the place
with no consequences.
But I'm very good at dealing
with pests, with vermin.
I have a perfect score
with Consumer Reports.
So if I promise you
that I will make
your problem disappear,
your problem will
never, ever return.
I can't allow
Mr. Axelrod...
Shut the fuck up!
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ ♪
I understand
what you're offering.
But I cannot ask you
to do it, at this time.
♪ ♪
If it were me
and I were standing
as naked as Paris Hilton
and twice as fucked,
I would not hesitate.
I know you wouldn't.
And that perhaps
it's what's called for.
So, then, you want me to do it?
You have to say it.
I have to hear you.
♪ ♪
Why are you willing
to do this for me?
Look at this from my
particular set of binoculars.
I gave you my assets.
At least in part
because Taylor was going
to help manage them.
So when they fucked you over.
They fucked me over, too.
But I ask your permission
because, really,
she is your property.
Not mine.
Well, I'm grateful
for your loyalty.
My loyalties are clear.
Can I respond by tomorrow?
[Grigor] Sure.
Shame about Taylor.
So smart.
Loss for everyone.
♪ ♪
[Hall] You seemed
to take that seriously.
Damn right.
When I've suggested
such actions in the past,
you never even considered it.
Well, once a guy like that
puts it on the table,
you have to think about
what happens if you say no
as much as if you say yes.
If you decide
on something this final,
it shouldn't be farmed out,
it should be done in-house.
Yeah. Maybe.
I don't know.
Look, I need to think about
what other options I have.
And how to protect myself
no matter which choice I make.
And I need to look
Taylor in the eye.
[elevator bell chimes]
[elevator door closes]
Shit, Axe,
look, it was time for a change.
I'm sure you thought so too.
I want to thank you, of course.
Figured I would
when the dust settled...
Shut the fuck up, Mafee.
You did what you did,
you got your money,
but no amount I give to charity
will help me atone
for the ass fucking
I will give you
in this business.
You hearing me?
Now go get
your new fucking master.
The palace coup is complete.
Today you settled
all family business.
I get that you're angry.
But I think it's because
I left before you
could finish me off.
You think I was
acting against you?
The undercutting,
the manipulation,
and public,
and private, humiliation.
The lies and broken promises.
All while I good soldiered it
and made you money.
But how long, really,
was it going to be
before you sent me
off to slaughter?
Wrong.
I wasn't getting rid of you
or working against you.
You were on the inside.
We were succeeding together.
I trusted you in a way that
I almost never trust anyone.
It may have seemed unorthodox,
but that's the truth of it.
And now you've taken from me.
You've stolen from me,
under false pretenses.
And you've betrayed me.
I did what I had to do
to survive. And to win.
You've got to understand that.
I did it for me,
not against you.
Sure. Right.
Congratulations,
now you have your own shop,
billions under management.
You're moving even quicker
than I did.
Yes. I'll surpass
your assets under management,
at the rate I calculate,
in three years at the earliest,
eight at the latest.
Maybe.
You're ready for the summit.
But you know what they call
that spot up on Everest?
The Death Zone.
Some people that make it up,
and then they make it back home.
But there are countless more,
fucking dead,
encased in ice for all time.
That's where you are now.
And very few people
can even survive
on the available oxygen up here.
Even fewer can perform.
So we'll see.
Young lungs.
So yeah, we will.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ ♪
You know your history,
so you know what happens
to usurpers.
Charles Edward Stuart,
for example.
Bonnie Prince Charlie. Yes.
His troops slaughtered.
Him exiled from the kingdom...
More like on the run
for the rest of his life.
And that was one of
the more civilized responses.
♪ ♪
You have to know
that anything I do
to stop you is warranted.
♪ ♪
I anticipated that
being your reaction.
So do what you must.
And I'll defend as I have to.
♪ ♪
General, I didn't expect
to see you back in town so soon.
Makes two of us.
Listen, the reason
I called you over
is there's a legal matter
of some subtlety
that I may need your help on.
I'll be as delicate
as a scrimshander then.
There's a prosecution
in the works.
If you can call it that.
More like a political
hatchet job.
Against you?
Nah, against my brother.
Designed to splatter on me.
Down in Texas?
Well, who's prosecuting?
Perhaps I know him
and could give a nudge,
help steer him away.
New York. State of.
[taps paper]
Alvin Epstein.
Oh.
Rep on him is he is
a straight fucking shooter.
Epstein presents a real problem.
I know him enough to nod
at him, but I'm afraid
I've heard the same thing
as you about him.
He's a crusader type.
Probably not enough dirt
to dig on him either.
Forget about him.
I know who this whole thing
hinges on.
Seedy financier type I knew
in the old days, Ashley Cutler.
He's had his nose bent about me
and my brother for years.
I bedded his sister
back in the day, truth be told.
So did my brother.
She was something
of the town scooter.
But that aside,
if I could somehow
get ten minutes with him,
I'm sure I could remind him
what really matters
to him and his family.
General, I think
you should fall back
and just let this
play out in court.
Let justice take its course.
Safer that way.
Yeah, I could.
But no, I'm gonna give justice
just a little bit
of fucking help.
♪ Suspenseful music ♪
♪ ♪
Well, a course of action
comes to mind
that could get you
what you want,
but it's a dangerous one for me.
So if I were to engage
on your behalf,
I'd expect something in return.
[chuckles softly]
Would you now?
♪ ♪
Well, I can't say
I'm a hundred percent surprised.
A man looking out
for his own interest
is a man who can be counted on.
What do you want?
To be guaranteed my post
until the end
of the administration.
Chuck, you pull this off,
how could I live without you?
Granted.
And Southern becomes
the sovereign district
once again.
I call my own plays from now on.
♪ ♪
Well, I didn't realize my input
was so rankling to you...
♪ ♪
Fine, I give you your latitude.
Then I will do all I can.
♪ ♪
You'll hear from me soon.
There are men, with
the kinds of resources I have,
who would deal
with this betrayal swiftly
and without mercy.
And are you one of them?
Am I?
Without mercy?
Without regard
for Taylor the person?
Not sure.
I'm that angry.
That I'm sure of.
What if you didn't go anywhere?
Did nothing.
Most people in the business will
think you sent Taylor off,
invested with them.
Maybe you still can?
He who makes the money wins.
Or take comfort in the knowledge
that the betrayer will
suffer for their actions.
Suffer how? Internally?
Yeah.
And when the reversals
show up, which they will,
and Taylor has to go it alone,
with no one to turn to...
They will have down years.
And they will spiral.
It's unavoidable.
All you have to do
is wait for it.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
I don't know that I can.
♪ ♪
Well, General, it is indeed
Cutler at the heart of this.
I've subpoenaed him
on a federal matter.
New York State is gonna scream,
but I'll deal with that.
I have him installed
in a hotel under guard.
I know that an assuredly
private conversation
is of the essence for you.
So I've landed on the spa...
[Chuck] He'll be in a room
[Chuck] that's safe
for that conversation.
[Chuck] You'll be able to know...
To see... that he's not wired.
[Chuck] I have trusted FBI
watching him.
♪ Suspenseful music ♪
♪ ♪
[Chuck] And at
the appropriate time,
[Chuck] I'll have them
pulled off the detail...
Yeah?
♪ ♪
We're out.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
[Chuck] You will then
have your time with him.
♪ ♪
I am moved by
your loyalty, grace,
and tactical efficiency.
[glasses clink]
Gracias, amigo.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[cellphone buzzes]
♪ ♪
Alvin?
We got him. It worked.
I can play you the tape.
Oh, yes!
I-I'll come right over
to your office.
I can't be sure
my office isn't bugged.
Meet me at yours.
Very good.
♪ Suspenseful music ♪
♪ ♪
[gasps] Jesus Christ.
No. Just me.
[scoffs]
What do you want?
You.
[chuckling] You think
I'll actually come with you?
Haven't you done enough damage?
I'm building, not destroying.
That's where you come in.
I'm assembling a place
that's tech-centric,
but I want my people
as frequently tuned
and upgraded as the software.
And I don't want them merely
calibrated to make money.
I want you to make sure
their whole selves
are being attended to.
It's a place free
of any arrests,
or indictments, or insinuations.
It's a place where
we can be our best.
Nice ideas.
But you are
no moral fucking compass.
For a moment,
I thought you might be.
Because you needed me
to think that.
But you used me.
If anyone has been using
people for their own ends...
Oh, don't even try that shit.
You preyed on me
and my empathy for you.
Programmed me to get you
what you wanted from Axe...
Being part of the raise.
So... fuck you.
You don't seem to understand...
I'm not just offering you
a job for my sake.
I'm offering you
a fresh start, for yours.
A re-set from your slew
of fuck-ups.
You let things devolve
at Axe Capital.
You didn't see me
being pushed out the door.
You couldn't stop Axe
from succumbing
to his own worst nature.
Instead you succumbed to it.
And who knows what other
fallout you've created
or at least allowed
elsewhere in your life.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
You're a brilliant person.
You have a lot of answers.
But you are very young
and there's a lot more
to this business
- than you've learned so far.
- Like?
It is not just about numbers
and decimal points.
The thing that makes it matter
is: Lasting relationships.
True loyalty.
Real trust.
♪ ♪
No, I'm pretty sure
there's only money,
and it can buy all those things
or at least the same result.
That's what you and Axe
taught me.
♪ ♪
[Axe] That thing you said.
About keeping it 'in-house.'
Maybe pride.
I have the...
craft, you know?
But doing it at a remove,
that makes much more sense.
Oh, so you've been
thinking about it, too.
The thing you said about saying
no to someone like Grigor,
that's where I've spent
most of my thinking time.
How it ramificates out
if I don't give the green light.
Yes.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
Mission e-val.
Just as you would've
for a superior officer
back in the day.
If Grigor did this,
it would be handled cleanly.
There would be an accident...
Falling debris on the street.
An overdose.
A car crash.
A heart attack from a blockage
no one saw coming.
They are employing
a refinement of work flow
in this area
that is simply unmatched.
It would never come back
to you as a matter
law enforcement would bring.
But then...
Yes.
Then Grigor would have
the thing on you forever.
Suddenly he decides you'll
manage his money for no fee.
Then maybe he'll suggest that
you pay him, for his silence.
And once you let him get
the offer out of his mouth,
once he let you hear it...
Then I have something
on him now.
Almost as bad.
How you say yes or no
will determine a lot.
And I have a question
for you, too.
What is your objective?
With regards to Taylor?
Total destruction.
Not out of anger.
But if it becomes clear that
I can be taken advantage of,
that I can groom you,
bring you along, prop you up,
then lose you and a serious
chunk of business, too...
I agree. That's not
a tenable situation.
And it's not tenable
to have Grigor in my city,
knowing that I'm either
indebted to him
or that I rejected him.
But you should know.
Should you move forward,
even through me,
that psychologically...
I do know.
Residue. Of course.
More than residue.
Weight.
Whatever you decide.
However. Whenever.
I am ready.
Good luck.
Hey, Hall...
put extra security
on Lara and the boys.
The kind they don't see.
[car door closes]
[Grigor] So, have you
come to a decision?
I'm gonna pass on your offer.
I didn't have you
as a squeamish man.
A little delicate,
maybe, on the outside.
But I thought
you were a man like me.
A man with steel
in all the places one needs it.
Maybe we just need it
in different spots.
Ah. So you're beyond
this sort of thing, then.
Or you could say this:
I was raised in a place
that didn't require
these extraordinary measures.
You weren't.
If you don't want
to tell me to do it,
but want it to happen anyway,
that's fine.
No. I don't.
♪ Suspenseful music ♪
Fine. Okay...
Then I will pull all my money,
and I will give it to Taylor.
I promised I would
give you a warning...
This is it.
Look, nothing in the way
I operate my business
has changed.
You loved it last week.
How can I keep my money
with a man
who won't kill for it?
I don't want Taylor dead.
I want them alive to experience
all that I am gonna do to them.
I'm gonna destroy them
in ways that'll make them wish
they got what you offered.
Sure. Why not?
Have fun.
But remember,
if what you do to them,
costs me,
we will meet again.
♪ ♪
Until then, goodbye, Axe.
I'm expecting
Alvin Epstein shortly,
see him right in.
Morning, Kate...
You recognized I was
a political animal.
You fed it.
Nurtured it.
And I warned you
it might bite you.
That's where we are.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ ♪
Well, glad you
could join us, Chuck.
♪ ♪
Regrets, Chuck.
Tiger's breath was just too hot
when it was right in my face...
♪ ♪
I can't be sure
my office isn't bugged.
Meet me at yours.
♪ ♪
See you in Washington, General.
We'll break bread together
soon, Mr. Deputy.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
[Jock] That's a good man,
right there, my new Deputy AG.
If you say he is.
That's right.
'Good' means something
when I say it.
These people...
They're good, too.
They've proven it.
The young lady was kind enough
to be of assistance.
♪ ♪
And especially these young men.
[Connerty] Oliver Dake reminded
me of our true purpose:
Restoring justice
to the Justice Department.
[Dake] We reminded each other.
Now, General, I know
things didn't end
particularly well between us...
Certainly from
your point of view.
Nonetheless, I gained clarity
as soon as I left New York.
And then Mr. Connerty
came to me and...
we've discovered something
of a putsch against you.
[Jock] The fellas told me
what you had in store for me.
[Jock] So I decided
to let Cutler sit there.
[Jock] By his lonesome.
Naked and afraid.
Of course, by now, he's free,
back upstate,
with his loved ones.
Because there is no case.
There never was.
[Jock] My brother's
down in Texas,
[Jock] unmolested,
as he should be,
[Jock] tending to his flock.
[Jock] What I know now, señor,
is that character cannot
be taught or learned.
It is innate.
Some people have it.
These boys do. Miss Sacker.
♪ ♪
- You clearly do not.
- General...
[Jock] This is as fine
a head covering
as a man could ever
hope to possess.
Yet you have it here as what,
some kind of joke at my expense?
[Jock] You ingratiated
yourself to me, Chuck.
[Jock] You inveigled
yourself into my life.
You invited me and my wife
into your house.
YOUR HOUSE!
[Jock] Only to do me
like some combo
of Iscariot
and Salvatore Tessio.
Well, I'm gonna do you
the same as they got.
[Jock] Now, I'm sure
you are aware,
but I will say it for posterity.
This is not
obstruction of justice.
Because that bullshit case
was brought by Mr. Epstein.
Not by you.
You had nothing.
And now you are nothing.
[Jock] As of this moment,
you are a trespasser
[Jock] in these
hallowed halls of the law.
♪ ♪
You, Charles Rhoades Junior,
are relived of duty.
On power of the President,
you are fired!
♪ ♪
Mr. Connerty,
as your first detail
[Jock] as Interim
United States Attorney
[Jock] for the
Southern District,
please show this gentleman out.
My pleasure.
♪ ♪
What'd you manage to get
for yourself, professor?
I got to watch all this.
♪ ♪
[Jock] Yeah, look at him,
going out like the teaser
I always knew you were.
Pathetic.
♪ ♪
Enjoy this.
You've outplayed me.
And you have earned it.
But don't, even for a second,
think that that smile
on your face
is gonna be there
for very fucking long.
Oh, Chuck,
that's not my smile.
This is.
[laughs evilly]
♪ ♪
Move him along.
Come on, Chuck.
♪ ♪
Bryan, think about
what you're doing, man.
Drop your credentials
at the desk,
and Get The Fuck Out Of Here.
♪ ♪
[sniffs]
I've brought you
some redemption...
Redemption Roasters Coffee
that is.
To wish you good luck
on your new venture,
and because, to make it go,
you'll be working
all night long.
Thank you, Oscar.
How'd you find me?
Word's traveling fast.
I also brought you this...
My letter of intent to come
on-board with some seed money.
Initial investment
of 500 million.
Thank you. Wow.
Would you like to meet up later?
There's a secret new
dumpling spot in Queens...
Doesn't even have a name,
just a door.
I'd like to talk, to try...
I'm happy to put
capital with you,
because you're smart.
And I think
you'll make me money.
But after what you did,
I could never open myself
up to you again.
♪ Frank Sinatra's
"One for my Baby" ♪
♪ ♪
♪ It's quarter to three ♪
♪ There's no one in the place ♪
♪ Except you and me ♪
♪ ♪
♪ So, set 'em up, Joe ♪
♪ I got a little story ♪
♪ I think you should know ♪
♪ ♪
♪ We're drinkin', my friend ♪
♪ To the end ♪
♪ Of a brief episode ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Make it one for my baby ♪
[cellphone vibrates]
♪ And one more for the road ♪
Hey.
I saw Taylor.
They tried to bring me aboard.
Can't imagine
that went well for them.
Or are you about to shock me?
Fuck them.
As I said.
That's right. Good.
No, I mean fuck them over.
You have to. We do.
Well, that's different
from: "look inward."
Yeah.
Well, you know what?
I'm different.
♪ Can't you make the music ♪
♪ Easy and sad ♪
♪ ♪
[knock on door]
♪ I could tell you a lot ♪
♪ But you've gotta be ♪
♪ True to your code ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Just make it one ♪
♪ For my baby ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And one more ♪
♪ For the road ♪
'Lo Bob.
Charles.
You know, Wendy asked,
and I said,
Mm, you know, I'm no longer
the US Attorney.
So there's no conflict.
And I have nothing
against the guy.
Not anymore.
I said much the same.
So come on in.
Join us.
Love to.
[sighs]
So, you know how you're
gonna go after Jock?
[smacks lips]
Some ideas floating
around my head, yeah.
And, uh, Taylor?
Yeah. Yeah.
Got a plan that's
starting to form.
[Velvet Underground's]
["We're Gonna Have
a Real Good Time Together"]
Tell him about it.
♪ ♪
There's no one better
at breaking down a strategy.
♪ ♪
You want to hear it?
Hit me with what you got...
♪ We're gonna have
a real good time together ♪
♪ ♪
♪ We're gonna have
a real good time together ♪
♪ ♪
♪ We're gonna have
a real good time together ♪
♪ ♪
♪ We're gonna laugh and dance
and shout together ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Na na-na-na-na na,
na-na na-na na na ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Na na-na-na-na na,
na-na na-na na ♪
♪ Oh, baby, oh ♪
♪ Na na-na-na-na na,
na-na na-na na ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Na na-na-na-na na,
na-na na-na na ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ We're gonna have
a real good time together ♪
♪ You know that we're gonna have
♪ ♪
♪ We're gonna have
a real good time together ♪
♪ Ohhh ♪
♪ We're gonna laugh and dance
and shout together ♪
♪ Get it ready, now ♪
♪ Na na-na-na-na na,
na-na na-na na na ♪
♪ Oh, baby, na na-na-na-na na,
na-na na-na na ♪