Previously on Billions...
Sandicot's not getting
the gaming license.
The committee chose the
location that will bring
the greatest benefit to the
greatest number of people.
The gaming license
was the guarantee
that Sandicot would
pay off the notes.
So, it's fallen upon all
of you to figure out
how to get us un-fucked.
Austerity. It's
your only option.
Axe Cap was not what I
thought it would be.
You care to be a
little more specific?
I'm supposed to give
their lawyer a heads-up,
but I think I'm pretty
safe to talk...
if you bring me a subpoena.
The Churchill World War II.
You sure, Chuck?
"Never give in. Never give in."
From the day I passed the bar,
I have said those
words to myself
the first morning
of every trial.
- You can still say the words.
- Hello. I'm Taylor.
My pronouns are "they,"
"theirs," and "them."
You see things differently.
That's an edge.
That's Camelot right there.
That is a picture of a
man running for office.
- Our deal hold?
- Yes, but not for you.
You want a session?
See someone else.
My office is off-limits.
I should've told you about Wendy
before I even spoke to her.
What if I won't see her?
I'll draw a line.
Black Jack Foley.
How are you, Charles?
I'll be better if you help me
out with a little something.
I know what you and
your two daddies did
up in Sandicot.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
Thanks, Wags, but... really?
You got me VR goggles?
What, am I turning 13?
If you were, Uncle Wagsy
would be getting you laid
by the most beautiful
call girl in the state.
But you're a big man
having a big birthday,
so the gift matches. And
you're not there yet.
It's called The Arque,
the foremost luxury
bunker for end times.
A hedge against humanity.
Stocks of non-perishable food,
water purification
equipment, seed banks,
DNA cold storage,
medical supplies,
and surgical equipment.
Everything you need,
jefe, even weapons.
- For what?
- I don't know.
Terrorists. Cannibals.
Happy birthday.
This coin means that you've
got a spot reserved.
I made the down payment.
And I'm not too classy to
say that it ran me 360K.
Sic Transit Imperium.
"So passes the empire."
Thanks, Wags.
I can see you put a lot
of thought into this.
You get a spot for yourself?
If humanity has to be rebuilt,
it sure as fuck shouldn't
be in my image.
Besides, you know I wanna be
on the outside, rocking
with the marauders.
Let's go.
You went with a
sailcloth option.
- Huh?
- Tent.
Oh, yeah. Lara picked it.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
Axelrod has never made a
move as brazen, as public
as looting a working class town.
Yeah, now he's like the bad
guy in a Springsteen song.
Exactly so.
Oh, he's the boss man
closing down the factory
and kicking Johnny
99 to the street.
We're going to attack. Bryan.
Now the thrust of
this muni-bond deal,
buying of the debt,
forcing austerity...
Austerity. What a lovely word
for fucking the life
out of 180,000 people.
Yeah. Well, the bond deal
itself, reprehensible as it is,
is completely legal. It's
the timing that's suspect.
Axe jumped in when he did
because he knew something.
We laser in on how he
came by the information,
who's involved, how money
may have changed hands.
Information like
this is never free.
There's bribes and
payoffs under it.
Real Meeting Across
the River shit.
What, only white men can
listen to The Boss?
Oh, not at all. No.
In fact, like the main
character in that deep cut,
Axe is not gonna win here.
Something has to
tie back to him.
We're on a path. Uh, location
board, gaming commission.
Uh, it's Albany.
You can't have a PTA bake
sale without kickbacks.
Let's mount up.
Sandicot team has a
long drive ahead of us.
Kate? That subpoena come
through for Steph Reed?
Thirty minutes ago. I will have
her in here this afternoon.
It's a big deal,
source that close.
You have my complete confidence.
I thought Connerty did.
I have enough confidence
to go around.
Aparicio Rodriguez.
- Plays third.
Kid's the next Sal Bando.
First round draft
pick next June.
I've been paying for private
lessons for him since he was 13
in exchange for a chunk of the
kid's future signing bonus.
- It's recoup time.
- 2,000 percent ROI...
even counting the dozen
other kids I invested in
- but had to cut loose.
- All right, guys, take a break!
- Rodriguez, bring it in.
I got you a birthday present.
- Him?
- No. Klaxon.
- Belgian car company.
- An auto scheme?
I'd rather have the ballplayer.
At least this guy can hit.
This is better.
It's something I couldn't
discuss at the office.
Did you know about this?
Not the details, only that there
was something worth hearing.
I heard rumors. Dug into it
off-campus, off the books.
They're headed for a recall.
Major fines, sanctions.
- Bottom's gonna drop out.
- When?
Unknown, but we gotta move
fast to lay in our position.
This news won't hold long.
What's your level of certainty?
♪ Tense music ♪
I am not uncertain.
Any particulars I need to know?
No.
I'll think about it.
Whoa, wait. This...
this is automatic.
This cow's got a
bolt to its head,
and it's hanging upside-down.
You just gotta carve
it up and eat it.
Times are changing.
No matter how not
uncertain you are,
these days, I take a laparoscope
to the fucking guts
of every deal.
Gents, if I may...
What's to gain?
A hundred million? It's
a drop in the bucket.
It's not worth giving the
government the opening.
Perfectly said, Wags.
Has he made you
afraid of Rhoades,
whispering pussy
excuses in your ear?
You're really that
fucking scared, Axe?
You back off, Bill.
Why? 'Cause he can end my
world, burn my contacts,
and keep every cent of
my bonus for himself?
That... That's supposed to
make me hold my tongue?
- Fuck, yeah.
- See? That...
That's why you will never
buy and sell equities.
No, all that's supposed
to make me more brazen
when I know I'm fucking right.
It's okay, Wags. It's okay.
Come Here.
If I were standing
where you are,
I'd be even more
strident in my approach.
But I'm standing here, so I
have to be the opposite...
- reflective, calm, considered.
It's just about who I am at
this precise moment in time.
What business are we in, hmm?
I thought it was a
business of profit,
of free men and women,
beyond the apparatchiks
and their pathetic rules.
Yeah, all of that and
"Who is John Galt?"
Look, I'm a rich man.
You're a very rich man.
If we can't live how we want,
then the terrorists
have already won.
Back in the cage!
- Let's go.
- What the fuck was that?
That was a guy who was giving
me all the right questions.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
We're looking at a police
force at half-capacity.
The library is open
12 hours a week.
Why, that is... revolting.
No, I see what's happening here.
You are not invisible.
You matter.
- Lock him up!
- Yeah!
If the law gives me
the power, I will.
And... if the law doesn't,
well, then somebody needs to
get to work changing the law.
- Yeah.
Robert Kennedy said,
"Every society gets the
criminal it deserves."
Sandicot sure didn't
deserve Bobby Axelrod.
But you do deserve
the law enforcement
I plan on bringing.
- Right, right, right.
Thank you.
Go! Gotta go!
You sure you don't
want to talk to 'em?
No. I don't need to
sound my own horn.
Now if the people of Sandicot
wanna trumpet it for me...
Sir.
Will you come with me?
♪ Tense music ♪
Well, well.
Impressive ground game,
showing me there's no corner
of the state you don't touch.
Ah, I planned to be up here.
Sure.
Ah, so...
Uh, is your granddaughter
enjoying Washington?
Just getting settled in. Hmm.
She and I remain touched by the
generosity of your spirit.
Good. That's nice to hear.
Ah, there's someone,
uh, I need you to see.
George Minchak.
- Okay.
- She vets all of my candidates.
You want her to know everything.
It's a stress test.
- Yeah.
- We prepare for what
- the opposition will use.
I'm not really sure I'm
entirely comfortable with that.
My last candidate who
did not use her...
was Spitzer.
I'll fit her right in.
And we need to do it right
now because of the attention
this, uh, unofficial
campaign visit will bring.
I'd have told you if
I'd thought that...
No, you... you don't need
to tell me everything.
You need to tell
Minchak everything.
Then Minchak tells me.
Hmm.
- That was a joke.
- Okay.
Uh, what you're doing up here,
um, feeling their pain?
It's a time-honored tradition.
And the way you refused to,
uh, play to the grandstand,
thus ensuring that the, uh,
reporters will chase you
to the next whistle stop,
that brings a smile.
Yes, I felt that to do
interviews at this time
would only have downside.
Yeah, it's as worthless
as a $100 dollar bill
to a rooster with a hard on.
Well, if you're thinking of
having a meal before you leave,
try the Garbage Plate.
It's a local delicacy.
That looks hard to resist.
You'll hardly be able.
Eat the shit out of it.
I've been angling to get
into investor relations
for 16 months.
Hmm. I didn't know that.
Does that mean I haven't been
doing it assertively enough?
Maybe, um, not necessarily.
We can talk about ways
to be more clear and
more goal-oriented,
if that's what you're
interested in.
It's just... I don't know
what I'd be selling.
Sandicot is...
is hard to swallow,
placing the calls,
crowing about our returns
at the expense of a town.
- Just makes me feel...
so isolated...
and kind of sad.
A lot of people are
having problems with it.
Do you ever feel that way,
like the things we have to
do compromise us somehow?
♪ Tense music ♪
This isn't about me.
But why are you
feeling this way?
Is it just about Sandicot?
No. There are other
things that I see.
And I remember being a kid
and our reverend saying,
- "He who looks..."
- Yeah, we need to stop here.
I'm not sure having an
overgrown conscience
is gonna help you get that
investor relations job,
you know?
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know what I hate?
- Fish, fowl, or mammal?
Learning something about myself.
When is that bullshit
just gonna stop?
- Dollar Bill?
- What he said,
he's kind of right.
I've become a pussy.
No. We just made a choice to
stop living on the edge is all.
Is it?
- What'd she say?
- She told me to suck it up.
Then she said an overgrown
conscience isn't gonna help me.
She said that? Okay.
She saw through it.
- Axe, I was thinking about
my position here, and I think
I would make an excellent...
It was a script, Deb.
Don't internalize.
Look who's making a
racket in Sandicot.
He's coming again, isn't he?
He never wasn't.
♪ Tense music ♪
Tell Dollar Bill no on Klaxon.
What do you get a billionaire?
God, I wish I had the stones to skip it.
I hate these things.
You love parties.
Well, I recently took the
Myers-Briggs personality test,
and it turns out
I'm an introvert.
I'm not sure that
test is rock-solid.
I thought I like
parties, but I don't.
On a deeper level, it
disturbs my equilibrium.
Is that why you woke up the
day after the Christmas party
in a yellow snow drift
behind the strip joint?
Exactly.
- Bearing of a Roman Centurion?
- Or slices through rough seas
- like a Man-O-War?
- What?
Birthday speech. You got skills?
Not for... all that.
But the party, I
have a conflict.
I want to gauge the
importance of attending.
Axe doesn't take attendance, but
he knows who's in the room.
- I'll leave it at that.
- Fuck.
Did you just say "fuck"?
I did.
You're one of us now.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
What was the nature of
your job at Axe Capital
as you understood it?
I was to be next to
Axe in every meeting,
to be the firewall against
illicit dealings.
I was a witness and to make sure
things were being
done above board.
Tell me about Axe.
He was unreadable.
At three o'clock, he
was writing checks
to aid earthquake victims
in the Caribbean.
At 3:45, he was
cornering the market
on Churchill first editions
just to stick it to an enemy.
And then one day, he
just fragged my ass.
I never really saw it coming.
Did he give an explanation?
No. I guess he just didn't
want a witness anymore.
Referred to himself
as a Terminator.
What does that mean?
A cybernetic organism,
programmed to kill.
Living tissue over
robotic endoskeleton...
I've seen the movie.
I just meant...
He has some sort of
programmed mission,
and I was standing in the way.
The day before he fired me,
Bill Stearn approached
with a play that was
clearly over the line,
citing a source named Victor.
Did he say the...
They didn't talk about it...
because I was in the room.
But without me, one
or both of them
would have circled back,
no doubt about it.
Or else Axe would've
filled my position.
No. He wanted no impediments
to illegal activity,
and that's what he has now.
Dollar Bill's tough.
We have a history.
Anyone else?
Try Taylor Mason.
They have become something
of a prodigy, a go-to.
Anything big Axe is wading into,
Taylor's there with
a snorkel mask.
♪ Tense music ♪
I believe it's time,
nay, long past time,
to transform your charitable arm
and engender a
permanent foundation.
Properly stewarded, it
will write the name
of your benevolence on the ages,
alongside Carnegie, Vanderbilt.
A creation of consequence.
Because otherwise, what's it all for?
Is that right?
I don't pretend to answer
that which lies in the
realm of the theologians.
Yet you just happened to pitch
me legacy on my birthday?
I won't claim happenstance.
This is the time
when a man like you
allows reflection
to dictate action.
He thinks I need him to steward
this whole legacy thing.
You don't need me,
but I would be qualified
for such a position.
What do you make at
your current gig?
I prefer not to
really get into that.
It's public record, Sean.
Have some dignity and
spare us the time.
Two-hundred
twenty-five thousand.
Okay. And a, uh, "true steward"
of a multi-billion dollar
charitable foundation,
what would that put
me back, Wags?
In the range of $350,000
to $500,000 a year,
I think it was.
Yeah. See, I have looked
into this before.
And you are not the
first one in here
looking to double his salary.
But today is your lucky day,
because I do want to set
up a permanent foundation
with you as its steward.
I accept.
- With one urgent
recommendation.
Cancel your party.
That's direct.
You just offered me
enough, so I have to be.
You cannot throw a lavish party
at the very moment when you're
draining the meager resources
of what amounts to a village
of apple-cheeked orphans.
That party was organized long
before Sandicot got grounded.
A change of course?
That's reactionary. Weak.
I am not hiring you
to serve me weak tea.
You're really hiring him? Why?
Hired. We shook.
I'm setting a course that
needs to be acknowledged
in all future stories about
wherever we go next.
Ayles may be what he is,
but he speaks the nasal language
of culture and credibility.
And you just bought that.
It's what all the great
philanthropists did,
wrote their names on the ages
and laundered their
reputations in the process.
I'm keen to get started.
- Hey. I gotta go relieve Wendy.
- What was so important?
Ice Juice.
It's a natural beverage company.
A proprietary process
called Flash-Pas.
I own a chunk of the company,
and I've represented the founder...
forever.
He's done. He wants out.
I can take it over.
Majority ownership.
It is within reach.
I just need the cash.
Your, uh, lockup
period is ending?
You said you wanted to
do something for me.
- Now is when I need it.
- I meant what I said.
I owe you, but, I mean,
you know my money's
in a blind trust.
I know. I don't want your money.
Oh, I see.
My father. You want his money.
Except I never get involved
in his business deals
for ethical as well as...
personal reasons.
Chuck, this is my chance.
This IPO is... It's
a blockbuster.
This is... This is that leap
that I've always talked about,
the one I've been waiting
my whole life to take.
Well, you know him. Why
don't you just call?
Well, if it comes from you,
he'll take it more seriously.
If I make the call, then it's
tantamount to me endorsing it,
which is... not something
I can do right now.
Look, you know I see
the inside of more deals
per day than anyone.
This is the one that
I've been waiting for
to get me out of that
goddamn law office.
I do know that you
would not be here
unless the deal was a winner.
- I'll...
Let me think.
Of course. Of course.
All right.
Look what Wags got me.
The Arque?
Luxury survival bunker.
It's a scam.
Why does everything
need to be a scam?
When the Armageddon comes,
the doors will be locked.
I think it's a good
idea, a fail-safe.
The end could come sooner
than anyone might think.
Yeah, it might
already have come.
We just don't know it yet.
Well, what do you
think'll happen
when it all really goes to shit?
- Well...
Getting to the mountains
could be a problem.
We'd have to let the pilot
and his family in the Arque.
Yeah. We'd really have
to build it ourselves,
recruit all the security forces
just to ensure absolute loyalty.
- Mm, and secrecy, you know?
No VR sales tours.
And we'd also have to
make room for my family,
Matty and Mary and Ned
and Connie and Lu and Mo, Sean.
Yeah, I'm not sure
about that, Lar.
Excuse me?
Well, we wouldn't leave
them just to die.
We'd buy two Arques, ours
in the Canadian Rockies,
- and one for your family in...
- Jersey.
- So generous.
- Well, fuck it.
I should probably just go
down with the whole ship,
this fucking tent, hedge
funds, all of it.
Half my life now is
ass-covering and optics,
fucking optics of everything
from parties to put options.
♪ Tense music ♪
I'm spending half a mil
on some stuffed shirt
to brush up my fucking image.
Come on, maybe we should
split for the weekend, now,
before we need the
goddamn Arque.
And bail on the party?
Just the two of us. We'll
celebrate our way.
No.
Big occasions like this
need to be marked,
acknowledged,
for posterity and for fun.
You deserve to be celebrated.
And you should be surrounded
by your whole gang
so they can honor you, too.
They work for me.
They're not my friends.
What about Wags and Dollar Bill?
If they're not your friends,
they're kind of like brothers.
You know, they deserve a chance
to show you how they feel.
I'm not even gonna tell you
who you sound like right now.
And Wendy, too.
You know I decided
not to see her.
And I was clear about that,
and I've stuck to it.
So... I don't know
if she'll want...
Just because you don't
talk to her professionally
doesn't mean that you
can't take one night
to commemorate the
importance of it all.
She's foundational to Axe Capital...
and to you.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
- No, it's okay. I was... tired.
You were out of town?
Uh...
Yeah. I don't know if you heard,
but I was up in Sandicot.
It's a real mess up there.
Looking to punish
those responsible.
I was invited to Axe's
birthday party.
I said no.
Hmm. What's that about?
My readjustment back
at Axe Cap has been...
more difficult than I
thought it would be.
How so?
I've felt manipulated.
I may have done
some of that, too.
I may have given
you the impression
that I was happy there, and
I may well end up that way.
But the truth is,
it's been bumpy.
Well, why are you staying?
Oh, you don't have
to answer that...
No, it's what I've
been asking myself.
I built something.
I put myself into it, and now...
It's not what you remembered,
not what you fell in love with.
I think I went back to
see if I still could.
Something I tell my patients
when they're hesitating about
making some kind of move
in their own life is, sometimes
you have to jump in...
- Mm.
- All the way in to find out.
They are lucky to have you.
It's easy when it's
about someone else.
Yeah.
It's about you,
it's hard to know.
When do you... keep
working at it?
When do you... give up?
♪ Tense music ♪
I don't know.
Dollar Bill's telling the truth.
It looks clean.
Even if they trace his burner
or get into his air-gapped
laptop, like I did,
nothing will come back to you,
unless somebody talked.
Like his source?
Victor Mateo. You were right.
Fuck.
This is complicated, because
Victor always puts himself
where the money is, but it's
usually far from pristine.
Well, then he's the
potential weak link.
He's either looking to
get back in your graces
or trying to get close enough
to jab a ricin-tipped
umbrella into your thigh.
- Hello?
Oh. I was... calling for Wendy.
She's not available.
Who's calling?
Lara Axelrod. This
must be Chuck.
That's right.
Can I tell her what
it's regarding?
My husband's birthday party.
She RSVP'd "no," and I
just wanted to make sure
she knew that both
Bobby and I would
really be delighted to
see her at the house.
Well, uh, I will certainly
pass along your message.
But I do know that she
was feeling a lack of...
clarity in terms of going.
I'm guessing things are tense
and complicated right now,
and this can't be helping.
You're not guessing.
I know this is weird. I was
just calling to say...
she's back at the company,
and the company will all be
here, so she should be, too.
You know, if we don't
mark the milestones,
we're just passing
with the time.
Well said.
And I'd invite you
as her plus one,
but under the circumstances...
Yeah. There is such a
thing as too weird,
even for all of us.
Well, uh, I will pass
along your message.
Good night.
♪ Melancholy music ♪
Chuck.
- Hi, Chuck.
- Hey.
You know, I think that you're
not going to the party
because of me,
which pleases me in a way
that it probably shouldn't.
Oh, Chuck.
Wendy,
I say go to the party.
Either it'll feel
right or it won't.
- But...
you gotta jump in and find out.
How's Victor been?
Look, I would've told
you it came from him,
but the last time I
mentioned his name...
For good fucking reason.
- Because Steph Reed was there.
- Yeah, because I fired his ass.
And sure, I paid him off
to keep the peace, but...
My God, I think he'd
still love to roast me.
You trust me? Right?
With my life.
Because there's certain
guys you just know about.
You look 'em in the
eye, and you know.
Other guys, you
know things about.
And with Victor, it... it's both.
Yeah, I know him.
But also...
I know things about him.
And the things I know,
he can't fuck me,
so he can't fuck you.
So that might be enough for you.
I understand.
But it's not enough
for me, not anymore.
You know, before the
Old West gunslingers
were turned into dime store
paperbacks and cartoons,
the word "outlaw"
meant something.
It meant that the law
didn't apply to you.
No protection.
You run across a guy
on a forest road,
he could kill you.
No repercussions.
I mean... you used
to love Victor,
and trust him before
all this started.
He didn't do anything to
deserve the fate you gave him.
That's what makes this
decision so tricky.
He had the right
to cold dish me.
I just don't know that
he's past it yet.
Oh.
Why don't you ask him yourself?
Look him in the face.
That's your present.
And you might find it's worth
more than a hundred million.
♪ Tense music ♪
So, Steph Reed...
I wish she were
more of an asset.
Axelrod has been very careful.
Here are the notes from the
interview, if you're interested.
Terminator?
Cyberdyne Systems, series
800, Resistance Infiltrator.
- Got it.
- It's kind of a miss,
so I went back into
the Sandicot file
- and ran this down.
Old stock car.
Title was transferred to casino
developer, Donald Thayer,
from Bobby Axelrod.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
Thought you forgot
the way in here.
Know it by heart.
Couple things.
- Okay. Go.
- Deb Kawi.
I knew you made her.
The next time you tell someone
to lose their conscience
- will be the first time.
- Don't run people at me.
- Got you in the office.
- No.
I'm here because of
the other thing.
Your birthday.
Okay. What, specifically,
about that?
Your wife asked me to come.
Said you wanted me there.
- Is it true?
- I think you know me well enough
to know the answer
to that question.
♪ Tense music ♪
♪ Dramatic music ♪
Quite a hole you've dug yourself
right here in the middle of
scenic Kingsford, Thayer.
It's not my best.
It's not my worst.
I just have one question,
the only question that matters.
Who is Bobby Axelrod to you?
He's a friend.
Why else would he have given
me that Dodge out front?
Figured you knew that if you
were here asking questions.
I also know about that
above-market lease
you signed on his Sandicot land.
Is it wrong to overspend?
My wife dings me for
that all the time.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah, you know,
- I see something I like...
- Nah.
No one will believe that.
Oh, not when we run 'em through
the litany of business
dealings you've engaged in
that could, uh, most charitably
be described as shady
and most accurately as criminal.
Fraudulent loan applications,
union payoffs, stiffing vendors,
and yet, writing off the
expenses on your account.
You do everything to save a
buck on the business end.
Are you leveraging me?
I've been strong-armed
by the vowel guys.
- Never bent.
- Oh.
Oh, I bet you'd like to
put me in that hole...
- like you used to do it.
Then pour the concrete.
They never find 'em when
you do that, do they?
No one wants to tear a
whole building down,
but you can't now. Now,
you're respectable... ish.
You've changed your narrative.
So let me suggest a new
chapter in your story,
one in which you are the
unindicted co-conspirator
rather than a defendant.
Which story is that?
The story of Sandicot.
Let me tell it to you,
then you tell it back,
if it's true, of
course, which it is.
You and Axelrod entered
into a criminal conspiracy
to bribe Marc Capparello
for inside information
on the deliberations of
the Location Committee
and where they were
gonna put your casino.
Wow.
You're some fucking gangster,
swaggering up here,
making threats.
From you, "fucking gangster"
sounds like a compliment.
Not how I meant it.
Axelrod is not your friend.
Let me help you keep
on the right side.
You'd love to know
what I got on him.
Problem is,
I don't need whatever
deal or immunity you got.
See, I already have my umbrella.
I'm singin' in the fucking rain.
You?
You're just standing
there, gettin' wet.
I'll see you on Pearl
Street at my arraignment...
if you got the brass.
♪ Pensive music ♪
Three and two, count is full.
I grew up playing stickball.
You wanna grab that broom
handle and stand in?
I'll get too intense.
Okay.
People are telling me I
can't miss your party.
No, because those people think
the only way to advance
is by following the
rules and social mores.
They have no fucking idea
why we do what we do.
I don't think I'm any
better than them.
Of course you do.
You even know it a little bit.
Do not feel obligated to attend.
- Okay.
Why are you missing
it, by the way?
You don't wanna party with me?
It's my sister's wedding.
Rehearsal dinner on
Mackinac Island in the U.P.
- Michigan.
- Oh, yeah. I know.
Not a lot of flights.
You're rich. They're
called private planes.
- I almost booked it.
I just don't know if I
can actually get on it.
The carbon footprint alone is...
You're really that worried
about the world ending?
Yes.
What about your own world?
Not so much.
Well, before that existential
dread racks you,
buy some offsets.
Donate to the
Rainforest Alliance.
As a matter of fact,
if you do that,
I'll have Deb book the plane for ya.
Done. Move on.
It's not just that. It's...
I never thought I'd be thinking
about living this life.
You're living it already.
Do you think I ever
thought I'd be here?
I never thought I'd be more than
just a numbers guy at the track.
Aqueduct?
Nah. Trotters. I'd
still be at the track
if it weren't for this
one guy, a gambler.
He worked a seat at Commodities.
He thought I'd be good.
So he took me to Four World
Trade, and I saw it immediately.
I could read the tape just
like the odds on the board.
It was like walking
into something
between a casino and the U.S.
Mint.
So I bought a seat at
the exchange for 64K,
and that was it.
Is that a common
career trajectory?
Not anymore. Wasn't
back then either.
And you're glad
it went this way?
Yeah. Why shouldn't I be?
So before I let you get
back to your childhood,
the moral of the story is...
just get on the
fucking plane, huh?
No.
The moral of the story
is, you get one life,
so do it all.
Why did I have Thayer
dead to rights,
and he wasn't even nervous?
Why were you sitting with
Thayer in the first place?
How does that help you with
headlines, blind items...
community leaders?
Oh, you weren't encouraging
me to be smart.
You were protecting
one of your own.
Did you handpick
him for the deal?
Did I make a mistake with you?
Are you fighting for
inches or yards?
I am so close to getting Axe.
I can run on that.
I can win on that.
That's what we both want.
If you are the man I think and...
and hope you are,
you will get him...
on something else.
You know it's not the first time
Axe has gone bad on something.
What did Thayer give
you, four points?
I don't handcuff. You're free
to go after Thayer if you want.
But play out those
dominoes first,
and not just for Axe.
♪ Pensive music ♪
Thayer takes a hit,
the casino goes away.
Those upstate jobs go away.
It leaks that my father
started things in Sandicot...
and the last one falls on me.
Chuck, Sandicot is a circle.
Wherever you start on that path,
it leads right back to you...
to us.
And right now, no one knows
that you and my father
crushed that town
as much as Axe.
- Yes.
And why don't we
keep it that way?
You know what, Jack?
I think I'll get Axe
on something else.
Whatever you feel is best.
♪ Well, I know that
it's getting late ♪
♪ But I don't wanna go home ♪
♪ I'm in no hurry, baby ♪
♪ Time can wait ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't wanna go home ♪
♪ Listen to the man
sing his song ♪
You're seeming... shy tonight.
We can't escape our nature.
Enough with the
Myers-Briggs, Mafee.
- Cheers.
- The man here yet?
- Nah, I haven't seen him.
- Cheers.
What? Weird.
- Yeah?
- Hey.
Have a seat.
Fuck. Thayer stonewalled us?
I'm not gonna shield you
from this, Bryan, all right?
I have decided not to
pursue Thayer or Sandicot,
for strategic reasons.
- Politics.
- Yeah.
Plain and simple.
- Tell the team.
Welcome to my bowling club.
I worked it out so I had
it private tonight.
Sweet. How are ya, Victor?
Lots of times, I thought
about, if I ran into you,
what I might say... or do.
Here I am. Hit me.
I can take it.
That's in the past.
Fuck you, Axe.
You think every time you take
a meeting or take a shit,
it's deep and
filled with wisdom.
But you made a mistake
letting me go.
You cut me, but you cut
yourself worse in the process.
You're not wrong, Victor.
You were collateral damage.
I regretted it.
- Really?
- Briefly.
And for a few moments
after, which surprised me.
You getting soft?
♪ Tense music ♪
I came all the way
out here, Victor,
on the recommendation
of a dear friend,
to look at you.
What do you see? A
man who's stuck...
at a boutique firm, a
glorified day trader.
Making good money, but not
as good as it used to be.
But that's not the sticky part.
You can't be who you are,
and it's ripping you up.
Bit by bit.
What do you have and
what do you want?
I want back in. Not
with the main fund.
I understand you can't do that,
and I don't want you to.
I want my own shop, a satellite.
Terms will be very
generous for you
the first few years,
and I will give you the
prime fucking meats.
Everything I know about Klaxon.
Internal memos,
company documents.
It's bigger than a recall.
You leak this cover-up,
they'll drown in lawsuits.
You could cover at zero.
Start looking for office space.
Welcome back.
Donna!
I need Sacker now!
- This. What the fuck is this?
Steph Reed says that Axe
bought some enemy's books?
Yes. He cornered the first
edition book market
for those specific books
to spite a rival.
And did she say...
which books?
Second World War by Churchill.
Motherfucker.
♪ Tense music ♪
This is what they do.
How the fuck do you compete
with something that powerful,
that swims around
for days on end,
just waiting for the
faintest smell of blood
so it can attack
without warning,
and with all the ferocity
and half the conscience
of a goddamn bull shark?
You can't.
Unless you can somehow
anticipate where it will strike
and then match its
strength when it does...
which you can't.
I can see books are a
trigger for you...
Thank you, Sacker.
♪ Pulsating music ♪
Dad, I'm messengering
something to you,
and I will be over to
discuss it in a while.
- Good.
Son, credit where it's due.
This Ice Juice thing is a win.
I've already spoken to Ira.
He... ran me through a
few more of the numbers.
Yeah, well, I knew if Ira
said it, it would be so.
Yeah, he told me you almost
didn't bring it to me
out of some worry about...
conflict?
That would've been shortsighted.
I agree, and I am most certainly
taking the longer
view at the moment.
Good boy.
We can't let this
opportunity slide by.
This IPO could be the start
of a billion dollar windfall, and
it's a life-changer for him.
You keep saying "we."
I'm not liquid enough
to pull the trigger.
I find that hard to fathom.
My cash on hand happens to be
tied up in an few real
estate deals right now,
and it's not the
right time to sell.
Huh. Let me guess.
Kingsford?
I think it's best we
not discuss that.
With your position, that
would be unethical.
But there is a solution.
The chunk of cash I need
is on a statement
with your name on it.
- The blind trust.
- But, uh, why tell me about it?
Uh, isn't the whole point
to a blind trust that
I'm not supposed to know what
you're doing with the money?
No, not this time.
That trust was set aside
for you and the children.
But even the safest IPO
has a different risk profile
than a normal investment.
You have to know before I do it.
You want me to break
my public vow?
The moment that
I'm transitioning
into elected office?
It's only damaging
if it gets out.
I'll invest silently.
Your role will be hidden.
We'll replace the funds as soon
as we sell some of the stock.
No one's the wiser.
Hmm.
Well, if this is
what it takes...
uh, to help you and Ira...
- Does that mean...
- Yeah.
Crack it open.
- Use a bit for your venture.
I trust your judgment.
As always.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
♪ Jazzy rock music ♪
Excuse me. Wendy.
- Lara.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
You know, we never really had
you over to the house enough.
Thanks for the invite.
And I appreciate the
personal follow-up.
Chuck was, um...
quite surprised
to hear from you.
Well, I'm glad you came.
Bobby will really
value you being here.
Hmm. I couldn't tell when
I spoke to him at work.
Oh. I thought you weren't
really talking at work.
I'm sure it must be hard for
you to not have access to him,
but we think it's
best for everyone.
Clear boundaries this time.
Right...
which is why I set the policy.
It was the only way
I could work there.
I couldn't keep seeing him.
It wasn't like doctor-patient
or even athlete-coach.
It was more Hannibal-Clarice.
♪ Tense music ♪
Not seeing him was one of your
conditions for coming back.
I thought it was important
for both of us, really.
Thanks again for the invite.
I could use a drink.
Where are you?
I'm at the front gate.
Come meet me.
Let's get outta here. Fuck this.
It's a mistake.
I see how we made it...
because we forgot.
I forgot... where I'm from.
I forgot that I don't give
a fuck about any of this.
It's all sailcloth
held up with poles
lit by lighting designers and
ripped to the ground tomorrow.
I wanna be with you.
I wanna take you
somewhere that matters.
Everyone's waiting for you.
Wags is about to
give his speech.
I've had quite a
challenge this week
to put together words,
ordinary words,
to describe the most
extraordinary man I ever met.
A man as steely as
a Roman centurion,
cooler than Jean-Paul Belmondo.
He's a jaguar shark,
an American Sniper,
every decision in the
space of seven breaths.
If you cross him,
he'll put a fucking
ding in your universe.
But these are all
exaggerations, derivative.
They don't limn the truth
of an indefinable essence.
They don't speak to
my real feelings.
It's no exaggeration to say
that Bobby Axelrod is the
man who gave me my life,
or at least let me keep it.
But even more than that,
he's given me friendship...
the kind of friendship,
it's more than money,
it's more than talent, it's...
almost family.
But unlike family,
he never turns away.
He's the only one who truly
sees me and doesn't judge.
He accepts me as I am,
and that kind of
friendship is...
everything.
It is the stuff of life itself.
So thank you...
for my life.
Traders trade.
Lovers love.
Cars are meant to go.
Happy birthday, Axe,
wherever you are.
Way to go, Wags!
Axe didn't show up?
Who does that, skips
his own party?
That's fucking fantastic.
Maybe he's an introvert, too.
No, he's not an introvert.
He just remembered
he's an outlaw.
A fucking desperado.
Hey. Axe said to
give this to you.
♪ Bob Dylan's "Visions
of Johanna" ♪
♪ Ain't it just like the night ♪
♪ To play tricks when you're
tryin' to be so quiet? ♪
♪ We sit here stranded ♪
♪ Though we're all doing
our best to deny it ♪
♪ And Louise holds a
handful of rain ♪
♪ Temptin' you to defy it ♪
♪ Lights flicker from
the opposite loft ♪
♪ In this room, the
heat pipes just cough ♪
♪ The country music
station plays soft ♪
♪ But there's nothing,
really nothing to turn off ♪
♪ Just Louise ♪
♪ And her lover ♪
♪ So entwined ♪
♪ And these visions ♪
♪ Of Johanna ♪
♪ That conquer my mind ♪
♪ In the empty lot where
the ladies play ♪
♪ Blind man's bluff
with the key chain ♪
♪ And the all-night girls ♪
♪ They whisper of escapades
out on the "D" train ♪