Previously on "Billions"...
Get everything you might
possibly need,
'cause they will destroy
anything left behind.
You blew up your family
for Bobby Axelrod.
I'm Keyser Soze, motherfucker.
Judge on the Dollar Bill case
is going to be
Whit fucking Wilcox.
- Ugh.
- I wonder
if re-presented a warrant
for bugging the Axelrod home.
- No. Asked and answered.
Look into Wilcox.
Go wherever it leads.
You're making a move
on a federal judge.
Is he in your way?
If you were in my situation,
what would you do?
You know, if you hadn't
done anything wrong,
but you were targeted anyway.
You want me to pressure
my husband to back off.
You know I can't do that.
- Why not?
- So I'm thrilled
you got someone
on the inside at Axe Cap.
I have no idea,
because as you damn well know,
I've recused myself.
- FBI!
- There's someone in the house.
- It'll be fine.
Sorry about your front door.
It's all right.
He can afford another one.
- Go.
Donnie Caan walked out.
He say anything about
where he was going?
I think it'd be good
if you found him, soon.
Where... the fuck... is Donnie?
He could decide to walk
into their office
and tell 'em everything.
I'll testify against Axe,
but right now I need...
- Ugh!
- Holy shit. Donnie? No.
Donnie.
- Oh, fuck.
- Donnie.
♪ Theme music ♪
♪ pensive music ♪
You know, I was, for a time,
supposed to become
a Grandmaster.
Supposed to become
Chess.
14 years old,
and leapfrogging up
the standings.
Put me in a practice game,
and I'd be a young Boris Spassky
in his prime.
By all rights,
I should've dominated
live competition,
but I had a flaw.
If I decided that my opponent
didn't... respect the game,
or me, or if I didn't like
the way he carried himself...
If I decided for whatever reason
that he wasn't worthy,
a dark rage would come over me.
And this rage became the driver.
All the strategy, patience,
and practice would vanish,
and I would begin obsessing
about total destruction.
Some kid could fail
to look me in the eye
while shaking my hand
at a tournament in the fall,
and I would carry it until
facing him again in the spring.
But then, while I was trying
to destroy him...
I'd forget to win.
I would play bold moves
designed to intimidate,
show him that he wasn't
as smart as me... or as brave.
Leave voids in my defense.
That's not how you win at chess.
I knew better,
but, uh...
but I couldn't do better.
And then,
at the end of the game,
my opponent's arm
would be raised in victory
while I sat,
humiliated and alone,
bathed in anger and defeat.
Here I am again, beaten.
Although it has yet
to be confirmed,
there is no doubt
that Donnie Caan is gonna die.
Soon.
I sat up all night
until I saw it.
Bobby Axelrod used Donnie
to feed us information
that he would never live
to testify to
or confirm in court.
We'll claw back
some of his trades, sure,
but we have to assume
that the names he gave us,
the specifics, all of it...
False.
♪ Pulsating music ♪
No, I wish this loss
were mine alone,
but I cost all of you as well.
Soon, probably within the hour,
uh, Adam DeGiulio from
the Attorney General's office
will walk in here
and take us off
the Axelrod case.
It won't matter that Axelrod
is everything I said he is...
A bloodless man.
A man who would use
his dying friend
in the manner that he did.
We needed to be bloodless
to catch him,
and we weren't.
I wasn't.
♪ Pulsating music quickens ♪
We were all suckers here, Chuck.
No, don't try to fall on it,
Bryan.
I set the tone.
That's what the papers will say.
- They'll call me sloppy.
- Driven, unhinged.
And, uh, for once,
they'll be correct.
What can we do?
We can,
from this moment forward,
remember how the game
is supposed to be played.
We'll play perfect strategy.
We will retreat so we can attack
when it is to our advantage.
And then someday soon,
we will be standing here,
and it will be our turn.
♪ Music fades ♪
♪ music fades ♪
I don't wanna stop you, Chuck.
No, we were just finishing up.
♪ Pensive music ♪
All right,
get out there
and make some fucking money.
You got a handle on this?
I do not.
Well, I don't think it's good.
- How fucked are you?
- Can I say it's nothing?
Could you let me
get away with that?
Flu, maybe?
God, what would you pay to have
the flu right now, Donnie?
Anything.
- Cancer.
- Yeah.
- Shit.
- Pancreatic.
Shit.
How far along?
With this kind, it doesn't
really matter.
- Far enough.
♪ But I get up again ♪
- Can we have the room?
- Sorry?
Piss elsewhere.
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
You should've come to me
right away.
I've been, ah, you know,
letting it settle.
Kids know?
Not yet.
We'll access the best,
most creative,
most forward-thinking
medical treatment there is.
You'll see my guy, Ari Gilbert.
Top oncologist out there.
Works with select clients.
World leaders.
I've been funding his research
for years.
Thank you for offering,
but you don't have to do that.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
It's what we do.
♪ Dramatic music ♪
Get yourself together.
Come and see me
at the end of the day.
I have a thought.
Donnie's gone.
I, uh, I have to make
some phone calls.
I'll help you.
♪ I tried my hardest
not to be ♪
♪ I locked the door,
and I broke the key ♪
♪ Why can't I sleep
through the night? ♪
♪ Daddy, do you think
I've turned out... ♪
How are you set financially?
Are Walter and the kids
gonna have enough?
Nobody's gonna starve,
but I could've done better.
When I met Walter,
finally accepted who I am,
I felt so guilty about Karen.
I remember.
It was tough on both of you.
Yeah, so I kind of just
gave her everything.
Didn't shelter it
or put it in a trust.
Just sort of heaved it
over to her.
Practically started
back at zero.
That's all chutes and ladders,
isn't it?
- It sure is.
The guy she remarried...
He's got control
of the money now,
and I can't be sure
what he's gonna do with it.
Emma and Harry are exposed?
Yeah.
What were you hoping to get to?
I-I don't have a number.
I just want them
to be taken care of.
Good education,
their first house, no debt.
Sure. Also, you want them
to be able to do what they want,
- not what they have to.
- Yeah.
Thought I was going to take care
of that in the next 10 years.
Forty million.
What if we could
get you there, pre-tax?
- For all the family?
- Big ladder.
But there's a way
to make it happen.
To guarantee it.
Rewards of paradise
here on earth?
Really sharp evangelists
could con me
out of my house right now.
Unlike him, I'm gonna
give you the downside.
It won't be simple.
It'll require deception.
And your final weeks and months,
they won't be your own.
Are we talking about
breaking the law?
Because I-I can't spend
one minute in jail.
Well, let's leave that
to the lawyers.
♪ Tense music ♪
- Let me save you some breath.
Now the Attorney General thinks
it best that my office
drop its pursuit of Axe Capital.
And you tried to argue with her,
but she was insistent.
Kids would hashtag that
"one hundred."
Any matter related to
Axe Capital
is to be handled by
the Eastern District
from here forward.
You know, the only thing
I can't figure
is if the AG's fear
of negative publicity
is because she's planning
a Senate run
or a return
to the private sector.
Put on a blindfold,
spin yourself around,
and pin the tail on the donkey.
- You know?
- I do.
Defy her in any way,
she will recommend
that the President fire you.
And he will not hesitate
to take a recommendation.
I know.
And I would do the same thing
were I sitting in her office.
I accept it.
I am off Axelrod.
Good man.
But, you know, that is not
what you and I really need
to talk about today.
It's not?
Let's go out and take some air,
and I'll tell you why
musical chairs
is a much better party game.
- Oh. Walter.
- Hey, Wendy.
Friends.
Friends, may I ask that you all
please take your seats now?
Fuck.
Come on. I'll sit with you.
What are you doing here?
Came to pay my respects.
Not appropriate.
I knew the man.
Better than you let on,
I'm sure.
Turn and leave.
Why would I?
Get the fuck out of here.
All right.
It's a real loss.
Yeah. For both of us.
Those ungrateful fuckers
have to make me
focus on this now?
They hope you are
too distracted and sad
to focus on it at all.
Oh. I can still focus. Talk.
So lonosphere Fund...
They set up shop downtown.
Carly's in charge?
Or Channing.
Definitely not Hlasa.
How much?
Two-hundred million under
management, 40 of it's theirs.
Where's it coming from?
They stole this list.
Some of these people are ours.
Can we block that?
We absolutely could.
All three of them signed
non-competes.
But they can fight it,
claim that
Axe Capital was no longer
the place they signed on to,
that their deals should be void.
They can't win, right?
Not likely. But with the current
sentiment, who knows?
And I don't think you want that
kind of attention right now.
No, but we can't have
the perception
that the real talent
at Axe Capital
is flying under a new flag.
Where you going?
- Breakfast.
I'm not putting
our friendship on the line.
I'm just asking.
- I'm just trying to warn
you that this lonosphere venture
is doomed.
You trained these guys, right?
I taught 'em all they know,
not all I know.
But you extend them
credit, it's on you.
It is.
I already have.
I'm first money in,
I got very favorable terms,
and I don't see a reason
to give that up.
Do this for me, and I'll cut
your fees to one and ten
over the next three quarters.
I can't.
Check, sir.
It is the love
God has instilled in us
that has been our refuge,
that has sustained us
for generations.
Before the mountains were
brought forth,
or the earth was born,
- there was love.
And it is love that turns us
back to dust,
saying, "Go back,
oh, child of earth."
It is love that sweeps us away
like a dream.
Your honor, our argument is
simple and straightforward.
My client provided
emergency medical care
to Christina Grunwald.
Mr. Stearn met
the young lady's father,
learned of her desperate
medical condition,
had the resources at
his disposal to save her life,
and was moved to action.
I ask, uh, you to
look at this photograph
and tell me that,
if you were in a position
to save this child's life...
♪ serious music ♪
wouldn't you do it
just because you could?
Mr. Stearn had no idea
that medical treatment
had any link
to alleged inside information.
I ask you to consider the wisdom
of putting altruism itself
on trial.
May I?
- Mr. Connerty.
The people are
fully prepared to prove
benefit was provided
in the form of medical expenses
to the tune
of some 211,000 dollars.
And that, as a direct response
to insider information
provided to Mr. Stearn.
Further, we can demonstrate
that Axe Capital
used this information
to gain
an 89 million dollar profit.
An 89 million dollar return.
On a 211,000 dollar...
- investment.
- Investment.
Altruism is not on trial here,
but the fairness of
the financial markets is.
The US Attorney's office has
made a considered decision
to pursue and prosecute
precisely this new brand
of criminal.
They are bastardizing
the fair market
upon which this country
is built.
Passionately executed,
Mr. Connerty,
but the humane gesture of
providing medical treatment
for an afflicted child
as material benefit,
begs that a jury learn
the unknowable...
That is, what lay
in Mr. Stearn's heart.
I deem it best
that the court grants
defense counsel's motion
for dismissal.
Your honor,
I vigorously protest.
Nonetheless, my decision stands.
And I further advise that
you and the Southern District
reconsider the deployment
of government assets
in the settling
of personal scores.
This session is adjourned.
He said "personal scores"?
He used those words?
- Direct quote.
Motherfucker.
How goddamn comfortable
in your seat do you have to be
to do that?
To do that?
Should we start clearing
the Axelrod files or...
Tomorrow.
What you need to do now
is take the day, at least.
- Come back ready to go.
- I can hang in here...
Go!
Breathe in some fall air.
I'd like to imagine someone
is doing that today.
Might as well be you.
I bet Dollar Bill
is doing exactly that
with a giant fucking smile
on his face.
What are you gonna do?
Well, we've lost the Axe case.
Wilcox cut
the Dollar Bill thread.
We need to get circular
with our thinking.
Turn the impediments
into our own blockers.
Don't worry.
I know what I'm talking about.
He wanted to see me?
He did, but not right now.
This about those
Ionosphere traitors?
Quislings?
Don't answer that.
So, Deb...
Don't.
I make stupid money,
and I'm ready
for a relationship.
I make plenty,
and I'm out of your league.
You're right.
Guys around here avoid you like
you're a dangerous fighter,
because you're
a triple threat...
Power, speed, and footwork.
So give me some credit
for stepping up.
Credit for the honesty.
If you have dinner with me,
I'll buy you a Mini Cooper.
Oh, see?
See? You smiled.
And you know and I know
that a smile
is a gateway to
multiple convulsive orgasms.
I smiled because I'm too long
for a Mini,
and you almost look cute
when you're nervous.
Hey, Mafee, get in here.
Go on in.
Keyser, Keyser, Keyser, Keyser,
Keyser, Keyser,
Keyser, Keyser...
- Thank you.
- Keyser, Keyser, Keyser...
- Thank you!
- Keyser, Keyser...
- Thank you, my children.
Bill Stearn!
I'm back, baby!
Get your ass in my office
right now.
Close the fucking door!
Um, you wanna tell me
what I did here?
Pretend we're having
an argument.
You wanna fucking tell me why?
I want the Street to think
that you and I are on the outs!
I especially want those fuckers
who left to hear about it!
♪ Quite contrary,
how'd you get your... ♪
I wanna give Channing, Carly,
and Hlasa a good fucking!
I heard they went out on their
own! You didn't bless that?
- I did not bless that at all.
- That's a shame!
They were talented,
and I kind of liked them!
Oh, so you don't wanna
help me out?
Fuck that! They fuck you, they
fuck me, so let's fuck them!
What do you want me to do?!
I'm gonna poke you.
Poke me back.
I'll poke you all goddamn day.
You throw in with them,
you tell them I was a prick,
but you stuck your neck out...
More to come.
- Got it!
You've been through a lot.
You all right?
It was hell, but I survived!
When you walk out that door,
I want you to tell me
to go fuck myself,
good and loud!
They're gonna hear me
in the back office!
Come bonus time, I am gonna
show you enough love,
you could start a third family!
Two's fucking plenty!
- I'm gonna shove you now!
- Go ahead!
♪ Oh ♪
I love you like a brother.
♪ All torn down ♪
I fucking love you, too, man.
♪ Down ♪
Go fuck yourself, Axelrod!
And now let us take a moment
to appreciate
the beauty of nature,
which Donnie loved so well.
- Amen.
And now,
according to Donnie's wishes,
we drink and have a good time.
We drink and have a good time.
Walter.
Donnie said,
and I'm quoting here,
"Have them all bury my picture
in autumn leaves,
and as they do,
they should make a wish
for the world...
That has nothing to do
with the financial markets."
♪ acoustic guitar
playing tenderly ♪
The paint was about
eight layers thick and hard,
but I scratched it.
And beneath the layers?
Wilcox.
Greasy muck on his shoes.
Talk to me.
Well, I looked at
his sentencing history,
and about seven years ago,
there's a significant
pattern shift.
Suddenly, he becomes
the toughest hanging judge
on the federal bench,
but not on white collar crime.
- Oh, no?
- No, not on white of any kind.
He lets the white guys skate
if he thinks you have access
to lawyers or press
or other noisemakers.
But poor Black and Latino
boys from the hood
get slapped
with all kinds of time.
Uh-huh. Now is that racism,
or is there money somewhere?
Well, I did a deep dive
on his financial history,
and seven years ago,
he joined an investment group.
One of their holdings...
Baldinger Prison Systems,
a privatized
for-profit prison company.
They charge inmates a dollar
a minute to use the phone...
And then soak the government
with a 300% markup.
They net 17,000 dollars a year
per prisoner.
Wilcox is building his business
from the bench.
Exactly.
And he's doing it
to poor kids...
with public defenders
who are far less likely
to file an appeal
and far less able to win one.
Jesus Christ.
Where is the money going?
It bounces into the Caymans,
but it winds up in Dominican,
where he has a condo.
This is great work.
And he's fucking
his Dominican housekeeper.
- I'm gonna get you back
from Eastern and make you happy.
- I'd like to be happy.
Fuck. Really?
Pretty grown-up, huh?
If I live to a hundred,
I wouldn't be this grown-up.
You want anything?
I'm fine. Thanks.
This isn't from Ikea, is it?
No.
But it works the same way.
♪ Tense music ♪
♪ Men were made to talk ♪
♪ Babies born to cry ♪
♪ Tears will make 'em tall ♪
♪ The fear of God
gets in their eyes ♪
♪ Sticks and stones ♪
♪ May break my bones ♪
♪ But words will make... ♪
Dad. What are
you doing here?
I was going through some things,
and I came across this.
It's your Indian Head penny
collection.
Thought you might
get a kick out of it.
You came all the way out
to Brooklyn to give me
my penny collection?
No, I'm meeting Perry
and Richie at Luger's later.
I thought, as long as
I'm over here...
Oh, fuck it.
This isn't the year that
I start choosing my words
to avoid offense.
- Just when I got my hopes up.
Okay, you want delicate?
How about this?
Perhaps it's time to be
more careful
about how you process and react.
- It's a critical time.
And here's
the less delicate way...
Stop... fucking... up!
Insightful.
This must be how Ali felt
when Angelo Dundee
whispered in his ear.
Do you know what the press
is saying about you?
Didn't bother checking.
I have a general idea.
Well, they are clubbing you
like a baby seal.
It's time that you got out
in front of this.
You are a target
for the Attorney General now.
Maybe it's time
you got out of there...
before you get fired.
And do what? Hmm?
Go over to Horvath?
Maybe I get
on my hands and knees
and crawl up to Westport,
drum up some business
defending Bobby Axelrod
or his friends. Huh?
I didn't show up here
with just my rod in my hand.
No. You brought coins.
And I have an idea.
Go ahead.
Take a year off.
Move the family up to the farm.
Mount Kisco?
It's beautiful.
Wendy can open a practice.
God knows there are plenty
of bored housewives
that could use her help.
And you write a book.
In no time,
you will have established
residency.
Ahh.
Patrick Esposito's
congressional seat.
Oh.
- Patrick is tired.
I talked to him.
He'll step aside.
You'll be a shoo-in.
Congress.
Boy, that sounds like fun...
535 stooges and blowhards,
some of whom even believe
in science.
Well, you'll stand out.
You know, if you had listened
to me in the first place
and hadn't blown up
the deal with Axelrod,
we would not be in this spot,
would we?
"We"?
We?
No. You don't get
to do that.
Not anymore.
Let me be delicate now.
The game has changed, and you
haven't changed with it.
Your advice
is no longer welcome.
So the next time
you wanna waltz in here
with your "I told you so"
routine,
do us both a favor
and stay the fuck out.
Four million dollar rip on DKA,
up 2% in our first week.
There are tips,
and there are tips.
You plan on
telling us where you got it?
You'll hear the next one
yourself.
He's here.
Dollar Bill,
Mr. Hundred Cent.
Billy Buck Buck, motherfucker!
I should've known.
Everyone's been talking about
your brawl with Axe.
Fucking prick.
I keep my mouth shut,
risk doing time for him,
and then he treats me like that.
Look at this.
Little shop that could.
And from the acorn
grew the mighty oak.
No doubt,
all-star team like this.
Could always use one more.
Champagne?
I'll take
one of those Heinekens.
- What do you say?
We can talk after
the first of the year.
I am contractually owed a bonus.
Meantime, want some more candy?
Yeah.
You know how Penn Consol's been
rising on takeover rumors?
I've been watching that.
Behind the scenes?
There's a bidding war.
It is fucking on.
Sure?
I am not uncertain.
- Come on in, Chuck. Sit down.
I can deliver this on my feet.
Know that
if this "urgent meeting"
is to slam me for my ruling
on the William Stearn case,
you should proceed to
the other side of that door
and tell it to the doorknob.
Whit, that's a closed case.
Forget "Dollar" Bill Stearn.
No, this is about
Daquan Forrester.
You remember Daquan, the first
offender kid dealing pot
he bought in New Jersey
his senior year of high school
that you slapped with 15 years?
What about him?
It's about Julio Lopez.
Remember him, too?
11 years for credit card fraud
because he bought a PlayStation?
Because he bought a PlayStation?
♪ Tense music ♪
This won't do anyone any good.
Some of those are your cases,
your office.
How did I miss it for so long?
You know,
all those middle class types
walking out
of your courtroom free.
All those Black and Latino kids
going upstate for 20 years.
I am no racist.
Oh, no.
That's selling you short.
You're worse...
A racist and a profiteer.
You want proof? Wait for it.
Baldinger Prison Systems.
There's no way
to reopen those cases.
I can draw a straight line
to you and your partners,
your offshore bank account,
and even your little
girlfriend, Maribel Solarte,
at your condo in Punta Cana.
Theories and accusations.
After I've spent a lifetime
on the bench,
until I got splinters
in my ass and all for...
a civil servant's wages.
We both know they're not
just accusations, Your Honor.
What do you want?
You will resign immediately
for undisclosed
personal reasons.
And there will be a little party
and tearful goodbyes,
and you will stride off
into private practice.
Or the FBI could come in here
and give you
a far different reception.
You... won't prosecute?
No. You do it that way,
and the Southern District
declines to prosecute.
Because if we did, you would dig
those badger teeth and claws
of yours in and fight.
It would take two years,
and you would go to jail,
but the Southern District
believes
that your swift departure would
be best for the justice system.
Oh...
And shame on you.
Hi.
How you holding up?
Funeral arrangements
were a welcome distraction.
I brought a casserole,
just like it was the '50s.
This Secret Santa project
looks overwhelming.
- Do you need a hand?
Help is literally on the way.
Lara's taking over
the whole operation.
Oh. So good of her.
She's been great.
Both of them, really great.
You're in
a... complicated position.
Yeah.
It was... hard on Donnie,
not being able to tell you.
- What do you mean?
I just mean his privacy,
you know.
It meant a lot to him.
Did other people know?
Hey.
I've got a big truck outside.
- Oh, do you need me to move?
- If you wouldn't mind.
It's so good of you to take over
the Secret Santa thing.
Yeah. We were pretty close.
And closer in troubled times.
That's the true test
of friendship.
Yes, it is.
What are you doing here?
I'm saying hi to Walter,
seeing if he needed anything.
He's taken care of.
I see. Well, I figure,
at a time like this,
the more the merrier.
At a time like this,
a family pulls together.
That's what Axe Capital is...
A family.
One I'm part of, too.
Of course you are.
We're fine.
Thanks for the casserole.
♪ I tried my hardest
not to be ♪
♪ I locked the door,
and I broke the key ♪
♪ Why can't I sleep
through the night? ♪
Want company?
No. I'd be no good.
All right.
You okay?
Sure.
You and Donnie were close,
especially
these last few months.
♪ I just wanna make... ♪
How long you figure it's been
since we've had a session?
- We talk all the time.
- No, a real session.
♪ It's a sign,
it's how I've always been ♪
♪ Did you love me... ♪
Three and a half years.
♪ He was just my friend ♪
Will you come see me?
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Papa, you're the one
that taught me ♪
♪ By his strap, he sought me ♪
♪ And with his blood,
he bought me ♪
- ♪ Daddy ♪
♪ You're the one
that claimed that ♪
♪ He'd love me
through the flame ♪
♪ Now why can't you
do the same? ♪
- ♪ I've been born again ♪
♪ First was born in sin ♪
- ♪ Did you love me then? ♪
♪ Did you love me then? ♪
Hey.
Christmas coming
a little early this year?
This is Donnie's
Secret Santa project.
I took it on.
- We're elves.
- Slave elves.
Gordie.
Pretty big job here, boys.
You want some help?
What are you doing?
I'll get a half a dozen interns
from the office.
They'll knock this off in
no time. They're Ivy Leaguers.
- Yes.
- Conference.
You two keep wrapping.
Remember, there are
more presents in the other room.
This is one of those
teachable moments
that we talked about.
The idea is that we do something
with our own hands
to benefit the less fortunate,
as a family.
Is this a teachable moment
for me or for the kids?
All right, I'll wrap.
And, Bobby...
I ran into Wendy
at Walter's today.
And?
She was probing Walter
for information.
Is that right?
It made be wonder about
her continuing value.
We're vulnerable,
and so are they.
I trust her.
- Mmm.
Thank you.
- Your Honor.
- Counselor.
- Mmm.
- You didn't have to come.
Oh, of course I did.
Wouldn't be seemly otherwise.
Boy, you know what I love
about this cake?
- What?
- Sour cream.
It's just like my grandmother
used to make.
Gives it a little... tang.
- Yes, it does.
- Yeah.
You like a little tang
every so often, don't you, Whit?
- Sure, Chuck.
- Yeah.
It's a really nice crowd.
I think I'll say a few words.
No, that won't be necessary.
I love to speak.
- Uh...
- Ladies and gentlemen?
Ladies and gentlemen, may I have
your attention for a moment?
Thank you.
Hmm.
Justice.
Rooted in truth,
watered by tenacity,
and flowering in wisdom.
May be the single most beautiful
expression of humanity.
For a man to dedicate his life
in its pursuit
rings of a certain nobility.
Rings of a certain nobility.
And this day we gather
to acknowledge that nobility
in the Honorable Whit Wilcox.
Devoted servant of justice
and one of its most
industrious sentinels.
- Congratulations, Judge Wilcox.
And thank you
for your noble service.
- Mm.
- ♪ For... ♪
♪ He's a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ For he's
a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ Which nobody can... ♪
Hello, Judge.
You're going to jail.
You may even own it.
You're a fucking liar.
I said the Southern District
wouldn't prosecute.
I can't speak for Eastern.
- You'll be coming with us.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you
in a court of law.
Twenty-eight percent
of our goddamn fund
by the time we dug ourselves
- out of the position.
Was there ever even a real
takeover being considered?
Who cares? It's over.
How are we gonna explain
this to our investors?
Nice space.
Edgy.
Mind if I take a seat?
Going forward,
you might want to consider
vetting your information
a little better.
Lesson learned.
I could take pleasure
in watching you three
circle the drain,
but I am a practical man.
And there was a reason that
I hired and trained all of you
in the first place.
So... here's what
I'm prepared to do.
I will seed lonosphere...
Stupid fucking name,
by the way...
With 250 million dollars.
That should keep the lights on.
You'll be required to sign
non-compete
and non-solicitation agreements.
We will enter into
a revenue share agreement.
The current rate for seed money
is 20 to 25%,
- so why don't we call it 40?
- 40?
Swallow that and wash it down
with this.
You will provide
total transparency.
I want your trade files
sent to my office every night.
There will be a limit
on how much outside capital
you can raise.
At no time can you manage
more than 999 million dollars.
There will be no buy-out
to eliminate
the revenue share agreement
and no lock-up on my money.
I can pull the plug at any time.
That's the deal.
No negotiation.
I'm counting to five,
and then it's off the table.
- One...
- We'll do it.
♪ Pensive music ♪
Wise.
And I'd better see you
at the funeral.
I, uh, I don't go to funerals.
I can't bring myself to.
I-I skip 'em.
I send mountains of flowers
and food to the wake,
convince myself
that's the right thing to do.
Convince myself
If I were asked why, I'd say,
"Well, we wanna remember him
how he was,"
or some other bullshit.
Truth?
I like to keep moving so I don't
have to think about it.
More truth?
I'm not the type to grapple
with it all.
But...
There was no way that
I was gonna skip this one.
Because Donnie...
grappled with all of it.
He was courage.
And... hope.
And his intelligence
and his kindness
made me wanna be
all those things, too.
As it did all of you.
I am so angry that he's gone.
So glad that while he was here,
I was one of the lucky few
who knew him.
I admired Donnie Caan.
And I am proud to have
called him a friend.
Let's do this. Donnie.
To Donnie.
Why you working from home today?
I went to a funeral
and got kicked out...
by my wife.
I needed the quiet.
The Judge Wilcox arrest...
Mm-hmm?
- Slick move.
- Mm.
That wasn't it. It was
just the opener, right?
You got rid of an impediment,
but that's not enough.
You're putting in
your own blocker.
You wanna put someone
in that seat...
Someone who'll owe you,
not someone who's compromised.
Just a more... willing ear.
The person
needs to be qualified.
He or she needs to check out
gold stars across the board.
It's a Senate appointment,
the Judiciary committee,
so it won't be immediate,
but it won't be long either.
Yeah, you're almost there.
Hmm.
Adam DeGiulio?
And then he's out of your way
at the AG's office, too.
And maybe he leaves a friendly
behind in his place.
Wow.
Don't get too excited
by how good it sounds.
Everything's gotta fall
just right.
And the odds
of that happening...
Still, you're playing
the game again. Clear-eyed.
Oh, that I am.
Drink?
No. I'll... I'll keep mine
clear, too.
You all right?
Sad.
Yeah. Good guy.
One of the few people at work
who were remotely interesting.
Tell me about it.
And... he was our gay guy.
That make a difference?
Yeah.
These days,
it's great to have a gay.
You are a complete
goddamn animal.
I ruined his life.
Say again?
Donnie.
I was able to patch him up,
keep him in a game
that made him miserable.
If I just...
let him fail, get fired,
he would've been better off.
Let him fail, get fired,
He could've made the life
he wanted.
That's kind of a stretch, Wendy.
Oh, he would've been
so much happier
if he'd returned to academia.
Give me a break.
College professors are broke
as fuck and bitter, too.
They certainly don't leave
40 mil to their families
when they knock off.
Now, what...
is really going on,
Dr. Rhoades?
Is it a little case
of projection?
Donnie walked with 40?
Hyperbole.
Just making my point.
Right.
Worst part of my job,
I'll tell you that.
- Ari.
- Hey, Bobby.
Thank you, Dr. Gilbert,
for the excellent care,
for trying so hard.
Walter, we're gonna take off.
A messenger's
gonna stop by tomorrow.
You'll have all the info.
Any problems,
you have the number, right?
Yes.
Thank you.
I should be thanking you.
I took him away from you.
He should've been
with his family, with you.
No. You pulled him
out of a dark well,
made him himself again.
Got him reaching for
that final piece of life
instead of watching it go.
Oh, honey.
It was a good send-off.
It was very Donnie.
So nothing to worry about
on the Secret Santa front.
I really couldn't have that
around the house.
Donnie loved doing it so much.
He kept saying, "I just
wanna make it to Christmas
so I can be Santa
one more time."
He'd see them get the gifts
and beam straight through
New Year's.
He just didn't make it.
Okay. I'll meet you
in the waiting room.
Okay.
Ari? How is he?
It's not contained,
and it's spreading quickly.
I'm not into the calendar game,
but... two, three months.
That's a shame.
He is a candidate for
a drug trial in Pittsburgh
that's been yielding some
pretty interesting results.
Such as?
Slowing growth down,
buying time, really.
How much?
Three or four months more, six.
I can get him in,
but it is
a pretty rigorous course.
So... kind of rough
for a guy who's been through
a lot already.
It can be.
Maybe we shouldn't bring it up.
You think? I...
Well, I mean,
what kind of quality of life
will he have?
Best not to bring it up then.
- Yeah.
♪ Tense music ♪
♪ tense music ♪
♪ Oh, Danny Boy ♪
♪ Danny Boy, Danny Boy ♪
♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down
but I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
♪ I get knocked down,
but I get up again ♪
♪ You're never gonna
keep me down ♪
Mm.