Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
After we dump this in storage,
let's hit the bar
and see if we can get a cute
lieutenant to argue with me.
And see if we can get a cute
Interesting.
Why would you want that?
I don't know. Getting
some uptight hunk all wound up
- just gets me all...
- Supplicate yourselves!
- Just gets me all...
- Ah! What the heck?
- Whoa. It's one of
those transdimensional
energy creatures.
Behold and tremble at...
Quick, Tendi,
grab me one of those canisters.
Wait, shouldn't
we call security?
- I will destroy you.
- No, no.
We can use this thing
for all sorts of cool stuff.
Hey, grab the pod.
We can figure it out later.
He's a sentient creature.
Are-are we even allowed
to stuff him in something?
He's a bad guy. He zaps people.
I shall make a feast
of your misery!
- No, wait! Don't put me
in the pod!
I-I can grant you wishes.
And I'm listening.
I can rearrange air molecules
into whatever you want.
Even one of those
fancy new tricorders
- with the purple stripe?
- Ooh, those are nice.
Oh, that would use up
a lot of my...
Okay, okay.
Just... I'll try.
There.
That's... There you go.
- Where's the power cell, dude?
- What, really?
Like I was going
to ask for something
that didn't come with batteries.
Okay, okay.
Thank you.
I really got to think
of something cool
- to say when we're
going to warp.
- Die, mortal!
- to say when we're
going to warp.
- Die, mortal!
Something like "It's warp time!"
What do you think of that?
Is that good for you?
Hmm.
What you watching?
Oh, it's this video
of Vice Admiral Gibson
falling off a stage
during peace negotiations.
You got to check it out.
- Ah, it's classic.
- Guess which command ensign
just scored the best assignment
on the ship.
- Uh, Castro?
- No, not Castro.
Too bad.
- She's the best.
- Castro's overrated.
Just because she served
on the Enterprise
- for, like, one minute...
- Ooh, was it P'jok?
- For, like, one minute...
That guy can do anything,
and what a snack.
No! It's me. I got it.
I'm the guy that got it, okay?
I'm gonna be piloting General
K'orin down to Tulgana 4.
K'orin. How do I know that name?
Maybe because he's like
one of the most decorated,
battle-hardened Klingon warriors
in history?
Or maybe it's just 'cause all
Klingon names sound the same?
Like, they all have
an apostrophe for some reason.
Yes. That's it.
Well, clearly I'm being rewarded
for all the hours I log
into the simulator.
For all the hours I log
Your idea of a reward is
an escort run?
Oh, you have the bar set
way too low.
What's punishment?
Something actually fun?
What is wrong with you?
Look, all I know is, I'll be
flying down to a bustling,
exotic planet while you're stuck
right here.
Exotic planet while you're stuck
Uh, check yourself.
It doesn't get more exotic
than this.
All right, nobody talk to me.
I got to brush up on my formal
Klingon greetings, okay?
Nuqneh, nuqneh!
Yeah, keep it subtle. Nuqneh.
Well, if you see an unaligned
EPS conduit, don't call me.
Mine are aligned as hell.
Wait, aren't there, like,
a hundred of those?
How long have you been in there?
A solid week.
Crawling through cramped ducts,
prying open panels, and
adjusting red-hot power cables.
Look, look look. I've got
blisters on my blisters.
Oh, wow, you must be so relieved
to be done.
Oh, I'm not done.
Now I get
to recalibrate everything.
That's another three,
four days in the tubes!
Oh, but I thought
we were gonna watch
the Trivoli pulsar together?
Oh, I did promise you
I'd do that.
Well, don't worry.
Some people agree to do stuff
when they don't actually mean
- they're going to do it.
- No, no, no, no.
I'm Starfleet.
I never go back on my word.
Eh... you know,
if I quit my job in Engineering
and switch divisions,
I wouldn't have to be
in the tubes at all.
Really?! Oh, you can do that?
- Sure. When's the pulsar?
- 0800.
Ah! This really means a lot.
I don't have a lot
of friends yet,
and doing science on my own
really bums me out,
so thanks, Rutherford.
All right,
looks like I just have to...
find a new career.
Uh...
Ooh! Pew, pew, pew.
Good work, gents.
Let's keep her right and tight.
Pew, pew, pew.
Uh... At ease, carry on. Sorry.
What? Mariner?
Oh, hey, Boimler. You want some?
What are you doing?
Get out of here.
You're getting broth
on the controls.
- I got to prep for takeoff.
- Oh, I know. I'm coming with.
You got the same mission
assignment as me? How?
Pulled some strings.
I mean, you made this sound
so rewarding,
I just had to see you in action.
Keep reading.
I'm your copilot?
You're taking on more work?
Just to bug me?
Calm down, man. We can't
have you co-flying angry.
I need you co-calm.
Ooh, nice dress uniform.
- You getting married after this?
- No.
- I wish you would take
this seriously.
- I am.
Ooh! This is the new shuttle
with the blast shield. Yeah!
Rutherford,
great work on the EPS grid.
I wish I had
more engineers like you.
My life would be a lot simpler.
Uh, th-thanks.
Uh, can we talk for a second?
Just for a second?
Don't tease me. Come on, man.
You're my number-one-
with-a-bullet systems guy.
I got time for you in spades.
Um...
I just wanted to let you know
that I'm going to be exploring
other opportunities on the ship.
Are you saying what I think
you're saying, Ensign?
Uh, I'd like to request
a transfer out of Engineering.
Consider your request...
granted!
Oh, man, this is exciting.
I'm sure wherever you end up,
they'll be lucky to have you.
- Rutherford! Rutherford!
- Aw, thanks, guys.
- Rutherford!
- I'm gonna miss you.
Buried alive...
-Marooned for eternity...
Moons of Nibia.
-Ugh. Unbelievable.
Oh, sorry. I keep having
this awesome dream.
General K'orin is gonna be here
any second.
Let me do the talking.
I've been studying him all day.
- Is he single?
- Will you just...!
Rein it in.
We need to show him deference
and respect.
General K'orin.
It is an honor
to escort you, sir.
Allow me to say...
Nuqneh.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
- Mariner, what are you doing?!
- What? No!
What are you doing? What...?
No!
Starfleet has made you soft,
Mariner.
Not as soft
as your ngech, K'orin!
Wait, wait, wait. W-W-Wait.
Hold on, hold on.
Do you two know each other?
Yeah. We did some off-the-books
gray ops stuff back in the day.
We're, like, the same age.
Back in what day?
Now they've got you
pushing PADDs
on a ship full of children.
- Well, can't beat four weeks'
shore leave.
Well, general,
as I was saying, Nuq...
Okay. Yeah,
just holding your sword, then.
I must update you on my many
sexual conquests, Mariner.
What, both of them?
Okay, you go down.
There we go.
Where did you even get flagons?
Boy! Land in Little Qo'noS.
I want gagh!
Uh, well, my orders were
actually to deliver you
-to the Federation outpost
so you could...
-Copilot, just set us down
-to the Federation outpost
so you could...
-Copilot, just set us down
in the Klingon district.
The man wants hot worms.
Yes, sir.
Coming right up.
Do you remember Jaxxa Prime,
the commander who didn't believe
you about rectal insectoids?
Ha! Yeah, I got chewed out,
but his ass got chewed up.
Federation shuttlecraft,
this is Tulgana 4
space traffic control.
Landing code challenge epsilo.
Transmitting confirmation
on secure channel gamma sev...
Will you two please be quiet
so we don't get shot out
of the sky? Whoa!
Sending confirmation code now.
Thank you.
Mm, mm.
Mmm, the smell
of a Klingon district.
We'll have to get
the shuttle washed for sure.
If anyone asks,
this was your call.
Okay, snippy.
Ooh, yeah, I'm snippy.
Drinking, landing
in an unsecured district?
That's how you choose
to represent Starfleet?
Me and the general
are blood-bonded.
It would have been weird
if I acted all stuffy.
He's passed out
and he pooped on his sword.
He's a lightweight.
I mean, don't sweat it.
We'll get him a hot cup
of raktajino,
- he will be ready to go.
- Oh, no.
- Oh...
- Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
The shuttle! The shuttle!
What the hell?!
- No.
- Ha. Classic K'orin.
Ah, he did this on Vulcan.
And on Earth.
He steals a lot of things.
We are stranded here
because of your recklessness.
Oh, relax. We can just beam
back to the Cerritos
and remotely trigger
the return autopilot.
Sure, yeah, if Tulgana 4
wasn't protected
by an ion field that restricts
comms and transporters!
By an ion field that restricts
Do you even read
the mission brief?
I'm sorry,
I skimmed almost most of it
and read some
of the captions, so...
- Dude, where are you going?
- I'm tracking down our shuttle.
If we're not back to it
by the next rotation,
- we'll be court-martialed!
- Don't knock it
till you've tried it.
This is serious! I think we're
violating the Khitomer Accords!
Yeah, I don't want to go
to a penal colony either,
but I am not going
to speed-walk.
What is this speed-walking?
- You know we're going
the same speed.
- Stop it.
It's to conserve energy.
Section 31 does this.
Yes, General K'orin
was here a short while ago.
It was my honor to serve him
a warrior's meal.
Do you know where he went?
- Are you tracking him?
- Oh, well, I, uh...
Whew, I think, uh...
Uh, no, we-we want
to kneel before him
and lick his boots like
the Federation dogs we are.
And lick his boots like
He went north,
in search of stronger ale.
- He was already wasted.
- Is that a problem?
Uh, no. I mean, uh,
drinking to excess is cool.
All right, come on.
There's an Andorian district
just north of here.
So we're Federation dogs, huh?
Hey, if it got us
what we needed, woof woof.
I know this is fun,
but we really need to get back.
I'm not having fun.
Geez, these guys are acting
like they've never seen
a Starfleet uniform.
Well, they're Kaelons,
and Kaelons are
notoriously isolationist.
And that...
- Oh, shoot, sorry.
That's my fault.
Boimler, let's keep moving.
No, no, no, I need to apologize
in his native tongue.
Let me think.
He's a, uh, a Taxor.
Right, and they communicate
through guttural tones.
Hey back off, blue!
No! Don't hit him!
We have a treaty!
You made the right choice
transferring into Command, son.
Nothing compares to the firm,
hot pulse of a joystick
in your hand.
The bridge is
where the action is.
Should be interesting, sir.
Let's start with
a classic bridge simulation.
Computer, Command Trainer 43.
Initiating advanced simulation.
Ensign, the bridge is yours.
Be gentle but attentive.
Get her where she needs to be.
- Guide her home.
- Okeydokey.
Uh, maintain course.
Captain, we're being drawn
into a temporal rift.
- Uh... Uh...
- Shields at ten percent!
- Warp core breach
in 30 seconds, Captain!
- Oh, man.
Captain, we need orders!
Uh, uh... maintain course?
Ship destroyed.
105%
Wait. How did I kill
more than the whole crew?
Okay, that was a rough start.
FYI, in situations like that,
try employing
the Janeway Protocol.
Got it. And what's that?
Good one.
All right, let's try something
more straightforward.
Computer, Command Trainer 4.
Initiating basic training
simulation.
Captain, we're directly
in the path of a small asteroid.
Should we move to avoid?
Uh, do the Janeway Protocol.
Uh, are you sure, sir?
Yes?
Collision alert, sir.
The kindergarten on Deck Eight,
it's gone!
Uh, uh...
No.
No, no, no.
Now the pre-K is gone.
All the ship's children
have been ejected into space.
- All those kids...
- Freeze program.
In thousands of simulations,
that's literally
never happened before.
That's literally
Let's try another one, on a ship
with even more children.
I can't believe I messed up
so bad with that Taxor.
I've read, like,
five books about them.
Hey, don't sweat it, B.
I got you.
That's even worse.
You didn't study them at all.
I study by doing, you know?
Maybe you need to spend
less time in the library
and more time
letting Boimler get nasty.
No. I need to up my studying,
spend even more time
in the library.
Whatever, man.
Just hang here for a second.
I got to go blood-pee
some blood wine,
maybe get some intel
on the general.
Oh. I see we both have
a thing for red.
- Uh, me, what, red? What?
- Your shirt.
- We match.
- Oh.
Uh, yes, well,
this is my work shirt.
- And I'm Ensign...
- Ensign Brad Boimler. I know.
I can sense your thoughts,
your desires.
I know you like jamaharon.
Mm...
Mariner, what the hell?!
That thing is an Anabaj.
It's gonna implant eggs
in your throat, dummy.
What are you...
I know you still want it.
I can hear
your nasty boy thoughts.
Jamaharon.
This boy wants jamaharon!
Love your sarong.
- You okay, Boims?
- Yeah, I just...
I-I've never even
heard of an Anabaj.
How did you know?
Affinity for red,
drawn to the weak-minded.
Plus, I kind of dated one once,
but only to make my mom mad.
Weak-minded?
An Andorian in the bathroom
said the general's
at a bar just down the road.
Come on.
You can tell me
about jamaharon later.
Ah, you're doing a bang-up job
with that endocrine system,
Ensign.
It's not so different
from engineering.
The heart's an engine.
The brain's a computer.
The eyes are a different kind
of computer. No... cameras.
- Eyes are cameras. Camera eyes.
- Sure.
Whatever you need
to tell yourself.
The next part gets dicey.
Keep him distracted.
- Are you sure you don't
want me to reroute...
- Go chat him up!
That's an order!
Tendi, exoscalpel.
Uh, hi. I'm supposed to
distract you from all this stuff
- over here, so...
- I'm gonna be okay,
though, right?
- over here, so...
- I'm gonna be okay,
though, right?
My implant says there's
only a small chance you'll die.
- What? How small?
- 18%. Oh, uh...
Now it's up to 20. You might
want to control that heart rate.
Oh, God, I'm gonna die!
What the hell
are you saying to him?
- Just calm him down.
- Uh, uh...
Take your mind off of this.
Uh, think about work.
- Think about the warp core.
- I got burned in the warp core!
Those are dilithium burns?
How are you still alive, man?
You should be dead!
Get out of here!
Tendi, take over.
- Wait, but...
- Sorry.
Don't worry, you're looking
just fine, inside and out.
Oh, my God. Oh, thank God.
That robot said I was dying.
Listen, kid, you're great
at digging around in a body,
but if you can't muster up
some bedside manner,
you may as well be
with the grunts in security.
You may as well be
Welcome to security.
Why don't we throw you into
the fire and see if you burn?
Computer, initiate
Combat Simulation Smorgasborg.
Initiating.
Borg!
Oh, crap.
I don't know how to fight.
Maybe this thing does?
O-Okay.
Oh, I can do that?
Ha, man. Ha!
Take that. Chop, chop, bang!
Karate! Ha, ha.
In the name of the Prophets.
I-I put people
into that simulation
so they can learn
how to deal with defeat.
So they can learn
Ensign, you are
a natural-born warrior.
Oh. Okeydokey.
Keep your head down.
Andorians don't mess around.
Um, Andorians were a founding
member of the Federation.
Please don't explain them to me.
I can look out for myself.
You want to tell me
about Tellarites, too?
Maybe shut up and keep
an eye out for the shuttle?
How about that?
No, you're hurting me. Please.
My bones.
- They're killing him!
- Boimler!
Please, no. I-I can explain.
Explain it to my boot.
Starfleet! I order you
to step away from the elder.
You idiot!
That's no elder, it's...
Now I'm a little boy.
A shapeshifter? Ah, boo.
That Vendorian is a thief,
and you let him get away!
They must be working together!
Oh, no! Aah!
Stand down. This is in violation
of the Tulganan Neutrality Pact.
Kirk hands!
Hello, alien people.
Alien creatures and beings.
Look up here. Thank you. Okay.
I would be happy to hand you
all your asses, but right now,
we're kind of on a deadline, so
how about instead of fighting,
the next five rounds are on me?
It's cool. I stole it
from that Taxor!
Excuse me, sir.
I don't know you.
That is Starfleet property
you're handling.
Ah, apparently,
we just missed K'orin.
- If we hurry,
maybe we can get him.
- I don't even care anymore.
- What?
- Oh, man, how much blood
did you lose?
- Ow.
- Oh, man, how much blood
did you lose?
- Ow.
This whole time, I've either
been one step behind you
- or totally in the dark.
- Yeah, but only because
I'm pretty amazing.
Look, everyone has bad days.
All that studying,
and where did it get me?
Klingon threw a knife
at my head.
I nearly got eggs
laid in my throat.
Those guys at the bar
wanted to eat me.
What is that?
What are you doing?
Kitalia leaves...
They contain a numbing agent.
I've never once seen you study,
but then you just
breeze in here
knowing cool plant tricks
and which aliens
are which... how?
Dude, I told you
I've been places.
I just pick stuff up
along the way.
I could never do that.
I guess I'm just not cut out
for Starfleet.
Oh, please,
you're Mr. Starfleet.
No, I'm not, not like you are!
I should just turn in
my uniform and go
work on a research asteroid!
Work on a research asteroid!
No, absolutely not.
Do not even joke about that.
That is the lamest thing
you could do.
I should just
study bugs on a far-off planet
and then eventually get eaten
and no one will even know
until they stumble
across my distress call,
but it'll be way too late,
and then they'll have to spend
a bunch of time
deciphering
how things went wrong
based on my final
shaky video logs.
Based on my final
I'm sure you wouldn't get eaten.
Starfleet doesn't just need
badass cool people like me.
They need, like, book-smart
people like you, too.
When we get back, I'm done.
All right, everyone, huddle up.
I want to introduce you to the
newest bear in our bear pack.
Rutherford's blood runs
yellow and black.
He's one of us.
Security isn't like
the other departments.
No, it's a higher calling.
We stand shoulder to shoulder,
holding the line
against dangers
known and unknown.
Against dangers
No greater honor
than to die
beside you in battle.
Yes, Rutherford, you're
never going to have to see
the inside
of a Jefferies tube again.
Thank you, sir.
This all sounds fun
but not for me.
What?
My heart's in engineering.
I'd like permission
to leave the bear pack.
Rutherford, that is...
outstanding!
Got to be true to yourself!
Am I right, bears?
- Hoorah!
- Aw, bears.
Come on, we got to take
a shortcut.
We're almost out of time.
Whatever. Who cares?
I clearly do.
Greetings, "hyoo-mons."
I noticed you are injured.
Perhaps I could
provide you transport.
Uh, no, thank you, sir.
Yeah, right.
Can you believe this guy?
Actually, yeah,
that would be great.
- We're kind of in a hurry.
- Wait, what?
Excellent. My shuttle is
just beyond that ridge.
Come, come.
What are you doing?
We can't trust a Ferengi.
- What? He's not a Ferengi.
- Yes, he is!
- No, I think he's a Bolian.
- Oh, my God!
He could not be more Ferengi...
The big ears, the beady eyes,
that greedy thing they do
with their hands.
That greedy thing they do
"Hyoo-mon."
- Myah.
- Ferengi are
the most untrustworthy race
in the galaxy.
He probably just wants to lure
us over there so he can mug us.
Look, we need a ride now,
and my gut is telling me
this is fine.
Need I remind you
that you've been wrong
about literally
everything today?
Not this.
Uh-huh, sure. Okay, buddy.
- Let's go.
- Good, good.
- Follow me right this...
- What's your landing code?
Uh, what?
Tulganan security requires
all shuttlecraft
to provide
a secure landing code.
If you really have a shuttle
here, you must have a code.
Oh, my code, yes.
It's, uh, right... here!
- Give me your profit!
- Oh!
Aah! Starfleet!
Hey, Ferengi,
get-get out of here!
Get! Get!
Okay, maybe you were right.
That, uh...
that seems like that
might've been a Ferengi.
I was so right, yes!
Holy crap, it's the shuttle.
It's the shuttle!
- Bye-bye.
- Isn't that illegal?
What are they gonna do,
send me a bill in space?
Fair enough. If we gun it, we
can just make it back in time.
Oh, man, he drank everything!
- What do we do?
- Grab a leg.
Let's drag him out
and leave him by the front door,
unless you don't think
that's Starfleet enough.
It isn't, but let's do it.
I demand
you give me an honorable...
Someone contact the Cerritos,
tell them
we finally found K'orin.
He is just in time
for the peace accords.
Fetch me my drinking horn.
I need ale.
Are you kidding me?
No! Stop that.
Whew, what a day!
Man, that escort mission
kind of went off the rails, huh?
Sure did.
Can't believe I didn't realize
that was a Ferengi in the park.
Hey, uh, so do you think maybe,
maybe, fun idea, we could
just keep it between us?
For sure.
We're in a circle of trust.
This is a shuttle of silence.
So the Ferengi's right there,
and I'm like, "Mariner,
we can't trust this guy.
And I'm like, "Mariner,
He's a Ferengi." And then
she says, she says, get this,
she says,
"Oh, no, that's a Bolian."
- Bolian!
- Okay, okay.
Yep, yep, all right.
After this long day
of being a badass,
Captain Know-It-All over here
doesn't even know
- what a Ferengi was.
- It wasn't as clear as that.
- What a Ferengi was.
"Myah, myah, hyoo-mon!"
He was doing the hand thing
and everything.
All right, yeah,
no, that's my cue
to go just launch myself
out an air lock.
You guys have a great night.
Lucky I was there!
I spotted it. I called it.
I called it.
Tendi, I'm sorry.
I tried to make it work
in another division.
I just couldn't do it.
I belong in the tubes.
- I'm not gonna be able
to watch the pulsar with you.
- All right, whatever.
I'll just watch it
in there with you on my PADD.
Wait, you can?
We don't have to go
to the observation deck
or anything?
Nah, I just wanted company.
I mean, it's not like you were
trying all those new jobs
just to hang with me, right?
No, yeah, no.
Could you imagine?
Ah, Mariner, was I
convincing enough for you,
"hyoo-mon"?
You were perfect, Quimp.
Thanks for helping out.
Of course. I owed you one.
- How's the wife?
- She's good.
We're actually looking to
get away to Risa this weekend.
What? Ah, jealous.
Oh, you know what you guys
should try? Jamaharon.
Wow.
Isn't it amazing?
It's beautiful.
Subtitles Diego Moraes(oakislandtk)
www.opensubtitles.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org