A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
TEUTOBURG FOREST, 9 AD
THREE ROMAN LEGIONS
ARE ADVANCING TOWARDS GERMANIA
THE LARGEST ARMY IN THE WORLD
IS MET WITH MANY QUARRELING TRIBES
THE ROMANS CALLED THEM BARBARIANS
THEIR ENCOUNTER
CHANGED
THE COURSE OF HISTORY
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Come on, I'll get you!
Come on!
Come on, guys!
Ansgar!
Ansgar, stop!
Hey, little brother.
Are you hunting?
Show me what a good hunter you are!
Come on.
A mouse? A frog?
Father.
Thusnelda, leave your brother alone.
Let's go.
He'll be here any minute.
Let your hair down.
Welcome to the Cherusci,
Reik Hadgan.
Your long journey was not in vain.
We've been waiting for you.
The hips are a bit small.
Good teeth.
Hmm, strong muscles.
And a firm fist.
Don't touch her hair, Hadgan.
She's not yours yet.
There's the matter of the price.
Don't start again, Hadgan.
The bridal price is set. Five mares.
In times like these?
For a woman so skinny?
Think it over.
I'll walk you to the gate.
Should I stab him for you?
I can take care of him.
It's a steep price, but I'll take her.
You're buying more than a wife, Hadgan.
You're buying an ally.
In half a moon, I'll return for her.
She'll obey. You'll see.
Romans!
Augustus,
emperor of the holy city of Rome,
has appointed a new governor for Germania.
Senator Publius Quinctilius Varus.
Do you understand
what he's saying?
No.
Fuck,
these brutes don't understand a word.
From now on...
Rome will no longer waive your tribute.
Segestes, what is it?
The Romans want tribute.
Varus requires
every tribe to pay the value
of 20 cows
or 50 centners of grain.
They want cattle and grain.
Are you blind?
Does it look like
there's anything to take from us?
What?
Say that again.
He wants you to say that again.
You have three days.
They're giving us three days.
What?
Why are the Romans breaking our agreement?
We made peace with Rome!
Without any tribute.
Enough!
Rome is bleeding us dry
even after I gave them my sons.
What do you want to do?
The Romans have the upper hand
and I don't need
to remind you by how much.
Indeed you don't, Segestes.
- The mother of your sons...
- Do not speak of my wife.
Do not speak of my sons.
Send out messengers.
To every tribe.
We'll put it to them.
Everyone will have a vote.
That's useless.
You know the tribes will never unite.
I will commit them all to fight.
The Romans won't take any more.
You're the reik.
Reiks!
The Romans are now
demanding taxes from all Germanic peoples.
We have to decide tonight.
Will we let the Romans subjugate us...
or will we fight back?
"Germanic"?
Since when are we Germanic?
The Romans call us that...
because they can't tell us apart.
Then they're blind!
I've got nothing in common
with you Cherusci.
- Or with those damn cattle-thieving Marsi.
- Take that back, Hadgan.
I'd rather drink piss.
Then open your mouth!
- Come on!
- Stop it!
What's wrong with you?
No blood shall be spilled when we meet.
What do we get
if we pay this tribute, anyway?
- Right.
- Even more overfed Romans.
I say enough is enough.
I say we fight them!
You want to rise up
against the greatest army in the world?
You may as well smash your own heads in.
There are 10,000 Romans here.
5,000 coming across the Lippe.
Do you get it or are you all stupid?
It's peace that we need.
Your idea of peace
amounts to a reeking pile of shit.
I'll pay no tribute!
Never!
We need a decision, reik.
We have an alliance with Rome.
And you gave a great deal for it.
Aldarich of the Marsi.
No war with the Romans!
We haven't heard
from Hadgan of the Chatti.
No war with the Romans.
The tribes disagree.
What do you say, reik?
Will the Cherusci go to war...
without the support of every tribe?
We'll keep the peace.
Were you spying?
So what?
You won't be saying that
once you've been punished.
It's better than being touched by you.
Not one of you has any balls.
My little brother's braver
than all those asses.
Yes, but you're his sister.
And you're a woman.
- And our reik isn't a real man.
- Careful, Thusnelda.
I've sworn Segimer an oath.
You know that.
We've sworn each other an oath, too.
Or does this not mean anything?
Report me to the reik.
I'm going to.
- I'm waiting.
- I'm going to.
Yes, please do.
- I will.
- Please.
- Yeah, I'm going to.
- Then do it.
- Do it. Do it.
- I will. I will.
- Yes, I will.
- Yeah?
- I will.
- I will. I'm going to.
- Do it.
Hey.
- I have to go.
- Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
I'm so tired of meeting in secret.
Folkwin...
Yeah?
My father has a bridegroom for me.
Who?
A reik.
Hadgan.
The ugly Chatti?
The Reik of the Chatti.
A man like you...
Your father's a brewer.
- My father is a lord.
- Your father is a damn Roman-lover
who's just waiting for his opportunity
to stab our reik in the back and who...
sells you like an ox.
And what should we do about it?
Just run away?
Yeah.
I'll steal you.
Here and now.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Folkwin.
I want you...
but they'll banish us.
You don't want that.
Maybe the Romans will kill him.
You're finally here, my son.
Welcome to Germania.
It's good to see you again
after all this time.
I could really use
your strategic advice in this crazy land.
Come here, you little berserker.
Do you know what day it is today?
Today is the day
that you get sacrificed to the gods.
First, I'll throw you in the bog,
and then comes Woden.
And he will gnaw the flesh...
...from your bones.
And bless us with sunshine
for days and days.
Oh, no, no. No.
Hey. Hey.
As long as I live,
no harm will come to you.
Okay, little brother?
Promise. What's a wolf say?
What's a wolf say?
Folkwin, we have to gather the tribute.
- Order of the reik.
- No.
Get.
We don't even have enough
to feed ourselves, Mother.
We'll give our last goat
to keep the peace if the reik asks us.
No, no, no...
Sheep are going, too.
Where's the rest?
I asked you a question. Where is the rest?
- Slurp it up by yourself at home. Just go.
- Leave my father alone.
You are not the reik.
That's not even enough
to wipe my ass with.
He praises our efforts
toward mutual friendship...
but he's not satisfied.
Go!
What's going on? Wait.
Segestes, tell them to stop.
We have nothing more to give you!
You can't do this!
This isn't even close
to what Rome requires.
He says it's not enough.
We kept our part of the deal
and Rome is now going to.
Governor Varus expects
a demonstration of your loyalty to Rome.
Your leader should kiss our standard.
They demand
that you kiss their eagle.
Go on.
On your knees.
Reik.
- No! No!
- Stop it.
- Enough! Calm down, Thusnelda.
- What are you doing?
- Don't!
- Not now.
- Let go of me!
- Hold him down!
Ansgar!
Rome wants a sign of our friendship?
Fine!
Rome victorious!
No, no, no, no...
Please!
Mother,
I didn't want this to happen.
Women of the woods...
take my sacrifice.
Mother of Blood...
give me bravery...
and strength...
until my brother is avenged.
Mother of Fire...
misgivings and doubt be burned...
until my brother is avenged.
And Sister of Wrath...
grant me cruel twins...
death and doom.
And be a good sister to me now...
though I was not.
Though I was not.
Most of the tribes
have submitted and paid the tribute.
But not him.
I'll give you one more chance, barbarian.
Metellus.
The tribes don't understand this.
According to their law,
a man cannot sentence another man to die.
There is no Germanic law.
There is only Rome.
They must learn.
Ansgar is
a favorite of the gods.
Because he survived?
Because he's been to the Kingdom of Death,
and he returned.
It seems he still has a task
to complete up here.
What task must I complete?
What do the gods want?
Only Woden, the father of the gods,
can see what will happen.
That's why he sacrificed his own eye.
If you are truly meant to fight,
the gods will send you a sign.
The past shadows...
become the light of coming days.
A sign?
It's complete bullshit. I hate oracles.
You don't believe the gods send us signs?
I believe in my sword.
And I will do everything I can
to avenge your brother, if you want that.
- I don't want to wait for a sign.
- Then let's make our own.
We'll capture
the most valuable thing to them.
Their holy symbol.
- How will you do that?
- Not me.
Us.
Then they'll all see
that you're more than just a swordsman.
And we show everyone
that Rome is not invincible.
Let's go bird hunting.
If we don't do something now...
then soon everything
here will belong to them.
But if we manage this...
we're not just taking the Roman eagle,
we're taking our people's fear away.
Yes, of course.
I mean, there are
worse reasons to die, but...
So this is the plan?
The four of us raid the Roman fort?
How will we even get in?
You go through the back,
the two of us through the front.
I've got what every legionnaire wants.
Hello.
For...
Metellus.
A slave.
For Centurion Metellus.
- I wasn't told about this.
- Who is this slave?
Shh. Shh.
A prostitute... a sex slave.
Let them in.
If Metellus doesn't have her,
he'll have you.
Yeah.
Call me a sex slave once more
and I'll cut your balls off.
- Say we manage to get inside.
- Mmm.
We just walk up
and take the eagle with us or what?
No, we'll take care of that.
- Halt.
- Hello.
Hello.
You want an orgy? An orgy?
Orgy? Huh? Huh?
Roman shits.
You go first.
Next time, I wanna go through the front.
You can touch her, too.
Go ahead. Yeah, yeah. Come.
Here, look, yes. Yes.
She's all yours. Look at her.
Everything's exactly
where it should be, right?
You two will make sure we have a way out.
And how?
Quick.
Greetings.
I found one.
Secure the camp.
Secure the camp!
Hungry wolves surround you.
Teeth bared, ready to mangle you.
What do you do?
Close the gate!
Quickly!
We have to be hungrier
than all the wolves.
Steadfast.
If we're ready to give everything...
Fetch water!
Hurry!
Then we get what we want,
and the Romans get...
what they deserve.
The eagle is sacred!
The guards will all be punished,
just as Mars will punish us.
Give me a hundred legionaries, Governor.
Oh, yes?
I will bring it back.
How do you know where to go?
There are hundreds,
thousands of barbarian villages.
I will burn them down, one after another.
And provoke a rebellion?
That's exactly what they want.
I'll look for them.
Give me the Germanic mercenaries.
I'll have the eagle back by tomorrow.
Go to Adjunct Prefect Talio.
I want you to ride out at dawn.
The Romans feast
on meat, and we only get the bones.
Shh! Just be quiet.
Where can I find
the leader of your cohort, Talio?
What is this?
What the hell are you doing?
The barbarian started it, dominus.
Is that true?
I asked you if that was true.
Forgive me... dominus.
They may wear Roman armor,
they may get Roman pay...
but they are
and will remain damned barbarians!
You're not exactly
a model soldier, either.
Dismissed!
I have a mission from Varus himself.
You and your men will be my support.
We ride out at dawn.
Men! Ready your mounts!
We're off come sunrise.
We have to lick
Rome's stinking cunt again.
Is that your humble
opinion of our empire, then?
You speak our language?
That's enough.
They have the eagle!
The eagle! They have the eagle!
Long live Folkwin!
Long live Thusnelda!
Long live Hanno and Eigil!
You know what this means, don't you?
Yeah.
That we can beat them.
It means blood.
A lot of blood.
Revenge is certain.
How will they even find us, huh?
Between us and the Romans,
there are hundreds of villages.
Look there.
Just look.
They're all waiting for a sign! Look!
You go this way,
and you, that way.
Come on. Come on.
Romans! Romans!
Romans!
Bring it inside.
Close it!
Open the gate.
Open the gate!
Hello, Father.
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN