Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
What?
Mor e salt?
Not too fin e, eh?
Sometimes you cut it too fine,
then all you taste i s the garli c,
Let's go, Five mi n utes, h uh?
- Cristiano, let's go. Hurry up.
- My God, I can't bel ieve it.
Remi n d me tomorr ow to cal I th e plumber
to come back so I can ki II h im,
- Ready?
- I'm r eady half an hour,
Wait, the risotto.
,
Yes, go.
Th an k God,
Ok ay, her e we go,
I'm just so hungry.
That look s good.
You got I eaves with yours,
Here we go.
Ok ay.
Mon sieur, i s thi s wh at I or der ed?
,
Yes, it is risotto, a speci al r ecipe
that my br other and I bri n g fr om Italy,
It's delicious, I pr omi se,
It took so long I thought you went
back to Italy to get it,
I know, but it's worth it, I promise.
You would lik e fr esh pepper or cheese?
- No, I don 't n eed ch eese,
,
- Ch eese, yeah,
Excu se me, Didn't you say thi s would be
ri ce with seafood?
Yes, It is Itali an arborio ri ce,
,
the best,
Th en with shrimp and scallop and...
I don't see anything that looks lik e
a shri mp or scall op,
I mean, it's just not
wh at I expected.
But I get spaghetti with thi s,
right?
Wh y? Well, no,
I thought all mai n cou rses
come with spaghetti.
Some yes. But you see,
ri sotto is rice, so it is a star ch,
And it doesn't go r eally
with pasta,
Honey, order a side of spagh etti,
that's al I.
- An d I'll eat your meatball s,
- He'I I have th e meatball s,
Well, the spagh etti comes
without meatballs,
There ar e no meatball s
with the spaghetti?
No, Someti mes spaghetti lik es
to be alone.
Then I guess we'll also have
a side or der of meatballs.
This i s fi n e, Let's ju st eat.
All ri ght, no meatballs,
We'll have a side or der of spaghetti,
Pri mo, please, just...
Come on,
I want to kn ow for who.
Just mak e me the si de order
of spaghetti, please,
Secondo, I want to know
,
who i s it for,
For the lady with the risotto,
Wh at? Why?
She I ik es starch.
I don 't kn ow! Come on!
Bitch!
I'll mak e it myself.
Who ar e these peopl e in Ameri ca?
I n eed to talk to her,
Please, wh at ar e you going to do?
Tell the customer wh at she can eat?
That is what sh e wants.
This is what th e customer ask for,
Mak e it, Mak e the pasta,
Mak e it, Mak e it.
- Mak e th e pasta. Let's go!
- How can sh e want? They both are star ch,
Maybe I shoul d mak e mashed potato
f or on the other side,
Don 't, because th ey ar e th e fi rst
customer s to come in two h ours.
No, she's a criminal,
I want to talk to her,
You want to talk to h er? Ok ay.
That's gr eat.
You want to talk to her?
Ok ay, good, fine,
I'm sick of this every fu cking night,
You want to talk t o her?
Ok ay, her e we go,
Go talk to h er.
No, Sh e's a Ph ilisti n e,
I'm not gonna talk to h er.
Sh e no understand anyway.
It will be just a moment,
Good morn ing.
PI ease, sit down.
Th ank you,
- Ci garette?
- Yes. Th an k you,
Thank you. Th is i s completely differ ent
than wh en I was h ere befor e,
It's a beautiful r enovation,
We went thr ough that with our restaur ant
when we first started,
It's a I ot of work,
a lot of mon ey,
A pai n in the neck, you kn ow?
But I think it come out good,
you know.
'Cau se it's simple. It's a very
simple pl ace for the fami ly to come,
Very ni ce, casual,
- You lik e Italian food?
- Yes, I do, Very much.
I'm going to h ave to ch ange
the dir ection of this conversati on n ow.
Yes, I understand, Okay,
Is there somebody you can borr ow from,
back i n...
Back home?
No, because we did that alr eady
to come her e,
I see.
You have an y saleabl e assets?
Somethin g to sell,
li k e a car for money, to pay us,
- Yes. I under stan d,
,
- I wasn't sur e you...
I speak En glish,
No, I don't. My car? No,
I have a car but it's no Cadil lac.
I need my car for the business,
I see.
I don't know,
Your payments over the past two years
have h ardly been consistent,
Yes. I kn ow.
,
I'm afr aid we can't give you
any mor e time.
- What do you mean?
- We can't give you any mor e time.
Mr. Pier ce, let me explai n
something to you, ok ay?
I'll explai n my situation to you,
wh ich i s un u su al, all ri ght?
I don t want to both er you, but., .
li sten, my br other i s...
It's a diffi cult situation. Because
what we try to do her e is very har d,
- I hate to see bu sinesses fail, okay?
- But I want you to understand,
- I hate to see bu sinesses fail, ok ay?
- Yes, me too.
,
But we're a bank, We can 't h elp people
who can't help themselves,
If we don't receive your payment by
the end of the month. We'll for eclose,
- Th an k you very much.
- Sur e,
- I wish I could pay yoi with money.
- Please, What would I do with money?
Th ank you,
I have t o go now,
Thank you for the painti ng,
Thi s is the bi ggest one.
It's a heavy one.
- Good night,
- Good night, Stash,
- Good ni ght. Secondo.
See what h e give us?
Look. It's a landscape, See?
Don't you love it?
Gr eat,
Put it with th e rest of th em.
Primo, I et me ask you somethin g,
What do you thin k
if we tak e risotto off the menu?
Primo?
Wh at do you th ink about that?
Tak e risotto off the menu.
I'm sorry,
What did you say?
Forget it,
No, I don't hear what you say.
Tell me what you say.
It's just that,, .
risotto costs u s a I ot.
And it tak es you
a I on g time to mak e,
You have to work so h ard to mak e.
,
you kn ow?
And th en we h ave to char ge mor e, so., .
I th ink tak e it away,
Sure. Good.
- Really?
- Yeah. Th at's good,
Yeah, grazie. Ok ay.
Maybe instead we cou Id put...
Yes, tel I me.
,
I was thi n king.
What do they call it? You kn ow,
It's... Come se dice?
Manicotti?
Is a h ot dog?
Hot dog. Hot dogs.
I thi n k people would lik e th at.
Th ose,
Fine,
If you give people time,
they I earn,
Wel I. I don't have time
,
for th em to learn,
Th is i s a r estaur ant,
,
not a fucki n g sch ool.
It's bu sy again ton ight.
The man shoul d be in prison
for the f ood h e serves,
People love it.
Good n ight.
Wh ere you go?
To see Ph yll is.
Ah! Say hi for me,
You go out?
- Yes,
- Wh er e?
Out, to a movie,
You want to come?
Why? No.
I go see Al berto.
- Wh at i s the movi e?
- You want to come?
Come on. Want to come?
Call up the flower lady.
What s h er name? An n?
Wh o?
- Doubl e date?
- Wh o?
Why wou Id I call her?
I don't know,
Al berto sai d that you and she wer e...
- What?
- You know.
- He said th at?
- Yeah.
It's n o secret,
Tak es you longer each time
wh en you go to bu y the flowers.
I do not grab just any flowers,
I lik e to pi ck the right one,
But don't tak e too I ong. Someone el se
ni ght pi ck the one you want,
Good n ight.
Why wou Id Secondo say you said something
and you say you sai d n othing?
- Wh at? Wh at's the matter?
- No, Ph yll is, I can't.
No, I can 't,
,
Hon ey, n o, I can 't, No. I can't.
I don't want to,
I just get sad.
- Sad?
- Yes,
Hon ey, "sad" is the wr ong wor d.
Wel I. N o, I don 't mean sad,
,,
I mean, you know.,,
it just gets me all jazzed up,
you kn ow?
And then I want to go to my place.
but I can 't go ther e,
You know.
,
I h ave to go crazy.
We don't have to be...
I mean, you kn ow,
we've done other thi n gs,
I kn ow.
So wh at's the pr oblem?
I know. I ju st want it to be...
I can 't, I can't, No.
I just want it to be.
for you and me to be, .,
okay, someth ing,
all ri ght?
I mean, I want for it
to be th e ri ght time, Ok ay?
I mean, becau se thi s i s
,
a very important thing, ok ay?
I know it, We'r e not...
It's not for me a casu al th ing, It's
okay, lik e that, It's not lik e th at.
I know it's not li k e that
for you eith e...
I want it to be, you know,
when the time is right,
Because now everything i s just too much.
and I ju st can't...
I just... I want it to...
I want us to be
when I am more set,
- Set?
- Yes.
Oh. So it's about fi n an ces,
,
It's about mon ey.
No, Ph yll is, it's not about money,
An d don 't mak e it sound lik e that,
Don't mak e it li k e... It's n ot I ik e th at,
'Cause I'm her e working, trying to do
something. It's very har d.
And th en my brother's driving me crazy,
Ok ay?
I'm just sayi n g that
it's about mon ey, yes, ok ay.
I'm sorry you don't under stan d money,
Yeah, I don't under stan d noney.
I work i n a bank.
What did you say?
I under stan d money,
Good.
Honey, I ju st...
All I want is for the ti me
to be right, ok ay?
And I want it to be ri ght for you,
An d the time,
,
it is not ri ght for you,
You un derstand what I mean?
You know, .,
I don't th ink you know what you want,
I r eally don 't,
What do you mean?
What?
Wh at do you want?
Do you know exactly what you want?
What do you want? You want me to ask you
to marry you right n ow?
- Is that a pr oposal?
- Wel I. No,
,
Do you want to marry ne?
- Do I want t o marry you?
- Yeah.
Yes, pr obably, someday.
Yes, in the futu re, I want to marry you,
Phyl lis, but n ot right now.
Thank you very much,
but no, not ri ght now,
I'm sorry,
- What?
- Noth ing,
Just forget it,
I don't know,
I'm so tired.
Yeah.
It's very late,
how ar e you?
Is he h ere?
I don't know,
In the back.
Ciao. How are you?
You 'r e busy tonight,
Oh, Friday ni ght!
- Hey, Number Two. You'r e her e early!
- Charlie, how are you?
- What's your poison?
- Scotch and soda, please,
- You're busy ton ight, huh?
- Hey, Friday night, You know.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I present to you!
- Unbelievable. Hu h?
,
- Some guy, huh?
Oh, boy, Ch eers.
Thank you very much,
You fu cking guy.
You see me over ther e?
You know, I shou Id be in the cir cus,
,
Yes,
You got everythi n g you need?
Everything?
- Charli e, you tak e car e of my friend,
- I'm all set.
I dropped my cigar ette.
I I ove thi s guy,
I r eally do,
You are I ik e my br oth er.
You are the best.
You ar e the best guy, you kn ow?
He i s the best guy,
and so fucking handsome,
Look at thi s suit.
Di d I see this befor e?
Cesar e. Table n u mber six.
,
Give th em a bottl e
of whatever they'r e havin g on the house,
An d don 't open it,
I'll be ther e in one minute,
- So, fucki n g gu y, you close early.
- Yes.
What happen ed?
Did you ru n out of food?
I nak e a jok e.
Pascal, I want to ask you,
can I talk to you?
Of cour se, Fr ee,
But I 'm not just me.
I am me and my brother.
You kn ow, so...
,
So you guys are not even thinkin g
about coming to work for me,
I should say, with me,
- Beli eve me, I thi n k about it, but...
- Yes, I see you th inking,
And I am flatter ed.
,
but my br other has ideas.
Ideas is ideas.
I had to convince hi n to come h ere
to h ave ou r own place,
Becau se I kn ow in Italy you work h ard
and ther e is n othing.
But h ere, you work hard and...
I kn ow,
That i s why we all come h er e, huh?
It's the land of fucking opportun ity,
right?
But you can't come h ere
and expect the figs., .
the fir st year you plant the
goddamn tree, no matter who you ar e!
- You know what I'm saying?
- Bel ieve me. I know.
,
Th at's exactly what my brother said too,
It's funny.
But. Seco...
,
may I say something I learn ed
without being too big?
A guy goes out to eat
in the eveni ng,, .
after a lon g day
in the office. Whatever.
,
He don 't want
on his plate, .,
something th at he has to I ook an d think,
"What th e fuck is th is? '"
No, right, What he wants is,
hey, steak,
"Thi s is a steak.
I I ik e steak, '"
You kn ow?
Mmm, I'm happ y!
You see wh at I mean?
But don't get me wron g,
I think that your br oth e.
i s a good, goddamn chef.
- Maybe th e best I ever see.
- He is th e best.
Yes, but., .
,
th is is what I have to say to you,
Give to peopl e wh at th ey want,
Th en later you can give them
what you want, Eh?
- Bel ieve me. I know.
,
- Hey, fucki n g guy.
You an d you r br oth er.
you come to work with me,
I know. But...
,
But the kin d of money you ask me for
I can't lend to you.
That's ok ay.
I under stan d,
,
and I'm sorry...
You know.
,
everyth ing has just,, .
become,, .
too much.
Hey, fucki n g guy.
Wh at i s thi s "too much, '" h u h?
Hey! It is n ever too much!
It's only not en ough!
Bite your teeth
into the ass of I ife, .,
and dr ag it to you!
Th at i s wh y I come her e to you,
you kn ow?
No, no. N o,
,,
You don t need money,
Wh at I speak about
has noth ing to do with money.
Who's that?
- Hu mphrey Bogart,
- Humphr ey Bogart, that's right.
I'I I tell you a story.
Two years ago, h e was i n town,
I sent th e cham pagno, th e best,
to h im at h is hotel.
"Conpl iments of Pascal. '"
That's it, on my card,
li k e that,
"Compl iments of Pascal. '"
By hand I write, h uh?
Two days later, I get that pictur e
of h im, sign ed to me.
See?
Now I ook at that pictu re ther e,
Go on,
Six months later.
Who do you see, .,
h aving a din n er
in this restaur ant?
- Humphrey Bogart,
- Hu mphr ey Bogart. You see?
See that?
That's me with Loui s Pri ma.
You know him, right?
Buona sera, buona sera
,
Signorina
Yeah. He's a big jazz guy.
I love Loui s Pri ma.
Friend of mi n e,
He's in town n ext week.
You cook for hi m. Eh, for hi s ban d
,
on a night off.
Th en who knows?
The word will get ar ound.
La vita e d ulce per tutti,
I set it up for you.
Really? Louis Prima?
He's a friend of mine,
Louis Prima.
Gr eat, That sounds, yes, gr eat,
I just have to tal k to my br oth er,
but it shoul d be...
But no, it's good. I'm sur e I can do,
No pr oblem, I do,
I mak e a call, I set hi m up,
Ok ay?
- You know Gabriel la?
- Yes, Hel lo.
Baby, li sten.
I am for you li k e on e of th ose thi n gs
with the li ghts,
Wh at?
With th e sh ips in the storm
with the li ghts!
- What?
- What do you cal I it?
- Th e li ghthou se,
- That's wh at I am for you!
If it rain, you look for me,
I show you the way home.
- Suppose h e doesn 't want to go h ome?
- He doesn't want to come home?
- He's i n the fu cking r ain,
- Some people li k e the r ain.
Gabriella, go check the menus, please.
Pascal, let me ask you something,
If my br other knows th at you...
Please,
That cr adl e will not be r obbed by me,
I tell n othing. Th is is al I your s,
Hey, you kidding?
I love secr ets.
Secr ets mak e the fri en dship str on ger.
That son of a bitch fish man,
,
you see how he changes song?
Louis Prima at oir place tonight,
Boom! The best fish.
What's the matter?
Are you sick?
People should come
just for the food.
I know.
Primo, I need your hel p here. Okay?
Louis Prima is comi ng!
He's not ju st some guy! He's famous!
Famou s? Is h e good?
He's gr eat,
People should come
ju st fo. Th e food.
- They should come ju st for the food,
- I know that. I know,
But they don't.
Whoa. Cadi II ac!
,
The newest.
It's beautifu I. H u h?
,
Cadi llac,
Big,
Primo, tell her to mak e them,
,
you know, .,
somethi n g for tonight, ok ay?
Pri mo. Ask her if sh e wants
,
to come ton ight.
You can 't tell me this,
I h ad five order s to deliver,
That's all I have t o say to you,
Good-bye.
- Trou ble today?
- I won't even... No,
Listen, I don 't h ave you r i rises,
The del ivery didn 't come,
Somebody not do thei r job,
- Somebody di dn 't think it was important,
- That is even mor e worse,
Come on.
,
we'll find somethi n g else.
I th ink for toni ght, .,
my br other,
he want somethi n g...
- Speci al.
- Yes, yes,
Some bi g jazz guy comi n g,
Loui s Prima.
I love Loui s Pri ma.
- You know h im? He's good?
- Yes,
He's very good,
Boister ous,
- Lots of en ergy.
- Ah. Th at's good,
Uh. Wel I., .
,
something speci al.
Th ese are ni ce,
Listen, I'll tell you what,
I coul d probably get
somethi n g special together, .,
and I could bri n g it over to you
th is afternoon.
- How much does that leave?
- $62.47,
- Thank you, si r.
- Th an k you,
Ton ight you will close early?
I guess, Wh y?
Well, because I th ought,
the no del ivery,
Yeah, I guess I'll h ave to.
It doesn't matter, I started a new book.
So I'll probably go h ome
and get in th e tub.
Ah, good.
- Ok ay, thank you.
- Th an k you,
- Good luck t on ight,
- Yes, and thanks,
,
What is the story?
- I'm sorry?
- In the book.
Th e story in th e book,
- Oh, the pi on eers.
- Ah. The Wild West!
,
Buffalo Bil I.
Sort of.
Famili es on the tr ai I.
Yeah. Tou gh ti mes.
Well, times ar e always tough
for somebody.
Tou gh,
I'm takin g a I ong time her e, so., .
uh. Thank s., .
,
and I h ope you li k e the book.
The pioneer s are, you know, .,
ok ay.
Hey, boys, you go fishing?
Beautiful, huh?
Hey, boys, see you later, h u h?
- You invite hi m?
- I invite everybody,
Who mak e thi s go on?
- It's Lou is Prima!
- Oh, my God!
- What?
- Oh. Jesus! Phyllis,
- I'm sorry,
- That's okay,
- Did I burn you or anything?
- No, no, I'm sorry.
It's ok ay,
- So, how are you?
- I'm fine.
- How are you?
- Ah, I'm fine. You kn ow,
I'm fine.
- I didn't cal I you,
- I kn ow,
- I didn't cal I you, eith er.
- That's tru e,
I thou ght toni ght you coul d u se
some hel p, right?
Yes,
So. I'n h er e,
,
I'm gl ad you ar e her e,
- Seco, delive. Y"s here!
- Good, Let me go do thi s,
They're small. Huh?
They"r e small but they'r e fine.
Mostly bl ack,
They're fine.
- Are they fr esh?
- Fr esh today.
Come on, look s dead.
I ik e a week.
I'm sorry, Pri mo, that's it.
That s all I got,
Well, we need them. So...
,
It"s you r party.
Primo, come her e,
Can I talk to you?
I want to talk to my br other
one second, okay?
Ok ay, is th at...
- Okay, sorry, Charlie,
- You guys ch oose a new Pope?
No, We have a party.
You want to come?
- Yeah? Are you cooki n g?
- Yes, I am, Come.
,
Yes, Ph yll is, can I ask you to get me
the white tub from over th ere, please?
An d Cristiano, my fri en d,
the oth e. One.
Now fi rst we must clean th em.
Primo, ar e you crazy?
Th ere i s not time,
- And Seco, you start th e r abbit.
- Wh at's tim pano?
- Primo, I have to be seri ou s h ere.
- What is tim pano?
- Seco, you tel I me th is i s a bi g n ight,
- No, what are we making her e, exactly?
- Phyl li s, cal I th e plumber, please!
- I call ed h im alr eady!
Phyl lis, tlm pano i s a pasta, see?
With a special cru st.
And it"s sh aped li k e a drum.
Lik e a ti mpani dru m,
- What are you doin g? Do someth ing.
- And the insi de, .,
all of th e most i mportant thin gs
in the world,
Seco, th e ph on e is for you,
Seco!
Hel lo. Yes,
No, I can't ri ght now, No.
Ok ay, I wil I be there.
Yes, ok ay. Good-bye.
I have to go.
Primo, I h ave to go talk to a guy
about the booze.
I'I I be back in one hour, okay?
Yeah, ciao.
,
- What should I do?
- I don't know, Primo wi II tel I you.
- Don't worry, Bye.
- Bye,
Can you call the booze gu y, pl ease?
Not everybody have everything
given to them with a silver lini n g,
You coul d very easy serve th e shit
at your ol d man's pl ace, Very easy.
Mik e, hi, I'm Gabri ella,
Can I ask you a favor?
I have a frien d,
he n eeds... I don't kn ow what h e n eeds,
,
but he'll come by later.
- No, I'm coming now!
- Give him a good deal.
Hey, Mik e, you'r e the best of them all,
You kn ow that?
Whenever you r wife leaves you,
you cal I me. Okay?
Hey, love you.
Bye, Mik e.
- Wh o's th at?
- Mik e,
Go, Go get you r cheap booze.
He's not here.
You gotta come back when he's h ere.
Come back in a h alf h ou r.
Then he'll be here.
I'm tir ed today,
I'm so tired.
You tir ed today?
- Ther e you go,
- Th an k you,
Tak e a br eak,
You mu st be tir ed,
No, I'm okay,
You i n the mark et?
Are you in the mark et?
Uh, wh at...
,
Good-looking fellow li k e you shou Id have
a good-looking car li k e thi s,
We al I should h ave a I ot we don t have.
I detect an accent.
- Wh ere you from?
- I'm Ital ian.
- Just visiti ng or move here for good?
- I will never go back,
- Ther e's a h istory, huh?
- In Italy, ther e is n oth ing but h istory,
Fu n ny,
Beautifu I pl ace, th ough, Italy.
- Yes, it i s, Have you been?
- No. N ever.
,
- Her e, get in. Go ahead.
- I don't know.
I r eal ly can't, but...
- Oh, boy! Wow!
- Beautiful. Huh?
Yeah. Th is i s beautiful,
Real leather tri n, ful I ai r.
,
Yes. Th is is the n ew one,
This is th is year's car?
- No, th is i s next year"s,
- Next year's? Wow, Boy,
Th is year you buy next year's car,
an d n ext year, .,
next year"s come out
alr eady again.
Yeah, You got kids?
I've got two kids, They see their frien d
with a n ew toy, they gotta have it.
I've got enou gh tensi on in my house.
You know wh at I mean?
- Sur e,
- I'm Bob, Wh at's your name?
- Secon do,
- Pleasur e,
- What did you do to your...
- I hurt my hand.
- How?
- I have no idea.
That must be diffi cu It to...
Right?
- What?
- You kn ow.
Wh y do I n eed my h ands?
Secon do, lik e second?
,
Wh o's th e fi rst, your pop?
- No, my br other,
- Scoot over,
Come on.
I h ave a younger br other.
I hate h is guts,
- Wh y?
- He's ch eap,
Well, but he's your br other,
He's a per son.
I h ate cheap people,
- Me. Too.
,
- Yeah, I could tell that,
You h ave good taste, Secondo,
Not th at taste and mon ey
ar e r el ated.,,
but it's really wh at you do
with wh atever you h ave, right?
- Yeah. Yeah,
- Power steering, power br ak es.
Power, power,
You r br oth er I ik e cars?
No, my brother,
he does n ot even drive.
Some people pr efer to walk.
I tel I you,
my brother mak e on e ride,, .
from Italy to America.
An d I guess that's enough ri des
for him, you kn ow?
- Let's tak e a test-drive,
- No, n o, I h ave to go,
Come on, No commitment,
So come, ok ay?
You bring a car, park it out front
and th en see wh at happens.
I love Loui s Pri ma.
Cristiano, go get th e booze in th e car,
- "Please. Cristiano, It would be n ice."
,
- Please, please, please,
Wher e h ave you been?
Wh at took you so I ong?
You don 't even want to kn ow,
I want you,
Embrace me!
I will embrace you!
Thi s cheap booze guy, it's th e last time
I u se him. He dr ove me crazy.
I'm sorry, all right?
Excu se me,
Amore, I I ove love.
Mr, Pascal,
I h ave to go sh oppi n g, honey.
- You need me for an ything?
- He n eeds you for everything,
You're cr azy, Good-bye.
You come back,
Ameri can girl s!
You fu cking guy!
How"s it going?
- Gr eat, Can I mak e you someth ing?
- No. Looks good,
Fuck. You guys are goi n g to town!
Come on, I'll buy you a drink.
- So, shapi n g u p,
- Yes, huh?
,
Anythin g you need,
you let me know.
- I bou ght a boat,
- You bought a boat?
Sail a way
Into the sunset
- So, h ere i s to ton ight, yes?
- To toni ght.
Maestr o!
Th at fu cking sauce! Unbel ievable!
- What can I say?
- You say thank you,
- Pascal bought a boat.
- That mean you gonna sail away?
Maybe, if the sky is red i n the mo. N...
No, if th e sun i s r ed.
No, th e sky.
Wh at i s the rhyme?
Yeah, when i s the good one?
Red sky at morning
mean it will r ai n outside,
Wh at about rain inside?
- Huh? Nothing,
- No, Wh at you mean?
You say, "rai n outside, '" and f or you
to u se the wor d "'outsi de'" is funny.
- Wh y?
- Because it can't rain in side.
I no say "'insi de, '"
I say "'outside, '"
I kn ow.
- So where is th e problem?
- I don't get it,
Well, you don't have to say "outside'"
because it can't rain i n side.
- What th e fuck?
- I know it can't r ain i n side.
F o. Get it,
- Wh at th e fuck i s he talking about?
- I'n confu sed,
- No, I nak e fu n,
,
- You mak e fun of your brother,
- No, I mak e li k e a jok e!
- I don't hear th e jok e.
It's not...
- I mak e a toast.
- Not for me, It's too early,
It s n ever too late!
So thi s is to ton ight.
Th e big ni ght
wh en I bring you together,, .
my ol d fri en d Lou is Prima
with my two n ew fri ends,
You guys ar e simply th e best.
- He's your fri en d?
- Wh o, Louis Prima?
,
Yeah. You kn ow that.
- No.
- Yeah. I told you,
No, you n o tel I me.
Yes, I did.
,
You just don 't r emember,
No, I woul d remember,
,
I tol d you,
Come on.
I know everybody,
There's nobody I don't know. Hey!
Hey, Primo, let's have anoth er.
Fuck it.
I fuck ed up.
I'm so sorry.
Do you know what goes on
i n that man's r estau rant every night?
Rape! Rape!
That is what goes on in th at pl ace
every n ight!
Th e r ape of cuisi n e!
- Wh at happened?
- Please, please, please,
What happen ed?
- Wh at's wrong?
- Noth ing.
Thi s eggplant is no good.
It's too thick,
If I cook it I ik e th is. Too th ick.
,,
it's too heavy, I can't u se it.
It's how your br other t old me
to cut it,
My br other was wr on g! Ok ay?
He was wr on g! What can I say?
He was wr ong!
Can you bel ieve it?
People mak e mistak es, That's what
they do. You shou Id know that,
When someone gives you advice,
you shoul d thi nk that maybe., .
they're making a mi stak e!
Okay? Wh at you need to do i s decide
for you rself wh at you want,
You under stan d?
Exactly what you want.,,
and then I won't have to thr ow
every goddamn thi ng away!
Oh, my God!
I r eally think you n eed to be
by your self for a whi le.
Phyll is? Phyl li s?
Th ese shou Id be what h e wanted,
If ther e's a pr oblem,
h e can call me,
But we will see you ton ight?
The party.
My brother invited you, right?
No, he di dn 't,
,
Signorina, ny brother
wants you to come,
But someti mes h e's too...
You kn ow?
Yes,
You come tonight,
It woul d be our honor,
- Thank you, but...
- No "but, '" Tonight, 8:00.
All ri ght, Thank you,
You I ook beautifu I.
- I tri ed to call you,
- I was probably in the sh ower,
I h ave to talk to my br other
for one secon d, ok ay?
I'm gl ad you ar e her e,
- So, how"s everythi n g look?
- Good. Good.
Go ahead.
- What do you think?
- Mor e time.
- How much?
- 'Ti I it's don e,
Hey, look.
Say formagglo!
Cristiano, come her e, please,
Go outside an d watch for Louis Prima,
I don't kn ow what h e look s I ik e.
Her e, Lik e that,
Okay, go.
He says, "Ah, it was the first day
with milk, '"
What you got th ere?
Help yourself to an ything you want,
Cristi an o, tak e care of my frien d,
Cristiano, right?
Do you have a car?
Here. Cheer s to you,
Eat thi s, Drink that,
Ah, the r eporter, Li sten.
Hel p your self to an ything you want,
I'll be back.
- I'm Jamison. Daily Sun.
- How ar e you?
Are you "El Segundo '"?
Gabriel la's friend?
- Secondo, Ni ce to meet you,
- GI ad to know you. Is Mr, Pri ma her e?
No, he i s not her e yet,
but he will be h ere soon. Don't worry,
- Is Gabriell a her e?
- No, she's not h ere, Please, come i n,
Can I fix you a dri n k? Somethin g?
Have an appetizer.
I don 't think you can say,
"'lf I do this, th en that wi II h appen, "
You can, but if you do th at
al I th e ti me, then where would you be?
Per sonally, I think, nowh er e.
Th is i s focacci a, which is ni ce,
We mak e that, my b. Other an d I.
This is a nice cr ostini, Excuse me.
Don 't mean to touch with my fin gers.
Thi s is n ice.
In side has olive oil and goat cheese.
- That fl ower lady!
- What?
How ar e you? So nice to see you,
Th an k you for comi n g,
- You look beautiful,
- Th an k you,
Watch the stove.
- Bi g brother! Here you go.
- Th an k you,
How ar e you?
Look at you.
Oh, my God,
I'm so glad you are her e.
Now you can see wh er e go.,,
you r beautiful flower s,
Yes! Did you see behind th e bar?
They'r e beautiful,
It's a lovely r estau rant.
I love all the pai ntings.
Oh, yes,
- Show th e lady!
- Oh, yes. Yes!
Well, we start h ere with thi s on e,
Her e, my aunt and nephews.
What a cr owd!
I bri n g someth ing for you,
You kn ow Gabri ell a, right?
Ph yll is, you 'r e a vision
of I oveliness,
Th ank you,
Phyl lis, you know Gabriella?
Gabriell a, Phyl li s,
Phyllis is Seco's fi an ce?
No, not quite,
Wh at ar e you waitin g for?
A sign fr om above?
- He is I ik e my mother,
- Come on! Am I. Ight?
I I ove this guy!
- Look at th at goddamn table!
- It's ni ce, right?
It's the Last "fucking'" Supper!
We ar e just waiting
for the guest of honor n ow.
Fu cking musicians! Forget about it,
Don't wo. Ry, he'll be h ere.
Wh ere's you r bother?
I'I I say h i.
I see h im! Hey, Primo!
Wait, I'I I come with you,
Anni e, I love that corsage!
Th ank you,
You kn ow Ann, yes?
Secondo. It will be fine.
,
Go, eh?
Is a party, n o?
Is fu n, Good,
- Oh. Mr, Fun!
,
- Go.
Come her e, come here.
- Don't worry, It's gonn a be fine,
- I'm n ot worri ed,
Have a little si p of my drin k,
Ch eers.
He pl ays the trumpet.
He sings,
They call h im "The Li p, '"
Wher e did you go?
- Just going to tak e test-drive,
- Be right back,
- Mor e Scotch?
- Her e, tak e the bottle.
,
It's a Fior entina sauce,
But qui ck, f. Esh. N ice. See?
Someti mes you can put i n cream,
if you li k e,
But not for me,
It's no good for my stomach,
My mother cook ed with cr eam,
everythi n g,
Have you ever been to Bol ogn a?
Oh, I tak e you someday ther e.
- I mean, you lik e cream?
- Yes,
Yes? I thought you do,
Well, you wil I love thi s place,
Bologna i s sad, a little.
The city is ol d,
OI d is ni ce, but is dark,
But the food!
They mak e th ere a dish cal led,
I isten, lasagna...
Lasagn a Bologn ese,
You can 't believe h ow good th is is.
When my uncl e, in Rome,
at this restaurant, when he mak e th is., .
you eat and th en you go and.,,
you have to kil I your self,
After you eat this,
you can't I ive!
Smell, Smell, Here.
- Is nice, huh?
- Th at smell s good,
Ok ay, this is done.
Now. Taste,
,
Taste.
Oh. My God.
- Is good, h uh? You li k e?
- Oh, ny God!
"Oh, my God'" i s right, see?
Now you know,
To eat good food
is to be close to God,
You know what they say?
To kn ow God...
- To have the kn owi n g?
- Kn owledge,
Th e kn owl edge of God
is the br ead of angels,
I'm n ever sur e what that means,
,
but i s tru e,
- Th an k you.
- Tak e deep breaths,
You know h ow th ey get you, these people?
Men? Boys?
They mak e you th ink they h ave secr ets
they will tell,
But th ey h ave nothi ng to tell,
And then they talk.
An d they talk, tal k and k eep talking.
An d wh at do they say?
- Noth ing.
- Ri ght.
And th en they smok e.
and th en they talk some more.
An d then th at"s that,
Have you ever been to the west?
Out west?
Yes,
Real ly? They say it's beautiful,
Yes, very beautifu I!
- A littl e too vast for me,
- Too what?
Vast. Spaciou s, Bi g,
- Oh, vast!
,
- Yeah,
- How do you feel?
- I feel better.
- Want a puff?
- Thanks,
So you prefer it h ere,
the east?
I do,
I see.
Maybe I shou Id go out west.
Fi n d a cowboy with a h orse.
Wh at do you think?
- A cowboy.
- Yeah, I want one.
,
Strong, silent, .,
li k e a statu e,
Cool, always th ere.
Cowboys ar e con sistent,
A girl went back to Na poli
Because she missed the scenery
The native dances
and the charming songs
But wait a mlnute
Something 's wrong
Ay, mambo
Mambo Italiano
Go, go, go
You mixed-up Siciliano
All you Calabrese
Do the mambo like a-crazy
Well, ay. Mambo
No more tarantella
Ay, mambo
No more mo zzarella
Mambo Italiano
Try an enchilada
with the fish baccal a
Ay, mambo, I love-a how
you dance the rhumba
Phyl li s, what ar e you doing?
Oh. Gabriel la. H ell o,
,,
How ar e you? Hi, hi,
What a fucki n g ri de!
Come on, Bobby, I et's get a drink.
And ay. Citrull '
You don 't-a have to go to school
Just thlnk-a with a beat bambino
It's-a like a vino
You 're-a good looking
but you don 't know what 's cooking
Ay, mambo
Mambo Italiano
Oh. Ho, ho
,
You mixed-up Sicillano
It 's-a so "delish '"
everybody can capisci how to mambo
Italiano
Primo's cooking!
Let's eat!
Thi s i s the gr een on e that my br other
has nade especially for you,
Th is i s pesto, thi s is regular ri sotto
an d thi s is seafood ri sotto,
- That one,
- Thi s on e?
- Can I come back for more?
- No, absolutely not.
- Do you thi n k he'I I mak e it?
- Louis Prima?
he better mak e it,
He don't know what he's missin g,
Eat! Taste it, You'll lik e it.
No. Save th is one
,
for Lou is Prima, Ok ay?
- Maybe too h ot stil I.
- No, n o, we have to serve now.
No, wait!
,
Cut it at the table.
- I worry it's gonna fall apart.
- Th at's wh at I say, is it too hot?
No, we don't h ave ti me. Let's go,
Cristiano, open the door,
- What is th at?
- A tim pano.
It's a secr et reci pe they br ought
fr om their h ometown.
I on ly hear d about it.
My God! Damn it!
Goddamn it, I shoul d kil I you.
Thi s is so fucki n g good
I should kill you.
Paradise!
What s the matter?
My moth er was such a terrible cook,
Listen,
I'm gonna try and get someone out here
to write a revi ew,, .
but that could tak e awh ile,
I can't do a story about Louis Prima
because he di dn 't sh ow up,
But you wer e ri ght.
It was the best ever,
- Th an k you,
- I gotta go.
Wh at time do you have?
It's 3:00,
Good ni ght, Good ni ght,
On e, Two.
Thr ee, Now, car efu I., .
,
becau se if it's too mu ch wi n d, .,
they fall over,
An d they go up,
Isn't that beautifu I?
Listen,
I don 't kn ow what to say,
I'm so fu cking embarr assed!
I'n sorry.
But you know wh at?
These people had
a gr eat. Goddamn ti me.
You shoul d be pr oud I ik e hel I.
Everything wi II be ok ay,
hey, we talk tomorr ow,
Yeah.
You cannot be caught
with th e ri n g,
You mu st I ie and cheat
an d swear and ki ck, Come,
Stan d in a cir cl e,
Ok ay, everyone tak e the strin g,
So you're not supposed to know.
You try n ot to h ave it,
Trick th e person.
Everyon e stand i n a big, r ound...
Good,
- Ann, you start. You go in th e middle.
- Me?
Close your eyes.
- Are we supposed to say we have it?
- You must lie.
Where ar e you going?
- I gotta go, I'm going.
- Gabri ell a, stick ar ound.
,
- We'r e waiti n g for Louis Prima,
- Don't hold your breath,
What? What do you want with me?
Wh y don 't you tel I your n ew fri en d
about who's comin g toni ght, hmm?
What? What do you say?
Tell h im,
He work ed very hard.
Come on!
What?
No, we should go n ow,
Let's go,
- Tell your new friend. Come on.
- Come on, let s go,
No one i s coming toni ght,
No on e was ever coming,
Phyl lis, come here!
What ar e you doin g?
Come her e!
Come her e, You'll catch col d,
I want to talk to you.
Oh, my.
What are you doin g?
Phyl lis, come here.
I want to talk to you, Come, pl ease,
I was just upset
and she was just...
Don 't do that!
I hate that!
- Can I just talk to you?
- No, I'm not here anymore.
He's n ot coming.
What?
Pascal never call ed,
What do you mean?
Pascal never called
so h e's not comin g,
- How do you know thi s?
- Gabri ella,
Pascal li ed to you.
He I ies.
Wher e is everybody?
I shoul d go say somethi ng,
- Come on,
- No, No mor e,
Ju st I isten,
- Good.
- Good?
You go.
I'm going to stay her e,
No, n o, You go, ok ay?
Fuck hi m and fuck you.
You go back,
You let somebody el se
tak e care of you, ok ay?
Ok ay, okay, good,
Go, Stay, Go, go, Stay,
You! You ar e the one!
You ar e the one!
What do you think?
Do you th ink th ings ar e so simple?
Do you think it is ju st I ik e th is
and lik e that, and that's all it is?
,
Is that what you thin k?
We were dyi n g
and I did something!
For two years,
I have been doin g it all!
- You h ave don e nothing!
- Wh at ar e you doing?
I ask ed f or your h elp,
I n eed you to sacrifice.
And what do you do?
You give to me n othing! Noth ing!
Is that what you thi n k?
That I give you n oth ing?
Yes, th at i s wh at I thi n k,
Hey, Secondo, gr eat party, even if...
You know.
- Can I tak e you somewh er e?
- No, no, Thanks, though.
Ok ay, see you.
I used to play at one time,
You ruined me.
- Because of a woman?
- Oh, pl ease, Seco, be seri ous,
Wh y?
Because I wanted to save you.
And then we woul d go with you?
Where el se wou Id you go?
What I di d,
,
I di d out of r espect,
He's a gr eat i n vestment, your brother,
You too, of cou rse.
You will never h ave my brother,
He I ives in a worl d above you.
Wh at he has and what h e is
is rare.
You ar e n othing.
I'm a busi nessman.
I'm an ything I need to be
at an y ti me.
Tell me, what exactly ar e you?
Ar e you h ungry?
I'll do it,
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org