Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
♪ I just kept hoping ♪
♪ The way would become clear ♪
♪ I spent all this time ♪
♪ Trying to play nice ♪
♪ And found my way here ♪
♪ See, I've been having me
a real hard time ♪
♪ But it feels so nice ♪
♪ To know I'm gonna be all right ♪
♪ And I've been having me
a real fun time ♪
♪ And it feels so nice ♪
♪ To know I'm gonna be all right... ♪
Hey.
Can I get a water, please?
Thank you.
Hi. Is Abby all right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All in all, it's, yeah, great.
Thank you.
And it's a pretty smooth... six days?
- Yeah?
- So...
- Other than our little...
- What?
Well, our little, uh, dust-up.
Oh, you mean my dust-up.
No, I didn't say that.
Well, you didn't have to say that.
I was wrong to question your decision
to cancel the SAT tutor, I guess?
I didn't think you were wrong.
Because who cares if Abigail
doesn't get her scores up
or if she goes to a college that
requires more than a pulse.
Okay. Do you see what you're doing here?
I came here, actually,
to propose that you and me
and Bonnie and Ed have dinner together.
You wanted to propose that?
Yeah, you know, to discuss
the transitional parenting
paradigm of Abigail.
Make sure there aren't
any glaring "ch-asms,"
like, uh... you know,
like this whole tutor thing.
"To discuss the transitional
parenting paradigms
to make sure we don't have
any glaring chasms?"
Who talks like that, Nathan?
Why don't you just say
this is Bonnie's idea?
Yeah, okay, yeah. It's Bonnie's idea.
Personally, I think the idea of us
all getting along is ridiculous.
But that's one of the things that
really defines being a husband,
is your willingness to go along
with your wife's fucked-up ideas.
- Give me a break.
- Like, by way of example,
when I was with you. You remember?
I paid $9,000
to ground the house against
electromagnetic fields
so that we all didn't get brain cancer.
Or the time when we went camping?
I said, "Fucking mosquitos
bite the shit out of me."
Doesn't matter as long as our skin
doesn't come in touch with DEET.
What is your point, Nathan?
My point is I did a lot of
fucked-up things in our marriage,
a lot of hoops I jumped through for you,
and now I'm doing those
same things for Bonnie.
Personally, I'd rather shove
an electric eel up my ass
and have it gnaw through my intestines
than sit down with you
and fucking Psycho Ed.
But you know what, I'll do it,
'cause that's the kind of fucking
fucked-up fuckshit father I am.
How about that?
The man is losing his mind.
Can you believe it?
So, did you schedule the dinner?
Yes! I mean, a couples dinner?
He would've never done that
when we were together.
Never! But for Bonnie,
he's Mr. Fucking Sacrifice.
Why don't you bottle up
some of that anger
- and put it to good use?
- What do you mean?
Mm, I think I could use you and Joseph
at the meeting with the mayor tomorrow.
Joseph can speak
to the content of the show
and we could use your passion.
I cannot possibly thank you
enough for this, Celeste.
I haven't done anything yet.
- Thank you.
- I'm actually having fun.
Thank you, thank you, thank
you, thank you, thank you.
Anyway, you wanna meet at Blue Blues
in the morning after drop-off?
- I'll brief you.
- Okay. 'Night, honey.
Mm-hmm. Night-night.
Briefing?
The mayor is trying to shut down
this production of "Avenue Q"
at the community theater
because it's not appropriate, so...
I told Madeline I'd help her out.
Helping her out how?
Legal help?
Yeah.
Are you practicing law again?
Not practicing law,
just going to a meeting.
Oh, because this is the town of Monterey,
you can't afford to hire an attorney?
The town of Monterey is the one that's
trying to shut the production down.
Okay.
How come we didn't have
a conversation about this?
If you were here long enough
to have a conversation.
After the talk shifts from the kids,
you're off packing your bag
for another business trip.
You gonna hit me now?
Do you want me to hit you, Celeste?
Here we go again.
Sometimes I wonder.
Ed?
♪ One night with you ♪
♪ Is what I'm now praying for... ♪
No, no, no, no, no.
♪ The things that we two could plan ♪
♪ Would make my dreams come true... ♪
Okay, honey, you're gonna wake up Chloe.
♪ Just call my name... ♪
Okay, Ed.
♪ And I'll be right by your side... ♪
- That's great.
- ♪ I want your sweet helping hand... ♪
- Let's wrap it up.
- ♪ My love's too strong to hide ♪
The neighbors actually heard them
practicing for the talent show.
They came to Trivia Night
with their game faces on.
We're talking about
viciously competitive people.
You really are a nutjob, you know that?
Yeah, but I'm your nutjob.
That's true, as opposed to...
What?
That meeting with Nathan, honey?
He wants us all to have dinner.
You, me, Bonnie, Nathan,
all getting together,
exchanging niceties
and, what, group talking
our parenting skills?
Well, could be a good idea.
Are you kidding me? It's fucking Bonnie.
She probably just wants to show
off and serve us organic quinoa
with her kale she raised in her
sustainable vertical garden,
probably while she was meditating.
So help me God, if she so much as
teaches me how to peel a potato,
I'm gonna go for her fucking throat.
That might not be a good idea.
Oh, what about "Suspicious Minds"?
"Pocketful of Rainbows"!
Oh, no. Honey, you've gotta go to bed.
You never sleep.
You need to pick a song
no one else will sing.
- Well, it's not even listed, honey.
- Exactly.
Ed.
- ♪ I don't worry ♪
- ♪ Worry ♪
- ♪ Whenever skies are gray above ♪
- ♪ Above ♪
- ♪ Got a pocketful of rainbows ♪
- ♪ Rainbows ♪
♪ Got a heart full of love... ♪
♪ Of love... ♪
It's kind of nice.
♪ Got a pocketful of rainbows ♪
♪ We're gonna stay up all night ♪
♪ And not go to school tomorrow... ♪
- Am I dreaming right now?
- Yeah!
Ziggy.
You were sleepwalking, baby.
What happened between you and my dad?
You can tell me.
You guys met one night
and then that was it?
He was gone?
Yeah.
You don't have to look for him for me,
if that's what you're doing.
I'm okay, Mom.
We'll be fine.
Scoot over.
I love you.
I love you more.
I said it first.
I mean it more.
Ha.
I love you more than
all of those stars combined.
infinity times infinity.
I'm concerned.
About?
Your stress level.
I'm fine.
Well, you couldn't get pregnant.
When you were working, the doctors
all agreed that it had to do with...
I'm not trying to get pregnant.
No, I'm just saying, the anxiety.
Yeah, I know my history.
I'm not trying to get pregnant.
I'm just trying to help out a friend.
What's the big problem, hmm?
Why is it such a big deal for you?
It's not.
I'm just looking out for you, Sparkles.
If you go to pieces again, who's
gonna put you back together?
Madeline?
I'm the one who's always there for you.
Always will be.
It's just difficult
when you try to control me.
Yeah, well, the idea
of you resuming your career...
I'm not trying to resume my career.
I want to have another baby.
- A daughter.
- What?
It's too late.
- You know I can't.
- It's not too late.
- Hey.
- What are you...
Hey.
Can you imagine?
Having a little girl of our own?
Being your husband,
Max and Josh's dad...
Sometimes I wish we had 10 kids.
Well, that was sounding romantic.
Let's have that little girl tonight.
Come on, I've got a busy day.
Come on. What are you do...
- Hmm?
- I gotta get up early.
Yeah?
Yeah, you're probably right.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's just call it a night, then.
Oh!
You think you're so
irresistible, don't you?
Huh?
I love you so much.
Yes, Ed likes to dress up in costumes.
- Presley?
- Yeah.
I think he has a fetish or something.
One night, I came home and he
had a full vampire costume on,
with fangs and everything,
and an accent.
And I think he thought it was sexy
and it would spice up our sex life.
- It didn't?
- Well, I mean, it was funny.
Uh, I don't know.
I don't know... I don't know why
I'm talking about sex so much.
Tom? When you get a chance, honey,
can I get something puffy
with chocolate on it?
- You got it.
- Thank you.
Why don't you mean to talk about sex?
Mm, no reason.
Because I was raped?
Well, I mean, I'm... I'm
trying to be sensitive, honey.
I... I don't always know
the right thing to say.
- But I certainly don't judge you.
- I know.
It's actually really weird.
Ever since I told you about Ziggy's dad,
it's like this thing that's
been happening to my body.
Like it's wanting to wake
up again or something.
- Oh.
- I always knew
that my reaction to that
night had been too big.
I pretended like it meant nothing,
so of course it came to mean everything.
But it's like I had
to say those stupid words
that he said to me out loud to you
for them to lose their power.
Like keeping them a secret
helped them retain their power.
So ever since then, I just keep
finding myself looking at men.
- It's weird.
- Really?
But not in, like, a sexual way.
Like more just
in a appreciative way, maybe?
- Really?
- Sensual way. Mm-hmm.
Like that guy's arm over
there, with the tattoos.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know. Then my mind takes over
and takes me back to that stupid night.
There's no way you could've known
he was such a fucking sociopath.
Fuck, yeah. Psychopath.
- Dickhead.
- Asshole.
- Abominable pig.
- I'd kill him if I could.
Well, I mean, I wouldn't say that
out loud, like, in public spaces.
I'm just kidding.
Oh, my God.
Have you really thought any
more about counseling, or...?
No.
I have been thinking
about something, though.
Don't get mad at me.
I just... I don't know.
It's really hard.
- I think maybe we need to move back.
- No!
Well, Ziggy's just not happy here.
- I can tell.
- No, honey.
- Hey! How we doing?
- Hi.
Is this your go-to meeting outfit?
- Yes, this is it.
- Wow!
- Is there a cape under there?
- Would you stop it?
You'll just have to wait and see,
won't you?
Mm, we are gonna win.
So...
Ugh, in breaking news, madam just told me
that she's thinking about moving.
- I'm just thinking about it.
- What? No.
No freaking way.
Come on, don't give in.
Ziggy didn't do it.
Do not let them get to you.
I'm not giving in.
I just... I don't know.
I need to do what's best for my kid.
I don't know what that is, but...
What about what's best for us?
- We would miss you.
- Madeline.
We would miss you.
You're gonna make me cry.
And we're gonna win this case,
I'm telling you.
I think the mayor is gonna
like your... argument.
- Would you stop it?
- Ha ha!
We've had who knows
how many orientations.
Nobody ever got choked.
Who are the new variables here?
Jane Chapman and her son Ziggy.
Whose eyes are abnormally far apart.
A sign of a sociopath.
Are we gonna make some changes today?
That's right.
We're gonna start with uppercuts.
And one.
Extend those arms.
Two, one. First position.
One, and serve the platter.
In, out. Out.
And lift.
♪ I feel unhappy... ♪
And whip.
Whip, whip!
Other side.
♪ I have lost the best friend ♪
♪ That I've ever had... ♪
- Hi.
- Uppercuts.
God, I just love sweat on, uh, women.
Sorry, that was
more of a general observation.
I'm going to assume that you're not
here to talk about physical fitness.
Yeah, Madeline told me
about the dinner you and
Nathan are proposing,
which I think is a
potentially a good idea.
But...?
Well, Nathan and Madeline...
that's a pretty volatile cocktail.
- What about you, Ed?
- What? What?
You've been a little
aggressive as of late.
Yeah, well, I'm only trying
to be supportive of Madeline.
She was kind of abandoned by her dad.
He only made time for her brothers.
And she felt abandoned by
Nathan, and now Abigail.
It's like a triple whammy.
She's in a pretty fragile state.
You know, we all have baggage, Ed.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
It doesn't help, by the way,
that you're this
seemingly perfect step-mom.
Anyway, we're gonna do this dinner,
but I think it'll be up to you
and me to keep things civil.
- I hear you.
- All right.
Oh, also, it's probably best
if you don't give Madeline
any kind of advice,
like how to peel a potato.
Okay.
♪ Otter Bay ♪
♪ Together we stand strong ♪
♪ Come on and sing along ♪
♪ Beautiful ♪
♪ We learn arithmetic ♪
♪ Science and aquatics ♪
♪ Otter in the bay! ♪
Amabella.
You weren't singing. Is there a reason?
No. I just didn't feel like it.
Oh, you typically love the sing-alongs.
Seems like something's
a little wrong, sweetie.
Are you sure you're not
upset about something?
You can tell me.
I promise I will keep it a secret.
How are things with you and Ziggy?
Fine. He's nice. We're friends.
That's great!
What do you and Ziggy
like to do together?
We just like playing and stuff.
And he's nice to you?
Yes.
Amabella...
is somebody still hurting you?
I found Ziggy's father.
You found him?
Well, I think I found him,
but it's Saxon Baker.
He's an interior designer
in San Luis Obispo.
Hold on, didn't she say
his name was Saxon Banks?
- Well, I think maybe he only gave
- Maddie!
his real first name.
She said he was an architect,
but sometimes interior designers
say they're architects.
Oh, this is not good.
Thanks so much for helping us out,
but I'm... I'm having
second thoughts about this.
- What?
- Look, even should we win this battle,
we make an enemy of the mayor's office.
- We have all of our funding!
- Long-term, it's not a good idea.
And we're starting in two weeks, Joseph.
But what about the next production
and the one after that?
Listen to me, do you think "Avenue
Q" is worth fighting for?
Yeah.
Well, then what are we talking about?
The future of the theater itself.
If we piss off the mayor...
and I've been told
he pisses off easily...
I can keep it civil.
Oh, no.
Or maybe not.
Look, I'm not looking to, like,
chill artistic expression.
I hear it's a great play.
That said, puppets fuck.
We can't have puppets
fucking in Monterey.
- May... may I be heard?
- There is one scene, and one scene only,
where two of the puppets simulate sex.
There's no nudity.
Yeah, well, naked puppets
don't bother me.
Fucking puppets, on the other
hand, well, it's vulgar.
Even if it were,
you'd still have to prove
that it has no legal,
artistic, or literary value.
I'm not talking about legals.
We're gonna have to talk about the...
To shut down a show simply because
it makes you uncomfortable
two weeks before it's about to
open, I don't think that that's...
Okay, look, look.
I'm new to the whole controversy, okay?
It's just been brought to my attention,
mostly by concerned parents,
so I'm bringing a fresh eye
to this thing, you know?
You can tell me I'm full of shit.
It wouldn't be the first.
But from my perspective,
the whole point of the theater
is to bring community together.
- You know, to entertain.
- Mm-hmm.
To have an affirming effect on society.
This thing here?
- It's already divisive.
- True.
And I'm certainly not
trying to connect the two,
but, uh, there are zoning laws
that prohibit sex shops
and strip clubs...
Oh, please. Come on.
- This is hardly that.
- Yes, but...
This play deals with love,
and racism, and same-sex marriage,
which are all redeeming themes,
conversations this community
should be having.
I mean, and if you want
to continue to have...
Puppets fuck.
You are adorable.
May I speak for a moment?
Not as a member of the
Monterey Planning Board,
but, really, as a mom?
I think we can agree that the
world has gone to hell, right?
I mean, we're living in a
time where our little ones
have lockdown drills at school
because of gun violence.
They don't even feel safe
in their own classroom.
So what if we brought back
a little good old-fashioned nostalgia?
You know, a little "Sound of Music"?
I mean, we're Monterey, right?
So, what do we want to say?
And maybe the question
isn't "What is this play?"
but "Who are we?"
Hmm.
I take your point. It's a good one.
- Right.
- We, uh... we all have small children
and this is the village that
we've chosen to raise them in.
And, um, I would say,
among other things,
I hope we're open-minded.
I mean, I think what draws
a lot of people to Monterey
is its progressiveness.
But opinions aside,
legally, you've already lost.
The California Constitution
goes way further than the federal
one to protect the First Amendment.
But to answer your question, Renata...
"Who are we?"
I don't think we want
to become synonymous
with suppression and prior restraint.
We're going to face accusations
of being anti-American
and anti-free speech.
I mean, that's not the politics that
you've been practicing, Mayor Bartley.
So I would say there are
bigger black eyes
than putting on a controversial musical,
especially ones that have won Tonys.
Stick that up your tight ass, bitch!
You were fucking brilliant!
- Oh, really?
- Um, yeah.
It's actually kind of annoying
that you look like that
and you're smart and educated
and intelligent and sympathetic.
You even had Cruella agreeing
with you in the end.
Did you see her face? I mean, come on!
Yeah, thanks.
What?
- What's wrong, honey?
- Nothing, nothing. I'm sorry. God...
Oh, stop it, Celeste!
I don't know where this is coming from.
I really don't.
Well, maybe you do, honey.
It's just for six years
I've been wiping runny noses,
organizing playdates, doing, uh...
everything to be a good mom, you know?
And today I felt alive, I felt good.
- Is that crazy?
- No.
I feel so ashamed for saying this,
but being a mother,
it's not enough for me.
It's just not. It's not even close.
It's evil, right? I'm evil.
- I've said it out loud.
- You are not evil.
- I am. This is...
- I'm not gonna let you say that.
- What, you think it? Do you, ever?
- Yes.
I got so consumed
with Abigail and Chloe.
- Their lives were everything...
- Mm-hmm.
...that I almost forgot I had my own.
And... and I just had to do something,
so I decided to volunteer
at the theater.
I'm not a performer. I'm not a director.
I didn't know what to do, but it just
made me feel like I was doing something.
I wanted more, you know?
I want more of that! That feeling.
- 'Cause that made me feel alive, too!
- Mm-hmm.
I want more!
Okay.
- Jesus.
- Oh.
- And you know what?
- What?
- You're gonna be a lawyer again.
- No.
I mean, I have never seen you like that.
For four years I've known you, and...
your face looked different,
your body changed.
- You miss it.
- Mm-hmm.
You're right.
I fucking miss it!
Whoo!
Thank you for agreeing to meet me.
I would've asked you
to come to the school,
but it's kind of a fish bowl there.
People can gossip.
What's going on?
I have reason to suspect,
and only suspect,
that Amabella Klein
is still being bullied,
and that Ziggy may be the culprit.
I haven't seen anything,
but I feel certain
that something
is going on with Amabella.
She's made no implications.
In fact she claims that she
and Ziggy are friends.
And my personal experience of Ziggy...
he is a sweet little boy.
Yeah, so then where
is all this coming from?
Well, I sensed some tension
between them this morning.
Amabella was visibly upset
about something.
I observed Ziggy looking at her.
And from my vantage point,
he appeared to know
exactly what she was upset about.
Maybe he saw her being bullied.
Maybe he was concerned for her.
That could very well be,
though it wasn't my take.
Look, if I think that a child
is being physically
or emotionally abused,
it is my duty to go forward with that,
first and foremost, to the parents.
What fucking evidence do you have?
Jane, believe it or not,
I'm actually on your side here.
No, you know what?
If you were on my side,
you would not go to Amabella's parents.
That is only going to make things worse.
You would find another solution.
This is ridiculous.
Okay.
Do you have any reason
to suspect that Ziggy could be violent?
- No.
- Maybe something from his past.
No!
Ziggy is a sweet, docile young boy.
He's never hurt a fly.
Wouldn't someone have fucking
seen this, for God's sakes?
They're in a classroom!
Okay, you know what?
Maybe you're gonna think
this is way off-book, but...
♪ Everyone's a little bit racist ♪
♪ It's true ♪
♪ But everyone is just about as racist ♪
♪ As you... ♪
♪ If we all could just admit... ♪
Yeah, that's all I need.
No, that's perfect.
Thank you. Yeah, yeah.
- Isn't she amazing?
- Amazing!
I cannot believe
she's doing it for free.
She's my best friend.
She'll do whatever I ask.
- What if it goes to court?
- It's not gonna go to court.
That is a done deal. It's amazing.
You have nothing to worry about.
You're so good to me.
I believe in you.
- Oh, my God.
- I know, out of nowhere.
- But...
- I'm still shaking.
One minute we're talking,
and then the next...
Oh, no. Uh-oh.
...he puts his tongue in my throat.
This is assault. He assaulted you.
Mm.
- I mean, I might've kissed him back.
- What?
It was like a reflex, you know?
Somebody kisses you, you kiss them back.
I might have grabbed his ass.
I don't know.
- What?
- It just all happened so fast.
And the next thing I know,
he has his hand in my shirt.
Or was it my hand in his shirt?
- Oh!
- What? It was a reflex!
- Ugh!
- So you're saying the thing's mutual.
No, he jumped me
and then he yelled at me.
I'm in love with you. You hear me?
I'm in love with you, Madeline.
I have been...
For months?
So I slapped him.
What?
This is not funny, Celeste.
I'm a married woman and
he forced himself on me.
Okay, "forced himself"
maybe is the wrong word,
but I hated every minute of it.
I didn't.
- Afternoon, ladies.
- Hi, Perry.
Hi. What am I missing?
- Nothing.
She's always laughing at me.
She's my best audience,
and apparently I'm a very funny girl.
Uh-huh.
- How fun was it in court today?
- It wasn't court.
She was incredible, Perry.
You should've seen her.
She was amazing.
She doesn't know when to stop laughing.
Oh, I kind of already knew that.
It wasn't court, it was a meeting.
And it went very well
and it's done now, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm.
If my baby makes up
her mind to do something,
you better get out of her way.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey! My little men!
- I made an Ollie today!
- Wow!
I made a noseslide!
I don't even know what that is,
but it's really exciting.
Mom, did you film all this?
- No. No, I didn't.
- I want to show you, Dad. Come on!
Incredible! I want to see it,
but let's do it after dinner.
Just gonna chill
with Mommy for a second.
- And funny Maddie.
- Go on, baby. Go.
All right, all right, all right.
There will be wine waiting for you.
We're gonna go work
on our noseslides now.
- Bye, Daddy.
- Bye. All right, outside.
- He's such a great dad.
- Mm-hmm.
So... what really happened?
♪ One pill makes you larger ♪
♪ And one pill makes you small ♪
♪ And the ones that Mother gives you ♪
♪ Don't do anything at all ♪
♪ Go ask Alice ♪
♪ When she's 10 feet tall ♪
♪ And the white knight
is talking backwards ♪
♪ And the Red Queen's
off with her head ♪
♪ Remember what the dormouse said ♪
♪ Feed your head ♪
♪ Feed your head... ♪
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, buddy.
What's the matter?
Let me see. Let me see.
There's no blood.
Take a deep breath. Come here.
Should we go to the hospital?
I think we should call the ambulance.
I think we need to call 911.
- No.
- I think we should.
Should I call the tooth fairy?
- No.
- Or Santa Claus?
I'm sorry, buddy.
The last time we had pizza
and we went to the zoo,
you told me we were moving to Monterey.
What now?
You're gonna go see
a child psychologist.
I think he plans on signing
up for a class, that's all.
Did he hit on you at all?
What did he say?
Just that it should fall to me and him
to keep the peace at this dinner.
I don't disagree.
Did he, um... did he say
anything off at all
or cross you in any way?
'Cause I'd love to have
a reason to pop him one.
Nathan Carlton.
I'm saying the guy's off, Bonnie.
Come on, admit it.
The whole point of this dinner
is so we can all get along, okay?
- Not so you can pop him one.
- The guy's off.
At some point, boundaries
are gonna have to be set.
Hey. Hey, where you going?
- I'm going to Becky's.
- Becky?
Wait, is she the stupid one?
Your mom's always nagging me about
letting you hang out with stupid people.
- Dad!
- Well, she's still upset about the tutor.
- Hey, what... what do you have there?
- Nothing.
What are you carrying, darling?
- I'm...
- Nothing!
I can check my bar.
What?
You need to relax.
We don't want anyone
getting hurt, do we?
You know, we can always move.
We don't have to live in Monterey.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You wanna move?
Okay, first of all,
Skye loves it here a lot.
Second of all, we're never gonna
find public schools this good.
And third, what about Abigail?
She goes back with her mom?
She'll just move away with us.
That'll be the last straw for ex-thing.
Okay. All right.
- A man's allowed to fantasize...
- Stop!
What you doing?
Nothing, just staring at the sunset,
thinking how lucky we are to
have that in our face every day.
That is not what you were thinking.
Abby know you go on her Facebook page?
Probably.
I leave comments sometimes,
though under an alias.
What's your alias?
God.
So, you went to visit Bonnie
at her studio?
Wow.
No secrets in this town.
I was thinking about doing a sit-up
and wanted to get her advice.
Went to talk about the dinner,
how to best avoid friction.
Or animosity.
- Violence?
- Exactly how psychotic do you think I am?
Mm.
Come on.
You doing okay, Maddie?
Tell me. Tell me.
I'll make you feel good, baby.
I just feel like I'm...
losing control a little bit.
Of?
What I am.
How so?
I don't know.
You don't know?
♪ Do you need me ♪
♪ Like I need you? ♪
♪ I'm crying from wanting you ♪
♪ Make me forget ♪
♪ The pain that you caused ♪
♪ Understanding is a great thing ♪
♪ If it comes from the heart... ♪
I love you.
There's nothing like
the sound of crunching cereal
in the morning.
Wow!
Not too summery?
No, it looks incredible.
It's funny how clothes always
seem to do that on you.
You're sweet.
What's the occasion?
I have a meeting with the
attorney representing the town.
- Another meeting, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
I think we're gonna settle it today.
Yeah?
What if it doesn't settle?
Oh, well, we'd probably go to court,
but it would just be a one-off.
They really don't have any grounds.
So, a court appearance now, huh?
Probably not, but what's the big deal?
Well, the big deal
is that you lied to me.
You said it'd be one meeting
yesterday, and then it'd be over with.
- I never said that.
- Now you're going to court?
I said I thought
it would go away quickly,
and I still believe that it will.
I don't want you doing this.
Well, it's not your fucking call.
Mom?
Okay, let's go, sweetie.
Hey, champ.
- Hi, Dad.
- Have a great day.
We're gonna be late.
Come on. Quick, quick.
Let's go.
Bye.
Ms. Chapman?
Come on in.
We had a nice conversation.
He's a... he's a very smart little guy.
Yeah.
Please...
have a seat.
I, uh... I can see that you're nervous,
so I'm just gonna cut
right to the punch line.
I... I do not think Ziggy is a bully.
I brought up the incident that you
had mentioned at orientation,
and he made it very clear it wasn't him.
And I'd be surprised if he's lying.
If so, he's...
he's the most accomplished
liar I've ever seen.
And frankly, he doesn't show
any of the classic signs
of a bullying personality.
He's not narcissistic.
And he certainly demonstrates
empathy and sensitivity.
Sorry.
Are you sure?
Pretty sure.
I definitely would like to see
him for another appointment.
I think he's suffering
from a lot of anxiety
and I... I believe that there is...
there's a lot he didn't
share with me today.
And I wouldn't be surprised
to learn that he himself
is being bullied at school.
Ziggy?
I could be wrong,
but I wouldn't be shocked.
My guess is that it's verbal
and that some smart kid
has found his weak spot.
He also brought up his father,
who, believe it or not,
he thinks might be Darth Vader.
What?
Children often get caught halfway
between fantasy and... and reality.
And he's only six.
And I asked him if the two of you
talk much about his father.
He said it upset you
and that you're not
saying much about him.
Yeah, it's very complicated, so...
He said that be aware
that if we're talking
to my mom about my dad,
that she's gonna get
a funny look on her face.
So I take it that Ziggy's father
isn't exactly a good guy.
No, not exactly.
And I assume that Ziggy's never met him.
Yeah, no, he never will.
Well, as I said, I think you have
a caring, sweet
little boy on your hands.
But I would like to see him again.
Okay.
Wanna see him?
- Ziggy?
- Hi.
Look, Mom, a giant Harry the Hippo.
Maddie.
- What are you doing here?
- To talk to you.
Have you been following me?
- No, I haven't been following you.
- Oh, my God.
I wanna talk to you about
what I did at the theater.
You can't do this out of nowhere!
It was unacceptable, inexcusable.
That said, it didn't happen in a vacuum.
What do you mean?
You know what I mean, Madeline. Come on.
What happened a year ago
was an accident.
I told you that was a mistake
that's not gonna be repeated again.
Well, it was repeated several times.
Okay, stop. It's been erased.
Erased?
Yes, it didn't happen.
I am a happily married woman.
- Really?
- Yes!
You know what? You told me you agreed
that you were not gonna
open this up again.
Well, I don't agree anymore.
All right, you know what?
You stay in your life,
I'll stay in mine.
Hey!
My major concern is
as to how he might react.
To the idea that you
want to go back to work?
What did he say, his words exactly?
That he was afraid of me, um...
going through him.
Ah.
Yeah, so I'm...
I suppose I'm just worried
that he's gonna take it as a rejection.
You were working when he first met you
and when he fell in love
with you, right?
Yeah, but he, um...
he just likes me to be
at home in the house,
and we have the twins, and...
He's not that crazy about me
having too many friends.
He's just possessive.
That's who he is, so...
And I hoped that you'd have
some ideas on the best way
to communicate with him
about me going back to work.
No?
Well, I could certainly suggest
some communicative tools, but...
for me, the issue isn't how
best to talk to your husband,
but why you're afraid to.
I'm not, um... I'm not afraid.
I'm just...
I just want to have...
I suppose I want to communicate
it in the best way.
That's...
Okay.
I'm not afraid.
The week leading up to Trivia Night,
something changed with Celeste.
Still beautiful.
- But in her face...
- Her eyes...
Not a look like she could
actually kill somebody,
but, um...
Yeah, I think it's him.
If I heard his voice...
I can still remember his voice.
I can also still remember
that disgusting smell.
- Where did you say he lived?
- San Luis Obispo.
You're not thinking
about going down there?
- ♪ And you have no idea ♪
- ♪ Idea ♪
♪ No idea how it feels
to be on your own ♪
- ♪ In your own home ♪
- ♪ With the fucking phone ♪
- ♪ And the mother ♪
- ♪ of gloom in your bedroom ♪
♪ Standing over your head
with her hand in your head ♪
♪ I will not say I'm all right for you ♪
♪ With her hand in your head ♪
♪ I will not pretend,
I will not put on a smile ♪
♪ I will not say I'm all right for you ♪
♪ When all I wanted was to be good ♪
♪ To do everythin' in truth ♪
♪ You bloody, motherfuckin' asshole ♪
♪ Oh, you bloody,
motherfuckin' asshole ♪
motherfuckin' asshole... ♪
♪ Oh, you bloody,
motherfuckin' asshole ♪
♪ Oh, you bloody ♪
♪ I will not pretend,
I will not put on a smile ♪
♪ I will not say I'm all right for you ♪
♪ For you, 'ever you are ♪
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com