[EXHALES]
["I'VE GOT THE MUSIC IN ME" PLAYING]
♪ Ain't got no trouble in my life ♪
♪ No foolish dream to make me cry ♪
♪ I'm never frightened or worried ♪
♪ I know I'll always get by ♪
♪ I heat up ♪
♪ I cool down ♪
♪ When something gets in my way,
I go round it ♪
♪ Don't let life get me down ♪
♪ Gonna take life the
way that I found it ♪
♪ I got the music in me ♪
♪ Feel funky ♪
♪ I feel good ♪
♪ Gonna tell ya I'm
in the neighborhood ♪
♪ Gonna fly like a bird on a wing ♪
♪ Hold on to your hat, honey ♪
♪ Sing, sing ♪
♪ I heat up ♪
♪ I cool down ♪
♪ I got words in my head,
so I say them ♪
♪ Don't let life get me down ♪
♪ Catch ahold of my blues
and just play them ♪
- ♪ I got the music in me ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
♪ I got the music in me ♪
- ♪ I got the music in me ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
♪ I got the music in me ♪
- ♪ I got the music in me ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
- ♪ I got the music in... ♪
- [GASPING]
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
What the...
Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com
Mama needs an update.
Please, come on in.
So, what exactly
is the look we're going for in here?
Third-grade science fair?
Ooh, white girl corporate housing?
Or "she was quiet and kept to herself"?
Uh, I just don't spend a ton
of time in my apartment, and...
I can see why not. So, tell me.
What's the latest on this
musical power of yours?
Hear anybody new sing their feelings
out loud to you lately?
Thank you for asking, Mo.
I appreciate you being so concerned.
No, no, don't be flattered.
I view you more as a social experiment,
Like a rat running through a maze
or that one time that I
kissed a girl in college.
[SIGHS] To be honest, um,
my musical power isn't going so great.
Because of whatever this new ability is,
I discovered that all the
programmers at work hate me.
On the other hand, I was able to
communicate with my dad again
and bond with my office crush.
On the other hand,
my office crush has a fiancée,
and my best friend is in love with me.
Or at least thinks he's in love with me.
He did say, "I think I love you,"
when he sang, so hopefully
that'll just blow over.
I'm sorry. I got bored about three
"on the other hands" ago.
There just doesn't seem
to be any rhyme or reason
for when a song happens, Mo,
and I need to figure out
how to control it A.S.A.P.
so that it doesn't get in the way
of my job or my sporadic attempts
at something resembling a social life.
As a resident music expert,
I do have some
theories I'd like to try out.
I don't have time right now, okay?
I have to go meet my family, and then
I have to give a big speech
at work this morning.
I get it. You're busy. I'm busy, too.
I don't just wake up looking like this.
Can you meet me at The
Golden Gate Grind at lunch?
Mm, sounds bougie. I'm in.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
This is literally the
fourth doctor's office
I've been in this week.
I mean, between Dad
and all of Emily's prenatal exams,
I don't think I've seen
this many physicians
since you were convinced I
had A.D.D. when I was nine.
Oh, I love these things.
That's a cute jacket, Zoey.
Something big happening at work today?
I'm giving my first speech as
the new manager of engineering.
Wanna look good and be prepared
in case there's any curveballs.
Yeah, like, forgetting your own name.
I'm not making fun of her.
She actually wrote down, "Hi.
I'm Zoey," on here.
You are gonna do great. You always do.
Your dad and I are very proud of you.
Isn't that right, honey?
Oh, check out that
impressive hand movement.
I like to see that, Mitch.
Looks like you brought the whole
beautiful family with you today.
Dr. Hamara, we've noticed quite a few
positive changes in Mitch lately,
more facial movement,
more agility in his hands.
It seems like he's getting
a little bit better.
Uh, is that possible?
Let's take a look.
Follow the pen.
Squeeze my hands, will you?
Not so hard.
I've still got other
patients to see today.
And blink for me.
Here's the good news.
Mitch's new meds are working.
It's not a cure, but it might
slow the progressive
supranuclear palsy down,
give him a bit more
movement and dexterity.
I'd take advantage of it if you can.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Ah, Zoey, just the person
I wanted to see.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I'm not in trouble, am I?
What? No. Why does everyone
keep me asking that?
I think maybe it's
just a tone thing that...
Zoey, not a real question.
Look, since it's
your first week as manager,
I just wanted to check in.
How are you feeling?
And, more importantly, do you have
any new strategies
you'd like to implement?
Well...
after reading multiple books
and listening to
several popular podcasts
on how to be an effective leader, I...
Oh, my God. Bottom line, please.
I think we need more team spirit.
Okay, as long as you're not
talking about instituting,
like, crazy hat day or something,
in which case,
you should start sending
your résumé around.
No, no, nothing like that.
Look, I'm sure
you've got it all figured out,
but if you want some advice, here it is.
Be strong, be bold,
and keep your personal life to yourself.
Now get out of here.
- Oh.
- You have work to do. Jesus.
Thank you, Joan.
[WORKERS LAUGHING]
Um, guys,
coders, friends.
Hey.
Uh, I realized, as the manager,
I didn't give a big introductory speech,
so hello, best programming team ever.
Whoo! Best programming team ever!
Thanks, Max.
Um, I have lots of ideas
for how to make this a
positive work environment
and for how we can be
a harmonious, well-functioning team.
Uh, I thought we were
a well-functioning team,
hence the "best
programming team ever" part.
Good team can always
be better, can't it?
So, with that in mind,
I have two things to hand out.
First is a tiny memo with
some small suggestions
just to kick things off.
Tiny memo?
This thing has a table of contents.
Mm-hmm. And the second
are journals that I bought
for everyone for you to write down
your daily progress, inspirations.
Pick your color.
I have kept one myself every day
since my first day of the job.
Oh, cool. I've always wanted a diary.
Are you there, God? It's me, Tobin.
- [CHUCKLING]
- It's nice to write down
your inspirations and
ideas before they just...
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, no. No, no, no. Not right now.
♪ We go together ♪
♪ Better than birds of a feather,
you and me ♪
♪ We change the weather ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- Max.
♪ I'm feeling heat in December ♪
- ♪ When you're round me ♪
- Do you mind?
I'm kinda trying to give a
speech to the troops here.
♪ I've been dancing on top of cars ♪
♪ And stumbling out of bars ♪
♪ I follow you through the dark ♪
♪ Can't get enough ♪
This really isn't the best time.
♪ You're the medicine and the pain ♪
♪ The tattoo inside my brain ♪
♪ And, baby, you know it's obvious ♪
What's obvious?
- ♪ I'm a sucker for you ♪
- Oh, God, really?
♪ You say the word,
and I'll go anywhere blindly ♪
♪ I'm a sucker for you, yeah ♪
♪ Any road you take,
you know that you'll find me ♪
♪ I'm a sucker for all
the subliminal things ♪
♪ No one knows about you,
about you, about you ♪
♪ And you're making the typical me ♪
♪ Break my typical rules ♪
♪ It's true, I'm a sucker for you ♪
♪ Ooh whoo ooh, ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh, ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ It's true, I'm a sucker for you ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
I'm sorry. Uh, where was I?
I think you were explaining
what a journal is for.
Right. Um, how about
you read the section
on, um, better work efficiency
and how not to be
distracted in the workplace,
and we'll... reconvene later.
Go, team.
Whoo! Go, team!
You're yelling, bro.
Hey.
Hey, friendo.
Great news. I won the lottery.
- What?
- Well, the restaurant lottery.
I finally got us into that
fancy farm-to-table place.
You got us into Hand-Picked?
Yeah, Thursday night. Is it a date?
Is it a date?
What? No.
I just mean like, can you go?
Why are you acting weird?
Am I acting weirder than normal?
Hard to tell.
Anyway, they're doing this fancy,
uh, 10-course tasting meal and...
- Sounds romantic.
- Or delicious.
Do you know that they
make their own butter?
Apparently there's an actual
cow on the premises and...
What's happening over here?
Nothing. Not a thing.
Max, you remember Simon.
Uh, well, we haven't officially met yet,
but Zoey might have mentioned
your name once or twice.
Or... Well, it's a very common name.
You know, maybe it actually wasn't you.
You two must be close.
I feel like I see you
together all the time.
Just close the way friends are close
when they're friends with each other.
Yeah. What she said.
Listen, Zoey,
I've got a project for your team
I need to talk to you about.
Great. Let's go talk about it.
Max, let me just check my schedge,
and I'll get back to you
about that dinner ASAP.
Was that code for
"I've got some heavy
dad stuff to unpack?"
No. This is actually a real work thing.
- Oh.
- The marketing team
is gonna throw a
party here at the offices
to get the word out about
the new Sprq Point Watch.
And you want me to post about it,
'cause my Insta's blowing up right now.
Pretty sure I've got
at least 12 followers.
[LAUGHS] Uh, thanks,
but we already sent out beta versions
to various bloggers and
YouTubers and tech titans
months ago, so I think we're covered.
Okay, well, my followers
are gonna be devastated,
but, you know, do what you gotta do.
However, here's how
I could use your help.
I talked to Joan, and she said your team
could send push
notifications on the watch
as an official party invite?
Anything specific?
Blast to all the beta users
with the party details...
- Time, place, whatnot.
- I could do that.
Or...
we could have a little bit
more fun with it instead.
What'd you have in mind?
We could turn the whole thing
into a massive scavenger hunt.
- Oh.
- Um, we could push live clues
to everyone's watches.
Taking them to different
landmarks all around the city.
We then merge them into even
bigger groups as they go,
and, once they've
converged into a critical mass,
the final clue will lead
them here for a total rager.
- Boo-yah!
- [OBJECTS SHATTER]
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. Just a major
humanitarian award I won.
Super sentimental.
- No biggie.
- Mm-hmm.
Believe it or not, I didn't really
play any sports growing up.
I'm not surprised by that information.
I gotta say, it is nice to
talk to you about something
other than dead and dying dads for once.
That reminds me,
I actually got some good
news about my father today.
The new drug he's on seems to
be having some positive effects.
That's amazing, Zoey. I love that.
What does that mean?
It means a tiny bit more mobility
and a few more facial expressions.
We'll take the win.
All right.
Uh, have your team
start working on the art,
and I'll get my team on the tech.
- [TROLLEY BELL RINGING]
- It happened again.
I heard Max sing another
love song to me this morning,
and, this time, it seemed way
less ambiguous than last time.
Mm, what song was it?
- "Sucker."
- Ooh, that song's hot.
- How did Max look doing it?
- It doesn't matter.
My best friend is super into me, Mo,
and now he wants me to go to
Hand-Picked for dinner with him.
He won the lottery? Huh.
So go. He doesn't know
you're aware of how he feels.
But I know, and I can't unknow it.
And I don't want to talk
about his feelings with him,
and I don't wanna live
in the awkwardness.
With everything that's
going on in my life,
I just want to keep things
exactly how they are between us.
Then, tell him you got
sick or that Hand-Picked
uses store-bought arugula or something.
It's bigger than just one dinner.
Max is becoming a
major distraction at work.
I can't focus and be the
team leader that I need to be
with him singing heart
songs to me all the time.
- Heart songs?
- I just coined the phrase.
- I'll allow it.
- [SIGHS]
I've got to figure out
how to control this thing
and get Max off me so I
don't lose my mind or my job.
Uh, Zo-ldilocks, calm down.
I have the answer to all of
your musical-based problems.
These are the best
noise-canceling headphones
in the entire world.
I wear them to sleep,
when I'm DJing at the club,
every time an Uber driver says,
"How's your day going?"
[POPS LIPS] They're incredible.
Ooh, check them out.
Looks like they're trying
to make a baby up in here.
♪ Clock strikes upon the hour ♪
♪ And the sun begins to fade ♪
♪ Still enough time to figure out ♪
♪ How to chase my blues away ♪
Mo, can I try those on?
♪ I've done all right up till now ♪
♪ It's the light of
day that shows me how ♪
♪ And when the night falls ♪
♪ The loneliness calls ♪
These headphones are useless.
Wait. Are you hearing a song right now?
Yes, and the music's in my head,
not my ears,
and I can't just block it out.
♪ Oh, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ I wanna feel the heat with somebody ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
Unbelievable.
All I see is a bunch
of mostly white people
drinking overpriced coffee
while you get a whole show?
What song is it?
Uh, I think it's Whitney Houston.
You think Whit...
This power is wasted on you.
- What are they doing now?
- Now they're in the middle
of some sort of emotional
dance-slash-instrumental break.
It's actually...
very beautiful.
And you're still talking to me.
- Has this ever happened before?
- No.
I've never spoken to anyone
during a song before.
What are you doing?
We want to figure out how to
control this thing, right?
Somebody has to take notes.
♪ Oh, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
And they're back.
♪ I wanna feel the heat with somebody ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance with somebody ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
♪ I need a man who'll take a chance ♪
♪ On a love that burns
hot enough to last ♪
♪ So when the night falls ♪
♪ My lonely heart calls ♪
[MUSIC FADES]
Hey, Autumn.
Hey, Zoey. The usual?
Yeah. And, actually,
I think I'll get something to go...
for my buddy, Max.
Speaking of Max,
what's your take on Max?
You like his vibe? Appearance?
General outlook? You a fan?
- Um, Zoey?
- Working here, Mo.
Sure, he's cute and funny, I guess.
Why are you asking?
Oh, no reason. Just curious.
But, you know,
while we're shooting the breeze,
what do you, uh,
think about farm-to-table food?
Oh, I love it.
Have you heard of
this place Hand-Picked?
Turns out they have an
actual cow on the premises.
- How great is that?
- So, so great.
AUTUMN: Is this weird?
This feels weird.
Are you sure he's cool with it?
Are you kidding?
Max is the coolest.
Come here.
- Max.
- Hey.
Guess what? I used Dijkstra's algorithm
to find the shortest paths
between all the hunt locations
so we can make sure our
guests get to where the... Hi.
Max, you remember Autumn
from our favorite place,
The Golden Gate Grind.
Yeah. Hi, Autumn.
Uh, did we win free coffee or something?
[LAUGHS] Better than that.
So, turns out I got a
family thing Thursday night.
- Oh. What?
- But Autumn is a huge foodie,
and she would love to go
to dinner in my place.
But only if you're cool with it.
I promise I will still
serve you your black coffee
every morning if you say no.
You remember my drink order?
I remember everyone's order.
People say I have a
foam-o-graphic memory.
[MAX CHUCKLES] Well, yeah.
Um, I mean, I can't
really think of anyone else
I would take at the moment,
because, I mean,
I just ended things with, like,
four girls last week, so...
Their loss.
Yeah.
I gotta say I am loving the energy.
[CHUCKLES]
So, I am gonna leave it to you two
to sort out the details.
Okay.
- ZOEY: Hello?
- Hey, you remember
that old game we used to play, Taboo?
- You remember that?
- Uh, I remember Dad and I
crushing you and Mom at it. Why?
Yeah, okay, so check this out.
One buzz for yes. Two buzzes for no.
Watch this. Hey, Dad.
Do you like talking like this?
[BUZZ]
Would you rather watch TV?
[BUZZ BUZZ]
Do you find that sound just
to be a little bit annoying?
[BUZZ]
All right, Zoey, you try.
Okay, uh, Dad, are we going too fast?
[BUZZ BUZZ]
Do you want me to come over later?
[BUZZ]
- Do you like me more than Zoey?
- [BUZZ]
I am really sorry you had
to find out like this.
Isn't this awesome?
I... This is the first time
we've been able to really
communicate with him in months.
[SIGHS] I can't wait to show Mom.
- Hey.
- Looks good.
Hey, Zo...
Will you tell me the truth?
Why didn't you want
to go to dinner with me?
- What are you talking about?
- Don't do that.
You tried to set me up with our barista.
Ever since I mentioned Hand-Picked,
it's like you haven't been into it.
I have a lot going on, Max.
I know, I know, but, you know,
something just feels
a little bit different
between us all of a sudden.
Is this because of your new power?
Um, come here for a second.
Okay.
- My new power?
- Yes.
Your new power over me as my boss.
Is that what this is about?
Yes, that is exactly...
- ... what this is about.
- Okay.
As your boss, I feel it's necessary
to create some boundaries
between the two of us,
and I guess I-I don't think
it's quite appropriate for us
to be dining at fancy foodie
restaurants right now.
And what's the fear, exactly?
That we eat some pickled
beets out of a Mason jar
and I end up with stock options?
This is all new to me,
and I'm figuring it out
- as I go, so please respect that.
- Okay,
but I just think that you're
seriously overreacting.
Everyone knows we're friends.
We've been friends
since the day we met
at company orientation.
You becoming team manager
shouldn't change any of that.
And, yet, it does.
It changes everything, Max,
because, when people look at us,
they don't see two friends.
They see a boss and an employee
who look like they're
in the middle of a...
lovers' quarrel.
I'm pretty sure nobody cares,
but if you need to create some
boundaries between us, fine.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I should go back to work
before my boss starts
yelling at me again.
- Anything?
- [BUZZ]
- Oh, God.
What about, um, this?
- [BUZZ BUZZ]
- What is going on, you crazy kids?
I leave you alone for two minutes.
Oh, I can't even joke about this.
Your father has been trying to
tell me something all afternoon,
and I don't know what it is.
- Mitch, is it like...
- [BUZZ BUZZ]
I've taken everything
out of the cupboards,
everything out of the fridge.
I've gone through eight
different photo albums.
I even tried on that old hula skirt
when I thought maybe Hawaii
was leading us somewhere.
Nothing. Apparently it's a lot harder
to communicate with yes-no
answers than we thought.
That must be really frustrating.
[BUZZ]
It is.
But on the bright side,
the hula skirt still fits.
You know what? I'm
gonna clean all this up.
Why don't you talk to him?
Maybe you can have
better luck than I did.
Hey, Dad.
Any desire to tell me
what this is all about?
Take your time.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
While you gather your thoughts,
I'm just gonna vent.
[SIGHS] I'm fighting with Max.
I don't know how I'm supposed
to be his boss while also...
[MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Well, it's a marvelous night
for a moondance ♪
♪ With the stars up above in your eyes ♪
♪ A fantabulous night to make romance ♪
♪ 'Neath the cover of October skies ♪
♪ And all the leaves on
the trees are falling ♪
♪ To the sound of the
breezes that blow ♪
♪ And I'm trying to
please to the calling ♪
♪ Of your heartstrings
that play soft and low ♪
♪ And all the night's magic ♪
♪ Seems to whisper and hush ♪
♪ And all the soft moonlight ♪
♪ Seems to shine in your blush ♪
♪ Can I just have one
more moondance with you ♪
♪ My love? ♪
♪ Can I just make some
more romance with you ♪
♪ My love? ♪
Remember how I told you I could hear
people's innermost feelings
expressed through song?
[BUZZ]
Well... [SIGHS]
I just heard you sing a song to Mom
that I've never heard before,
but it definitely had the word
"moon" in it multiple times.
Does what you want to say to Mom
have something to do with that song?
[LONG BUZZ]
Good. We're getting somewhere.
Now, why the moon song, Dad?
[SIGHS]
Right. Not yes or no.
[WHEEZES]
Okay, don't despair.
I'm gonna go do some research
on this and get back to you.
Thank you for getting those.
Oh, I just wasn't in the mood
for another over-the-top
song-and-dance number
by lonely, overcaffeinated people again.
Huh. Understood.
Having to witness
amazing private concerts
throughout the day must
be incredibly tedious.
My heart breaks for you.
[SIGHS] So, since we really want
figure this thing out,
I have some new ideas.
Seems to me, since you're
hearing people's inner thoughts,
we need to go where their
inner thoughts are the loudest.
I got bigger fish to fry right now,
like trying to figure out why
my father sang "Moondance"
to my mother in front of me last night.
You don't know that song, do you?
Of course I know that song.
It's a very famous song.
Do you know that song?
- Not until last night.
- Oh, Jesus, take the wheel.
I've been racking my brain,
trying to figure out why that song,
and after going home
and googling the lyrics,
I think that maybe...
Your daddy wants to get
it on with your mama.
- Does he, though?
- Mm.
That's not open to interpretation?
"Well, I want to make
love to you tonight.
I can't wait till the morning has come."
It doesn't get more clear than that.
We didn't quite get to
that verse when he sang it.
Fine. Guess I have no choice,
but to talk to my mom
about my parents' sex life.
Mm, with great power
comes a whole lot of nasty
stuff don't nobody want to do.
Hi, Daddy.
[SIGHS]
I don't get it, guys.
I told you to establish a model
for how fast each leg of
the scavenger hunt will go.
I gave you all the parameters.
I told you I'd be
checking your progress.
The project needs to be
done by tomorrow morning.
I couldn't have been clearer,
so can somebody tell me
why isn't the work getting
done and getting done properly?
Maybe we're just not used to someone
standing over our shoulder
every five minutes.
He's right.
I haven't felt this kind of stress
since I got into both MIT and Harvard.
"What are you gonna do, Tobin?
What are you gonna do?"
Hack into the CIA and go to
prison for three years instead.
- What?
- I think I need to sit down.
- My sciatic is acting up.
- Now?
You've been at a
standing desk for years.
Are these actual complaints,
or are you guys just messing with me?
Okay, forget about it.
It was my idea. I have the vision.
I'll just do the entire project myself.
[TRAFFIC HONKING]
[MAX SIGHS]
Wait.
What am I doing wrong?
Am I being too hard on everybody?
I don't know. I'm just following orders
and trying my best to please you.
Right.
I'll text you some pictures
of the food at Hand-Picked,
unless you think that's
crossing another boundary.
No, that would be nice.
Well, um, I hope you and your work
have a lovely evening together.
[KNOCKS ON DESK]
Are you all right?
Yeah. Hi. What's going on?
Well, everyone's waiting
in the conference room
to see our final presentation.
Should we do it later, or...
Oh, no, uh-uh.
I finished it. Let's do this.
Wait. Oh, wait. You have a little...
- Hmm.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay. [LAUGHS]
I'm not not mortified right now.
Don't worry.
And once all the influencers
are grouped together,
the last clue will lead them all here
to our offices for one
big rocking shindig.
This is a seamless integration
of Simon's marketing department
and my... well, our engineering skills.
Yes, team, we've done it again.
Go Sprq Point and Sprq
Point and Sprq Point!
Whoo!
Hey, Zoey, um...
good work on the app,
but what is going on?
Your hair is a mess,
and you're wearing leftover clothes
from the company volleyball tournament.
That presentation was
like a talk of shame.
Oh, wow, that is not good at all.
- No.
- But, still, are we only
talking about my appearance?
'Cause if I was a guy...
No, no, you smell bad, too.
Listen, as talented as you are,
you can't take on these
projects all by yourself.
It's unsustainable,
so go home, get some rest,
and, remember,
the swag is for the interns.
It keeps them happy so we
don't have to pay them.
Please tell me your
day was better than mine
and you finally solved the case
of the mystery Taboo buzzer.
[CHUCKLES] Sadly, no.
I thought for a moment we got
back a tiny bit of control
over this thing, and then... [SIGHS]
Is it possible that nonverbal
communication was almost easier?
You really don't know what he wants
or what he's trying to say?
No.
Okay. Okay.
Well, um, I am just spitballing here,
but have you ever thought that maybe,
just maybe...
he wants to have...
sex with you?
[LAUGHS]
Sweetheart, it is very kind of you
to be worried about our love life,
but we're doing just
fine in that department,
thank you very much.
You are?
Do you know the song "Moondance"?
Yes. Why?
Because I was just watching a
show with Dad the other day,
and his face lit up
when that song came on,
and he kept pressing the
buzzer over and over again,
almost like he wanted to
sing along or something.
Uh, when we were dating...
your dad and I went to
a Van Morrison concert.
Do you know who that is?
Um, yes. I have recently
become quite acquainted
with his body of work.
[SIGHS] Sorry.
And, in the middle of that exact song,
your dad turned to me
and gave me the biggest kiss
and said, "I love you,"
for the very first time.
Mom, then maybe that's
what he's trying to say...
that he loves you.
[CHUCKLES]
And he wishes he could go
back to that night with you.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Are you expecting somebody?
Mm-mm.
Max. What are you doing here?
Oh, I was just dropping
this off for your dad.
I didn't think you'd be here.
After the all-nighter
you pulled last night,
I thought that you'd be
at your place sleeping.
Mm, I power napped,
and then I had to talk
to my mom about my parents' sex life.
What's in the bag?
Oh, Hand-Picked has this
incredible butterscotch pudding, and...
I remember you saying that your dad
can only swallow soft food,
so I thought maybe
he'd want to try some.
That's really nice of you.
Uh, come on in.
Yeah, well, your dad's
always been so nice to me,
letting me crash holiday dinners
and birthdays and
barbecues in the summer.
And you know I don't
have that same dynamic
with my own dad, so...
it's always meant a lot.
It was really hard not
asking you to stay at work
and help me last night.
Yeah, it was really hard
to see you all alone and not stay.
Here.
And Hand-Picked was?
Was fantastic. Yeah.
You really missed out.
And how was Autumn?
She was also good.
I know I didn't handle
the work thing well.
Yeah, well, that makes two of us.
Oh, um, do you want to see him?
Can I?
Yeah, of course.
Um, just prepare yourself,
'cause it's been a few months,
and he might not be exactly
how you remember him.
[SOFTLY] Okay.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad, Max is here.
Hey, Mitch.
How you doing?
I see you're in your favorite chair.
That hasn't changed.
Remember when I spilled
soda all over this chair
and Maggie got so mad and
you didn't care at all?
- [CHUCKLES]
- [MITCH COUGHS]
- [SIGHS]
- It's good to see you.
I'll call you later. Okay.
And she's back.
Do I need to hide all of my breakables?
Nah, I think you're safe.
This QB is hanging up his jersey.
Um, can I ask you something?
You manage a whole team
of people just like me, right?
Yeah.
How are you out of
here at 6:00 every night?
'Cause I've read a bunch of books...
- I-I never did any of that.
- [GROANS]
It's actually something
my pops taught me.
Oh. Well, then, we don't have...
No, no, it's a good story.
So, growing up,
my dad owned a small chain
of electronic stores in Michigan.
Uh, had a lot of stress,
lots of employees,
but every Friday was "Let's eat" day.
He'd make a giant vat of chili
or cinnamon rolls or spaghetti
and go from location to
location and serve everyone.
It's just a small personal
touch he'd bring to the table...
just to let everyone know
he cared about 'em.
And that one thing made everyone
want to work that much harder for him.
I...
... can't cook. [LAUGHS]
You should see the inside of my fridge.
Just mustard and baking soda
and several science experiments
growing out of an old chow mein.
Then, find another way to let
them know you care about them.
But what if I don't?
Is that really true?
There's nothing good about those guys?
[SIGHS]
I want to read you all something.
If it's from "Sisterhood
of the Traveling Pants,"
please don't spoil the ending.
- [LAUGHING]
- It's, uh, my journal
that I've kept since my
first day on the job.
Thought maybe you'd like to hear
my initial impressions of everyone.
"Wow, I can't believe I
get to work at Sprq Point
"with all these incredibly smart,
"talented, and impressive men.
"Please don't say anything stupid.
Andy Howard is..."
Oh, wait. He works at Google now.
Sorry.
"Chin Wu..." Got fired.
"JP Feakins..." He had
a nervous breakdown.
Okay. Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Here's one. Um...
"Has there ever been a bigger
genius than Leif Donnelly?
[CHUCKLES]
"I'm intimated to even
be in the same room
as him and his dope cardigans."
Yeah, hey.
"And Tobin Batra?
"This dude's a legend in
the hacking community,
"and now he actually knows my name?
"I think I might be dreaming.
"And Max Richman.
Is it too early to say,
'Friend for life?'"
Look, I know not everyone is thrilled
to have me as their boss,
but believe me when I say
I know how good you are at your jobs,
so I'm gonna try to let
go and trust you more,
and, in return, all I ask
is that you trust me back.
Understood?
- Yeah.
- Yep.
- Mm-hmm.
Now get back to work.
[A CAPPELLA] ♪ Well, I want
to make love to you tonight ♪
♪ I can't wait till
the morning has come ♪
♪ And I know now the
time is just right ♪
♪ And straight into my arms,
you will run ♪
♪ Can I just have one more moondance ♪
♪ With you, my love? ♪
♪ Can I just make some more romance ♪
[BUZZ]
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[DOOR OPENS]
Yo, Zo.
Uh, okay. Wow.
I guess we've just breezed
right past the whole knocking
and waiting for the other
person to answer phase.
When I get inspired,
no doors will stand in my way.
Now, I got a whole bunch of new ideas
for us to try to test
your musical powers.
First one, sensory deprivation tank.
"I can't see anything.
I can't hear anything.
But is there music?
I don't know. Let's find out."
Number two, we put you in a room
with a whole bunch of mimes.
My worst nightmare may be
your musical breakthrough.
Creative.
Absolutely terrifying.
Oh, praise God. Hoo!
Number three, we go to karaoke,
see if people sing you their inner song
at the same time they sing
the crowd their outer songs.
Eh, could be cool. Could be confusing.
Could be both. Let's see.
Look, we can keep looking for ways
to control my new ability.
[SIGHS]
But what if there are no ways?
- I don't like that attitude.
- Nope.
Listen, it has happened enough times
that we have actual
research and data now.
Some songs go by in a blip,
as if no time has elapsed.
Other songs, I'm able
to talk to you the entire time.
Some songs are sung to
me by complete strangers,
others by my closest friends and family.
Songs never happen
when I want them to...
only when I'm meant to hear them.
Then, what do we do about it?
[EXHALES]
As a kid who took apart
my parents' broken VCR
and put it back
together when I was five,
I can't believe I'm saying this, but...
nothing?
I think I'm just gonna have to live
with my new musical
power for a bit and...
see what the universe brings.
Did I really just say that out loud?
Yeah, you did,
and I'm kind of obsessed with you
and inspired to paint right now. Mm.
Silver lining in all of this,
at least it's got us talking
and invading each
other's personal spaces.
Door's always open, honey.
Unless I have a gentlemen caller over,
so if you hear Sade playing,
I'd keep my distance.
You do know who Sade is, right?
Mm-hmm.
♪ I got the music in me ♪
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN