- They're double-crossing rats.
- Hmm,
and what are they up to?
- I don't know.
It can't be good if you
didn't okay the meeting.
- I know what is, Anttwon.
- Then put it to them.
You're not handling
our business, Ty.
You're all caught up
in this crap.
- This crap is where
we're going.
I can do this and take care
of a couple rats.
Now go get busy.
Trailers.to: Watch Full HD Movies & TV Shows
Premium Platform
- What you gonna do to them?
- Don't worry about it.
- Remember when we were kids,
when we'd go up
and see the Nines,
talk about how we was
gonna take on the world.
- We're getting there, Cleo.
- The crew isn't feeling it.
You need to show them
some.
- I know what I have to do.
- It's against the east wall,
near the corner, here.
There's always at least two
guards in the room,
and two more
here and here.
- All right, then we're gonna
need at least
- Well, yesterday, I took
some doctors into a village
to vaccinate kids.
I was scared, but we explained
what the medicine was for,
and then the parents
gave us permission to do it.
It was a good day.
The kids were afraid...
- Was this Marilou's idea?
- No.
Tali asked. And asked.
- She hasn't watched those
in years.
- Neither have you.
- Mommy,
I want you to come home.
- I know, sweetie.
I'll be with you on Christmas.
Two whole weeks!
- I can't wait.
I've got to run.
I love you this much.
- Can you feel it?
- Love you, Mommy.
- I love you.
- She was so pretty.
- Yes.
And when I look into
your precious little face,
I see all her beauty in you.
- Grandma,
if she loved me so much,
why'd she go to a place
so dangerous?
- Well, I have to think
about that one.
In the meantime,
let's go see if the chickens
have any eggs for us, okay?
- Tyrone Derek Jackson,
leader of the Rolling Sixes
up in the Bronx,
wanted for the murder
of five gang members,
two of his own and three
from the Loco Diablos,
a rival Latin gang.
Gang intel says they might've
been plotting a splinter group
against their own people.
Bottom line,
Ty set off a gang war.
- Still, a beef between
two street gangs...
- Wait for it.
DEA had an undercover,
Rafael Garcia.
Deceased with one shot from an
AR-15 courtesy of Ty Jackson.
- What's the evidence
on Jackson?
- NYPD has him running
from the crime scene.
They ID'd his
"Top of the World" jacket
and his bike,
which was found abandoned.
- And Jackson,
NYPD can't find him?
- They've been rounding up his
gang members and working them,
but him, they haven't found.
- Get with gang intel,
sweep up whatever they have on
Jackson's communications,
start connecting the dots.
We have his home address,
yeah?
- NYPD assured me
they tore the place apart
but found nothing useful.
- Well, we'll see.
Let's stay on our toes.
He's armed with an AR
and who knows what else.
- Local banger.
How far could he get?
We'd be home before dinner.
- Thanks, KC.
You just jinxed it.
- You worked the Bronx
when you were at the NYPD,
you know Jackson?
- No, it's been five years.
A lot of faces come
and go in five years.
Whoever runs the Rolling Sixes
runs that hood.
- And he killed five gangsters
single-handedly.
That's ruthless and daring.
- Not to mention crazy.
They did say
they tore the place apart.
- So Jackson must've been very
popular with our folks in blue.
Check this out.
He was trying to give back
to his community.
- Trying to be Nipsey Hussle
without the credentials.
Oh.
- There you go.
Probably crushing one
of his humanitarian awards.
He has a child.
- Not according to his file.
- Maybe not one he wants
anybody to know about.
Look at the way
he's looking at that boy.
Like a proud dad
on the first day of school.
We find the boy,
maybe we find the daddy.
- Ms. Colter.
Can we talk to you?
- I'm sorry.
Do I know you?
I need to get my son to school.
- We'll see that
he gets to school.
- What is going on?
- Just move over here.
- We're looking
for Tyrone Jackson.
- I don't know any
Tyrone Jackson.
- The people at Trenton
Elementary ID'd him
as the father
of your son Anthony.
- Mommy?
- I know.
We call our son
by his middle name, Zach.
Can you go over
to the neighbor's house?
It's two doors down.
Zack, honey, go with these
folks over to Willie's house,
and play with him
for a little while.
- Eyes on the backside.
- Come on, honey.
- Negative in the basement.
- Oh, so sweet.
He's a good kid.
- I don't know where Ty is.
I haven't heard from him
in five days,
but I know he couldn't do
what they're saying.
- You do know he runs
the Rolling Sixes.
- And he's leaving that life.
That's why he set us up here,
so he could do better by his
son than his father did by him.
- Innocent or guilty,
we still need to find him
or he needs to turn himself in.
Where would he hide?
- I don't know.
I don't know his friends
from that life.
- How about girlfriends?
What's her name?
- She means nothing to him.
He's gonna be with us.
If he was gonna
go on the run for good,
he wouldn't leave without
Zach and me.
Now I really need
to get my boy to school.
- What's her name?
- I don't know.
- Listen,
if she means nothing to him,
then she should
mean nothing to you.
So why are you protecting her?
- She's a thug.
Do you know what thugs do
to snitches?
- You have my word, Ms. Colter.
She'll never know
where it came from.
- It's Cleo Wilkens.
- I tried my best with Cleo,
but once she met Ty,
there was no bringing her back.
In high school,
they got together.
Still together
from what I hear.
- Would she hide him
if she could?
- Oh, you bet she would.
I don't know where.
That's what Cleo left behind.
I don't know why I kept it all.
Not like she's
ever coming back.
- Thank you.
- How'd you find me, anyway?
- Old police report on Cleo.
She mouthed off to a cop,
and you were listed
as her guardian.
- That girl's got a mouth.
- Did she draw this?
- When she was eight.
It broke my heart
when she showed it to me.
She said if she was big,
people couldn't hurt her.
- You raised her?
- My worthless son and his
worthless wife, they couldn't.
I mean, the fights,
drugs, booze,
they were in and out of
jail.
it was no place for a child.
- Julius Caesar,
Theodore Roosevelt,
Joan of Arc.
- Yeah, she was
always reading them books.
She said they were people
like her.
- This is dated five years ago.
"The Nine Bridges."
Mean anything to you?
- No.
- "Up here they can't
look down on us,
"standing with
the water under us.
"See all, be all,
right here from on top.
"Up here you and me
can make it all stop.
"From here we can see
the Nines,
Baby they're yours,
and baby, they're mine."
- A rap about a place
where they can see
the nine bridges of the city?
- Cleo wrote this
when she was in high school.
Probably around here somewhere.
Maybe on top of a building?
Maybe somewhere her and Ty
used to go to get away
from everything.
- There's nowhere to hide
up here.
- Building's clear.
- Tallest building
in the neighborhood, check.
Nice view, check.
- Can't see but four bridges.
- The lyrics say, "Standing
with the water under us."
All nine.
- It's a match,
Tyrone Jackson.
- As he lived and breathed.
- Two shots to the chest,
point blank range.
Maybe four, five days ago.
- Then he wasn't
gunning anybody down
two days ago, was he?
- Only one person could've
enticed him up there.
The same person who
killed those five bangers.
- Hello, Cleo Wilkens.
Take this to Jimmy,
tell him to post bond
for Sammy and Shorty and Jojo.
And tell him there's more
coming for Charisse and Anttwon
and whoever else they got.
- Why you ain't just
do it all now?
- Cash flow.
When it's cool,
Ty's gonna lemme know where
the rest of his stashes are.
- Why is he talking to you?
Why he ain't talking to us?
'Cause we his crew.
- You watch the news?
He gotta hide,
and he put me in charge.
So just do what you told.
Cleo Danielle Wilkens,
age 22,
is wanted for the murders
of Ty Jackson,
DEA Agent Rafael Garcia,
and four gang members.
Yes?
- Is it true Ty Jackson
was found dead?
- I can confirm that
Mr. Jackson was shot to death.
We believe these murders
are an attempt by Ms. Wilkens
to take leadership
of Mr. Jackson's gang.
I want to make it
crystal clear
Cleo Wilkens is a menace
to this community,
and to anyone who may be
helping her evade capture.
- You killed Ty?
- Of course I didn't, fool!
Diablos, po-po, who knows?
Why would I kill him?
Hmm?
They're messing with us,
but we gotta keep going,
don't we?
Let me tell you
a little secret about Ty.
He wasn't feeling it
anymore in here.
He was halfway out the door.
Me?
I'm in all the way.
So you with me or against me?
- I got mouths to feed,
and Ty?
He always took care of us.
- Nothing gonna change.
We got big money coming in,
and I got plans.
Jimmy, now.
Could've found
a better picture though.
- Hey Barnes,
this arrest report on Cleo
for assault two years ago,
they must've had
a rookie write the DD-5.
Can you can make
sense of it for me?
- Mm-hmm.
- So you're Barnes?
You worked vice out
of the 4-7?
Gun Hill, Pelham, right?
- That's right.
You?
- I was in the 4-9,
the 5-2, bounced around.
Wouldn't give it up
for nothing.
Not like you.
- Like me what?
- Couldn't handle the hustle,
huh?
Had to get one of these
cushy federal jobs?
- Yeah, it's great.
Straight 9-5, bad guys
who roll over like puppies.
it's just cocktails and bonbons
all day every day.
- Hey, do you wanna
wind someone up
or do you want us to help us
do your job for you?
- Hey, hey, hey.
We're just ragging
each other up, okay?
It's nothing.
Lighten up.
What are you doing?
- Hey, listen up.
I got something here.
Three Rolling Sixes just got
bailed out for ten grand each,
cash money.
- Cleo's keeping
the money rolling.
- Who's their bondsman?
- Jimmy's Superior Bail Bonds
on Sheridan.
He told the clerk at the prison
that he'd be back later
to spring more Rolling Sixes.
He also told her
not to bury them.
- I mean, how do you answer
a question like that?
- How would your wife
have answered it?
- Angelyne would've found
the words.
She always did.
But me?
How do you explain duty
to an eleven-year-old?
- Yeah, that's a hard one.
- He's moving.
- Special delivery, huh?
- I've got you covered.
- Yeah, right on time.
- Follow the gray hoodie.
We'll keep eyes on you.
'Cause I took her
for everything.
You know what I mean?
- Yo, you dirty, dawg.
- You know,
why you even doing that?
- It's a cold world.
- Cleo.
- He made us.
Forget him.
Hit the house.
- Five-oh, five-oh!
- FBI, stop!
- Go!
- Go, go!
- Stop! FBI!
- FBI, freeze!
- Move!
- Stop!
- Freeze!
- I said stop!
- You two, secure the front.
- Clear!
- Suspect's MIA.
Start taking names.
- Come on!
Sit down!
- The courier
must've texted her.
- I don't know no Cleo Wilkins!
- ID!
- Hey!
FBI, stop!
Let me go!
I didn't do anything!
- Stop fighting...
- That woman Hana's talking to.
I know her.
- I'm a nurse's aid
at the hospital.
- Five years ago
when I was undercover
in a drug sting,
she knows me.
- What's the name
of your friend?
- Ava.
She don't live here.
She justshe just
told me to meet her here.
- Did she know you were a cop?
- No, she's just someone
I met back then.
- What do you wanna do?
- She's lying.
- Obviously.
- She might've come here
for Cleo.
- So again,
what do you wanna do?
- Sit down. ID!
- I'll need to go home first.
- Charlotte won't like it.
I don't like it.
- People are dying 'cause
of Cleo.
This girl might get me to her.
It's our best shot.
- Hana, let her go.
- Get out of here.
Go to work.
- You promised me, Sherr,
no more undercover work.
- No, I didn't.
You just told me
not to do it again.
It's my job, Charlotte.
- This family is your job.
Our daughter is our job.
- You know the two of you
are my life.
- Then please, don't put
yourself at even more risk.
- We don't live in a bubble,
Charlotte.
If we can make the safer world
for Anais even a little bit...
You do it your way,
teaching the law.
I do it my way.
You won't be able
to reach me directly,
but you have
everybody's numbers.
Any of them will know where I
am and how to contact me.
- Mommy, I'm thirsty.
Are you going away?
- Just for a few days, baby.
Mwah.
- Line of sight, 200 yards.
- She's in place.
- Copy.
- This one.
- This is Agent Skye.
Anttwon Lane Perry,
date of birth, 9-2-96.
Has he been bailed out yet?
Hold him for us.
We're on our way.
- Sandra.
I figure I owe you
an explanation and an apology.
- You do.
You really do.
- Still have the same apartment
with a view of the park?
- Then you know the way.
- Step on up.
Come over here.
Have a seat.
- Why'd y'all bring me here,
man?
My bail's been posted.
- Not processed.
Sit down.
- It's about your brother,
Kendrick.
- Yeah?
What about him?
- 25 year sentence up
in Ray Brook lockup.
That's practically in Canada.
It's a long way for your mom
to go to visit.
- What do you want?
- Cleo Wilkins.
You know she killed Ty,
shot him twice in the heart.
It wasn't pretty.
Okay.
We can move you brother
Kendrick downstate,
closer to
the city.
Easy ride for you
and your mom.
- Your mom is in a walker,
right?
- You can really
get Kendrick moved?
- If you help us find Cleo.
I ain't wearing no wire
or nothing.
- The heat was on.
You were okay, straight job,
no cops looking for you.
I had to get out.
- But five years, Sherry?
You could've let me know
where you were.
- And give 'em a call to trace,
get you mixed up in my trouble?
- It cooled off.
Police put people in jail,
then everything
went back to normal.
- By then I was jammed up
in Florida.
I did three years.
- Baby, I'm sorry.
- I tried not to miss you.
You took such good care of me.
- Because I loved you.
I could take care of you again.
- I don't want your money,
okay?
I can earn my own,
but I need to get
back in the game.
- Is that a good idea?
- It's what I know.
I just need to figure out
where to start.
I don't know
the players anymore.
- Hmm.
- Still the same old Sherry.
Solid, knows her own mind.
Come with me tonight,
and I'll introduce you
to somebody who can help.
You have a place to stay?
- I got to town this morning,
stashed my case,
and went to find you.
- You can stay here.
- I'd like that.
- Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo!
Here he comes!
- You think you all that?
Huh?
You ain't nothing!
We the Rolling Sixes.
We got us and we got Cleo.
She been on the fly six days,
and y'all still
ain't find nothing.
She running your dumb ass
all over the block.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Cleo, Cleo, Cleo!
Cleo, Cleo, Cleo...
all: Cleo, Cleo, Cleo...
- So you believe him?
You think I killed Ty?
- Listen, they been trying
to take us down since forever.
This they new play.
Get us to turn on each other,
and take our own selves down.
So no, Cleo, I don't believe
you killed him.
I think they did it.
- So we got no problem.
- None with me.
Look, like Ty said,
"Cleo's the real deal."
You know that.
But we still got people
who haven't been bailed
out of jail yet.
- I'm on it.
This gets 'em out
and sets us up.
Y'all ready?
We all seen
this play before.
They plant evidence on us,
threaten to cut off
your mom's benefits
if she don't snitch on you,
chain up your baby brother
while they toss your crib,
and now they killed Ty.
Well, we're done.
Done hiding, done running,
done with being locked up
and shot for being black.
- We on our own...
- This girl's been to church.
- You think anybody's falling
for this?
- People paying attention,
that's what matters.
- Lies have consequences.
Hate has consequences.
And when they come
after one of us,
they coming after all of us.
- Amen, sister.
- Those biographies she read,
Joan of Arc, Julius Caesar,
those are instruction
manuals to her.
Grandiose, narcissistic,
delusional.
- Ty showed me how
to take on the world.
He said,
"Dreams aren't enough."
You've got to show them
the power,
and that's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna fix this.
Set up or step away.
With me or against me.
- Barnes is on the move.
- I remember this place.
They still have pumpkin burek?
- We'll eat later.
You nervous?
- No, but you are.
So who's this friend
we're meeting?
- Girl I know from high school,
and no, it wasn't like that.
Look, if you don't want
to do this, we don't have to.
- No, I'm good.
Slow feet don't eat.
Gotta make a living.
- It's her.
She's in the basement.
- Why the basement?
- There's a passageway
to the buildings next door.
- I'm losing her.
She's in the basement.
- I'm not letting her
fly solo.
Let's move.
- Here she is.
- You didn't say your friend
was famous.
- You want a selfie with me,
bitch?
- You got ten seconds
to convince me
why I should take you on.
- I can make you
ten grand a week
moving product in a world
you know nothing about.
I know ladies in penthouses,
townhouses,
up and down Billionaires' Row.
I did it then
and I can do it now.
All these knuckleheads can do
is work a corner.
- Forget it, Anttwon.
You got my stuff?
You wanna talk,
this ain't the place.
- Health department!
- This way.
- You killed him, Cleo!
You just shot him!
He wasn't doing nothing.
How could you do that?
- He was a snitch.
He was taking pictures.
You need to be like
your friend here.
You ain't even flinch.
- Not my business.
- I like her.
Gimme.
I'll reach out.
Be ready.
- You okay?
- No, we just left him there.
I want to call somebody.
- No, don't do that.
What's that you gave her
from the hospital?
- Anti-seizure meds.
She can't just go
to a pharmacy, right?
She's got epilepsy.
She got bullied about it
in school.
- You felt sorry for her.
You're too good, Sandy.
You know, maybe hooking up
with Cleo wasn't the best idea.
- Don't back out.
She'll take it personal.
- I can always ghost
out of here.
- Don't.
- You're gonna be late
for work.
I'll see you later, okay?
She was right behind me.
There wasn't a damn thing
I could do.
- This is not your fault.
Look,
ever since Cleo took over,
12 people have been gunned
down.
She created this chaos.
It's on her.
- She has epilepsy.
My friend Sandy sneaks her
anti-seizure drugs
from the hospital.
- Of course she has epilepsy.
Those books she reads,
Teddy Roosevelt, Julius Caesar,
they all had epilepsy
and overcame it.
She has a fetish for her
own condition.
She thinks it makes
her special, powerful,
but look at this.
Look at this.
The child towering over
the adults,
and the longer
she evades capture,
the bigger the child gets.
- Boss, take a look.
Anttwon's phone is missing,
but I found this in the Cloud.
Last picture he took.
Floor plans, looks like.
- The dollar sign
could be somebody's stash.
- Hana, put up the crime scene
photos from the shoot-out,
and show me that table.
After Cleo killed them,
she took the sketch with her.
That's what the meeting
was about.
They were planning a heist.
- The sketch was on
Diablos' side of the table.
Maybe they were planning
to rip off their own stash.
- That would explain
the secret meeting
with the Rolling Sixes.
- So now Cleo's
going after the stash.
- That would solve
her money problems.
- It might solve our problems
too.
Clinton, check with the DEA,
see if their Agent Garcia
got any intel
on where the Diablos
keep their stash.
And that's the toll so far
of the gang war instigated
by Cleo Wilkens.
I'd like to say a few words
about the man whose shoes
Ms. Wilkens
is trying to fill.
Tyrone Jackson.
Tyrone Jackson was a criminal,
but he also gave back
to his community.
He paid for funerals,
helped people pay
their heating bills,
he even helped bring
a supermarket
to his neighborhood
to give jobs to young people.
Tyrone Jackson
helped his people
with the tools he had
at his disposal
until Cleo Wilkins
cut him down.
- Leave it on.
- What has
Cleo Wilkens done?
She turned your streets
into a war zone.
By her own hand
or by her orders,
she killed
all these people.
And right now
13 of her gang members
are in jail because
she either can't be bothered
or doesn't have the money
to bail them out.
Maybe she just doesn't know
how to bring in the money.
Either way,
she's no Ty Jackson.
Thank you.
If that doesn't tweak her...
- Ty went soft.
Thought we could go legit.
You believe that?
You believe they're ever gonna
let us live like they do?
Ever gonna let us rise?
Nah.
What we want...
We gotta take.
Get strapped.
Now!
I need soldiers.
- Yeah?
Hey Cleo.
- You introduced me to her.
What do you think your friend
did for a living?
She's a thug, Sandy!
Thug life.
The hate you give.
All that bullying she got
on account of her epilepsy?
She's paying it back.
- Please, Sherry,
don't go with her.
I couldn't live with myself
if something happened to you.
- I gotta throw in with her.
I got no choice.
With my record, where am I
gonna get a straight job?
- I've got a job.
I'll take care of you.
- I don't want it
like that between us!
She called me.
If I don't show, I'm done.
- Where did you get that?
- Never mind.
I gotta go.
Do not follow me.
- I can't lose you again!
No, you're not going.
I'll talk to her,
she'll listen to me.
- I'm FBI.
I'm sorry, but just know people
have my back, okay?
Nothing's gonna
happen to me.
- You...
Were you FBI five years ago?
When you made me fall in love
with you?
When you pretended
to be in love with me?
- I wasn't pretending,
but I had a job to do,
and I've got one to do now.
Get out!
- Barnes is on the move.
- She's going to a meet.
Van just pulled up.
I can't tell if Cleo's inside.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Uh-oh.
New player on the field.
- Go home.
We'll talk later.
- I'm going with you.
- This is what loyalty
looks like.
- They turned down
an alley off St. Raymond.
We'll get made if we follow.
- Stay put.
If you lose the signal,
come to me.
- Huh?
- What?
- FBI!
- FBI, don't move!
- Get down!
Get down!
- Drop your weapons!
- Get down!
- Put down your weapon!
- Hands up, hands up!
Up against the wall!
Stand down!
- Let me out!
Let me out
or I'ma kill her!
- Let her go, Cleo.
- Why?
She brought you in!
You knew she was a cop.
- She didn't know.
She had nothing
to do with this trap.
- It was Anttwon.
The guy you let back in.
- Snitches all around.
I walk out
or this bitch is dead!
- You hurt her
and you don't come out alive.
- Sandra protected you.
She helped you when
you got sick in school.
She brought you meds.
She's a better person
than you or me,
and you're gonna kill her,
for real?
How's that gonna make you look?
- She's right.
You're already a legend, Cleo.
Seven days you had us
chasing our tails.
The whole FBI.
- And you never left your turf.
- That's right.
I outsmarted you.
- That you did,
but you hurt this
one good person,
all that goes out the window.
Those people you admire,
Joan of Arc, Caesar,
Alexander the Great?
For them, there's only one
power play that matters.
- And what's that?
- You give us permission
to take you in.
- Permission?
- You control your own destiny.
You'll stand tall, like all
those great men and women.
- Word'll get out, Cleo.
You called the play,
and when you get to prison,
you'll be walking on water.
- You better get used
to them bracelets.
- They'll take care of you
up North.
- She's crazy.
- You're gonna die in lockup.
- You good?
- Sure.
- You had us worried
when you jumped in that van.
- Iron Lady.
- Now go home.
Hug your kid.
- Bureau of Prisons
is on the line.
- This Agent LaCroix.
I'd to talk about
transferring a prisoner
down from Ray Brook,
name of Kendrick Perry.
- Why'd you get in the van?
- To make sure nothing
happened to you.
What are they gonna do to me?
- I don't know.
I'll see what I can do.
both: "Mr. McGregor
went back to his work,
"and Peter was alone again,
"but he was very frightened,
and he was very, very..."
- Hi, Mama.
- Hey, baby.
- Mommy, read more.
- Read more?
Okay!
- Yay.
- We can read more.
both: "Peter asked her
the way to the gate,
"but she had such a large pea
in her mouth,
she couldn't answer."
- Grandma said
that they were bad people,
and good people
had to stop them.
- And what do you think
about that?
- Why did it have to be Mom?
- I think it's all about love.
She loved you so much,
and your grandparents,
Uncle Clinton.
She loved her family
and friends so much
that she wanted
to keep everyone safe.
She felt like that was her...
most important responsibility.
Good night, Dad.
- Good night, sweetheart.
- Hello, handsome.
- Hello, gorgeous.
How's our baby?
She's excited
about turning eight.
You look tired today.
- Can't think why.
Maybe it's that double shift.
You want me to come over there
and kick some brass?
- Mm-hmm.
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN