Previously on "Lincoln Rhyme..."
You can thank
Officer Sachs here
for saving that evidence.
Do you know how the Bone
Collector got his name?
He wrote a letter saying
most people are just piles of bones.
What about the postmark?
Tracked it back
to Farmington, New Mexico.
Going through security video
from the originating post office.
He'd avoid cameras at all costs.
I'd love to get in a sneak
of your secret lair
one day when you're not at home.
You're not gonna believe this.
Jane... she's gone.
I think somebody took her.
Decay is as natural to death
as death is to life.
Decomp fields like this give us
a humane way to examine remains
when affected by various elements.
Weather, wildlife, indoor, outdoor.
No crimes.
Each of the field's residents
died naturally,
donating their bodies to science
to show us what death has in store.
Studying the process of decay
serves a crucial purpose.
To help solve murders
using forensic evidence
gathered from the remains.
By analyzing each stage
of the decomposition process,
we can help pinpoint the time of death.
A process that, as you can see,
takes time to get used to.
How quickly does a body
start to decompose?
The process begins immediately
after the heart stops beating.
Hey, guys?
I think this one's moving.
That's impossible.
Is there an animal under there?
Oh, God.
Call 911!
Oh, my God.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
Ready for some movie magic?
This is the first ever image
of the Bone Collector.
You're really going to pause for fanfare?
Okay.
I was able to restore
the manager's cell phone video
from the shipping center in New Mexico.
You'll be the first one to see
it along with me, right now.
- It's not him.
- No.
No, it's not.
Why risk mailing a package on camera
when you can pay some junkie teenager
to do it for you?
Wait, pause it.
Go back to before the kid went in.
Hey, zoom in.
That's him.
A white male.
Reflection's not helping much
with the details.
Looks like he made a phone call.
Please tell me you can get
something with that.
It's gonna take some time,
but I've got a few tricks I can use.
All right, use them all.
Lincoln? Fred Hawkins is here.
- Who?
- Sellitto's friend.
Firefighter, same injury as you.
I told you, I'm not interested.
And I ignored you and set it up.
Heads up, you're walking
into a firefight.
I've been warned.
I think I can handle him.
Lincoln Rhyme.
It's great to finally meet you.
Sorry you got dragged over here.
I'm actually tied up in a case.
That's great. You're back at work.
So if you'll excuse me...
Maybe just a quick cup of coffee?
Saw a great place by the corner.
Then I'll let you get back to it.
Despite what you might've heard, Fred,
I don't need a pep talk.
Last time someone told me to be hopeful
was the day my reawakened mobility
returned to its stubborn slumber.
I've been told that you've been creating
an amazing world for yourself up here,
and that's great.
I also think that the world out there
is still out there for you too.
That's truly motivational, Fred, but...
You had a deep love of this city.
No, I breathed this city.
It pulsed in my veins.
Every cobblestone path I walked,
every rickety stairwell I climbed,
the parks, the tunnels...
Now it's all gone.
Sellitto said you used to play chess.
In the park?
Now I can't even lift the pawn.
You're right.
That's hard. Everything's harder.
Things you'll probably never do again.
But the ones you can do...
Do them, Lincoln.
I'll take a rain check on the coffee.
- You do know you work for me?
- I also care about you.
And you think I'm not doing enough?
You are. But I see how you look
when you're watching Amelia out there
where you used to go and walk.
I just think...
That I should get out there?
How does that work for you, Claire?
Sellitto is on his way.
Tell me why I should love
this case so much?
Josh Marlowe. 17.
Found with a 14 inch cut
of steel rebar drilled through his heart.
I'll go out on a limb. He was murdered.
It's not cause of death
that makes this our case.
It's where they found him.
Saranac College,
their forensics anthropology site.
- Seriously?
- Forensics anthropology site?
A decomp farm.
It's like a playground of forensics.
We use them to study how nature
affects the human body post mortem.
A playground of dead bodies?
Mm.
They test the effects of everything.
Water, heat, sun, insects, time...
So that when it happens
to innocent people,
we have data to guide us.
Some of my happiest memories
from training were there.
Well, don't look at me like that.
Josh lived in the city.
He had no ties
to the university whatsoever,
except ending up dead there.
So the killers hid the body
amongst a bunch of other bodies.
Except there's no hiding
in a decomp farm.
Students and faculty do rounds
all day long.
Document every change and every cadaver.
They know what bodies
are supposed to be there,
and what bodies aren't.
So either the killer didn't know that,
or they wanted to show off
their handiwork.
Either way, we gotta figure out
how a live body
ended up in a field full of dead ones.
And by live, he means alive.
Took his last breath as they found him.
Now, the chief requested someone
who could investigate this
without harming
their delicate little, uh...
Science experiment.
Hey, we might already have
our first lead.
Victim's brother says
he might know who did it.
Hmm. If we're lucky,
the brother's right,
and it's our last lead.
Let's get justice for this family.
You have to get him. Arrest him.
- He killed my brother.
- Ray Coyne, your stepfather?
How many people
are you gonna let him kill?
Ben, I believe what you're saying.
Okay? And we're listening.
We just wanna be armed
with everything we know
before we talk to your stepfather.
Can you help us with that?
Okay, so you asked us,
"How many people
are we gonna let him kill?"
Who else did Ray kill?
My mother. Eight go.
I should explain.
Ben's mother, Grace, was my best friend.
She died from complications
of a heart condition.
They said that, but Josh knew
Ray did something to her.
- Josh knew based on what?
- He just...
Knew.
There were problems in the marriage.
The boy's father passed away
five years ago.
They never liked Ray, never accepted him.
When Grace died out of nowhere,
they blamed him.
Because he did it.
Ray has custody, but I try and help.
Ben, I wanna help you. You can trust me.
You've lost a lot, too much,
and I get that. Believe me, I do.
So can you tell us,
did Josh have any evidence?
He's been trying to get evidence.
- Trying how?
- He wouldn't tell me,
but he said he was getting close.
Ray must have found out
and followed him there.
- To Saranac?
- To the body farm, yeah.
I don't understand.
Why would your brother
be going to the body farm?
That's where our mom's body is.
Mother and son dead in the same spot
eight months apart.
Interested now?
Meet Grace Marlowe, accountant,
dedicated mother of two,
and for the past eight months,
resident at the Saranac College
Decomp Farm.
Died from complications
of Eisenmenger syndrome.
It's brought on
by an atrial septal defect,
a hole in the wall
between the top two chambers
of the heart.
Undiagnosed, it can lead
to cardiac arrest,
which is in our cause of death.
Well, alleged cause of death, right?
Official cause of death.
Let's not get pulled offsides by two kids
who don't like their mother remarrying.
Wouldn't be the first murder
to be labeled as natural causes,
but you knew that.
So Grace dies,
donates her body to science,
ends up a research cadaver
rotting in a field
for the better part of a year
until her son comes looking for her,
trying to find evidence she was murdered
and dies 20 yards away from her.
What a tragic reunion.
- Like that Paul Simon song.
- Hm?
Paul Simon.
He named a song after a dish
at a Chinese restaurant.
Chicken and eggs on the same plate.
Called it the mother and child reunion.
That's clever.
I need you out on the decomp farm
while Sellitto and Eric
run down the wicked stepfather.
As much as I love spending
every day in here,
the decomp farm is
my old stomping ground.
I could go with her.
She could go instead of me.
I need you here with me.
Fine. Go.
Knock yourself out.
This is gonna be awesome.
I don't know if anyone's
ever told you this, but...
You've a mocking tone.
The way you talk to people.
You're not a very nice person, Jane.
But you were a good friend to Danielle.
Made her feel happy...
which made me feel happy.
We were all happy.
But all good things must come to an end.
Quite a before and after.
He was steps away from her.
20 yards from finding out
whatever answer he wanted.
The question is:
what could Josh have possibly
retrieved here
that would help him?
In the elements like this,
Grace could've been fully
skeletonized for months now.
Amelia, Grace is in good hands with Kate.
- We need to examine...
- Josh's crime scene.
Yeah. On it.
Oh, rebar.
I think we can safely say
we know the origin of the murder weapon.
Which means this wasn't planned.
Our killer had to improvise.
Seems like finding evidence
isn't gonna be a problem out here.
Too many needles,
not enough haystack.
You will find
extraneous evidence, tissue,
bone fragments, footprints,
but by process of elimination...
Yeah, look for evidence
that doesn't belong.
I got it.
Look at the ground inside the site.
It looks damp,
but it doesn't look like blood.
Mm, let's sample it.
Check the tarp itself.
It's the one thing apart from the rebar
that we know the killer had contact with.
Okay.
Got something
on the underside of the tarp.
- Blood?
- Look, zoom in.
White hair stuck on blood.
Sticks out like a bloody thumb.
- I'll bag it.
- No.
Bring in the whole tarp.
I wanna test it for everything.
Hey, Coyne.
Detective Sellitto, Castillo, NYPD.
- I was expecting you.
- Is that right?
I haven't seen or heard from Ben
since I went to ID Josh's body.
Melissa told me he wants
to stay with her?
Figured it'd be a matter of time
before he told you
what he thinks about me.
What he thinks about you
is quite the accusation.
Oh. He's tragically misinformed,
and it breaks my heart.
I loved his mother.
Watching her die,
suddenly, awfully... It nearly killed me.
I know they didn't like me
taking their father's place,
but to think I could have harmed her?
When Grace was sick at the very end,
she didn't want the boys
to remember her like that,
so I tried to keep them
from seeing her at her worst.
Josh thought I was hiding something,
- but I got nothing to hide.
- Nothing?
Look, I was working
when Josh was murdered.
I'm a security guard. There are logs.
There's video.
Very sorry about Josh's death.
If you have any information
you think might help
or any questions...
I have one question.
What Josh thought
about Grace being murdered...
Could that really be true?
Is that why this happened?
You lock up the stepfather?
Seems there are two sides to every story,
which means we still have to do this.
- I hate morgues.
- Does anyone like morgues?
Kate.
Well, she'll have to enjoy remotely.
Lincoln summoned her back
when I interviewed the students.
You get anything?
Just the eerie feeling
that they're teaching each
and every one of them
- how to get away with murder.
- Yeah.
I think the idea is to teach them
how to stop people
from getting away with murder.
Now let's get a look at our victim.
The sooner we get out of here,
the better.
- Yeah.
Is it unusual for you, Dr. Wasden?
We never get murder victims here.
Uh, all of our bodies die
of natural causes,
so this is quite exciting...
Professionally speaking.
Totally get it.
And this one is unique.
Mr. Marlowe was impaled from behind
between 2:00 a.m. and 3:00 a.m.
The weapon entered
just below the right shoulder
before entering the right atrium
and rupturing the pulmonic valve.
But that's not what killed him.
The valve slowly leaked blood
into his lungs,
and he choked to death.
He must've suffered for hours.
The killer must've been in a hurry
if they left him alive like that.
Yeah, I thought the same thing.
However, the body was cleaned...
Meticulously cleaned,
swabbed beneath the nails
and on all the defensive wounds.
Defensive wounds?
Oh, yes, there was clearly a struggle.
He fought back.
But I found nothing
transferred from the assailant.
Covering up something like that
is no small feat.
So you're saying whoever did this
knew exactly what they were doing.
Forensically speaking.
Don't like to speculate,
but it's a fair conclusion.
And how many people with
that kind of knowledge
also had access
to the decomp farm at night?
Well, that would be everyone here.
Maybe a hundred people
every semester.
Officer Sachs,
someone's been waiting for you.
Did you talk to him?
Ben, what are you doing here?
I wanna know what Ray said.
I wanna know what you found.
Okay, well, we just started,
and yes, our people are talking to Ray.
- And what'd he say?
- Ben, come on, sit down.
No, I'm... I'm not gonna... I can't sit.
Look, Ben, I get
what you're feeling here.
No, you don't.
My brother's dead. My mother's dead.
You're right.
What you're feeling, no one else knows.
Okay, no one can understand
what that kind of loss feels like.
But here's what I need you to know:
it is my job, Ben, to get you
the answers that you want.
Now look, if that means Ray,
I don't know, but I can promise you
that I will not stop
until I find something.
Okay? So just sit down.
You're not in this alone, Ben.
We got your back.
You're not gonna tell me what you found?
I am when this is done.
- I want to believe you.
- Well, you can.
I promise you, I'm telling you the truth.
Wasden's fast.
Toxicology report. Marlowe, Joshua A.
No volatiles, no illicits.
Perfectly healthy kid
besides, you know...
The stake through the heart.
What about the tarp?
The only thing of note was
the hair Amelia found.
It's from an Angora.
Basically a house cat with white...
I know what an Angora is.
Okay, normally,
this wouldn't be that helpful...
Because all manner of vermin
descend on decomp farms
to feast on bodies.
Well, cats aren't technically vermin.
Anyway, the position on the
tarp suggests that the hair
was between the tarp and Josh's body.
Meaning it was there
before he was covered.
Which is why I asked Eric
to check in with Ben.
No cat.
I think it came from the killer.
So we're looking for a killer with a cat.
- Seems to narrow it down.
- It's something!
Felix!
Could you please use
the button on your chair?
I have kind of a thing
about being yelled at.
Have you found any connections
between Saranac College and Josh?
I'm looking into everyone.
Faculty, staff, students.
You should've been done by now.
I'm working on
the Bone Collector footage.
I told you to drop that for now.
Yeah, you also told me to use
every tool at my disposal.
Felix, after you get me what I need.
- He's not himself today.
- No, no, he is.
He's always been Lincoln-y
even before was in that chair.
And that's fine.
You know that's okay because he's good.
He's better than good.
I mean, I get to do things here
that I would never get to do
somewhere else, but sometimes,
it is just not worth it.
Honestly, I can't believe
you'd stick up for him
after the way he talked to you
this morning.
I was pushing him, and he wasn't wrong.
I have a condition.
A panic disorder, really.
I can't be in crowds, can't go in public,
can't even leave this apartment.
- Agoraphobia.
- I wanna get out.
I just can't.
He can, but he doesn't want to.
And that sets me off, which sets him off.
My two cents?
It's got nothing to do with you.
His problem is that he lost
to the Bone Collector,
and he cannot accept that.
You're right.
He's not stuck in here,
he's stuck in the same place in his life
ever since that night.
That's it. Of course.
- What?
- Stuck in the same place.
I've been looking at this all wrong.
Uh.
Claire, we just might find
the Bone Collector after all.
The beauty of chess is, you
never know how many moves ahead
your opponent is thinking.
So your point is, the same
is true in catching murderers.
If Ray Coyne killed his stepson,
was it because he also killed Grace?
He feared exposure?
There's two problems there.
There wasn't much left of her
to be exposed,
and Sellitto doesn't think Ray
looks good for it.
You wanna know how many
people I've arrested
who didn't look good for it?
Mm.
You're in high spirits today.
No different than any other day.
No, usually your
mild disdain and impatience
are part of your charm.
I come in here, and Claire's
walking on eggshells.
Felix is grumbling...
Maybe people should just do their jobs.
Maybe they'd do them better
if the work environment
was a little more...
- harmonious.
- Look.
I care about catching this killer.
I care about finding
what happened to Josh.
If I get impatient...
Fine.
I'll try not to get impatient.
We may have found our man.
Stepfather was all broken up
about his wife's death,
only guess what he failed to mention.
A secret girlfriend.
- One of the other great
motives: money.
Grace took out a $1/2 million policy
on her life a year before she died.
She didn't leave anything to her kids?
She did entrust,
and guess who the trustee is
until they come of age.
Josh was about to turn 18.
So Ray's share of the money
was about to go away.
Problem is, his alibi holds up.
Maybe because
he's not the one who did it.
This is the file Saranac College
gave us on Grace Marlowe.
Seemed pretty thin on evidence,
so I decided to check out
a couple of other ones.
This one and this one.
All the other files
on decomp farm corpses
include reams of info.
Detailed notes, photos...
You're saying someone
was trying to cover up
everything about Grace.
No, not just someone. Someone we met.
Autumn Bestin,
the TA of the class.
- The one who found the body?
- Yep.
She checked out the file three days ago
and emptied it of almost every
single piece of evidence
on Grace,
then suddenly finds her son's
body two days later?
I interviewed Autumn.
She said she didn't know Josh.
Sounds like Autumn lied to you.
I was scared. Who wouldn't be?
So you did know Josh Marlowe.
Yes... I mean, barely.
I'd known him for a week,
I helped him find information
about his mother,
and there he was. Murdered.
And you didn't think mentioning
that would be relevant?
I was freaked out.
I've seen bodies, but never a murder.
Well, that may seem more plausible
if we didn't know you
emptied out his mother's file.
No, that's how I found it.
Why were you trying
to get it in the first place?
Josh found out his mother
had donated her body here.
He went around to a bunch of faculty.
No one would give him anything.
I mean, they're really not supposed to.
- So why did you?
- I felt awful for him.
His mother had been murdered.
He kept saying her name.
I'd overseen her case
when she arrived at the farm.
I remembered the name,
so I told him
I would see what I could find.
So what did you think
when you found the file?
It was unusual,
so I went to the computer.
There should've been backups, copies...
Mm-hmm.
Grace Marlowe's file was empty.
Someone erased it.
You told Josh this?
I did, and I sent him copies
of what little I had,
my personal notes from the time.
- Do you still have them?
- I do.
It's not much.
A couple of photos,
handwritten descriptions...
You think Josh was right.
She was murdered?
And someone killed him
because of what I gave him?
Autumn's story checks out.
So Ray has motive, but also an alibi.
Autumn lied to us,
but seems like she wanted
to help find the truth
- about Grace's murder.
- Alleged murder.
Oh, God.
I guess that's what becomes
of us all at some point.
Standard Y-shaped incision,
which means they confirmed
the cardiac arrest.
Autumn said she took notes.
What else did she observe about the body?
Skin inflammation,
deep creases in the palms,
excessive white on her fingernails.
Huh, Eisenmenger's syndrome
should have caused
a blue tint in the skin,
not red inflammation.
Show me a more recent photo.
Zoom in on the sternum.
No evidence of bone disease.
And only one chemical
affects skeletal discoloration
post mortem.
Arsenic.
Changes the bone even after you're dead.
Josh was right.
His mother didn't die of a heart defect.
- She was poisoned.
- And that's not all we pulled.
Grace's medical history...
She had celiac disease,
which is hereditary.
Even if Josh didn't inherit the disease,
he would've had the antibody deficiency,
but in Wasden's tox report?
His numbers are normal.
You're saying the medical
examiner assisting us
on this case falsified
Josh's autopsy report?
I'm saying what I see in the numbers.
So, what was Dr. Wasden
trying to hide and why?
What are we not seeing?
Mm.
Right there.
We're too busy staring at the results,
we weren't focused on
the signatures at the bottom.
Look who performed
Grace Marlowe's autopsy last year.
Dr. Arthur Wasden.
Detectives! How can I help you?
Do you happen to own a cat, Dr. Wasden?
Allergic, I'm afraid.
What does this have to do with the case?
Why didn't you tell us
that you performed autopsies
on Josh and Grace Marlowe?
Josh Marlowe's mother, Grace.
Eight months ago,
you performed the autopsy,
and ruled it death
by congenital heart condition.
I perform a great number of autopsies.
A mother and son.
That didn't strike you as odd?
I wasn't aware.
Well, that's
an interesting detail to miss,
considering you're so meticulous.
I'm not sure I appreciate
the tone of this conversation.
Well, you're gonna have
to forgive our impoliteness.
We're just adding up all these
very strange coincidences.
You're the county medical examiner,
but you also run the entire
decomp farm facility,
don't you?
Which gives you access
not only to the entire grounds,
but every single cadaver
that enters those grounds.
And all the files kept on them.
We're gonna have a second examiner
perform an autopsy on Josh Marlowe.
Which requires a court order.
Or a request from the next of kin.
Josh's brother would like us
to take another look.
Well, I'm sorry. That's not possible.
It was apparently
a terrible miscommunication
with my staff.
Josh's body has been cremated.
Last one.
Have you seen my journals?
- Really?
- Really.
- You jerk.
- Hmm.
Why does packing
always take twice as long
as you think it's going to?
Yeah. Just think,
a few days from now,
we get to do it all backwards.
Mm, don't pretend you're not excited.
I am.
Yeah.
Why don't you check on the movers?
Okay.
I'm gonna take one last look around,
make sure we're not forgetting anything.
You are being paranoid.
- I'm being...
- Thorough.
Wait, how is it even legal
for an ME to examine a body
near his own office?
He's the county medical examiner.
Most counties don't even have one.
They rely on local physicians.
Well, they're gonna have
to find a new one.
Listen, if I were a betting man,
all my chips would be on Wasden,
but we can't arrest him.
He took our only potential evidence
and stuck it in an 1,800 degree furnace.
Well, listen to this.
In 2004, Dr. Arthur Wasden
was forced into rehab
for opioid abuse.
2006, filed for bankruptcy.
Then gets sued
because of a deceased woman
whose organs were, I kid you not,
mistakenly removed for donation.
Settled out of court.
So he doesn't have glowing Yelp reviews.
Doesn't give motive.
But he does have the skills
to hide evidence
on both bodies.
Yes, but why kill Josh at all?
Why kill his mother?
Apart from doing their autopsies,
Wasden has no connection to them at all.
He might.
Grace was an accountant, remember?
The firm she worked for,
they took on extra work
during the tax season,
and one of the accounts
they worked... Saranac College.
So what? The coroner's office
just accidentally cremated a body
in an unsolved murder case?
Doesn't that sound weird to you?
It does, it does,
and we are going to figure out
what happened,
I promise you,
which is why I have a few more questions.
Did Josh ever mention a Dr. Wasden?
He was the man who did
your mother's autopsy.
Why?
He had something to do
with this, didn't he?
Right now, we just don't know.
- Ben!
- He'll be okay.
And what about you?
I'll be fine.
I'm just worried about Ben.
I mean...
does the name Arthur Wasden
mean anything to you?
Not that I can recall. Why?
Well, you and Grace worked together
for Saranac College, right?
You both did the books for them?
Yeah, that's why she chose the program
to donate her body to.
Obviously, she didn't think
it would happen so soon.
So if Grace had any old notes or files,
any idea where they may be?
Any way to log in to her accounts?
No, I'm sure they shut down
access when she died.
I'm really sorry. I wish I could help.
I'll be damned.
The one clue we're looking for
literally just walked right up to us.
- You have a cat?
- Oh.
Not really.
It's just a neighborhood stray.
I fed her once,
and now she comes in and out
like she owns the place.
Wait, are we really saying
she killed her best friend
and her best friend's son?
- Everything okay?
- Mia, get out of there.
Yeah, no, I'm a... um...
Let us get enough evidence for a warrant.
I just realized something.
You worked on
the Saranac College accounts
with Grace, didn't you?
Amelia, what are you doing?
What do you mean?
Your company's records will show
that you do know Dr. Wasden.
I really don't know
what you're talking about.
So whatever you
and Dr. Wasden were doing...
You and Grace must've been
really good friends,
because she confronted you
instead of turning you in,
and you repaid that kindness
by poisoning her?
Then you must've regretted it.
That's why you watch out for the boys.
Until, of course, Josh
got too close to the truth.
I want you to leave.
Amelia, we don't have enough
to detain her.
You'd be better served
to look for that cat
so we can match the hair.
I am not leaving her here with Ben.
Who are you talking to?
Ben. Ben!
Weapon!
I am not counting to three, Melissa.
Drop the knife.
Don't make me have to shoot you.
Drop it!
Hands behind your head.
Think we have enough to detain her now?
Oh, my God.
Any sign of Ben?
We just got off the phone with Ray Coyne.
Ben was there 15 minutes ago.
He told Ray he was sorry,
said he found out it was
someone at Saranac College
that killed Josh.
Ray went to call off work,
and when he came back,
Ben was gone.
Took his truck and his gun.
Oh, God.
I mentioned Wasden to Ben.
I mean... he asked me
if he was a suspect.
You didn't tell him
that we like him for it?
No, of course not.
Look, if he is headed to Saranac,
we need to get there before
Ben makes a huge mistake.
And another body ends up on that field.
That's Ray's truck,
and that must be Wasden's car.
- They're in there somewhere.
- Well, we have to find him.
We can't let Ben get to Wasden.
All right, fan out.
Backup will be here any minute.
Deep breaths. Stay alert.
Jeez.
You got anything?
Nothing moving.
They're entering the
confined location area now.
What does that mean?
Decomp farms store bodies
anyplace they can.
Submerged underwater, in car trunks,
stuffed in barrels.
Lots of places to hide.
Great.
Go back.
Blue car. Glass.
There's condensation
on the driver's side window.
Oh, someone's inside.
NYPD! Get out of the vehicle
and put your hands where I can see them!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
- He's behind you!
- Ben!
No.
Don't pull that trigger.
You don't wanna do this. Trust me.
Okay. I'm putting my gun away.
- Amelia!
- See?
Out of the way.
- He killed my brother.
- No!
No, Ben, Dr. Wasden
did not kill your brother.
You're lying. You're just saying that
- so I won't shoot him.
- No, I promise you.
He didn't kill your brother.
He didn't kill your mom, either.
Then who did?
Just put the gun down.
Then we can talk about it.
Okay?
I don't think you wanna shoot me.
Come on.
Put it down.
Easy, Ben.
- Easy, easy, easy.
- Good job.
Good job.
Okay, it's over now.
Okay?
It's okay.
Not very smart, doctor.
Put your hands up.
Melissa was the one who poisoned Grace.
Doesn't make any sense.
Grace discovered Melissa and Dr. Wasden
were embezzling from the college.
He talked her through how to do it,
and how to make it look
like she just died.
When Josh got too close
to figuring it out,
Melissa had to stop him.
She must've followed him
out there, they had a fight...
- That was her too?
- She panicked,
called Wasden.
He talked her through covering it up.
I thought it was you.
I'm sorry. I'm just...
Sorry.
All I ever wanted to do
was to be a father to you.
I want you to come home, Ben.
I'd like that.
What's that?
Your case, wrapped up,
with a bow on it.
- You actually put a bow on it?
- Yes.
Yes, I did.
You actually went to a store,
bought a bow,
and put it on a homicide case file.
I have bows at home.
Two homicides, by the way.
Sellitto finalized the
paperwork on both confessions.
These are just the forensics
finally adding up.
They always do.
Eventually.
Thank you, by the way,
for letting me go out in the field.
- Felt like old times.
- Of course.
Claire?
Yes?
I don't do apologies well.
You don't do them at all.
So we can skip to the part
where you know I didn't mean what I said?
We could,
or we could just jump to the part
where we realize that my job
is to take care of you
and not to push you.
Sometimes...
those are the same thing, aren't they?
Fred Hawkins,
our nauseatingly pleasant
firefighter friend.
Still have his number?
New York is famously inaccessible.
Only half the subway stops
have elevators.
There's traffic, cobblestone streets.
Tourists.
But everything can be navigated.
And sometimes, you
just gotta ask for help.
This may come as a surprise.
While I may be amazing
at a lot of things,
asking for help is not one of them.
Yeah, that's not surprising at all.
How do we do this?
Well, I could
painstakingly move each piece
with a pointer stick,
or we could...
- Ask for help.
- Right.
Not your comfort zone.
William, do you think you
could move these pieces for us?
Of course.
Thank you.
All right.
How about pawn to E4?
It's your move.
Felix.
He's back.
- How did it go?
- I beat him in seven moves.
You said you have something
on the Bone Collector.
So I looked into the phone
the Bone Collector used
in the surveillance footage.
Even isolating the signal,
I can't trace the number back
to a person.
But you're saying you were
able to isolate the signal?
Um... all right.
First hit? Farmington, New Mexico.
- Our man in the mirror.
- The mail drop.
Next up, we got Norman, Oklahoma.
Chesterfield, Missouri.
Springfield, Illinois.
Columbus, Ohio. Quakertown, PA.
I think we can safely extrapolate
where this path is heading.
To the greatest city in the world.
And to start the game all over again.
It's good to be home.