Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[ARABIC]
[People, help me, please!]
[Somebody help me, please!]
[-People, help me, please!]
[-What's going on?]
[Bring some water.]
[Bring him over.]
[-Bring him over.]
[-I don't know what happened.]
[Lay him down.
Get an ambulance. Let me see.]
[Give him some water.]
[Some water, quick!]
[-What happened to him?]
-[Move over.]
[-I was hurt.]
[-What is it? Let me see.]
[Anybody who moves gets
a bullet in the head! Back off!]
[Back off!]
-Is everyone alright?
-Yes.
[-What did I do?]
[-Quiet!]
[-Quiet.]
[You wanted to smuggle in
nerve gas through Aqaba]
[and explosives through Syria.]
[I see you know everything.
So what do you want from me?]
[Someone's fixing us a big "shabang"
and we don't know who.]
[Neither do I.]
[Listen, I know you're worried too,
not just me.]
[Want one?]
[I don't smoke.]
[Why not?]
[Look,]
[with the treatment
she's getting,]
[Nadia could live for two years
maximum in total misery and then--]
[In our society,
someone of your status]
[would've gotten his daughter a kidney
transplant in Hadassah long ago,]
[but in your society, the Authority
gives preference to its people]
[and your children are at the
bottom of the priority list.]
[You could save her life,]
[your daughter could live well
like her friends do,]
[like she deserves.]
[I'm doing everything
in my power.]
[Ali, I've got five children,
may God keep them safe.]
[I promise you that if one of them
were in Nadia's condition,]
[I'd jump through hoops for him.]
[Nothing would stop me.]
[Ali, who's behind
the nerve gas story in Aqaba?]
[I'd kill everyone on this earth
for my daughter.]
[I'd give up my life for her,
no questions asked.]
[You, sir, all you need to do is
give me one name.]
[One name, Ali.
And we'll take care of your kid.]
[-Abu Ahmad.]
[-Who?]
[Abu Ahmad. Taufiq Hammed.]
[You're making fun of me.]
[This won't end well.]
[I swear to you.]
[-The Panther.]
[-The Panther is dead. We killed him.]
-Stop!
-You had it coming!
Stop!
Let's see what you've got.
You can feel the astringency.
-Is that merlot?
-It's not ready yet, Moreno.
Why are you here?
Abu Ahmad is alive.
-Which Abu Ahmad?
-Your Panther.
-Impossible. I killed him.
-Sadly, it is possible.
But don't sweat it,
he won't be alive much longer.
We're finishing him tomorrow
at his brother's wedding.
We got a heads-up he'll be there.
Most likely.
But I killed him, Moreno,
what's going on?
That's why I wanted you
to hear about it from me.
-But there was a funeral for him.
-Yes, there was.
I'm just not sure the team will get
a definite visual of him on field,
so I could use someone
who's already killed him before.
Look, if you feel unready to be
on field, stay in the command post.
We'll equip the team with cams,
you'll identify the bastard
and they'll finish him.
You'll get to cheer them
and eat all their pastries.
It's only for two hours.
What do you say?
Two hours. It'll be quite a show.
No, no, no. No way.
Too bad. I thought
you'd jump at the opportunity.
Opportunity?
To settle the score.
I've settled my score with the
Panther a long time ago.
I have a new life,
I'm happy.
I meant, settle the score
with yourself.
SILWAD VILLAGE
NORTH OF RAMALLAH
[-Congrats, groom.]
[-Thanks, take care.]
[-Shut up and you'll be fine.]
[-Let me go!]
[-I'm getting married tomorrow!]
[-Get in!]
[Let me out!]
[Please, help me,
I have to get out of here.]
[I didn't do anything.]
[Taufiq?]
[Wow, it's been 18 months
since someone called me Taufiq.]
[I've missed you guys.]
[I've missed you.]
[I can't believe my little brother
Bashir is getting married.]
[Stop crying.]
[Stop, or your eyes
will swell up.]
[Will you be at the wedding?]
[I'm a Shahid (martyr).
Shahids don't go to weddings.]
[But the Jews have stopped
looking for you.]
[Right, and I don't want them
to start all over again.]
[Take this, Brother.
It's a gift for you and Amal.]
[I couldn't.]
[Take it, don't let me down.]
[Groom.]
[Taufiq, you must see Amal,
she's so pretty.]
Dad?
What's up, sweetie?
What are you doing?
Give me the keys.
-Where are you headed? To Moreno?
-Yes. Give me the keys.
-Why get into this again?
-I'm not, don't worry.
So then why are you going?
To take care
of something and come back.
-Give me the keys.
-Let someone else take care of it.
Come on, give me the keys!
How could you do this
without telling me?
Is this because I'm doing it
or because I didn't tell you?
You need to discuss
things like that with me!
-What's there to discuss?
-A lot!
We have two kids at home
who need you.
-Gali, give me the keys.
-No way.
Give me the keys!
Talk to me for five minutes,
and I will.
For fuck's sake!
Doron!
Team 8200 will handle
the antenna
that'll pick up the signal
400 meters from the house.
The problem is
access to the house.
We can't physically block the area
and risk exposing our team.
I was thinking--
[-Good morning.]
[-Hey, handsome!]
[-My dear.]
[-How are you?]
[-Fine.]
[Our main man,
so good to see you.]
[-How are you, buddy?]
[-What's up?]
[-I'm fine, and you?]
[-Alive and well.]
Doron will remain in the command post
during the operation.
Moreno, I decided
to join the team on the field.
Anything you care
to share with me?
Didn't you tell him?
You said you wanted
to squash grapes.
Doron will help us
identify Abu Ahmad.
He's the only one
who saw him alive.
Bro, it's your call.
I don't want to interfere, okay?
If you want me in the command post,
I'll stay there. It's your call.
-Look who's here.
-Bro! Move over.
-What's up?
-Get a load of this hunk.
Give us a hug, man.
Bashir Hammed, the Panther's younger
brother, is getting married today,
and we'll be there too.
Abu Ahmad might show up.
According to Intelligence,
he's still alive.
How? Didn't Doron kill him
18 months ago?
-Apparently, he didn't.
-Ali Karmi claims he's still around
and we must
at least check it out.
But Moreno, he hasn't been on
the field in 18 months. No offence.
-What's with you?
-What's the matter?
Hey, this isn't open for debate.
Eli will go over the plan
with you and...
you'll be nice.
I don't get it,
we're going to kill a dead person?
Everyone,
study the route carefully,
especially this emergency
rescue spot.
And this spot
is the helicopter meeting point.
Steve, you lead the way.
Avihai,
according to aerial photographs,
you have a 50 meter clearance
to reach the house
and the street.
Naor comes in as a guest.
Doron and I enter with the pastries.
-Boaz, you'll be at the observation
post. -No way. I'm going in.
Look, we can't both
enter the house.
-It's not fair towards Gali.
-What's she got to do with it?
She's my wife and your sister,
that's what.
Eli and I decided
you'll block the street.
-Eli, come on!
-It's not up for discussion.
Boaz, are you a child?
It's a big operation, with many
people, entrances and exits.
I need someone outside.
Should that be me?
Field radios open, no talking
unless we're exposed.
Remember who we're dealing with.
Abu Ahmad killed 116 Israelis
in suicide bombings
that he himself carried out.
116 Israelis.
He's killed more than
any other terrorist.
Women,
children,
elderly,
and soldiers.
The bastard is a murderer
and a dead man.
He's a dead man!
Today we're settling
the score with him.
Good luck.
[Make it shorter
so it doesn't drag along the floor.]
[Hold on, I'll be right back.]
[What are you doing here?
Did anyone see you come in?]
[Of course not. They're all busy
getting groomed and pretty.]
[I can't wait for this mess
to be over!]
[Now it's just you and me here.]
[You're crazy,
wait for tonight.]
[You're a better person
than me.]
[Of course,
a million times better.]
[What's this?]
[-A wedding present.]
[-From whom?]
[Bashir, I don't take money
without knowing whom it's from.]
[I know whom it's from.
Don't you trust me?]
[We'll build a house with this money
and raise lots of kids.]
[No, no, no.]
[Wait for tonight, crazy girl.]
-Get out of the car.
-Why?
Just get out.
Soldier, bro,
I have to get to a wedding.
You're backing up traffic.
Move it.
-Move.
-Come on,
you can see the car
is full of wedding pastries.
Come on.
Get in the jeep.
[-Peace be upon you.]
[Congratulations, groom.]
[-Congratulations.]
[-Thanks.]
DAUD'S KNAFEH PASTRIES
[Welcome, dear guests.]
[We're here on this joyous occasion
that celebrates happiness and love,]
[but I'd like to just mention
my younger brother,]
[Abu Taufiq, may he rest in peace,
Bashir's father,]
[and Abu Ahmad,
Taufiq Mustafa Hammed,]
[the brave Panther and
Shahid (martyr), Bashir's brother,]
[who I wish
was with us today.]
[With us, however, is Nassrin,
Abu Ahmad's brave wife.]
[Let us say the "Fatiha"
to pray for their souls.]
["Fatiha".]
[-May God have mercy on us all.]
[When I see you, Bashir,
and you, Amal,]
[I say to myself,
this is the best revenge.]
[Despite all that the occupation
has done to us,]
[we still bear children.]
[We're successful, we raise families,
have children and prosper.]
[-Here you go, Abu Khalil.]
[-Thank you.]
[May God have mercy on us all.]
[We'd like to thank brother Abu Khalil
for coming specially from Amman.]
[And now, dear guests,
it's time to celebrate.]
[May God bring joy to you all.]
[Let's sing and dance.]
So, how's civilian life?
How are the olives?
No, no olives.
I grow grapes. I make wine.
Like merlot, Bordeaux?
That stuff?
Bordeaux is a place, bro.
Not a grape.
You've really cleaned up, ah?
So, how's Gali doing?
Boaz said she's thrilled
to have you home again.
Yeah, we're happy,
you know.
I don't know, bro.
-Samir.
-Copy.
Your boss at the bakery just
got a call, someone saw the arrest.
-Does the mother know about it?
-Not as far as we know.
Should we go back, Eli?
You want to go back?
I don't know,
are they on to us or not?
-Moreno, are they on to us or not?
-No, nobody's on to you.
Relax, I was just filling you in.
Chill out, it'll be alright.
Those two are like the old guys
from "The Puppets".
"The Muppets".
How do you know that show?
It was aired before you were born.
-You know I know everything.
-May God help me.
[Do you think
he'll show up?]
[I don't know.
You know I'm against it.]
[Why should he show up now?]
[He wants to see you,
don't you realize that?]
[But why now of all times?
Just to put himself in danger?]
[Now's not the time to discuss this.
It's Bashir's wedding. Let's go.]
[-Peace be upon you.]
[-Upon you be peace.]
[-Are you from
"Daud's Knafeh Pastries"? -Yes.]
[I'm Samir and this is Najib.
We'll take care of your wedding.]
[God willing, I hope so.]
[-What took you so long?]
[-We got held up a bit at the checkpoint.]
[Good thing you're here,]
[because leaving the Hammed family
with no sweets is a crime.]
[Go on, start serving.
Lower the flame.]
[-He's in the area, he should be here.]
[-How do you know?]
[His wife told me.]
Getting married, ah? Idiots.
-How's your ex-wife?
-Which one?
Moreno, get married already, so you
can get divorced and live it up.
What's up, Chuck Nurit?
Wanna marry me?
I don't believe it.
It's Amjad Abu Khalef.
We've been on his tail for two years!
-Not now.
-Hell yeah. Tell them to get him.
-Forget Abu Khalef now.
[Don't worry.]
[Thank you very much.]
[-What is it?]
[-The guy from "Daud's Knafeh Pastries".]
[He called to apologize that his guys
are held up at the checkpoint.]
[What? But they're here.]
[Tell them to call him
and calm him down. Call him.]
[They suspect us.]
[We have a problem.]
[What is it?]
[They're looking at us.]
[They must be on to us.
Let's go.]
[-Give me a minute.]
[-No, we have to go now!]
[Guys, please help us
move a table outside.]
[Sorry, we're in a big rush,
we have another event to get to.]
[You arrived late and now you won't
help? Don't make the guests work.]
[-Sorry, we're in a rush.]
[-Just five minutes.]
[Come with us.]
[Just five minutes. Come.]
[Please.]
[-Not a word.]
[-What did we do?]
[Not a word!
Answer only when spoken to.]
[We spoke to your boss.]
[We asked
where his workers are,]
[the ones who got held up
at the checkpoint.]
[-And?]
[-He said he sent two workers,]
[one with green eyes
and black hair with gel,]
[and the other is dark and fat.]
[We changed the staff last minute.
Abu Eyad wasn't at the bakery then.]
[I'm not buying this bullshit.]
[Sir, I'm really sorry
about the misunderstanding.]
[Please call him again.]
[Tell him they sent
Samir and Najib over instead.]
[Call him.]
Turn off their cellular reception.
No calls can get through beyond
a 200-meter radius of the house.
[It's busy.]
[-Sir--]
[-Step back!]
[You want to kill me?]
[I have a family to provide for.
The checkpoint held us back.]
[We have another wedding
to get to.]
[-I beg you, talk to him.]
[-Dial.]
[Still busy.]
[Sir, I'd hate to keep
the other family waiting.]
[If our boss hears we got there late
and that we upset you as well--]
[-Alright.]
[-Alright?]
[-Thank you.]
[Why?]
[Fauda, fauda (Chaos)!]
[Steve, get to the meeting point!]
[Move back!]
[Bashir!]
[Amal!]
[Bashir! Bashir!]
[Bashir!]
[Get out of here!]
[Let me through!
Let me through!]
-What's going on?
-He fucked up my leg!
-Drive, drive!
-God damn it!
[Stay with me.]
That's Abu Ahmad!
Stop the car!
I told you to stop!
Get in the car, Doron!
That's an order!
Reporting, abort! Abort!
Drive! Drive!
-I can't go through here!
-Follow him!
-They're in for one hell of a fauda.
-Those damn bastards.
Calm down.
-Avihai, contact Moreno.
-Okay, okay.
Moreno, do you copy?
Doron escaped, chasing some old guy.
He's sure it's Abu Ahmad.
The entire village is on your tail.
Get out now!
-Where's Doron?
-I don't know, Moreno.
Nurit,
send a chopper in right now.
Now, now, now!
-It'll be okay, relax.
-Why did he leave the vehicle?
-Why did he get out?
-He saw Abu Ahmad.
-He thinks he saw Abu Ahmad.
-I'm not ditching him, Eli!
Get in, get in!
They're headed west,
two alleys north of you.
-There he is, can't you see?
-Drive.
What's this here?
Turn on the flashlight.
Moreno, what's going on?
Do you see Doron?
You're inches away from him,
I repeat, inches away.
There are three men running east,
200 meters ahead of you.
There!
Guys, get ready for action.
[He's here, he's here.]
[He's here, I just know he is.]
[-Come on.]
[-He's here.]
[Enough, come on.]
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN