Go, go, they're driving off.
We're leaving.
-There's someone in the passenger seat.
-Any ID?
-It's not Walid, it's someone else.
-Maintain the status quo.
Eli! Someone got in without our notice,
Walid could be in the back seat.
-Steve, get closer.
-Copy. On our way.
[ARABIC]
[I know you've been betraying me.]
[-No...]
[-Be quiet.]
[-Walid...]
[-I said, be quiet!]
[Take it.]
[Look what I found.]
[Where are you traveling to?]
[Nowhere, I always carry it with me.]
[What is that?]
[I had no idea about that!]
[I'm sorry.]
[I didn't know, I'm sorry.]
We've lost the signal.
Guys, we've lost her signal.
-What?!
-Keep them in sight.
They must've found her passport.
[Walid... I'm sorry, Walid.]
[What did those dogs promise you
to sell me out?]
[I'd never do that, Walid. I love you.]
[-Walid...]
[-We were supposed to have children.]
[We're working on it, aren't we?]
[You must die! Now!]
[Close your eyes.]
[-Walid, what's gotten into you?]
[-Close your eyes.]
Eli, I'm about to lose sight of them.
You've got clearance.
Go, go, go!
[Taxi, halt!]
[Pull over.]
[Stop over there.]
[You keep your mouth shut, understood?!]
[Hey, bro, everything alright?]
[License and registration, please.]
[Here you go.]
[Is there a problem?]
[I don't know.]
[Do you know this man?]
[He's my husband.]
[Your husband.]
[It's him.]
[Step out of the car, please.]
[You, too.]
[-I swear I'll kill her!]
[-Drop your weapon!]
[-Drop your weapon, you son of a bitch!]
[Drop your weapon or I'll kill her!]
[I'll kill her!]
[On your knees!]
Doron! Doron!
Bro, let go of him!
We got Walid, I repeat, we got Walid.
Three to five gunmen.
We're engaging in battle.
Give me a sec.
[Are you alright?]
[We couldn't tell
if he was in the car or not.]
[Well, he was.]
[I know, and we caught him.]
[-Why did you tamper with my passport?]
[-I knew nothing about that,]
[really, I swear.]
[I'm such a fool.
Why did I ever believe you?]
[Enough, it's over.] [He destroyed my passport!]
[We'll issue you a new one.]
[You did your part.]
[Where will I be until then?]
[Give me a minute.]
No talking to him during the ride
so that he "sings" later on.
No problem.
What is she to do now?
-We'll take her in until her flight.
-I'm not keeping her in detention, Gabi.
-Expect me to put her up at the Hilton?
-Yes.
I never put a lead up at a hotel
in Tel Aviv, are you nuts?
I'll see if the apartment in Givatayim
is vacant.
Thanks.
-If it's occupied, vacate it, okay?
[-Yes, "sir."]
-I'll ask Ronen to update you every hour.
-Why Ronen?
-He's taking her there.
-I am.
-You wish.
-Gabi, look at her.
[Oh, man...]
Let me end this properly, okay? Please?
Fine. And clean yourself up,
you can't walk around Givatayim like that.
Thanks.
Hey, hey, hey!
Soldier, halt.
I'm taking her, it's okay.
Alright? Thank you.
[I'm sorry. Come with me.]
[I would’ve never agreed to this
had I known it would turn out this way.]
[-You thought he'd just hop in the car?]
[-I didn't think I'd be there to see it.]
[Fine. Buckle up.]
Bravo!
Don't stop. Keep pouring.
Is everyone set?
-You call this cheap crap "being set"?
-That's all the budget we have.
Well, I sincerely want to thank you all
for your truly exceptional work.
We caught that piece of shit!
I can tell you that I'm happier today
than I was the day we wiped out Al Jabari.
And y'all know why.
To Boaz.
-To Boaz.
-I want to keep it short.
-So keep it short.
This unit has suffered
some serious losses,
but you've managed to recover,
and that's downright admirable.
It's a pleasure working with you.
Some tough missions lay ahead for us,
but I'm sure we'll accomplish them all.
[They've caught Walid
and Hassan has fallen Shahid.]
["Never think of those who have been
killed in the cause of God as dead.]
[Rather, they are alive with their Lord,
receiving provision."]
[God's infinite justice.]
[He'll talk.]
[He won't. He doesn't know
about this apartment, either.]
[In the end they all talk.]
[Which is why we must carry out
our plan faster. We don't have time.]
[What do you mean, "we don’t have time"?]
[Nidal,]
[now that Walid is out,
you can replace him.]
[Samir,]
[even if they threaten to behead me,
I'll never work for Abu Samara.]
[This is your chance to become commander.
Who besides you can lead the movement?]
[That snake hates me
just as much as he hated Abu Nidal.]
[If you leave Hamas,]
[your men will leave you.]
[-I won't degrade myself, Samir.]
[-Degrade?!]
[I have a detailed plan.
I'm not wasting my time now.]
[When will you get Marwa and me
out of here?]
[Now's not a good time.]
[What's that?]
[I promised Marwa that we'd leave,
based on what you said.]
[Samir, getting you out
would mean transferring you to Jordan,]
[where the Jordanian Intelligence
is waiting to catch you.]
[Then I'll escape to Qatar, to Doha.]
[I know Hamas has ties there,
they'd find me a job.]
[Samir.]
[Samir...]
[To get both of you out of here without
getting caught, we'd need money! A lot!]
[And I refuse to beg Hamas!
Now, let me solve this my own way.]
[Understood?]
[I can't hear you.]
[Understood.]
[Good.]
[We're almost there.]
-Hey, how are you?
-Fine, and you?
Alright.
Go on up, I'll buzz you in.
[If you'd like to shower,
there are clean towels on the bed.]
[Where's Walid?]
[He's fine,
he's in the detention facility.]
[-What will they do to him?]
[-They're interrogating him.]
[You did the right thing.]
[Good night.]
[I can stay a bit longer.]
[I'd like to get some sleep.]
[Go.]
[Are you sure?]
-Hey.
-What's up?
[Shirin.]
[Leave me alone.]
[You're not staying here.]
[He'll kill me.]
[He's in jail.]
[-He'll send someone.]
[-I won't let that happen.]
[You think I believe anything you say?]
[Are you done feeling sorry for yourself?]
[Come on, get up.]
[-Come with me.]
[-Where to?]
[Home, with me.]
[-Your home?]
[-Would you rather stay here?]
[Let's go.]
[Come on, let's go.]
[Come.]
[How are you, Walid?]
[Praise God.]
[I'm Amira. Sorry we get to meet
under these circumstances.]
[Is there anything you need?]
[Can I help you in any way?]
[Have you had anything to eat or drink?]
[Do you really care?]
[Of course I do.]
[I don't like the way
they tied your hands.]
[I'll ask the guard to untie you.]
[In any case, you'll have to stand trial
for several indictments,]
[that's for certain.]
[But if you help me, we could help you.]
[Your friend Nidal,
who calls himself Al Makdasi.]
[Your wife
was more communicative than you.]
[She's smart.]
[Your exact opposite.]
[If that's so, then I'm proud to be dumb.]
[Why do you say that?]
[Look how pretty she is.]
[I bet you'll miss her.]
[I'll just leave this here for you.]
[I'll be back soon, so you can give me
some details about Al Makdasi.]
[I thank you all
for coming here today.]
[I don't take it for granted.]
[-What happened with Walid?]
[-I heard someone ratted him out.]
[We've heard all sorts of rumors lately,
but one thing we know for sure is]
[that Hassan and Jihad got to be Shahids,
in the name of God.]
[Two grooms in heaven,
[As Shahids,
will Hamas support their families?]
[Only God knows.]
[But now, with Walid in jail
and Hamas stuck in its tracks,]
[this is our chance.]
[Once we get to work,
we'll be unstoppable.]
[And I know very well that
you all need financial support.]
[God willing,
I'll get some cash tonight.]
[I promise you,]
[I have a whole plan figured out.]
[My good men,]
[Israel does not want peace.]
[Trust me, they left us with no choice
but the Resistance.]
[And you are the Resistance.]
[You are hope.]
[Let us unite]
[and with the help of God]
[we'll do things that no Zionist mind
could ever imagine.]
Well?
[Who's with me?]
[I'm with you.]
[-Me, too.]
[-So am I.]
[Ali?]
[I'm with you.]
[Nizar, check this out.]
[Nidal.]
[One second, guys.]
[What is it?]
[-I think my dad is suspicious.]
[-Why?]
[He keeps asking me where I am
and why I'm not at home.]
[What else?]
[-He searched my room.]
[-Did he find anything?]
[-No, I don't bring anything home.]
[-Any chance someone followed you here?]
[No, I don't think so.]
[Go home now,]
[stay with your family,]
[and go back to university.]
[-And?]
[-And that's it.]
[What? But, Nidal, you promised
I'd take part in an attack.]
[Maher, your time will come.]
[You'll be of more help to us
if your father trusts you.]
[Maher,]
[respect your father.]
[He is first and foremost your father.]
Hello?
-Did you drop her off at the apartment?
-Yes, a while ago.
Then why did the guard
tell me you took her out of there?
-We're going out to eat.
-Doron.
-What?
-Think carefully about what you're doing.
We're going out to eat,
what's the big deal?
Then order take-out, return to
the apartment and keep an eye on her.
I'm not taking my eyes off of her,
trust me.
Hamas is threatening to carry out
retaliation attacks following the arrest
of Izz ad-Din al-Qassam commander
Walid Al-Abed.
Head of Hamas' political wing
Mohammed Issa stated that...
[That's a French song.]
There isn't enough time
Come to the garden
The days are sad and hollow
Since you left me...
[You sing horribly.]
[Hungry?]
Ready to order?
[What would you like?]
[This. And I'll start with that.]
Okay. Some tahini and a salad, please.
Anything to drink?
[What are you drinking?]
-Water, please.
-I'll have a beer.
No problem.
[-Did you see the look she gave me?]
[-She's just a grouchy waitress.]
[-It must be my looks.]
[-You look like a princess.]
[I have to use the restroom.]
"Stuck at work.
I'll be home in a few hours."
"Gali: Don't bother. The kids are asleep."
"Call me if there's a problem."
[Everything alright?]
[Sure, why do you ask?]
[That was just my ex-wife.]
[Why did you get divorced?]
[Shirin, how about some small talk?]
[I think we're past that phase.]
[-We didn't get along.]
[-Why not?]
[I'm not sure.]
[At first I thought it was
because of my job, so I quit,]
[wanting to build a normal life for us.]
[You? A normal life?]
[Yes, I want peace and quiet.]
[So if you left, why didn't it work out?]
[She cheated on me.]
[That's life.]
Thanks.
[-Enjoy your meal.]
[-You, too.]
Say, couldn't those cheapskates
put you up in a hotel?
I didn't want that.
Come spend the weekend at our place.
-I couldn't.
-Sure, you could,
-you'll help me paint the gazebo.
-Screw you.
-When are you flying back?
-I don't know.
Miss home?
My son Ron cries whenever I call.
Poor kid.
I asked if you miss home.
I'm dead inside.
I can't sleep.
Take a sleeping pill, bro.
I'm on something else, I can't mix meds.
Viagra?
Pretty close.
What, then? Psychiatric?
Have you ever been in therapy?
Me, talking to someone for an hour...?
How do you say "post-trauma" in Arabic?
"Bost-trauma."
[Where've you been?]
[And don't you dare lie to me.]
[With friends.]
[With whom? Where? What did you do?]
[I'm not a little kid
who has to tell you everything!]
[Don't move when I'm talking to you!]
[-What did I do?!]
[-Why are you two yelling?]
[-You're waking up the neighbors.]
[-He's lying to my face.]
[-What's going on?]
[-Nothing. I was with friends.]
[This is between me and him.]
[Excuse me?]
[Fine, but keep it down.]
[I'm sorry.]
[What are you sorry about?]
[For lying to you.]
[Then talk. Tell me the truth.] [It's not that complicated.]
[-I know.]
[-Come on, tell me, I'm your father.]
[Talk.]
[There's this girl... but we didn't
do anything and it's over, I swear.]
[A girl?] [Fine. Go take a shower.]
[Did you two make up?]
[He said he's sorry,
said he was with a girl.]
[That's the last thing we needed.]
[I don't know.]
[Should I believe him or not?]
[Try to be more sensitive towards him.]
[For me.]
[He has to feel
that he can tell us anything.]
[Don't scare him away.]
[I'm scaring him away?]
[That boy is my life.]
[Don't forget, he's a very sensitive kid.]
[Fine. Don't worry.]
[Good night.]
[Give me the bolt cutter.]
[Hold this.]
[One, two, three...]
Doron?
Everything okay?
-Yes, sorry, didn't mean to wake you.
-I wasn't asleep.
[Shirin, this is my dad, Amos.
Amos, this is Shirin.]
[-Nice to meet you.]
[-Same here.]
[Shirin will be staying with us
for a few days.]
Alright, in my room
there are sheets, towels,
-whatever you need.
-Cool. I'll go get them.
[Be right back.]
[-Sorry for the inconvenience.]
[-No, no, it's fine.]
[Go ahead, it's the door on the left.]
[Thank you.]
-Where are the sheets?
-Upper shelf.
Doron,
-no good can come of this.
-I know.
[Well, let's take a break.]
[I'll be leaving soon.]
[I don't intend to talk.]
[You don't have to.]
[Just write down everything you know.]
[Where you last saw him,
how you contact Al Makdasi, everything.]
[May it be God's will that
you burn in hell until Judgment Day,]
[you evil spawn of Satan!]
Enough.
[Where is Al Makdasi?]
[In hell, where I hope you end up.]
More, please.
Stop.
[Where is Al Makdasi?]
[You think I'm stupid?]
[That your stupid strategies
will get me to talk?]
[You can't touch me.]
[Tell Gabi...]
[I know his name is Gabi...]
[that I will personally hunt him down]
[and murder him and his children.]
Ayub! Ayub!
-Ayub! Ayub!
-Move!
You'll have me kicked out over this!
Keep him in stress position for 12 hours.
[Motherfucker!]
[Hello?]
[We've been robbed.]
[-What did they take?]
[-50,000 shekels.]
[But I think I know
the son of a bitch who did this.]
[That bastard!]
[Sweet dreams.]
[Thank you.]
[Doron...]
[Could you sit here until I fall asleep?]
[Sure.]
[Thank you.]
[You're welcome.]
[Here.]
[Thanks.]