Welcome to a very special
season of The Amazing Race.
Well, hello, everyone!
My name is Tyler
Oakley. -Korey Kuhl.
I'm Joslyn Davis.
-And I'm Erin Robinson.
These 11 teams connect with
millions of people every day.
SuperVine in Birmingham!
(ALL SCREAM)
What happens when you take
the world's biggest social
influencers offline...
This is how I hitchhike.
Whoo!
Amazing. -Amazing.
...to race each other
in the real world?
Time to find out!
COLE: Mom!
(PHONES RING)
Our teams are at home
and have no idea the race
is about to start now.
Mom! BLAIR: Phil Keoghan!
Oh, my God, wait. How do I
get it? -What do you want, Phil?
PHIL: You're about to embark
on the adventure of a lifetime.
In just 21 days, you'll visit
18 cities in 10 countries
and travel more
than 27,000 miles.
Oh. Oh! Oh!
And I have your next
clue here in Mexico City
at the Monument
of the Revolution.
Monument of the Revolution.
We're going to Mexico City!
We couldn't even find our
way back home last night.
When I say 'go', grab
your bags, run outside,
make your way to the nearest airport
and then find me here in Mexico.
Whoo!
(SCREAMS)
Let's get things started.
We're starting right
now! Oh, my God.
The world is waiting for you.
Oh, my God! Good luck.
Travel safe!
-Travel safe.
No way.
-Let's go, Phil.
Oh, man!
-What the heck?
Go!
BOTH: Go!
(LAUGHS)
Oh, my God.
Alright, go! Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
-OK, grab this.
(SQUEALS)
Good luck, alright?
(SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
Alright, gotta go.
You tryin' to do that?
Are you tryin' to do that?
Oh, my God. -Wait,
Joslyn, you speak Spanish.
Si! Si! Vamonos.
I'm not even crying.
Bye. I love you. -Bye,
Mama. I love you, too.
Let's go, baby!
(SCREAMS INDISTINCTLY)
Daddy! Daddy!
Got my passport.
Alright, let's go.
Mexico City. We're going.
(ALL TALK OVER ONE ANOTHER)
Oh, there's our cab,
right over there.
Oh, my God!
Going to Mexico! How
do we get to Mexico?
Hi. We need to
get to the airport.
TYLER: Hi.
KOREY: Yeah.
Something like that.
KURT: I'm in!
Are you driving us to Mexico?
We are headed to
Mexico City. -Whoo!
To get that message from Phil, just
starting right now, it's so surreal.
I can't believe this is
happening. -Oh, my God.
Dream come true right now.
We're racing from home.
Like, what's going on?
Yeah, it's crazy.
This is definitely...
You really threw us
for a loop on this one.
Do you have the passports?
-Don't freak me out like that.
Welcome...to... BOTH:
The Amazing Race.
# Dah dah dah,
dah-dah-dah... #
I just love that song.
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
Thank you.
Oh, you want my
autograph? MAN: Yes, sir!
So cute.
Tyler and I met in college
at Michigan State University.
The day we met was actually the
day I made my YouTube channel.
You all look
incredible. (LAUGHTER)
We make videos online and
we have a podcast together.
I think that people watch us
because they might not feel
like they have somebody
that they can connect to.
I didn't have somebody
like that growing up.
Like, I may have had
gay characters on TV,
but I couldn't go online and find
somebody just sharing themselves.
Oh, my God.
We're super fans
of The Amazing Race.
We are 100% going to win. -You
can write the cheque right now.
Yeah. -We'll take it.
Monumento a la Revolucion.
There you go, but you're
making it sound French.
I know. Revolucion.
(LAUGHS)
Matt and I are in kind of
a high-stakes relationship
because we don't only work
really closely together,
but we have been engaged for
almost three and a half years.
We have not set a
wedding date yet.
Welcome to Dance
Tutorials Live -
the best place online
to learn how to dance.
I'm a choreographer,
a dancer and teacher
and I also produce the largest
dance YouTube channel in the world.
Yeah, I think that the
race is make or break.
It can be a huge boost for us
in just trusting each other.
I'm so excited. Oh, my gosh.
Working out! Working out!
Joslyn and I are internet hosts
and producers at Clevver Media.
Clevver is the number one
entertainment news outlet on YouTube.
Snap, snap, snap. Slay.
You know I'm excited
to do the race with you.
Yeah.
Zach and I met almost
three years ago.
Rachel was the first
girl that I ever kissed.
We have been married
for almost 11 months.
Whoo!
I make Vine videos.
In those six seconds, there'll
be a little bit of magic.
I kept growing the channel
and now it's at a place
where it's kind of thrown us for
a whirlwind for the last few years.
We are incredibly excited.
Pumped. Take a deep breath.
I'm an attorney and I'm
also an OBGYN by profession.
Work that runway.
It was hard on me when
Blair left at the age of 17
to pursue her
career on YouTube.
Mainly my videos are
make-up and hair tutorials.
I can't believe what started
out as a hobby in my bedroom
filming videos - not
like that, Daddy -
was turning into this.
I am single for the
race and I am not afraid
to use a little bit of Southern
charm to maybe try to help us.
We bring age and maturity.
-And I bring the lipstick.
COLE: I'm kind of sad.
You know, we're both big
family people so we...
..we never leave.
My name is Cole Brant and
this is my mom. I'm her son.
My career has been
being a mom of six kids.
I do feel that
this race is a way
that I can show my
family a different side.
Mom, I'm going out.
-Is your room clean?
She'll never notice.
I really just
make funny videos.
And if you look
through my Vine page,
you'll see videos that I
make with my mom and dad.
Pretty sure that my fans like my
parents more than they like me,
so I've got to throw
them in there a lot.
It sounds like it's going to
be a lot of social media people.
That's what I do for a living.
I make videos on, you
know, frisbee trick shots.
We met at the 2006 Ultimate Frisbee
season at the University of Florida.
We ended up winning a national
championship together, so...
Oh!
My whole thing is
just trying to get
people excited about
throwing the frisbee.
It's been a real blast.
Being on the race, we're
definitely confident.
Brodie is the single one
on this trip. I am single.
We deal with hot chicks all the
time 'cause we're frisbee guys.
Brodie sometimes gets
distracted by certain things
and so I just have
to keep him on course.
This is gonna be the
time of our lives.
I know. Can you believe
we're doing this?
We have been dating for
the last three years.
And working together.
-We also work together.
And living together. -So we
spend a lot of time together.
Ashley started her career
as a professional gamer.
I knew who you were.
I was a big fan.
I was one of the first
members on his website.
We run an online video
channel all about video games
called Rooster Teeth.
Our first show that we
made, Red Versus Blue,
is the longest running web series
in the history of the internet.
Being a lifelong gamer, what we're
so excited about with the race
is that it takes the whole world
and turns it into one giant game.
We couldn't imagine
anything better.
Horrible, Jessica. Terrible.
Is it Cole and his mom? Yes!
We knew you guys would
be here. Wakey, wakey!
We just ran into Cole and
Sheri and we love them.
I knew who Cole was
from social media.
You guys haven't eaten
at all or anything?
No, we're starving. We're used
to it anyways. We're models.
Instagram has
definitely helped us.
It's something new that they're
integrating within modelling.
Clients say, "If we
send you this swimsuit,
"will you Instagram
a hot photo of it?"
And the more followers you
have, the more money you get.
We are absolutely planning on
using our looks if we need to.
We only have what we brought
and I guess we're bringing it.
I mean, to be woken up by
two models, it was usual.
Cole is strong. -Yes.
He's young, he's
smart. He's athletic.
I believe in multiple girlfriends.
I believe in multiple wives.
Are we cougars?
Maybe.
If we were in college,
we would go after Cole.
I might knock on his
dorm. In college only.
Oh, my God! It's
Tyler. (SCREAMS)
Oh, my God! (SCREAMS)
Wait, come love me.
How are you?
-Hi, how are you?
I've met Tyler Oakley before and
we have a lot of mutual friends.
I love his videos
and I am a huge fan.
Hi.
Sure.
Thank you so much. Of
course. Nice to meet you.
Do you do YouTube or...?
She does. She did YouTube.
Oh, what kind of videos?
Well, she did one viral video.
There's this Southwest flight
attendant, like, it went viral.
I've heard of that.
Everybody gets their very own
teeny weeny yellow Southwest bikini.
One size fits all.
I'm a flight attendant
for Southwest Airlines.
I've been flying
for about nine years.
I just like to put
my own spin on it
and I just feel like people kind of
pay attention more when it's funny
and it went viral
and within a week, we had 10
million and now it's 22 million.
I'm a single mom and we're both
pretty protective of each other.
I may not agree with every date
she's ever had in this world.
But she doesn't agree
with all my dates either.
OK, so what do y'all
do on social media?
We make Vines. -You do?
So my brother thinks
he's Barack Obama.
I'm running for president.
It's class president,
dude. -Haters gonna hate.
I don't think people would
actually assume that we are smart
from just looking
at our videos.
My mom went to
Harvard and made sure
that we were set in
terms of academics.
We were homeschooled.
We want to appear not too smart, but
we are gonna win The Amazing Race.
I can't believe I'm
meeting you right now.
ASHLEY: Burnie is very popular in
airports. He gets recognised a lot.
You guys made it...like, helped
me through some rough times.
We are the official pilots
for our flight to Mexico City.
Come aboard Mexico City
with Britt and Jess.
PHIL: All teams are
now making their way
from the United
States to Mexico,
where they must find me
here at the Monument
of the Revolution.
Oh, God. Be careful.
-I forgot to tie my shoe!
Taxi. Taxi. Taxi.
-Gettin' a taxi.
Monumento a la Revolucion? -OK.
Si, signor.
I want to go fast.
If you're not first,
you're last. (GIGGLES)
All I know is it's
pitch black out.
And we're driving super fast
down the road, but it's awesome.
I love it. This is so
awesome. It's exhilarating.
This is what it's
all about, baby!
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
(DRIVER RESPONDS)
Si. -Gosh, I'm
turned on right now.
We are in Mexico
City... -Mexico City!
Heading to the Monumento
a la Revolucion.
It's one of my
favourite monumentoes.
In Alabama, we don't
have taxis whatsoever.
We don't have taxis there.
But, hey, that's
what makes it fun.
Because we're in a car right now
and we don't know whose car we're in.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, my God. Burnie, run! Run!
Oh, my gosh. Don't jerk!
Phil! (SHRIEKS)
(SHRIEKS) Whoo!
Congratulations.
Whoa! Hey, you are the first
team to get to the Detour.
Be quick. Your
clue is right there.
First clue.
Detour.
The mariachi, a part of the
essence of Mexico and its people.
And 350 of them are
playing right now
here in the Plaza Garibaldi.
'Mariachi Madness' challenges teams
to find a musician who's faking it.
When they find the mariachi
who's just blowing hot air...
(MUSICIANS STOP PLAYING)
..they'll receive
their next clue.
Fireworks are an integral
part of celebrations in Mexico.
'Great Bulls of Fire'
requires teams to take a
crack at building a torito.
First, they must construct
and decorate the frame
for this papier-mache bull.
Once it's been
loaded with fireworks,
they must light it up
to get their next clue.
'Mariachi Madness'. -We're
doing 'Mariachi Madness'.
Fireworks. Fireworks. -Let's
do 'Great Bulls of Fire'.
What do you think? -Let's
I think this will be faster.
-Let's do 'Mariachi Madness'.
'Great Bulls of Fire'? -'Great
Bulls of Fire'. -Let's do it.
Detour - 'Mariachi Madness'.
That one. Alright, let's go.
Let's do 'Great
Bulls of Fire'.
I kind of think
'Great Bulls of Fire'.
Great 'Bulls of Fire'? -Yeah.
'Mariachi Madness'.
-Oh, that sounds awesome.
We're going to do
'Mariachi Madness'.
Go! Go! Go!
-OK, I'm runnin'.
Plaza Garibaldi.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
Two miles? OK. Two miles.
Is this the craziest first
leg you've ever seen or what?
Do you know where we're going?
-That's where we take a right, there.
You're doing great. Come
on, Mom. $1 million.
Maybe over here...
I really hope we're
going the right way.
Oh, my gosh. This
seems really far, y'all.
Where are we? -Oh, my gosh.
-This is really confusing.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
(OVERLAPPING SPEECH, CAR
HORNS AND STREET NOISE)
Oh, my God.
We're going to get eliminated.
Oh, my God. This is how
it happens. This is crazy.
I see no-one, which is either
a good thing or a bad thing.
This looks like a
plaza right here, dude.
Right? -We'll see.
(BRASS MUSIC PLAYS)
There's the music! Oh, yes!
(BAND PLAYS CIELITO LINDO)
Holy crap.
-Oh, my gosh! So many!
Oh, daddy.
Who's fake
playing?! Dear Lord.
He's playing.
Who's fake playing?
This guy's got no
sound. No sound.
Whoo! We got it.
Yes!
Si, Signor. Vamos!
Senor! Senor!
Escuela de
Mariachi. We made it!
(MUSICIAN PLAYS BARS
FROM CIELITO LINDO)
Alright. Come on. Come on! It's
alright. Don't get frustrated.
ALL: (SING) # Ay, ay, ay...
Let's get in the middle.
I love this song. Yeah.
(ALL SING IN SPANISH)
Who's fake playing?
Holy cow. This is it.
-Oh, my gosh.
They're all playing so loud
you can't tell who's playing.
It's literally a sea
of mariachi players.
Yeah, this is it. This is it.
Hey. Mariachi?
-Mariachi?
No mariachi?
-Can you be mariachi?
Yeah, don't go. Mariachi.
We don't even know if
we're in the right place.
We've been looking
around this plaza.
We think we're in
Plaza Garibaldi,
but we don't see any
mariachi fake players.
"Search the crowd for a mariachi
who is pretending to play."
So, he's a real mariachi. We need
one that's pretending to play.
Mucho gracias.
Yee. OK.
OK, Burnie, look at this.
-Oh, this is it.
El toro. -Here,
Burnie, parking garage.
There we go. To the
roof. Let's do it.
Hup! Hup! Hup! Whoo!
OK. -Here you go.
There's a bull.
So, are we building this?
That's a finished
example. That's it.
We have to build one of
these things right here.
Use the materials to
complete the frame.
We're doing this,
baby. OK. -Yeah.
We have got to make this bull
just like the example bull.
Stuck on top of
it like this? -Yes.
And it sits on
top of the pegs.
Oh, my gosh. This
is so detailed.
I hope I don't cut a
finger off doing this,
or anything else cut off.
I saw a bunch of bulls get
castrated once. That wasn't fun.
Here comes another team.
We have a tiny, tiny
head start, but not much.
We need to knock it out. -Don't worry.
We're way ahead. We've got this.
Hello. Hi, guys.
Do you guys do craft night
at home? -Not like this.
I'm gonna put
everything in place.
OK. Oh, my gosh, another
team is here. We gotta go.
OK, Mom, patiently,
OK? -I know.
I should've been a boy scout.
-Tie it like it's a hair tie.
If I think of this as if I'm tying
a hair tie, I've got it, Daddy.
BURNIE: There's got to be some teams
that do not know where they are.
Are you kidding me? Right
back where we started?
Yeah. -It sucks.
(MUSICIANS PLAY CIELITO LINDO)
I want to hear you play.
Oh, my gosh. Complete chaos.
Are you pretending to play?
Oh, my gosh. Are
you really playing?
(PLAYS ABOVE OTHER
MUSICIANS) Whoah!
Erin! Erin!
We got our girl.
OK. Vamos.
Signor!
Alright. He's
playing no music.
No music. -Oh, my gosh.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
"Make your way to the Cuevas de
Teotihuacan." (ATTEMPTS SPANISH)
Taxi. Taxi. Get a taxi.
No? Por que?
Ahhh! How do you
say that in Spanish?
He's a joker.
Oh, man. This is crazy.
Dana, I think we
have him. -You got one?
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
I think it's this
guy right here, babe.
Hola.
Mucho gracias.
-Si, gracias. Gracias.
ALL: (SING) # Ay,
ay, ay, ay... #
Let's go!
Are you really playing?
Holy crap, what the heck?
This is so cool.
OK. There's another team in there.
Babe, we got to get in there.
Let's keep moving. OK.
Are you guys playing? Are
you guys playing for real?
Oh, my God. Impossible.
They've already
got their wheels on.
Good job, Korey. How
are they going so fast?
I feel like we're
doing well now.
(GRUNTS) This bull
is getting annoying.
Come around. Alright,
you're good. Thanks, sweetie.
I love you. -I like you.
Hey. -A lot.
We had a whole bunch
of sticks and wheels
and we had to use an example
to reconstruct our torito.
Put a little surgeon's
knot up here on the top. -OK.
You had to glue paper
and all this stuff.
You had to make it real cute and
light it on fire. It was a firework.
You're doing so well, Daddy.
HAGAN: Another
team just got here.
We're gonna have to hurry.
Everyone's, like, killing us.
They came here after us and
they're already way ahead of us.
How are they doing it
so fast? -I don't know.
Can I help in any way?
-Everyone's almost done.
There's a lot of teams here.
Oh, my God. They just got
here. That's so good for us.
Wow, this is like
arts and crafts.
We can be the first ones
out. -Yeah, we're good.
I can't even breathe, Jessica.
This is a bunch of bull.
Come on, come on. -Is that
the earliest one? -Yes.
It's the earliest time. Are
we the first people here?
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
7:30. Did you guys
get 7:30 too? Yeah?
Quick. 7:30. 7:30.
You guys!
How many are left at 7:30?
-There's only one more left.
ZACH: This is nuts.
This is really hard.
Hey! Hey! That's
him, that's him!
(SPEAKS SPANISH) You, with us.
They found one maybe.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
Oh, hey. Hey.
Oh, gracias. Let's go! Ahhh!
There's nothing. It's him. It's
him. We got him. We got him.
(ALL SING IN SPANISH)
I think a bad thing is we haven't
seen any other teams at all.
I'm so sorry, Cole. I
feel like I messed up.
How'd you mess up? What
have you messed up on?
I wanted to do better.
We're not out yet.
Gosh.
We've gotten into a groove and
I think we're passing people.
Toro, come on. He didn't like
your story about castrating bulls.
He's, like, vaminos.
This one, like, won't go.
Just double knot
it? Double knot it.
I'm going to have
to redo that one.
Hey, show-offs over
there. -Getting there.
How'd you get here so
late and you're beating us?
I want that number one spot.
If you weren't my partner
I'd already be out.
I can't see up under
there. This way.
This is, like, where
the pressure kicks in.
I'm going to throw up.
Wouldn't our agencies love that?
OK. I'm ready
to present. -Yeah.
Judge. Es bonito.
Tyler cleared
it fast. -Quickly.
They tore through
this one, didn't they?
(LAUGHTER)
It looks pretty good.
Yay!
Oh, my God. Are they finished?
Pick up the bull.
-Good job, boys.
(HUMS THE AMAZING RACE THEME)
(THE AMAZING RACE THEME PLAYS)
Are we going to light
this sucker on fire?
Oh, my God.
Let's see the judge. -OK.
Holy crap.
Oh, my gosh.
Mucho bonito.
-Pretty good?
(BOTH SHRIEK)
Did they just finish?
-Oh, man.
Alright, time to
finish this up.
(LAUGHTER)
(FIREWORKS WHISTLE)
Oh, my gosh!
(READS ALOUD IN
HALTING SPANISH)
Oh, my gosh!
Don't pay attention to them.
Pay attention to us. -I know.
Whoa! Whoo!
(ALL SPEAK
INDISTINCTLY) Thank you!
Oh, my God. OK. That
lit a fire under my butt.
OK, let's go to the judge.
OK, that's it. -Yeah.
That's not good.
-Well, we better hurry, then.
Yeah, we'll hurry. We
gotta make sure it can spin.
Oh, snap. We're still in
this. -We're still in it.
Still in it.
Hopefully we'll be
there any second now.
And I'm hoping that
there's still other teams
that are struggling
as much as we are.
Is this it?
-Are these all taxis?
Let's go, mama. OK.
Cole, it's right there.
Grab 7:30. -Nice!
So, we're not
last? -7:30! 7:30!
We thought we were last!
-I thought we were last.
No, no, no.
Yay!
We're going to leave
at 7:40. -7:40am.
Make sure all
your wheels spin.
Horn spin? -Horn spin.
I think we are
getting close to done.
I feel like we're doing well because
we got here way later than anyone.
We're almost done right here, so we'll finish
this up real quick. -Gonna have to catch up.
Yah! (LAUGHS) Mwah.
Oh, my gosh.
Come on, let's go.
Whoo!
Thank you. Thank you.
(SHRIEKS)
That was unexpected.
-That was awesome.
Ahhh! Thank you!
Oh, my gosh, look at it go!
BOTH: Whoo!
Thank you.
All we got to do is finish
before blue. Last team standing.
7:40, 7:50. -Take the earliest.
Yay.
Oh, my gosh!
7:40. -We got 7:40.
But the last one is 7:50, so at
least we're not the very last group.
Vamos. Yes! Si! Si! Si!
Get ready, get ready.
Let's go.
We're in a race at this point.
7:40am.
-Take 7:40.
Grab a thing. Wow.
We're in last right now.
We just got a 7:50am.
We're in last place,
'cause we suck.
7:50. We have the last time.
And that put us in last place.
So we gotta play catch-up.
(TRIBAL DRUM MUSIC)
Whoo-hoo!
Vamoose, mama. Yes.
Come on, bro, let's
go. It's over here.
Nice, Kurt.
-That's it, that's it.
Roadblock.
"Who's ready to
pick up the pieces?"
One team member must make their
way to this cave, Teotichuacan,
and then search for 13
pieces of a Teotichuacano mask
hidden inside.
After digging through
this archaeological site,
they must use the pieces they find
to properly reconstruct their mask
and then get the approval of a
tribal elder for their next clue.
OK, I'm doing it. I'm
doing it. -You do it.
OK, I'm doing it.
You want to pick up
the pieces? -Let's do it.
Ready to pick up the
pieces. -I'm going to do it.
We're getting ready to go down
into this archaeological
mine of some sort.
I didn't know this was under
ground! I'm claustrophobic.
You get a hard
hat. Let's go, baby!
Put in some work!
Ooh, it's nice and
toasty down here.
Here we go. Oh, I'm
so claustrophobic.
They're going
into a cave. -Yeah!
Oh, dang.
I think one of her,
like, biggest fears.
I'm claustrophobic.
Oh, my God. Oh, no!
OK.
May take a wrong turn.
Oh, is this it up here?
Oh, my God! (WHIMPERS)
Choose a numbered
excavation site?
I guess these are the parts.
I'm just digging. I don't
really know what I'm looking for.
It could really be
anywhere in here.
It said to find 13
fragments of an artefact?
Look like maybe some
old pottery or something?
I really hate tight spaces.
Being in this cave is,
like, really freaky for me.
13. Alright, I got 13 pieces.
I'm going to put
these all in the bag
and I'm going to go find the
drums to find the artefact.
Follow the drums.
Anybody see drums?
13. I have 13.
13. (PANTS)
OK, I'm listening for drums.
I don't see any drums in here.
This is, like,
my biggest fear.
Go, Rachey.
You want to do it?
-Yeah, I'll do it.
Who's ready to pick
up the pieces? -You are.
You want me to do the
first one? You sure? -Yeah.
Got it? -I'll do it.
Oh... I hear drums.
This hurts.
Drums.
Yeah, I hear the drums.
I think it goes on top.
I think it's, like,
a outline of his face.
Yes, it goes on top. Look.
Look.
Mine fits here, yeah. -OK.
I don't know about some
of the other pieces.
They're different
colours, so...
I have to
reconstruct this mask
but I feel like I don't
have enough pieces.
Do you think
there's more pieces
or do they need to be
all the same colour?
I wonder.
I think they might.
I think maybe we do all blue
or all white? What do you think?
I think it's all
one colour. -OK.
So when I saw the mask,
it had to actually be one
colour or the other colour,
then I realised that I
didn't have enough pieces.
I'm heading back.
OK, I've got more than I need.
Here we go. OK.
Gotta find the drums.
Marty? -Yes.
How are you? -Good.
You find any fragments?
Yeah. -Are they all silver?
Not all silver.
Should they be?
13 fragments. I must
keep them with me.
Follow the drums.
13. I got them all.
10, 11, 12, 13. OK.
Where are the drums?
Are the drums this
way, do you know?
That's not it.
I hear the drums. Oh, my
gosh. I pray I have enough.
We're stuck in caves
and there's no drums.
Clue. Alright.
Darius is doing it, right?
Alright, Jess,
you're gonna do it.
I think it's me. I'll do it.
How do I get to the drums?
I came out. Everybody
is going back in.
I love you, Daddy.
You're doing great.
He's kind of amazing
and I'm not gonna lie.
Is that what this is?
OK. Where are the drums?
Blue's gonna be
on the bottom here.
Man, I just am stuck
on this one piece.
I feel like it needs
to go the other way.
I got 13 white pieces but I
realised some of them are duplicates
so I just decided to
start digging again,
see if I could get more pieces from
another colour and just start over.
Let's go back.
Is it all one colour?
I think it might
be all one colour.
OK, I'm gonna go back and get more
pieces. I don't think I have enough.
Maybe the drums are down here.
Holy cow! They were
down here all along.
I'm making big mistakes.
I dropped some of my pieces and
I don't know how many I dropped.
Alright. Where are the drums?
There's nine. I'm looking
for a couple more pieces.
Hey, where do you
think the drums are?
I don't know. I'd tell
you but I don't know.
Is it something in here?
Come on, Jessica!
Yeah, shovel, yeah.
That's why it's there.
I need two more.
Are you finding little
drums on the ground?
Scott, do you know where
the drums are? -I don't.
Do you think we
came up a wrong way?
I do. -You do?
Follow the drums. This
is getting desperate now.
I thought I had all the
white ones. I just...
For some reason, that
last one wasn't going in.
I'm going to try light blue.
I'm bleeding.
-You're bleeding?
Yeah. -Oh, my
goodness gracious.
That's hard.
I believe in you.
-Thank you.
You got this.
-One more.
Alright. Judge?
Yes. Yes!
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Whoo! -I got it.
Good job, babe.
"Make your way to
your first Pit Stop."
Mexico has more museums than
any other country in the world,
and the Museo Soumaya is the
most visited in the country.
The last team to check in there
at the mat may be eliminated.
Alright, let's go. Good
luck, guys. -Good luck.
OK. I'm ready to present.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Tyler finished before me but
I think we can catch up still.
There's a lot of teams
that are still doing it.
Are you done? -Yeah.
We're in second,
we're in second. -OK.
Bye, friends.
We can beat the dancers
'cause we're right behind them.
Yeah, numero uno. Whoo!
Where is Kurt?
Come on, Kurt.
(ALL SING AND LAUGH)
Oh, my God.
Shoot, shoot, shoot. Holy cow.
What did I do to myself here?
My dad is still over there
looking for something.
13.
He hasn't started building
anything. I'm so panicked.
I know I gotta go back in the
tunnel to get to the drums.
Yes.
I think I need to go back.
I think there's
a missing piece.
Dammit!
Thank you. Right.
Piece of cake.
This is ridiculous.
To work so hard this first leg
and to potentially come in first
would be like a
dream come true.
We could beat Matt and Dana.
They were literally probably only
three minutes in front of you.
DANA: Oh, my God. No, no, no.
Oh, my God, we
passed the dancers.
That was them. That
was the dancers.
So it's gonna be
a run. -Oh, my God.
We have to get
around that taxi, sir.
We have to pass.
Numero uno! Numero uno! Whoo!
It's so close.
It's going to be a
footrace to the mat.
It's literally going to be
a footrace to the finish.
Literally right behind us.
Go! You see them?
Gracias.
Go, go, go! Go, go, go!
Whoo!
-Welcome to Mexico City.
Dana and Matt, I am pleased to tell
you, on the first leg of this race
you are team number one!
(BOTH CHEER)
Oh, my God! -Man, you
made us run for it.
Tyler and Korey, I'm pleased to
tell you, you are team number two.
Pretty good way to start.
Not a bad way to start.
Are we going to see some interesting
things with your hair on this race?
What's happening right
now? -Well, it's...
It looks fabulous.
-It's wind blown.
Don't come for me, Phil.
We've been fans of the
race for years and years.
We've loved the race.
And to hear Phil say to us
that we were team number one...
It's a dream come
true. It really is.
Alright, get on that mat.
Why don't you tell Kristina
what it is exactly you guys do?
What's your deal?
-We make short, magical videos.
We're not allowed to use magic
on the race, unfortunately.
Phil, could I take a
selfie? -Can we take a selfie?
OK, that fit. Is
this the judge?
Yes!
Alright, I think I got it.
Thank you.
I think I'm just
missing a piece.
Oh, my God.
Just, I don't know if
I have all the pieces.
Crap!
Cameron, you look
a little relieved.
Ended up being in
the back of the pack.
No, you're more towards
the front of the pack.
Feels really good.
-Top half. It feels good.
(DRUMS BEAT)
Trying to figure out
what I'm doing wrong here.
I think I'm done.
Thank you. Oh,
my God, Brittany.
I think I got it.
Oh, baby Jesus.
Oh, my gosh. Thank you.
It's depressing to see
teams leave like that.
Brodie and Kurt, you
are team number five.
Yeah!
Sound good?
-Great job, guys.
Burnie and Ashley, that would
make you team number six.
Is it just us two, mama?
That really sucks, doesn't it?
Weren't we the first ones down here?
Yes.
Erin won't give up
while she's down there.
Oh, I know my dad won't give up.
-She won't give up. She'll keep going.
None of our team-mates
would give up.
Do you want to take the penalty?
-How long is the penalty?
Four hours. -Oh, gosh.
Are the other teams
putting it together?
I think they're done.
I think we're the last ones.
-What do you think?
I don't know. I don't
know if we should.
Let's do it.
Do you want to
take the penalty?
Do you mind going
back and just looking
and seeing if
anyone is doing it?
If they aren't, then you and
I will do the penalty together?
OK. -Want to do that?
Let's do it. -OK.
Alright, here we go.
He's still here.
People just ran in
so I'm good, I'm good.
You want to pick a number?
-Yes, I'm going to go with seven.
You are so correct.
Team number seven!
And you are team
number eight! -Whoo!
This cave is, like,
starting to get to me.
You want to take the penalty?
One more time and then if I
can't get this then I'm down.
13 pieces have
to fit together.
Um, did I just get this?
Alright, I'm going
to go try this.
Oh, I think you got it.
It would be a
miracle from God.
Oh, my gosh! Oh, I love you!
Come on.
Can I help you? Is
there anything I can do?
No, you just need to
go, sweetie. I love you.
Where'd all those
pieces come from?
Just all from my box.
I have everything of blue and
everything of white except for one.
I've got to go back to my box.
There's more in there.
Good job, Erin!
Thanks, guys! I
love your parents.
I'm missing a blue.
I'm cold and I'm starving.
At least 40 minutes
wasted looking for pieces.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, my God.
I found a blue piece.
This is for Blair. She doesn't
need to go home 'cause of me.
I do not want to lose this.
Finally. -Shoot!
Mom! Mom!
I'm so sorry.
-Mom, it's OK. We're good.
Hey, good luck!
OK. Here is your clue.
Here he is.
Sorry about that.
You did so good. The
last team just came out.
Right now we're heading
to... -The Pit Stop.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
This taxidriver is killing it.
Maybe the girls got
in a slower taxi.
You never know.
We're not even driving the speed
limit, but not that we would know
because our cab driver's
speedometer is broken.
We can still win. I'm not ready
to give up. Especially for you.
You know, anything can happen.
We're driving like on
a vacation sightseeing.
10 is just first with a zero.
(LAUGHS) That's right.
Phil! I see him. Yes,
to the right. Follow me.
Alright.
Sheri, you look absolutely
petrified right now.
'Cause I hope the other
team didn't pass us.
You're not 10th.
You're 9th.
-Oh! -Oh, my God!
Hey!
We ended up passing
somebody. Oh! Oh!
Oh, my gosh!
-Oh, my god!
You're good.
-We're good?
Erin and Joslyn, I'm
pleased to tell you
you are still in the race.
You don't have to go home.
You are team number 10.
Are you serious?
-I'm serious, I'm serious.
I love you!
Come on, Daddy. You got this.
Hola. Oh.
Scott and Blair,
Scott and Blair.
I'm very sorry to tell you that
you are the last team to arrive.
OK.
Well, guess what. -What?
You're not eliminated! -Oh!
Oh, my gosh,
that's impossible.
You are still in the race.
This is a non-elimination leg.
Did that feel good?
-I'm so proud of you. Yeah.
You got another leg.
-Bring on that Speed Bump.
You're so positive. -I'm just
happy this isn't the end.
I just want to be able to
go more places with my dad
and, you know, who
knows if we'll be able
to do something
like this again.
Captions by:
Ericsson Access Services
Synced and edited by:
Dzony95
PHIL: Stay tuned for
highlights from this season.
PHIL: This season on
The Amazing Race.
I hope it doesn't cock
a doodle doo doo on me.
PHIL: Teams will do
whatever it takes...
Oh, Lord, that is high.
Great jump, babe!
PHIL: As they push
themselves to the limit...
Never though I'd be
pulling camels through Dubai.
Go, go!
PHIL: And conquer
their greatest fears.
(SCREAMS)
Please, help me. (CRIES)
PHIL: Which team...
(SQUEALS)
Mom, I'm fine!
PHIL: Will win it all?
(SCREAMS)
-I don't know.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/kgrs
Help other users to choose the best subtitles