Hi.
Hey. Hey.
How you doin'?
I'm Doreen.
I'm Dee.
They call me Diamonds.
I'm Doreen.
Tully?
Doreen?
That is me.
Well, come on, get in.
Don't be scared.
You're a lot shorter than
I thought you were gonna be.
So?
Was your daddy short?
He looked tall to me.
Hitler was short.
Hitler was short?
It's a good thing
I am not datin' Hitler.
That would not work out.
Well, you ain't
datin' me neither.
Anyway, expectations
lead to sufferin'.
Did Hitler say that?
Nope. Buddha.
If I'm not mistaken,
it is forbidden
to quote Buddha.
Ignorance is forbidden.
Can't be
an Aryan by being a fool.
Did Buddha
say that to you?
No, I did.
Smarty-pants, huh?
That's what you are?
You're a smarty-pants?
Is that a smile?
Oh, he's cute
when he smiles, folks.
Say bye-bye.
You all right?
Fifteen years.
Yeah, it's a long time.
But good news
is you are out today.
And today
is a nice day to be free.
Nice day.
You know,
you should quit smokin'.
That stuff will kill ya.
Yup.
I just don't light it.
I hold on to it.
It helps me.
You could try that.
Where's the gun?
Gun is gonna be
underneath your seat there.
I went through hell tryin'
to get a hold of that thing.
Hold it down a little bit?
All right,
let's get to parole.
Then we'll make
the drop-off for Sobecki.
What time you
gotta be there again?
7:30.
Yeah, we'll get
there in time.
I'll get you there.
I have to.
Why?
Got to pick up
my little boy afterwards.
My little baby.
Shit.
Tully?
Tully.
Tully, Tully.
We got a cop behind us.
Fucking...
No worries.
It's a fucking nigger cop.
I hate fucking cops.
I didn't do anything.
Your fucking
taillights workin'?
No, everything's fine.
Then that guy...
I didn't do anything.
What?
Oh, Jesus fucking Christ.
Goddamn.
You just let me
do all the talking.
Do not fucking
take that gun out.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
They gettin' out?
Good evenin', officer.
License and registration,
please.
Absolutely.
Absolutely, yeah.
Your name, sir?
This is Deputy Rivers.
I'm in the middle--
Get on your
fucking knees, nigger.
Tully!
Just fucking go!
What did you do?
Just fucking drive.
Did you just
kill a fucking cop?
Just go! Let's go!
Did you fucking kill--
Just fucking drive.
A fucking cop?
Shit.
We gotta get
the hell out of here.
Yeah, but where?
Come on,
let's go, come on.
Come on.
Check the car.
Shit.
Come on, come on.
Shh.
Shh, shh.
Sonny, wake up.
What?
Wake up.
Sounds like someone's
in the house.
Okay.
Give me a minute.
I hear him
comin' up the stairs.
Wake your ass up...
Oh, God, oh.
Oh.
Sonny, who is it?
Who's out there?
Yo.
Hey, who the--
Hey, who-who
the hell are you?
Sonny, who is it?
Who the hell are you?
Sonny, what's happening?
Walking into a man's house,
all times of the night,
Sonny, who are
you yellin' at?
swingin' a-a-a damn pistol
every which way and everywhere.
What's goin'--
I will blow
your fuckin' head off, nigger.
Sonny!
How many
are in the house?
I said how many
in the fuckin' house, nigger.
Two.
Round 'em up.
And you?
Old man,
get your fuckin' pants on.
Let's go!
Come on!
Jesus Christ, come on!
I'm goin',
I'm goin', I'm goin'.
Get-Get in there.
Mom!
Do what he says, honey.
We don't want no trouble.
Where's the baby?
Where's the fuckin' baby?
There's no baby here.
Not my babies, no.
Mama!
Mom.
No.
Ah, shit. Look-y here.
Children in a brother's house.
Now there's a surprise.
I thought you said two.
Adults.
Two adults.
Yeah, shut up.
It's gonna be okay.
You think
you're smarter than me?
Huh?
You think you're
smarter than me, old man?
Shh.
Get in there.
Stay with me.
Anthony.
Wake up.
Get up.
Just open the door.
Get your fuckin'--
Get in there, boy!
Huh?
You want some?
No.
Huh?
Get back.
That's right.
Where are the phones?
There's one in the bedroom.
There's two downstairs.
One in the living room,
one in the kitchen and that it.
Cars, vehicles?
Huh?
Come on,
take what you want.
We ain't gonna
try and stop you.
How the fuck
do you know what I want?
You presumptuous bitch.
The Firebird's got
a blown gasket.
Somehow it runs.
Yeah, what else, nigger?
Old station wagon's
almost out of gas.
Firebird got gas?
Yeah.
Huh?
No, no, I said it has
a blown gasket but it runs.
It's got gas, yeah.
Guns, weapon?
Huh?
No guns... here.
You gotta be
fucking kidding me.
A blue lip
out here in the country?
Shit.
I'm an ex-con.
I have no
intention of going back.
An ex-con?
What the fuck
do you know about time, man?
I know about time.
Do you hear that?
The neighbors will be sure
to hear that, if it goes off.
Yeah? Let me tell
you somethin', mister.
This fires, you won't be worryin'
about no fuckin' neighbors.
Who's that man?
The Boogeyman.
You're not the Boogeyman.
Hush up!
Yeah, that's right, son.
I ain't the boogeyman.
You are.
Boo!
Come on,
leave the baby alone.
He's just a child.
Shut the fuck up.
Yo, stop pointin'
that shit at my mom.
No, no, no.
No!
Relax!
Fuck you!
Listen up.
There are more of us.
Lots more.
I'm just the unlucky fucker
that got sent up here to deal
with you niggers.
But let me tell you, the shit's
hittin' the fan tonight.
It's a fuckin' race war.
Armageddon.
Death to Jews
and Niggers, you get it?
Fuck.
What the fuck
happened in there?
How many people?
I don't know,
family of five, six.
I took care of it.
Six people?
We got keys.
I got eight hours,
so let's fucking go.
Whoa, whoa!
Wait a second. We can't just take the keys
and drive a car out there.
What if-What if-What if
they call the cops on us?
Yank the fucking
phones, fuck it.
How about they just go right
on to the neighbor's house?
Fine, we'll take
one of them with us.
I don't think
we got a choice, huh?
We'll take a chance.
We do not have
that kind of chance right now.
Do you understand
what I'm saying to you?
Do you hear all these
fucking cops everywhere?
Yo, I say we jump him.
Smash his fucking brains.
What?
And get us all killed?
You heard that man.
He's on some
white supremacist bullshit.
Like, sworn to hate.
He's not gonna listen to no shit we say.
That's why
we let him leave.
His business
is none of my business.
We can't just
fuckin' sit here.
The word is patience.
Sounds like fear.
You're gonna take him?
You ain't shit.
Fuck you!
No. Stop!
You ain't shit.
You're not
gonna treat my son
the way you treat yours.
Now, you stop it.
Come on.
For once,
Mr. Walker is right.
We just let him leave.
And God-willing,
then we call the police.
No, no, no.
No police.
No, I have
nothing for the police.
I can't have
no police here.
What are you
talking about?
You can't
put your pants on.
Let alone
pull 'em off.
What are
you gonna do?
Goddamn it.
Mama.
Handle it.
I said that's enough.
No, it's not enough.
I'm just
gettin' started.
Mama.
No.
We get out of here,
God-willing. I'm walkin'.
Then walk.
I had enough
of this shit.
You walk,
you run, do whatever.
You ain't no prize.
You ain't
no prize, either.
You ain't no prize left.
Okay.
So, what then?
If you're so goddamn smart?
I don't know.
I gotta calm down.
Huh? Huh?
I gotta think.
I gotta think about it.
We need to think about it.
'Cause takin'
that car is a stupid idea.
That is a stupid idea.
We can't argue with ourselves,
we can't
fight him by ourself,
beat ourselves up.
Yeah, but I'm not
trustin' that dude
to come back up
here and just wait.
Patience.
Understand
that, Anthony?
Just a little
patience, okay?
You saw him
when he talked about
when I talked
about when I did time,
that I wasn't
gonna do no time,
so I had no gun.
You saw the way he'd look?
He understood that.
He thought
he could belittle me.
he could take me down.
Because I had said that.
And I looked him
right in the eye. He's pointin' a gun at it.
I know what time is.
I know what this dude is.
I've seen these cats before.
He knows that us
alive, that's
what keeps him goin'.
He has
no place to go.
Where does
he have to go?
He's right here.
He's trapped in here.
He's even more trapped
then we are trapped in.
Now you
understand that?
Okay.
Remember.
They need us.
Would you
just fuckin' think?
I'm trying
to fuckin' think.
Not helping.
You know what, fuck you.
I'm gonna call. I'm callin'.
Who the fuck you're callin'?
I'm callin'-callin'
Sobecki's guy.
He gave me this
number and he said
call them if I ever get--
Which fucking guy?
Sobecki's guy.
Do you need
any more information?
What are you, like,
questioning Sobecki all of the sudden?
You done lost
your fucking mind.
My God.
How the fuck
did I get myself into this mess?
Hi!
Hey.
How are you doin'?
Sobecki gave me
this number, and...
I don't-- We don't
really know each other,
but I thought-- He told me,
he told me to call this number
if I ran into
any kind of trouble, and this whole thing,
we got this mess,
and now we got cops after us.
And just,
I feel like we need, mmm...
maybe we need somebody
to come get us or something.
License and registration,
please.
Get on your
fucking knees, nigger.
Feels good, huh?
I need more,
'cause I don't know.
You don't know--
Okay, no, it's no big deal.
I'll just...
Okay, thank you so much.
Really,
it's really good talk--
Talk.
I told you Sobecki
was gonna come through.
What did he say?
Eddie is gonna call
with a plan to rescue us.
Doreen, the fucking
place is crawling with cops.
Eddie also
said we gotta...
What?
We gotta kill them.
Kill who?
Whoever's
in the house.
Jesus fucking
Christ, Doreen.
Those were his exact words?
Kill them?
Yes,
that's what he said.
He said...
He said you gotta
take care of them,
but I know what he was
talkin' about.
For Christ's sake,
he was on the phone.
What is he supposed to say?
Kill everybody
while he's on the phone?
Maybe fucking take care
of them means take care
of them.
You ever think of that?
Discipline and action,
that's what Sobecki would say.
Discipline?
You really know a lot about that.
Like,
what are you gonna do?
You gonna
kill a baby?
What, are you gonna
fight me right now?
We are in this together.
Are you gonna
disobey Sobecki?
That wasn't Sobecki.
That was Sobecki's man.
And for me,
that's good enough.
What are you gonna do? You're gonna spray
the whole goddamn neighborhood
and walk out of here?
Do you think
for one second
that I want to kill anybody?
'Cause believe me, I do not.
I do not, but you know what?
I'm not gettin' caught.
Why'd you got
to go and kill that cop?
We were doing so--
Jesus Christ,
you think I had a choice?
Maybe if you brought
some fucking money,
we wouldn't be
in this fucking situation.
Goddamn.
Anthony. Anthony.
Let him come up here.
Anthony, you need
to calm your little ass down.
I'm not gonna wait for him.
Shh.
Come on, boy,
these people got guns.
Tell him
I'll fuck him up.
Anthony, shut the fuck up.
What the fuck?
What do you do to them?
Where are they?
They're
in the fuckin' closet.
Get me
the fuck out of here.
Get--
Okay.
Hey, hey.
What the hell
is goin' on here?
Shut the fuck up.
It's-It's over now.
He was just scared,
that's all.
He's tryin'
to make me kill someone?
No, no, no.
We'll do what you say.
There's a baby
and a little boy in here.
Oh, shit.
Out, now.
Come on.
All on the bed.
Sit down.
Get your ass
in the corner.
Nice to meet all y'all.
That's-That's
a cute baby.
How old's that baby?
Seven months.
Tomorrow.
You the father?
No.
Then how the fuck do you fit
into this little menagerie?
She's my sister.
Where's papa?
Oh, fuck.
It's not you,
old man, is it?
No.
Oh, shit, I see.
Hump and run,
black man's dream.
White man's burden.
Don't get any ideas
about suckin' up to these
fucking bitches,
'cause they're all the same.
Yeah.
Watch 'em.
And you, little missy.
You're gonna
come with me.
Where?
None of your
goddamn business where.
Get your fuckin' ass over here.
I don't want to.
We're just
gonna look around, is all.
If any harm comes to her...
You'd do what?
Shit your pants, old man?
What you gonna do?
Let's go, now.
Come on,
leave the niglet behind.
Mommy, no!
Jesus Christ.
You either come
with me, or I take the baby.
Mr. Walker,
please do something.
Jesus Christ.
Stop it!
Hey, hey.
You don't have to...
Everybody
just keep calm.
Just keep calm, okay?
Shut up.
Anthony.
Just keep calm.
Sit down, Anthony.
Sit down.
Come on.
Please.
All right.
We're good, right?
We're good.
They're just
gonna go outside for a minute
and we'll hang tight.
Okay.
You know,
if it weren't for me,
y'all would be
dead right now.
Dead.
You know that, right?
'Cause I said to him, I said
you can't be
just killin' people 'cause
of their color of their skin.
You scared?
It's okay.
I'm scared.
I'm freakin'
out right now.
I'm freakin' out,
look at my hand.
Oops.
Ah, shit,
look at that.
Ah, shit.
Ah.
Quick, quick, quick.
You want to hold it?
No.
You don't want to hold it?
No, no.
Come on, hold it.
Make a mess.
I can't.
I bet you sucked
a few of these, all right.
Look at those lips.
They're just made
for suckin'.
I should kill you.
I should, but I'm gonna
make you a deal instead.
You love
your kids, right?
Yes.
Yes?
You want to see
them again tomorrow, right?
Yes. Yes!
And the day after?
Good.
Then you're gonna
tell me what he's thinkin' what,
plannin' what,
sayin' what, comprende?
Is that a yes?
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay.
And if I should happen
to overhear something
that you
didn't report to me,
that would be
a fucking shame, right?
Yes.
Yeah.
A downright
fucking tragedy.
[sighs]
Um...
Nah, I'm good.
I don't
want to see it.
Tell me about
the truck you saw.
Blue, green.
Maybe brown.
No se.
Bullshit, no se.
It's the truth, I swear.
What about the woman?
White, maybe Black?
White or maybe Black.
Sarge, I got here
as fast as I could.
Sarge!
I got something.
The truck was
registered to a Doreen Lesser.
Rivers called this
in before he went down.
Pelican Bay says she's
an Aryan Brotherhood groupie.
Now, she picked up an inmate
this morning.
Garrett Tully. Number three
in the Aryan Brotherhood.
He finished
out 15 years today.
Of course.
We're dealin'
with a psychopath.
Luis.
A cop-killin' psychopath.
El senor.
If you saw anything,
okay?
We got a cop
down over there,
I need you to tell me.
Sir, I told you
everything that I saw.
I-I'm sorry.
Okay.
All right, thank you.
Listen, man.
We need the make and the
model of that car. All right?
Yeah.
We're gonna find
this racist bastard.
You good?
Yeah.
They've been comin' back
and forth.
Shit.
Trouble with the law.
It's none
of your goddamn business.
Now, don't--
Now, don't tell me.
Wasn't a question,
just a statement.
None of my business
what you've done.
No lie there.
Not interested.
Mm.
Made my share of troubles.
What kind of trouble?
Mm.
Real trouble.
Ah.
All I'm saying is...
I don't like the law...
and you don't
like the law.
You want out of here,
and we want
you out of here.
Sounds like we have
something in common.
You got a match?
You got a match, light?
Come on.
Don't tell me there
isn't a single fucking match
in this entire house.
Back here,
you got one?
Yeah, I got one.
Come on,
man, let's have it.
In my room.
Where?
I don't know,
in the drawer somewhere.
I don't smoke.
The fuck you don't.
Show me.
Yes.
I'm gonna show
it to you, anyway.
Get--
Patience.
Slowly, boy.
Go on.
Where's that
fuckin' lighter?
You've ever
done time, boy?
No.
Come on, it's a rite of passage
for you brothers, right?
No respect
without time.
Not in my book.
Or, your daddy ever done time?
I bet you he's done time.
My daddy's dead.
Your daddy's dead.
Whee.
How did he die?
Fucking gang-banging, holdin'
up the liquor store, or what?
Desert Storm.
He was a soldier.
I know what
you're thinkin', boy.
The old man's weak,
the women
can't do nothin',
so it's up to you, right?
It's crossed my mind.
Uncross it, motherfucker.
Ain't no use dyin'
before you see the big house.
It just wouldn't seem proper.
You know what I mean?
Let's go, boy.
You look like a farmer.
Are you a farmer?
No.
Scrap metal now.
I still fix cars, blinds,
you name it.
That sounds boring.
And what do you do?
Home care
for the elderly.
I could never do it.
What about you?
I bet you ain't got no job, right?
I got one.
Deliver pizza
on Fridays, sometimes.
Sometimes.
Shit, it must be
nice being black.
All that spare time.
Where the fuck are we at?
Anthony, no.
Not necessary, now.
He's got a knife.
Let me go, my God.
Get the fuck off of me.
I'm taking her
and my family with me.
Anthony.
I'll slice her neck, I will.
Cut away.
What the fuck, Tully?
Hey!
No.
Tully, it's me.
Yeah, I don't give a shit.
Slice, dice,
chop whatever the fuck.
Tully.
A-Anthony.
Put it down, boy.
P-Put it down.
You're gonna cut her?
Go on.
I got nothin' invested in her.
Tully.
Hey, hey.
You're gonna--
Shut the fuck up, bitch.
Get your hand off me.
Hey.
If he puts it down,
you promise
not to kill him?
If-If he
gives it up...
Stop touching me.
You promise
not to kill him?
Y-Y-Your word?
Your word?
You got
my fucking word, nigger.
Your word, okay.
No trouble, okay.
All right, all right?
Tell him that.
Tell him!
No trouble.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, your word.
Give him your word.
My word.
All right.
That's right.
This is the stupidest
thing I've ever seen.
He violated me.
Tully, he violated me.
He had
his hands all over me.
He didn't touch her.
He did!
Yes, he did!
Anthony!
Anthony, baby?
Anthony.
Anthony, no!
Your word.
Oh, my God!
Anthony.
Oh!
Your word!
He ain't
fuckin' dead, is he?
Come on.
Fuck.
Okay.
All right.
He is not fucking dead.
That isn't
the fucking problem.
You almost
got me killed.
Nobody fucking talks
to me that way, you understand.
Least of all you.
Shit.
Fuck you.
Fuck me.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Anthony got shot.
Is he okay?
Just rest, my baby.
Tell me.
What?
Is he okay?
You gave your brother up,
you little bitch.
What the hell
am I supposed to do?
My God, I got two babies.
And I told you
not to have them.
This is not--
But you had them
anyway, didn't you?
You had them, anyway.
...my fault!
None of it.
I'm tired of you
blaming me for everything,
and this is not my fault.
You don't do that.
You don't give
your brother up, baby.
Mom--
You don't, ever.
...Mother.
Give your brother up.
Ever!
What was I
supposed to do?
Ever, ever.
What you doin'?
Unzip your pants.
What?
I said,
unzip your pants.
It's okay.
I'm just gonna
do what I do best.
Yeah.
You deserve this.
You're fine now.
You like this?
Doreen?
What do I got to do
to get you hard?
I have to talk a little bit?
Huh?
I can talk.
Baby, what's it take
to get you hard?
You just tell me,
I'll do it for you.
All right,
Doreen-Doreen stop, all right?
Okay, look.
That's enough.
It's like a fucking record.
What's wrong with you?
White men are the nuts
and bolts of society.
And their warriors
must be as strong
and pure
as their philosophy.
What the fuck
does that mean?
It means you
sacrifice your petty needs
and desires for something
more important than yourself.
Something bigger,
you understand?
What, did you say that?
No, Sobecki did.
Sobecki said that.
Of course he did.
Well, I guess that means
prison done turned you gay.
Fuck!
Don't you ever fucking
call me gay,
you understand me,
you fucking bitch,
don't you ever!
Get the fuck off of me.
Don't you fucking touch...
Get off of me.
Don't you ever
fucking talk to me
or grab me like that again.
You hear me?
Don't fucking
touch me again.
Fucking touch me.
Fuck.
Let's just drive, okay?
Let's just fucking drive.
Don't tell me what to do.
Everybody told
you not to have them.
Tully. Tully.
Listen to me.
We need to do
what Sobecki said.
And just slit their throat.
Just slit their throat.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Use your brain.
Listen to me,
listen to me.
You gotta be
a man right now for me.
You have got
to do something.
Be a fucking Aryan.
Use your fucking brain.
They're more
valuable to us alive.
To who?
Jesus Christ, you don't think
we work with their kind on the inside?
This is--
Business
is fucking business.
We are
on the outside right now.
We are on the outside. And on the outside,
you do them before they do you.
That is the fucking business.
Fucking... If you're so fucking game,
why don't you start with the baby in the crib?
You are not getting it.
You-You need to do this.
You have got to do this.
And the baby?
Why shoot the baby?
The baby
can't fucking even talk.
Fine.
Fuck it,
the little boy then.
He's seen
our faces, start with him.
Shh!
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
Fine. I will.
Oh, fu--
How he's doin'?
He's gonna be okay?
I just--
I wanna apologize.
Um...
I'm real sorry.
About what I said.
Because, um...
sometimes you
just get into
this kind of dilemma,
and things come out,
you don't really--
you don't-don't really know,
and I really--
I want to apologize for that.
We-We all--
We all need to stick together.
Because he...
He's real unpredictable,
you know what I mean?
I'm scared.
I'm freezing, I'm hungry,
I just want to go home.
I'm hungry too, Mommy.
I know, baby.
You're hungry?
I'm hungry.
You want to go
get some food with me?
No.
You just
said you were hungry.
I'm hungry, too.
It's okay.
You want to go
in the kitchen with me
and help me find some food,
something to make, like,
a peanut butter and jelly with.
No.
It'll be fun.
You and me, we're gonna
go make peanut butter--
No.
He ain't goin' with you.
He ain't goin'.
The boy
stays with his mother.
Go to hell.
The boy stays with his mother.
Shut the fu--
Hey, shut the fuck up!
I am this close
to killin' all of you.
The boy stays with his mother.
The boy goes.
That's it, it's final.
Go!
...stays with--
Jesus fucking Christ.
You all listen
to me, you understand?
Let's just--
Goddamn, I'd never
thought I'd miss solitary.
Shut the fuck up.
You, go.
Now.
He's coming.
Come on.
He's bleeding to death.
Shit.
We got to get
him to a hospital.
I don't give a shit.
Let him bleed.
What?
We need to get him
to a hospital.
Bitch,
shut the fuck up.
You think
I don't know that?
I don't know?
Your mama said
your name was Jam.
Right?
What's that short for?
Jam?
Jamar.
It's, like, peanut butter
and jam, right?
I have...
a little boy.
About your age.
They-They took him
away from me, though.
That's the--
W-who took him
away from you?
The-The-The government.
The social workers
and police.
Are you
going to kill us?
No, baby.
No, that's crazy talk.
What do you
know about death, anyway?
I know whoever dies,
they go to heaven.
I don't know about that.
What do you
think heaven is like?
I don't know.
But it
is supposed to be cool.
Who's that?
Shh.
Is that the police?
Mama, that's the police!
Help.
Help. Help.
Uh-Uh-Uh.
They're just
makin' sandwiches, is all.
Can't you just
go and leave us alone?
Sit down.
Mama.
Help.
Stop. Just...
Shut up!
I said, calm down, please.
It's all right.
It'll end soon.
It's all right,
it's all right, it's all right.
See?
Baby.
10-97.
Mr. Walker,
please do something.
My boy.
They have my boy.
Your...
My boy.
Your word.
They hurt my boy
downstairs, Mr. Walker.
I hear him cryin'.
Mr. Walker,
please do something.
Please.
Oh, my God, Jamar.
Mommy.
Oh, Jamar.
Oh, Jamar,
are you hurt, baby?
Come here,
let me look at you.
Let me look at you.
Oh, God.
Do you all
believe in God?
I know you do.
'Cause you're black.
All y'all love
yourselves some God.
I feel like
God is fucking with me.
I feel like he has
all these favorites.
And then there's me.
[chuckles]
That's crazy, right?
What-What if God,
when he talks to you,
you can't hear
because you don't
understand what he's saying?
What do you do then?
'Cause see,
I'm confused.
I'm fucking confused.
I'm confused as to why
your name
is Odessa because that...
[chuckling]
is a white girl's name.
That is a fucking
white girl's name.
'Cause I went to school
with an Odessa and that girl
was the whitest
girl you ever saw.
You should have
yourself a pretty black name.
Black Moniqua
or Shaniqua or somethin'.
Those names
are so pretty.
It's like,
it's like name art.
Not like some
stupid name like--
Hey, Doreen.
...Becky, or take...
Doreen.
Those fucking names are shit.
That gives you a pass...
We don't have time
for this, all right?
straight into white trash land.
Hey!
Go get some air.
Go get some fucking air.
What if
he forgets about us?
What if he forgets about us?
He ain't gonna
forget about us.
I'm asking you now,
go get some fucking air.
Shit.
Goddamn.
Listen.
Sir.
What?
I have to go.
Go where?
To the bathroom.
Fucking hold it.
I'm an old man.
Yeah, no shit.
I don't want to soil
on myself in front of...
you.
Or my family.
That's why I'm asking.
All right,
make it quick.
Where's the fucking cash,
anyway?
What cash?
What do you
mean, what cash?
The cash Sobecki gave
to you to get me to Bakersfield.
No, no.
Don't try
to pull that bullshit.
What do you mean, no, no?
Sobecki did not
give me any kind of cash.
You have
$200 they give you--
Jesus fucking Christ.
...when you
get out of jail.
How the fuck do you think--
...we're gonna get there?
I'm not an idiot.
Okay?
They give you
$200 when you get out.
I know that for sure.
You think this
is my first fucking rodeo?
The fuck
are you looking at?
Give me
the fucking money!
Okay, okay, okay.
Give me
the fucking money, now.
Don't shoot,
I'm giving-I'm giving the money.
Okay?
I'm giving-- here.
Um...
Fucking idiot.
Please don't hurt,
please don't hurt me, okay.
Please.
Please, what?
Shut the fuck up, brown boy.
Speak English,
motherfucker.
What the fuck are you saying?
Shut the fuck up.
You want to fucking die?
You ever danced with
the devil, motherfucker?
'Cause you're dancin' now.
I'm gonna make some coffee.
It's windy.
Always is.
You get used to it.
I never will.
Mm.
Prison does
something to a man.
Makes him
bitter and...
flexible.
When I was younger...
I had the courage
and the will.
I mean, that was
never the problem.
But prison...
prison gave loyalty
to an idea.
You know, something that
was bigger than me,
stronger than me,
more important.
And I-I felt blessed.
You know?
For the first
time in my life,
I was more
than a piece of shit.
I ain't gonna lose that.
Mm.
What time is it?
Quarter to 7:00, there abouts.
Yep.
I was supposed to have a meeting
with my parole officer this morning.
I guess
I'm missing that one.
Yeah, been there.
That's...
Uh...
strong?
Black?
Next thing we need
to do is go from house-to-house.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're close.
All right,
keep me posted.
What happened?
They catch him?
No.
They're hidin'
in one of those houses.
That's where I grew up.
Ray, you have
to call your father.
This is no longer
about the stuff that's between
the two of you.
You need
to make sure he's okay.
All right.
That's it.
That's him.
Walker here.
Hey, Pop, it's Raymond.
Uh.
The reason
why I'm calling--
What is it, son?
There's a deputy
that was killed last night.
Not too far
from where you live.
We heard the commotion.
What do you mean,
you heard the commotion?
Um...
The whirring, helicopters
and... and all that.
Oh. Okay.
Is everybody-everybody
okay in the house?
Yeah, Ray.
You know, Dad, I'd be
more comfortable if you, uh...
you know, if I
stop by,
just check on you.
Ask him to coffee.
I was wonderin' if, uh...
me and you can
get a cup of coffee.
You almost blew it.
I did that
a long time ago.
You wanted me to call him.
What'd he say?
Baby, I can't be going
through this all the time.
Okay?
You know? Every time I get
on the phone with him, it's like...
I feel like a boy.
I'm nobody's boy.
I'm my own man.
Ray.
Honey.
Know what I'm saying.
Please do not ask me
to call this man again.
That's all I'm saying.
What the fuck
is taking them
so long?
Huh. Friends not showing?
They will.
Believe me, they will.
Aryan Brotherhood,
that's right.
Never sacrifice
one of their own.
You watch
your fuckin' mouth.
Sit your ass down.
Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doin'?
I'm just gonna
call this number right now.
Who the fuck you callin'?
Do you really want
to wait any longer?
Worth the stomach...
Stop it.
Shut the fuck--
Do not fucking touch me.
Just let me do this.
I think we've been here long enough,
and it's fucking killing me.
I can't do this anymore.
Hello?
Hi, hey.
Hey. Oh, my God,
thank God you answered.
This is Doreen,
Sobecki's girl.
Doreen?
Yeah. Are you guys
gonna come 'cause we're--
What?
Who is this?
It's Doreen, Sobecki's girl.
Called you last night,
we talked and you told him...
Who?
You got the wrong number.
What do you
mean, wrong number?
This is, this is Doreen.
I talked to you.
You told me last night you all were comin'
here and you were gonna--
You got
the wrong number.
Doreen.
This is Doreen.
I'm hanging up now.
And you-- Hel-Hello?
Hello? Fuck.
Oh my God. Fuck me.
Well?
Well? What do you
fucking think, well?
He acted like he
didn't even fucking know me.
What do you think he's gonna do?
Jeopardize the whole goddamn
word for a two-bit fucking skank like you?
That's really
fucking nice
to say to me right now.
What does that
make you, huh?
What did I ever--
You're still free
to take a car.
Thank you so much.
Considering there's
cops everywhere.
That's a great idea.
There's still
another way.
Go on.
They got
roads around here.
Dozens of roads.
Dirt roads connected
to private roads.
I know
every last one of them.
Better than them.
I don't think that
that's gonna work for us,
Tully.
I'm not
talking about you.
That'd be foolish.
I'm talking about me.
What, you're gonna
drive us out of here?
Give me a break.
No, sir.
I go alone.
You're crazy.
I take you,
and we hit
one roadblock,
and they see us
turn around, it's all over.
But an old black man...
drivin' a rusty automobile,
they don't pay it much mind.
Tell me you're not
really believing this bullshit.
And if you don't return?
Or you bring
back the law?
Yeah?
You need
more collateral?
I ain't got it.
Tully.
Tully, please tell me
you are not buyin' into this.
Fuck it,
you got a better plan?
Not yet.
Here's what I'll do.
I'll get gas.
I'll get groceries.
I'll empty out
my bank account.
Not bad.
$6,000 and some change.
And a map out of here.
Listen to me.
Do not let this
nigger hustle us right now.
Baby, we got to think.
We just lost
our only shot.
We gotta come up
with a better plan.
Do you understand me?
This is not it.
Him sittin' there
talkin' is not it.
Come on.
No, not this old man.
Because if he does...
I will fuck everyone
in this house and he knows it.
He ain't dumb.
Something goes wrong,
and you come back
to a heap of bodies,
you understand?
Understood.
I'm not leaving, unless--
Unless what?
Anthony comes with me.
I don't fucking think so.
Fuck you.
This is a stupid fucking plan.
Tully, look at me right now.
He is fucking
niggering you.
You are getting
hustled by a fucking nigger.
He comes,
or I don't go.
No, no, no.
There is no struggle here.
Look at this fucking black man
telling you what to do.
Shut up.
Fuck, Tully!
All right.
You're on.
Y-You hang in there, son.
Hey.
Anthony.
Hey, you gotta learn.
You fight
with your mind.
Yes, sir.
Okay?
Okay, son,
you did good.
All right.
I'm proud of you.
I am.
Okay.
We got roadblocks
on every major
road out of here.
Perimeter has been set
for 20 miles
in every direction.
There's been no reports
on any stolen cars.
These guys
are still here.
We need to go house-to-house,
door-to-door and smoke
these jokers out.
I want these fuckers found.
Sanchez, with me.
[Raymond]
After I read the report,
we'll be good.
We should
get on to my house.
They gotta be
in one of these houses.
I'm fine checking it out.
Hmm.
Why don't I look
around the side?
Okay.
You're okay?
Yep.
Cop.
Send them away.
Raymond.
It's funny,
I just saw my dad
driving down the road.
Did he tell you I called?
No, he-he doesn't
tell me much.
Huh.
The reason why
I'm here is that
there's been a murder.
And, um...
What happened?
A fellow officer
has been killed.
Well, um...
It would make me feel
really comfortable,
if you just allow me to come
and just take a little browse.
Okay, look, I'm not
gonna get in the middle
of what's going
on between you and your dad.
You're not gonna
get in the middle of it.
Raymond.
No.
This is not
your house anymore.
It's not about
it being my house.
It is not
a good time.
And you know
your dad will not like
like you in here.
Listen, I don't want
to get into any...
family feuds.
You and your dad,
what's going on
between the two of you
has nothin' to do with me.
Hey.
Everything all right?
Heard that.
Just family stuff.
Not a fucking word.
Cassie, I don't hate you.
You know I didn't mean them
things that I said upstairs.
Get on your fucking knees.
Sir, we can work this out.
Shut the fuck up.
Tully!
Shit.
Tully.
Tully. Tully.
We got a cop
behind us.
Fucking...
No worries.
It's a fucking nigger cop.
I hate
fucking cops.
I didn't do anything.
Your fucking
tail lights workin'?
No, everything's fine.
They're good?
I didn't do anything.
What?
Jesus fucking Christ.
Goddamn.
You just let me
do all the talking.
Do not fucking
take that gun out.
My God.
Fuck.
Fucking niggers.
Do you think he knows
about the gas station?
He's gonna
fuck with us.
No, he's not.
I'm just gonna do
all the talking, all right?
I got this.
Do not fucking say a word.
I ain't fucking
going back, all right?
Don't do anything crazy.
I'm pullin' over.
Just play it cool.
Let me do
the talkin'.
[Tully, muttering]
Don't you fucking stutter.
Correction, this is 234.
Good evening, officer.
License and registration,
please.
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Was I drivin'
a little bit too slow?
I was, wasn't I?
Yeah, I figured.
It's, um...
My-My doctor
h-has prescribed these, um...
these special
glasses for me.
Yeah, I have a, um--
License and registration
will work, thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, this is, um...
Besides drivin' too slow,
was I doin'
anything else wrong?
I got these.
We're in a little
bit of a rush.
I'm tryin' to get
him to his mom.
She's not feelin' so good.
Drivin' slow
for being in a rush.
I know,
it's the glasses thing.
They-- I, it's real
hard for me to see.
It's for safety
purposes, you know.
Can I see
your license, please?
Oh, right.
This is,
this is my license.
Terrible picture.
What is it with that, right?
Licenses,
you get the worst photos.
Thank you.
Yup.
Wait here, please.
Sure.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
That was real fucking smart.
The fuck
were you doin', anyway?
I was manipulating him.
Trying to get him
to like, you know.
You must have been doin'
somethin' for him to turn
the fucking lights on.
Did you hear
what you're sayin'?
I'm fucking slow.
Fucking clack cops, thinkin'
they got somethin' to prove.
Okay, just chill.
We're all good?
Your name, sir?
Tully.
Full name?
Man, I didn't
do nothin' wrong.
Nobody said you did.
Then you don't
need my name.
May I see
your identification, please?
I know my rights.
Tully, he's just,
he's just askin' for your--
What?
He's just pullin'
rank for no reason.
No, he's not.
He's just--
I need to see your driver's license
or form of identification.
She gave you
her license, all right?
Everything's in order.
We weren't speedin' or nothin'.
Just back off--
I'm going to ask
you one more time.
I need to see your I.D.
Please.
I told you.
I didn't
do nothin' wrong.
He's just in a mood.
Excuse me.
You need to step
out of the vehicle.
No, you stay put.
Step out
of the vehicle, now.
You hear me
talking to you.
Please.
That's how
you want to play it?
Sir, he's--
This is Deputy Rivers. I'm on--
Get on your fucking
knees, nigger.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Get down. Back up.
Hey, hey, hey!
Get down!
Hey.
Get down. Get down.
Put the gun--
Get on your
fucking knees, now.
Put the gun down.
Fuck you.
Get on your knees.
On your fucking knees.
Okay, wait, we can
work this out.
Get down!
We can work this--
Shut the fuck up.
Fucking cops,
you're all the same.
Hey, you don't need to do this.
You say you want to help us,
and then you stab us
in the fucking back.
I seen it every day.
It makes me fucking sick
Put the gun down.
We can work this out.
Shut the fuck up.
Tully, look at me.
Tully!
What?
Shit!
Tully.
Fuck!
Stupid motherfucker!
Look what
you made me do.
Look at what
you fucking made me do.
You dumb fucking nigger.
What? Huh?
What?
Do something.
Tully!
What the fuck
are we gonna do for now?
Shit.
Huh, what?
Do somethin'.
This is real?
Fucking go.
Fuck, Tully. Tully,
what the fuck did you do?
Let's go.
What the fuck
did you just do?
Just fucking go.
What did you do?
Just fucking drive.
What the fuck?
Did you fucking kill him?
Let's just go.
Let's go.
Just fucking drive.
Did you fucking kill him?
A fucking cop? Shit.
Shit.
Oh my God.
Don't say a fucking word.
Did you kill a fucking cop?
Did you just kill a fucking cop?
Shit.
I had enough
of this shit.
They done takin'
over our house.
They shot your brother.
We gotta get
out of here.
You can't be next.
They can't be next.
There will be no next.
What are we gonna do?
We get
an opportunity,
we're gon' take it.
Okay.
Get up. Get up.
Shut up.
Stay there.
Shut the fuck up.
Come on, pick it up.
Hello?
Ma'am, this is the hospital.
This is Odessa.
An-Ant--
The hospital, yeah.
Anthony.
Anthony, yeah.
Okay.
[sighs]
What the fuck? Where do
you think you're goin'?
What the fuck
is goin' on?
He's dying.
I don't give a shit.
I don't know
who you are,
and I don't know
why you came here.
And I don't give a shit
whether anybody
ever cared for you
or whether if you
cared for anybody.
You ever loved
somebody, Mr. Tully?
I love my daughter.
And I love my son.
But you shot him.
And as long
as I'm breathing,
my boy, he's not
gonna die alone.
Ain't gonna call no police.
That's not gonna happen.
If you're
gonna kill me...
you could shoot me now.
'Cause I'm leavin'.
Stop the car, sir.
Got a lockdown on the area.
No one can go in.
Hey, you must
know my boy.
Raymond Walker.
Deputy Raymond Walker.
The officer, when I left,
said I could return.
M-My wife's alone.
Being as you're a father
of an officer,
and live down the road,
go in but you stay
in the house once you get there.
Right, m-much obliged.
Yes.
Much obliged.
Okay, let's move that out.
Odessa.
Raymond.
Odessa, come--
Odessa, you're okay?
Raymond, Anthony.
What?
Anthony's bleedin',
he's been shot.
What do you mean?
He's been shot.
Mr. Walker tried
to take him to the hospital.
He's been shot?
We gotta,
we gotta get there.
Yeah, okay.
Wait, wait.
W-Who shot him?
The-The people.
They're White. They came into
the house in the middle of the night.
They're in the-- Are you saying
they're in the house?
We've been there
all night, Raymond.
Hey, guys, listen--
listen up!
She said
they are in the house!
1010 Mountain Way.
They're in the house.
Don't let them hurt
Cassie and the babies.
They're
in the house, too.
Okay.
Please.
Odessa, I-I won't.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay, okay?
Oh.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Guys, come on-- Take her!
Guys, take her!
Come with me.
Bring her to the hospital.
Make sure she's okay.
Got it?
Anything?
Nothing.
I called Marcus
and I called Paul.
Nobody's picking up. It's just ringing
and ringing and fucking ringing.
These fucking assholes,
I swear to God.
I fucking told you,
you should not have let him
out of this fucking house.
Fuck.
He brought the cops.
We're stuck. We're fucking
surrounded by cops right now.
Maybe if you had some fucking money,
we wouldn't be in this position.
There was no money.
There was
no fucking money.
They told me
to pick you up
and drop you off.
That was it.
There was no money.
Fuck, fuck!
Pop.
Pop, stop.
All that
bullshit about word.
Fucking word, word.
Fuck you, bitch.
You just got
fucked by a nigger.
How's that feel? Huh?
You let a nigger
fuck you with his will.
Does that
get it up for you, now?
Fucking piece of shit.
Do you want to see
your fucking boy again?
You want to help me.
Fuck you.
You don't know nothin'
about my little boy, or me.
Do you hear that?
You can go
fuck yourself.
Where the fuck
are you going? Doreen?
Let me take care
of Cassie and the babies.
Okay?
This is my house.
Pop, I know that.
But let me
do my job, okay?
Doreen, get your ass back here.
Fuck.
Doreen!
Pop, don't turn
your back on me.
You can't hang up
on me right now.
You can't hang up on me.
Just leave me
to my chores.
Dad, your chores is finished.
My chores
ain't never finished, son.
They ain't never finished.
Pop.
Fucking get up.
Get the fuck up.
Come-Come on. Come on.
Please don't hurt us.
You gotta get
out of here, Doreen.
You gotta make
one right choice.
Don't you
fuck about it, Jamar.
Keep your fucking head down.
Please don't hurt--
Get the fuck back there.
Please don't--
Fucking stay there.
Doreen,
I need your help.
Doreen!
Hey.
Hey, Cassie.
Hey--
You fucked me now, old man.
I didn't
bring them here!
You fucking lied to me!
I-I gave you my word.
One unit in the back.
Boss.
Secure the corner.
What do we got?
My father just went
on in the inside.
Negotiator's 20 minutes out.
We'll wait for him.
Sir.
No.
Come on.
We'll wait for him.
Nobody's negotiating
with my family.
You're gonna
make the call?
Yes, sir.
You're not being--
Forget protocol.
One flinch inside,
I'm calling SWAT.
Go ahead
and make the call.
I'm listening.
This is,
this is Mr. Tully, right?
Listen,
listen man, l-listen.
I can do something
for you right now.
Oh, yeah, like what?
You walk out
of that front door,
nobody gets hurt.
I can offer you
dignity and respect.
You got my word on that.
You fucking lie like
all the rest of them cops.
Cop's word.
No, no, no.
Shit.
I got this.
You ask me
what I want?
Yes, I-I asked you
what you-- yes.
A phone call.
And if I can arrange it,
to whom?
Sobecki.
Paul Sobecki.
Paul Sobecki. Yeah, y-you got
a number for that?
How the fuck should I know, man?
Pelican Bay Maximum Security.
Yeah, l-listen I need
something in return from you.
Yeah, like what?
Jamar and the baby.
Yeah, right,
get fucked.
Man, listen,
they're not a threat to you.
They're keeping me safe.
Then no phone call.
Fuck.
All right,
I'll make you a deal.
I'll give you the boy but you get me my
fucking phone call, you understand?
You give me my fucking phone
call or I'll kill everyone in this fucking house.
Get your fuckin'
ass in here.
Get the boy.
Get the fucking boy, now!
Don't you
fuck with me, old man.
Hey.
W-Where's Odessa?
She's gone.
I think she went
to get help.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
You okay?
Don't let him hurt my son.
Let's fucking move.
All right.
Mr. Walker, please help us.
Yeah.
Jamar, please listen
to Mr. Walker.
What the fuck you doin'?
Come on.
Please.
All right.
Let's go, come on.
Please.
Let's move.
What the fuck?
All right.
Oh, Danny.
I swear to God,
I did my best.
Okay.
I want you to walk
down that driveway.
Okay?
All right.
Hey.
Never look back.
Yes, sir.
All right.
Mr. Walker?
What?
You mad at me?
Why you say that?
'Cause you're always mad.
You never smile.
Oh, no.
I'm not mad at you.
Now, you go.
Be strong.
And kind.
Hey.
Strong, kind man.
Yes, sir.
Yeah.
And Jamar?
Yes?
Don't forget me.
Yes, sir.
You remember me real good.
All right.
3-2-0-1-4.
He kept his word.
I'm gonna see
if I can get somebody.
[phone ringing]
I gave you the boy.
Calm down, okay.
So where's
the fucking call?
Tully,
calm down, okay?
Listen, listen. Let's-Let's-Let's
make another deal.
Fuck you,
I already made one deal.
Give me Cassie
and the baby.
Fuck you.
I'm not giving you shit.
Calm down, okay?
Where's Sobecki?
Fuck you,
I'm not calming down.
Where's Sobecki?
Give-Give me
five minutes.
I'll get you your call.
Five minutes.
If you don't get me
that fucking phone call,
I'm killing the old man,
you understand me.
You don't have to kill anyone.
I'm killing the old man.
You don't want, you don't want
to kill nobody.
Fuck you, cop.
How the fuck do you know what I want?
No, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey.
Move, move.
Go get your ass over there.
Back, back,
back, back, back.
In here.
Get your fucking ass in here.
You fucking lied to me.
Doreen!
Doreen, get your ass
out in here.
I'm sorry.
I just don't know.
Nobody really
taught me how to do this.
Doreen!
Don't fucking move.
Jesus Christ,
what the fuck, Doreen?
What?
Whose is that
fucking money?
What-What money?
Who's goddamn
money is that?
This my money.
It's my money. This is the money
for the lawyer for my baby.
You cannot
have this money.
It's my money.
You dumb fucking bitch.
Hello?
Hello, hello,
hello, hello, hel--
You tryin'
Jew me, Goldberg?
Hey, Tully, Tully.
Tully, you there?
Where's Sobecki?
Hey, we're connecting the call.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Find him.
I ain't got all goddamn day.
What the fuck
are you doin'?
Doreen, they will
fucking kill you, you understand?
They will
fucking shoot you.
Shit.
Doreen, get down.
What the fuck are you doin'?
Doreen, where
the fuck are you goin'?
What are you
going to tell Sobecki?
That you killed me?
That you let a bunch
of niggers leave?
What about the AB?
The Cause?
It's a joke.
I need you.
Don't you fucking
walk out on me, Doreen.
You will fucking
die out there.
Help me. Help me.
Doreen, don't you
fucking do this.
I have to.
Please don't shoot.
Please don't shoot,
I'm a hostage.
What the fuck? Doreen!
I'm comin' out.
Doreen!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Come down the stairs, slowly.
Please don't shoot, okay?
I'm a hostage.
Get down on your knees.
Please don't shoot me.
Get down!
On your knees.
Don't shoot me.
I didn't do anything.
Get on your knees, now.
I'm a hostage.
Come on, y'all.
Patch him in.
Is that the phone
that stinks or your hand?
Hello? Tully.
Sir.
It's you, isn't it?
Yes, Paul, it's me.
It's a big
mistake, calling.
Doreen?
She fucking
walked out, man.
Straight
into their arms.
She's a fucking traitor.
She's probably
a nigger-fucker, too.
Paul.
I did not
kill that cop.
That motherfucker
tried to get me.
You know what
they're like.
Okay, what do you
want me to do?
I don't know,
I don't know, just--
Tell the screws
to let you go.
Fuck, man.
Just give me the word
and I will kill
every fucker in this house.
That's all I ask,
just give me the word.
My word, with half
the FBI listening?
I got fucking
hostages here, Paul.
I've been out of jail
for 24 fucking hours,
I am not going back.
You ain't got dick!
You ain't got dick.
You got a house
full of porch monkeys,
I got hemorrhoids,
and neither is doing us
any good.
You listen.
Last time I talked, you were supposed
to take care of Bakersfield.
You did not do that.
Now...
I got the Sureos
coming after me.
You think I want
to mess with those spics?
I fucked up.
I don't know what to do.
Just help-help me.
No. No, no, no.
Here's my help.
You gotta go
south on this.
I ain't surrenderin', Paul.
I ain't fuckin'
goin' back to jail.
You are going
to do as they say.
I ain't
fuckin' surrenderin'.
I ain't surrenderin'.
Don't. Shh, hey.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
I ain't surrenderin'.
Hey.
What's the white man do,
Tully?
What's a white man do,
He brings
the bolts down.
Now, right now
the bolts for you
are walking out of that house
with both hands over your head.
If I come back to jail, Paul,
what's gonna happen to me?
Am I gonna be safe?
Let me hear you guarantee it.
I did 15 fucking
years for you, Paul.
Tully. Listen to me.
Fifteen fucking years.
Tell me I'll be safe.
Do you hear what
I'm sayin' to you, Paul?
This ain't
no fuckin' Armageddon.
It's a business.
And you're out of it.
I need your fucking
help right now.
Don't leave me here, Paul.
All right,
they're-they're callin' me.
Tully, I gotta go.
Wait, Paul.
Paul, don't.
See you soon.
Paul.
Fuck. Paul.
Paul, I did
15 fucking years for you!
It's done, hang the fuck up.
To dawn, motherfucker.
Fuck you.
Don't you fucking
leave me, motherfucker.
Fuck!
You're a fucking dead man!
You're fucking dead.
I'm not gonna beg
for my life.
What is it, Tully?
Huh?
My skin?
If it's my skin...
killin' us
won't save you.
Hmm?
But what if it is...
something inside of you?
Something pained
deep inside of you
that you're fighting.
Well, if it is,
maybe we're fighting
the same fight.
We're in the same boat.
I lost everything
and I ain't goin' back.
You haven't
lost everything.
How?
You haven't
lost everything.
You feel afraid?
Yeah.
You're afraid.
You're afraid
of the choice
that you have.
And right now,
the choice you have
is to put
that gun down.
Right now.
And we walk out of here.
That's the choice you have.
This is my fucking choice.
And this is my choice.
And at the end of the day, you'll
always be a fucking nigger.
Yes. Nigger.
Nigger.
It always
comes down to that.
Lazy, ignorant.
Takes what isn't his.
Lazy. That nigger.
No.
Always are.
Always blaming
his circumstances
as an excuse
to get what he thinks
he deserves, that nigger.
Hell, that nigger
doesn't think
about the future,
tomorrow.
Today, he thinks
about getting his
sneaky, grubby, running,
grabby-- that nigger.
Yeah, that nigger.
Huh?
There's only one
nigger in this room,
in this house.
And that nigger is you.
That nigger's you.
That nigger's you, Tully.
That nigger is you.
The fuck.
Feels good, huh?
It's a wonderful world.
Come on.
Don't.
Come on, man.
It's okay.
We're goin' in.
We gotta move now.
There's no choice.
SWAT, let's go.
We're coming out.
Stand down.
Here we are.
We're comin' out.
Raymond, you're here?
Stand down,
my pop's comin' out.
Ray?
You there?
Yeah, Pop, I'm right here.
Tell them to back down.
We're coming out.
Okay? We...
are coming out.
Keep movin' forward.
Don't shoot.
Tully,
turn to your right.
Get down
on your knees.
Clasp your hands
behind your head.
Hands clasped.
Stay right there.
Hey.
Much obliged.
It's all good, Dad.
It's all good.
Mm.
Love you.
Got a lot of work
to do around here.
Yeah, son?
Uploaded and synced by UbuntuGo