Previously, on
"The Real Housewives of New York City"...
Well,
thanks for getting a hold of me.
- I'm really excited about this.
- Oh, I was so excited
to find you,
because I don't know,
hardly anything
about my family tree.
This is a part
of me that's excited.
You have
good matches, so possibly,
you could have
some half siblings.
Right. But, this is,
like a shot in the dark.
You just get
very angry recently.
That's what
we don't understand.
I'm not a ****ing doormat.
Your reactions are just,
like, over the top,
and that's what concerns us.
So, I'm gonna
do an event next week.
It's actually
called Black Shabbat.
- A Jewish Shabbat dinner?
- Correct.
- That's for Black people?
I hope she's not gonna
get on a soap box
- and start preaching to us.
- I-I don't know what to expect.
- Where's Leah?
- Okay, Leah, sadly,
was exposed,
potentially, to COVID.
Oh, no.
So excited
to have all of you here.
We are having
a "Jew Belong" Shabbat tonight.
When I went to college,
the Jewish people hated me.
- We're not talking about that.
- I'm just saying.
Right now, we're talking
about the Black race,
- and our Jewish friends.
- I wished I was born Jewish.
- Ramona!
- Sit down, shiksa!
We're not gonna make it about
you and your white isolation.
Are we getting our first course?
- We're not done with Shabbat.
- This is nuts, Leah.
Like this is why
I needed you here.
I need food.
What did they tell you to do?
I don't even understand
what happened to Ramona.
I kinda regret doing
this whole thing, by the way.
*THE REAL HOUSEWIVES OF NEW YORK CITY*
Season 13  Episode 15
Episode Title:
"Bitching and Ramoaning"
Like,
why does Sonja get it,
Luann gets it,
Ramona doesn't ****ing get it.
Well, I'm just gonna
have a little something,
because I'm getting
a little hangry.
Can I have this?
This is my plate?
I'll eat it now. Okay, great.
It's just, I need food.
You know, I was running all day.
I went with my accountant,
I did business with real estate.
I didn't have time to eat.
I really didn't eat.
And, we've been
here now for two hours,
and I know we're doing
all these prayers and stuff,
and you know, it was delicious,
but I need food.
What can I say?
Sometimes, when there's no food
to put in my mouth,
my foot goes in my mouth.
Like, I feel like
I'm being so diplomatic.
You know what I think?
I think we're flustering
the host, the hostess.
Is it host or hostess?
You know, they say,
it used to
be waiter and waitress,
and now,
it's just waiter, you know?
It's supposed to be,
like, singular sex,
I mean,
it's so confusing.
Her, she,
uh, them.
You know, seriously, things
have changed in this world.
I'm a little older,
and I'm learning the new world.
But right now, I'm starving.
I'm not gonna expose you
to this, this is a sh... show.
Yeah,
I'll call you after.
Thank you, I love you,
I'll talk to you later.
Thank you.
Love you.
Listen, I bring you to
a beautiful home, with beautiful
people, there's beautiful food,
and beautiful drinks.
All you gotta
do is shut the hell up
and enjoy,
and Ramona can't even do that.
I think I left my purse in here.
So,
it's like a feta, but better?
I left it in
the other room, I think.
Oh, those look good.
Oh, here it is.
But you didn't
add too much of it?
And then the roasted red peppers
are great.
- What are you doing?
- I'm starving,
- I haven't eaten all day long.
- You're kidding me.
They want to bless
the bread yet.
- Oh.
- We have another hour to go.
Ramona's in
the kitchen, eating.
Lu, let her eat.
That's fine.
What does that mean,
she's in the kitchen eating?
- She's eating in the kitchen.
- She's that hungry?
- Yeah.
- She's a grown-up, like...
Thank you
for making the effort.
Oh, effort!
I'm having a great time.
- Are you having fun?
- This is better than a show.
Good.
I'm giggling, because it's
shocking, and embarrassing.
I just feel very misunderstood.
Tonight wasn't even about,
actually,
it wasn't about Black people.
This is supposed to be about
human values that we all have.
Well, everybody
doesn't have them.
When Ramona's hungry, the human
values go out the window.
Shocking and embarrassing
leads to me giggling.
What can I tell you,
that's how I cope.
- Are you okay, baby?
- I don't know.
I think, I had a, I had a
meltdown. I had a meltdown.
I don't...
Listen, I didn't eat all day.
You haven't eaten a morsel,
so you're starving?
- You're hungry...
- No, it's hangry. Hangry.
I understand, you were hangry.
- We're ready to serve, right?
- Okay, fine. Yeah.
I'm just gonna
make the blessing over the wine.
- Perfect.
- On page five.
- Where's Leah?
- She said **** us.
I don't blame her.
I'd like to bless with tequila.
- Here's tequila.
- I don't think the Jews do that.
- Yes, they do.
- Do they?
- Jew Belong, are you kidding me?
- I'll Jew Belong!
Let her do the toast, please.
You should worry
about what you're saying.
Shh. Can I, can
I have a little bit of...
Shh, wait. Wait, just wait.
Everybody stay with me:
Sonja's been drinking non-stop
since we got on the bus,
like, three hours ago,
and with no food.
So, this is not
going to be pretty.
Yes.
Here's our entrees.
I'm gonna run
off to the restroom.
- Okay, baby.
- Thank you.
Thank you. This looks beautiful.
Challah!
- Challah!
Eboni,
I feel, were you happy?
- You feeling okay?
- I'm good.
I just want my
friends to see what we do.
We do this routinely.
I mean, it's hard.
You know,
in many ways, maybe Ramona's
outburst was accurate because everybody...
Everybody doesn't get what we do, Archie?
No, no,
I do this with my friends.
A lot of my friends are Jewish,
and I've gone to temple,
and I almost converted...
I would never think
you were anti-Semitic,
but what I do want you
to understand though,
Ramona, is the reason
this is Black Shabbat
- is because there's a special...
- Bond...
...between Blacks and Jews.
- Yeah, between Blacks and Jews.
- Yeah, I think it's fabulous.
- It's not meant to alienate...
- Right.
...Italians or Scottish
people or anyone else.
It's just to say
that in this country,
we kind of share
a unique experience.
I understand. I get it.
Thank you,
Ramona, for being open
to revisit it,
because that's important.
Guys, I hate to do this,
but I'm going to pull us
- back to the Shabbat.
- Don't hate to do it.
Don't hate to do it at all.
This is a Shabbat dinner.
Okay,
as I said at the beginning,
Shabbat is the perfect
time to do soul searching.
For so many people, it's so
hard to show their heart.
- So, show me your heart...
- I am.
Hold on, I have to think
about my questions.
I don't wanna read anymore.
I want talking now.
Wait, so I wanted to share
Ramona, you're not running sh...
You're running, alright?
It's not yours.
So, the questions
about the week are on page 20.
- So, everyone can pick one.
- Okay, what makes my heart beat?
- Whoa.
- More one-on-one relationships.
- Yeah.
- More of the one-on-one.
I need that, and I'm not talking
about with my girlfriends.
I'm talking about my
philanthropy, and my message.
I'm talking about now more on a
one-to-one basis for soul food.
You know what I mean?
Like I won't do the
$1200 ticket bull****
We raise real
money for real causes that
a lot of
people don't care about.
Sonja, a lot of times just
has one drink too many,
she has diarrhea of the mouth,
she's like
a broken record,
and she doesn't let anybody
else have a chance to talk.
- It's annoying.
- The dinners I do...
- Oh my God.
- ...don't even cover the wine.
So the wine that's donated
is like, I don't know, $1200.
Alright, who has
the next question?
- I don't, we don't have...
- Next.
Excuse me, jealous bitch.
- I'm not jealous.
- Well, why'd you cut me off?
Because she
took over the questions...
The charities I do
have step and repeats.
- That's great. Are you next?
- What you do you?
Why don't you tell us what
you're doing on a daily basis?
Because this woman is on the
ground, she is helping people
to come out of prison
and get a home, and a job.
What are you doing on
a daily basis to help somebody?
So don't shut me up.
- It's okay, Sonja, it's okay.
- Alright.
So, don't you ever shush me
for my works of faith,
and giving back compassion.
Never shush me.
Please, have some boundaries
and do something for others,
and stop social climbing,
social ****ing
climbing for yourself.
For what?
Another yacht?
Another plane?
Another dress?
- Another Gucci?
- Okay, Sonja, that's enough.
Wow. She's lost
her mind. This is scary.
Oh yeah, I lost my mind.
- Why don't you find one?
- No, no, no, no.
Find a purpose.
Find a ****ing purpose.
Oh, yeah. I lost my mind.
Why don't you find one?
Find a purpose.
Find a ****ing purpose.
Here's the thing.
She needs to cool off.
Archie, don't worry about it.
She's upset.
I feel nuts, but I feel like
we need to continue Shabbat.
Luann, I raised money
with Michael for AIDS awareness.
- I know, but don't, don't...
- These are not just
****ing people
to social climb.
- I know.
- She's not doing the hard work,
she's not
doing the heavy lifting.
- She needs to do more.
- But you know what? Now's not...
And then she sits
at dinner being disruptive
and she needs to get real
and do the
work and feel the other people,
- feel other people's pain.
- I know, but for some reason,
I don't think we're going
to change her mind tonight.
I'm gonna say
this, and I mean it with love.
Time out on the
white people for tonight.
- We're gonna go with...
- Oh, we're segregated now?
- That is so funny.
- We've been segregated.
Well, I'm both.
I'm white and Black.
Ramona just said she's
white and Black.
Ramona is pulling
a Michael Jackson tonight.
I go both ways.
We're gonna hear
from the culture.
And, we're gonna go to Linara.
What question
would you like to answer?
Yeah, Linara.
When did I feel that my
life was most meaningful?
Last year, at
this time, I gave birth
to a 29-weeker,
and I was in the NICU for...
Wait, excuse me, time out.
- Mm-hm.
- You gave birth early?
Because normal is what?
40?
- It's 40 weeks.
- Wow.
So me and my son almost died.
- Oh my God, are you serious?
- Shh.
I had some poor medical service,
as most Black women experience.
Do you think that
the treatment that you got
was because you were Black?
I know the treatment
that I got because...
Because why?
I have fibroids, and I had
a fibroid that was degenerating.
They just didn't believe
that I was actually in
as much pain
as I was communicating.
So, instead they thought
that I was addicted to drugs.
- What? Oh, come on.
- And they treated me,
as I was
asking for pain medicine
for five days that I was trying
to hurt myself and my baby.
And so because
I was in pain for so long,
- it induced my labor.
- So, how would a white woman
be treated
differently than you?
- That's a good question.
- Medically, medically.
How would I have
been treated, may I ask?
Should that have been
you, and there is a study
that just came out
last week that a white woman,
you would have
gotten the pain medicine
during the time frame
in which you needed to
in order to manage it,
and get ahead of it.
So, that, that would have
- never happened.
- Let me tell you something.
I gave birth
to my daughter,
and I was in
major pain and I had a nurse,
and she was Black,
and I said I am having
so much pain
and she wouldn't believe me.
She goes, "You're not
having pain." I was screaming
and I'm like, "**** you,
I need painkillers."
I mean, I didn't have a
second baby because of the
pain I had from my first,
and I was a white woman.
My doctor didn't take care
of my pain, my nurses didn't.
That's not how it usually
goes, is what she's saying.
I'm just saying I was in ****ing
pain and no one paid attention
- to my pain.
- Well, you're very special.
She's saying that's
not how it goes normally.
I'm just saying.
I mean it happens
to white people too.
Some white people,
not most white people.
- Did you hear what she said?
- This is a runaway train.
You jump out
the window, you're doomed.
If you stay in the
train, you're doomed.
I mean, either way,
you're gonna crash.
I feel like
you are the most graceful.
Thank you.
Like everything
you say is with grace.
She is.
Most people would have
cursed Ramona the **** out
- when you ask them that.
- Like me.
Well, I like
to ask questions, I'm sorry.
I know, but it comes
across, wait a minute,
Archie,
Archie, wait, one second.
I need to speak on this.
What Ramona
doesn't realize, and I think
I also have a high tolerance
for Ramona's inquisition,
at some point, the questioning
feels... adversarial.
- That's my personality.
- I understand,
but I want you to know,
because I do care about you.
- I question like a lawyer.
- We talked about it.
- I question things.
- Because I don't want you,
Ramona, looking unlike your
spirit, so therefore you have to
make space for the fact that
when you question this woman
about her experience
giving birth, surely...
No,
I'm in shock that a doctor...
So, then say "I'm in shock."
- I'm in shock. I am in shock.
- Thank you. Say that.
Okay.
I believe in Ramona Singer.
God help me,
And I really want Ramona to
understand that what she's saying
is not becoming,
and I don't even think
it's really her on a visceral
level, but I'm really about to
run out of patience with
Ramona's ass.
That wasn't Linara's answer.
Now, Lu's going to pick
- a number.
- I just have one more question.
Did you,
she was a different doctor?
- Yes.
- Are we closing this up soon?
We're not closing it up.
You can get an Uber.
- You need to go?
- It's like nine o'clock.
I've been here for four hours.
I'm tired.
- I want to go home and sleep.
- Yeah, go home.
Things are happening
here tonight.
Nobody that doesn't
want to be here should be here.
- No, I'm just tired.
- I understand.
You should go home, Ramona.
Go ahead.
- I get it.
- I'm not holding anybody hostage
- at god damned Black Shabbat.
- No.
If you don't want to be
here and listen to the spiritual
work being done,
get the **** out.
Nathan, I'm tired.
I've been studying, working,
so call me an Uber.
I'm gonna say
goodnight, okay?
Sorry, Archie,
this is too much.
No, it's not.
- You have went out of your way.
- I am so sorry.
I've been as patient as
I know how to be
with your
...ing friend, Ramona.
You don't want to do the work,
get the **** out.
- Don't blame her on me.
- I don't know what's going on.
Do you really want to leave?
Is this you trying
to undermine this evening?
And what it's about?
Or are you
just too damned selfish
to appreciate what is
in front of you? Bitch, bye.
I mean, if I wasn't tired,
I'd stay for another hour,
but I'm tired and you know what,
I have to listen to my body.
I appreciate that.
It was already an hour and
a half drive to get there.
I've been there for over
three hours. Even weddings don't
last more than three or four
hours, and this isn't a wedding.
Well, I'm leaving in
a couple of minutes, so.
Oh, you're gonna
take an Uber home?
Yeah. I'm tired.
You came, and you participated,
which is what I appreciate.
Yeah, I was going
to answer the question.
What would I like
to change about myself?
- To be more filtered.
- More what?
- More filtered.
- Oh, more filtered.
Because sometimes,
I say things...
Okay, before,
okay guys, guys,
Ramona's gonna leave
us probably a few minutes early.
But, she wants to
offer her answer first.
If I could change one thing
about myself, what would it be?
Oh, I love that.
- To be less unfiltered.
- Okay.
I sometimes
speak without thinking.
I didn't mean to insult
anybody tonight. I know I did.
I'm sometimes like
a two year old,
- I'm trying to get better.
- Yeah.
I know I'm not perfect.
No, that's what I'd like
to change, and I want
to still be
honest and say how I feel.
But sometimes, I don't think
about other people's feelings
and I don't take in
what they're saying, before
I jump on what I'm feeling
and thinking so.
- Oh, wow, well said.
- Have you always been like that?
- Even when you were a kid?
- I was worse.
- I've gotten better.
- No, you're much better.
- You don't understand.
- They say she's better.
- She's much better.
- That's embarrassing.
But I still gotta get better.
I gotta get better.
Ramona's come such a long way
and I thought we exhausted all
- that bad behavior.
- So I don't get why he's here.
I heard that you
never go out without him.
Is that really true?
That's like so strange.
At least I have friends,
you have no friends.
You have nobody in your life.
Right now, you have Jason.
You'll probably
mess that up too.
143 something?
114. Don't you think
you should have written it down?
So you remember? So you
don't have to ask me again?
You knew that if Avery
was coming down here,
it was because I have
a huge anxiety problem.
It would
be to get me on the plane.
Aviva, you're missing the point!
- Don't yell at me.
- Take a Xanax!
- Call my husband.
- Calm down!
You're in the press now,
being naked and doing soft porn.
Has anybody approached
your daughter?
Have you explained
to her the situation?
- At six? Yeah, she got a...
- No, I'm asking.
You look old
for your age and I look
young for my age,
and that's how it stands.
You are a bitch.
What did
I say that was so mean?
I'm just amazed that she still
had this
kind of behavior in her.
We want to
acknowledge that you had
the self-awareness to say that.
I'm construing that as a
bit of an apology to Linara.
- Absolutely, I apologize.
- About her experience,
-Yeah
-and that's good.
I apologize for losing
it on you, because, you know,
I love you like
family, and family does that.
- Y'all go ahead and do that.
- They just do that.
- You know, family does that.
- No, I'm serious.
They need to do that.
I'm not sorry
for a god damned
thing I said.
You have come so far.
- I mean every word.
- You really have come so far.
I love you, but you
have so far to go, still.
I'm grossed out.
I am so grossed out right now.
I'm always there
for Ramona, no matter what,
she has a soft place to fall
and maybe, she learned something
tonight, but I'm not
happy about what's transpired.
She eats, and she's done.
Yeah, she was hungry.
She was a ****ing...
She ate, then she was less
of..., but still a...
Coming up...
Ramona and I are night and day,
and yet, we're very aligned.
It's very weird.
And I never met someone
that I bonded with so fast.
I wouldn't say that
you are like Ramona
- but okay.
- No, we are.
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
No Avery, no cocoa.
I'm home alone.
Good thing I like myself.
- Hey, good morning.
- It's me, hi.
I'm just talking
about you, to myself.
You were talking to yourself?
- Yeah.
- How's that going?
It's going,
I mean, usually I talk to...
- It's hot here.
- Really? I'll open the window.
Because I'm always
hot, now I feel fine.
But, I'll open a window for you?
- Yeah. It's warm in here.
- Okay.
How you doing? Oh my gosh!
This view, you can never
get enough of this view.
I don't think Ramona even
has a clue
that she was like over the top,
rude to so
many people last night.
And uh,
you know, I'm not here to
pour gasoline on the fire.
I'm here to, you know,
help her figure out how she's
going to stand back up.
That was quite the night.
As soon as Sonja went nuts on
me, I just like blocked it out.
I know, but it's not the
first time she went nuts on you.
She started saying
really disgusting things,
and I think she's
just talking about herself.
I think she's projecting.
I do think it's sometimes
a reflection of what's going on
the inside, when people do that.
I feel like
I'm watching a train wreck.
I feel like, I feel like
she's on a train
and I know she's gonna crash.
- I know. I feel helpless.
- And there's nothing we can do.
Sonja, at this point,
has no regard for people's
feelings, people's
property and most importantly,
no regard for herself,
the way she's acting.
I love Ramona. Deflect. Let's
keep the focus on somebody else
like Sonja, and not myself.
Have you spoken to Eboni?
Yeah, I did.
Um, I mean I did.
First of all,
let me just give you
my opinion, before
I hear even what Eboni said.
First of all, it was so rude,
and I'm being
totally honest with you.
- I was starving. I'm sorry.
- I understand that, but you have
to reel it in and go,
"Oh my God, am I being rude?
"And I should probably
get back to the table."
I said, "Can I please
get something to eat, because
"I'm really hungry. I haven't
eaten all day."
They brought
out all those appetizers.
It wasn't enough for me.
I was still starving.
- If I don't get my sleep...
- Listen, then you go and sneak
a snack in the kitchen and
you get back to the table.
I mean, you actually,
you had a whole meal.
No, I didn't.
I just had the corn, the...
I went past the
kitchen to get a diet coke,
and I saw you had a full
plate of food. So, come on.
I had too much to drink.
I admit it.
You've done things on drinking.
So you know what?
-Don't throw it out on me now
-I'm... fine.
And attack me for my mistakes
that I've made,
because that's, that's ****ing
tone deaf, period.
I don't
need to apologize to you.
You don't need
to apologize to me.
- I apologized to Eboni.
- I'm not looking for an apology.
I'm looking for you to be aware.
Of course, I'm aware.
I called Eboni first thing
in the morning,
and I said, "I'm sorry
"about what I did.
I had too much to drink.
- "I'm tired..."
- It was nine o'clock, Ramona.
- I was exhausted.
- You go out dancing...
Not anymore,
not in the past week.
No, but still.
Not in the past week?
No.
The past week,
I've been in bed every night
at nine o'clock, 9:30.
When she's
not dizzy, she's hungry,
and if she's
hungry, she has to pee.
I mean, there's one
excuse after the other, why she
excuses herself from,
typically, Eboni's parties.
And my lesson
I've learned now, I'm never,
ever, ever, mark
my words, I'm never gonna
drink on an empty stomach.
You're funny.
Can you please bring
the cheese and wine out
- for Eboni, so we're ready?
- Okay. Yeah.
Are you,
do you have any clothes on?
What?
You know me, I hate pants.
- You have no pants on!
- No pants.
Is that part
of the fashion forecast
for next year?
I just started to wear proper,
grown woman dresses
that come to the knee.
Now, you're telling me we're not
wearing pants at all?
- Just the top?
- Millennial, OK?
Oh, millennial. Not boomers.
- Lady Morgan!
- Hi, Eboni.
I'm dying to meet you!
I'm Christie!
- Christie? You're lovely. Eboni.
- Yeah, nice to meet you.
You have no idea.
Everyone heard you were coming.
Hey baby.
Well, I met beautiful Miss Emma.
You finally met Emma.
She's been dying to meet you.
I don't think
last night went the way
Archie and Eboni planned.
But, the thing about
Eboni is she has this quality
where she can discuss
something with you in a very
calm manner
without being accusatory.
At this dinner last
night, I want to apologize
really, for losing it.
Because I was going through
this emotional thing.
That's not you. I think you
and Ramona need to talk.
You two have such a deep 30 year
sisterhood, and I know you both
love each other dearly, but
it's a little tense. You know?
But I don't want her walking all
over me in front of people in
- front of people I don't know.
- I know, baby.
And that's why you need
to go to her...
She's putting
out the wrong narrative.
And you controlled it.
I think that going back
to Martin, you know, he struck a
chord in you and I've seen
a difference that I love.
Which is you are not
letting people run over you.
What does Luann call you?
A slut!
A one night stand.
If I call
you a stupid slut,
that's
how hard you're gonna throw?
Show him he's a piece of sh...!
You are not letting
other people tell your story.
So, when Ramona started
doing that sh... last night,
you were like, "No!" And you
corrected the narrative.
But I want you two to do that,
maybe over lunch, or dinner.
Intimate, loving, but say
what you need to say to her.
You know? So that you don't
snap like you did last night.
Well, I need that
because, you don't act like
- that in front of mixed company.
- That's why... right, no.
And you know better, Sonja.
I'm proud that "Mission: Sonja
"stand up for yourself"
has been successful.
I really am. But sis, there's a
measure to these things, right?
Cheers to controlling
the narrative, and self-control.
So, we're gonna try to work to
find where that sweet spot is,
where Sonja does
stand up for herself, she makes
it very clear what she will
and will not take and stand for.
But also has like, some basic...
"social graces",
we'll call them.
- Now, you, my love.
- Yeah, and now about me.
I have to curse you out
because why did Archie call
me this morning, and tell me...
You might not even remember
this, do you know you peed
in Archie's driveway last night?
Yes, I did.
At the back of the bus.
How you been? I'm just gonna
pee behind the bus.
I'll be over...
Sonja, come on!
Sonja!
Holy sh...,
I'm peeing like a race horse!
- Sonja. The ****?
- I had to pee so bad...
- You were all in there.
- But we peed before we left,
'cause I know I can't hold
it 'til New York either, baby.
- I gotta tell you...
- I want you to...
I have done things like
that before, peed wherever.
This is horrible!
They don't
want pee on their corn!
Wait, Sonja, be careful!
You couldn't hold
it until we got out?
It's not
my proudest moment,
peeing behind the
van, but if I had gone
into the restroom, Luann
would've left without me.
Sonja, you are a woman
of such elegance, and class.
Stop it, Marley,
I'm mad at you!
Marley, you've ate the whole
damn board!
You ate more than me,
we didn't eat anything!
No, Marley at it all.
Marley,
get the hell out of here.
Yeah, we're talking to you!
And by the way,
I'm gonna talk to Ramona.
She did call me
today to apologize
because she knew she
was a ****ing hot ass mess.
Everything was designed to make all
of y'all comfortable
and she was a sh... show.
And you were great,
and Lu was great,
and it was fun...
Well, you were half great.
I was 85% good, until I got
to the van and I was
like, "Okay, I'm gonna pee."
Hey, baby.
I feel bad because
I know Leah likes to see us.
- I know.
- I missed her at Shabbat.
Oh, God.
I missed her at Shabbat.
It was like
I was missing my finger.
Having her at
Shabbat is so important.
- Marley, are you serious.
- Oh, Jesus.
- Is he humping your arm?
- Marley's humping my arm.
You're like any other guy.
You have your stomach
full, and now you're ready
to have sex.
- Right!
- Isn't that funny how men are?
As soon as they eat dinner,
they want sex.
Marley, you're
just full and humping.
You'd
be humping Ramona's dog,
but you didn't bring your dog.
I can't wait
for these two to meet.
Thank god I got her fixed.
Coming up...
So, I'm sitting there the
first six months, no court date.
- But to make a very...
- Which is unconstitutional.
- Whoa, no, no, no, no.
- 17 years old.
- Ramona.
- No, hello... no!
Oh sh...
- Hello.
- Darling, I'm in a Hutte.
I know right? It's like,
it could be Colorado,
it could be Switzerland.
Look at this. Isn't it cool?
Isn't it great? We miss you!
Aw, babe. Don't fall apart.
You're almost through it.
You're almost there.
Who are you having dinner with?
I'm meeting up with
the Fortune Society ladies.
Eboni and Ramona are coming,
Sonja, I don't
know where Sonja is.
After the
poop settled, and I started
plunging it,
it turned into poop soup.
When you get
the poop soup, and you
plunge it and it goes
on the floor, that's really bad.
Hi, my love.
- Oh, look who's here!
- Oh, Lele!
- Hi!
- Hey baby,
look how naked you are.
Look how naked?
She's so naked.
And we're in like turtlenecks in
the middle of this alpine lodge.
It's really cute, though.
- Isn't it sweet?
- It smells good.
I love it,
it's like in our neighborhood.
It's like our go-to.
I thought maybe it would
be nice to be isolated
for two weeks, but I'm
actually having a little bit
of FOMO,
and miss the ladies.
Oh, well, I mean...
How are they, Lu?
Well, I mean,
Ramona's coming tonight,
so we'll soon
find out how Ramona is.
And Sonja, couldn't come.
So, I don't know why.
If you leave the
water, the poop disintegrates.
I talked to Sonja over
the weekend. She was doing well.
Why would I pay
for someone to...
Oh my god,
when I poop, I feel so good.
- Hey baby!
- Okay.
Look who just
walked in the door.
Beautiful!
Wow, you're very elegant
for our little chalet over here.
Well, you know, you did such,
I have to say,
I had so
much fun doing that video.
I know last time,
I didn't want to do it when you
did it years ago,
but had I known I'd have
that much fun, I should've
done it. Your hair looks pretty.
Thank you, you too.
You look lovely.
It's typical Ramona,
you know. After she's burned
down the house,
it's like, "Let's be nice.
"Let's make a grand entrance.
Grand gestures, compliments."
There, she's very good.
You look great.
So, okay, we're talking
about Sonja and how we feel
like there was so
much venom and bad stuff.
- Oh, I sent her a text.
- You sent her a text?
So I wrote,
"Sonja, do you remember
"all the very
nasty comments you made to me
"at the Black Shabbat?
"You really hurt
my feelings terribly."
- And she didn't get back to you?
- Well, I only sent it
an hour ago. It'll probably take
her three days to look at it.
- No, I know.
- Oh, my food just got here,
- I gotta go, guys.
- Okay.
- Bye guys.
- Bye baby.
The last thing
I wanna hear about is like
Ramona gaslighting Sonja.
So, I'm out.
- Hey, guys!
- Hey, ladies.
Hi!
- Hi, my loves!
- Hi ladies.
- You look lovely.
- Oh, I love your mask.
I just got out of work,
just now. Thanks for having us.
The ladies from
Fortune and I have known
each other for the last
couple of years.
We have 80 beds in here
for people transitioning,
men and woman.
Been in prison,
coming out of prison,
getting their life together.
Look at this team of
people waiting for your girls.
I love you!
Mwah! Thank you.
It always brightens my day
when I see their faces because
they're such wonderful
people and such good women.
How many people are living
in the facility right now?
Well, I came home
in 2007, and I lived at
the castle when I was there.
There were
56 men and three women.
So, I was one of the women.
That was...
Are those good odds or bad odds?
I'm not sure.
Yeah, Ramona.
But, you know,
now I know there's maybe
more than
100 beds in there, now.
It's grown over the years.
How old were
you when you went in?
Distribution?
I was at the wrong
place at the wrong time.
Someone got shot.
And I was there.
I didn't go
inside of the building,
but I was outside
of the building.
So, what were they
convicting you of?
- Conspiracy.
- Oh my god.
So, somebody was harmed...
Okay, conspiracy from
a legal point of view...
- Go ahead.
- Is when you are aware.
And you weren't aware.
So, conspiracy is when you
have knowledge of it.
- It was two weeks later.
- And you're not participating.
Two weeks later,
I never reported anything.
- News articles.
- At some point,
- she did know that someone died.
- Yes.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It is, girl, a hot mess.
Just shut the hell up.
We've seen this movie before.
So, now I'm sitting
in Rikers Island.
There's always a glitch
in the Rikers Island system.
So, it said
my next court date was
December 31st, 20-9999999.
So, I'm sitting there the
first six months, no court date.
Which is unconstitutional.
No, no, no.
- Ramona.
- No. No!
Where is the radar
that Ramona was not born with
which says "Do not speak now."
So, I'm sitting there the first
six months, no court date.
Which is unconstitutional.
- You're sitting in Rikers?
- Oh yeah, I'm sitting in Rikers.
- No, no!
- 17 years old.
Ramona.
Yeah.
No, I really have to
pay attention to this.
So, they had no court date,
and they're allowing you
they make you
stay there for like, forever?
I believe they have 90 days...
- Did they give you bail?
- No. It's a murder charge.
- Multiple co-defendants.
- But you didn't murder anybody.
You just heard about it down
the road. You were only 17!
That's not
how the law works, Ramona.
Well,
okay, so ****ing change the law.
This is not good.
I don't like this.
These questions
Ramona's asking,
it's just her lack of awareness
and knowledge on the issue
is a little,
like, why would she know?
We don't talk about this
stuff enough, so I think Ramona
in this moment is indicative
of a lot of Americans.
So, I didn't
have too many options.
A lot of people see murders
and they don't talk about it.
Or know about it, they think
hearsay or whatever,
So, I don't... I think.
Unfortunately, the system sucks.
It often does.
And I had to settle with three
and a half years prison time.
- You plead guilty.
- I plead guilty.
It's important to
hear all of these stories
to make sure that more
people have the knowledge
and can have, you know, more
empathy and understanding
when it comes to these issues.
My first prison sentence,
I went up, I wasn't ready.
I know,
I had reservations,
I came back down, I relapsed,
I went back up again.
When I came
home, I knew everything
was gonna
be different, you know.
What my downfall was, was
that you know,
I used to have
blackouts all the time.
- I know those.
- I used to be able to call
somebody and tell me what I did.
They'd say,
"Oh, Vilma, this is what you
did." And I'd say,
"I don't wanna hear.
I don't wanna hear."
This time, the last thing
I remember was nine o'clock,
I woke up the next day, there
was drugs, there was money,
and I still don't know to this
day what happened to me.
- That was it.
- That was your wake up call.
You gotta get to bottom.
I did five
and a half years in prison.
And still,
it took that moment to
realize this can't be my life.
This can't be.
Can I ask you girlfriends
something?
Let's say you have
a friend that you really love,
- and you see her...
- Oh, sh...
...down the rabbit hole.
How do you like try to help?
- Oh gosh.
- I'm not naming names.
- I'm asking a question.
- I know.
The thing
is you can try your best,
but it has to come from them.
You can be there,
you can support them.
Yeah, just let them know
that the door's always open,
but you have to let them
go through their own process.
Like, I said,
it wasn't 'til the rock bottom.
That's the problem,
even if you say to her,
you know, "Oh,
you did this, you did that.
You left with a guy,
you forgot the caviar."
I would be mortified,
and Sonja is not mortified.
Sonja's like,
"I know, ha ha ha!"
In order for her
to do something about it,
she has to realize what's really
happening.
- Gotta hit bottom.
- I don't want her to go to
rock bottom,
that's the problem.
Yes, she beats up on me,
yes, she verbally abuses me,
yes, she makes up lies about me.
But I'm not giving up on her.
I don't want her
to hit rock bottom.
I just don't want her to.
There might
be something that's
just there that maybe she
hasn't spoken to you guys about.
She might be fighting
a bigger battle within herself.
And she's numbing. Sonja's
numbing. She's numbing hurt.
She's been doing this
for 10 years. It's nothing new.
And that's the part
that you two - no!
I can't.
No, you can't save her!
Listen, I don't like the way you
acted at Shabbat
but I like you Ramona,
and I don't want...
That is unfair to put on
yourself.
No, I agree.
Sonja is accountable to herself,
and all we can do as friends,
and all Ramona
can do as a best friend
is love and support
her friend, that's it.
I was supposed
to be gone two hours ago,
but I can't leave
these women.
Aren't they the best.
- I'm so glad.
- I'm supposed to be at
an interview with somebody right
now. Oh well, **** them!
To be honest,
I just love this.
I'm actually having a really
good conversation with Ramona.
- Oh, good.
- We always do.
We do, we do.
Ramona and I are night and day,
and yet we're very aligned.
It's very weird.
Yeah, and I never met someone
that I bonded with so fast.
I wouldn't say that you
were like Ramona, but OK.
No we are.
But you see
some things that are like
- uncannily similar, don't you?
- Well, like your body types.
No, beyond
that superficial though.
- Your shoe size.
- No, meeting of the mind.
You're not that
mind depth as we are.
Because I'm not mind depth?
What does that mean?
What does that even mean?
What's mind depth.
Ramona! Flag on the play!
Flag on the play!
Abort! Abort!
I don't
know what mind depth is.
We have this
brain thing going on.
It's very peculiar.
Yeah. It's surprising to me.
I want to be
mad at you, but I can't.
- Thank you for Black Sabbath.
- Thank you, Ramona.
Thank you
for coming and looking pretty.
And being a hot mess. Love you
anyway, though. Love you anyway.
Coming!
Kiki!
Hi!
Oh my god, my baby!
Hi.
I missed you.
No, you look so cute.
Is this a new jacket?
- I got it with Skylar.
- This is nice too.
You guys got all
dressed up for me, I see.
I quarantined
for two weeks, I'm all good.
I'm very excited to see Kiki.
- I'm going to my room.
- OK, you go to your room.
As much as I love Rob,
I've probably
never been
this happy to see him.
I want to make sure
that we're on the same page
- with the school stuff.
- Okay.
Like, all the schools
that we're looking at
are like, she'll
have a good experience,
you know, she'll have
a lot of opportunities.
She's have a whole different
experience than she did.
You know?
Isn't that exciting?
Real talk, like, $60,000.
You know.
I think, like,
the money is a bit crazy
for a kid to go to
high school at college prices.
Honestly, like, this is
why I work my ****ing ass off.
This is why we work
our ****ing ass off.
To give her opportunities.
And yes, some of this sh...
Is very elitist, and I'm not
completely comfortable with it,
but at the same time, we have
to separate that and think about
the education that
Kier is going to be getting.
The private
school application process,
when you hear and read things
about it being so competitive,
it's not an over-exaggeration.
If I did not hire someone
to help me with this process,
there's no way that
I could do this on my own.
She's a smart kid. I don't
really worry about her at all.
It's crazy. I don't know
how she ended up like this.
They want to
know what boards I'm on.
I'm not on
the board of anything.
There's no hospital wings
named after me.
I'm a little in over my head.
I'm exhausted.
Yeah, I'm tired too.
- I'm gonna get going.
- Okay.
Alright,
well, 'til the next time.
Do you mind if I just sit
here and not see you out?
- No.
- Are you gonna be,
- don't be offended.
- I'll be fine.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna say goodbye to Kier.
Goodbye, miss.
- Love you!
- Love you.
Make sure your mother behaves.
- Coming up...
- Ultimately, your DNA results
were enough
for me to then determine...
You're so ridiculous.
Hey, sis!
Girl, you know
Carey's gonna do her lap.
Come on in.
Thank you.
- How you doing?
- Good! Oh, hey, Carey!
She's so crazy.
Did you see Katie?
- No!
- Yeah, Grandma arrived.
Get out of here.
Like, I never seen an urn
in person.
- Me neither.
- She was a small lady
but she
filled this whole thing up.
Oh my goodness.
She'll be with me always.
- Wow. It's really nice.
- Only the best for Katie.
Today feels like a combination
of the first day of school,
Christmas, and the SATs.
Cheers!
I'm a bundle of nerves today
with Linda
coming to give me her news.
You said a gene... what?
So, yes.
Her name is Linda, she came
to the house a few weeks ago.
If I could find out
who my father is, great.
If I could
find out who some...
Even half-siblings are,
great.
- Yeah.
- Just anything that gives me
a broader sense of who I am.
So what do you think
she's gonna come back and say?
I don't think she's gonna be,
"Eboni, I know your dad."
I think that's like a big ask.
You know?
I'm excited,
but I'm nervous because
depending on what she tells me,
here's yet another thing
I now will need to process.
Okay, that's the door.
You gonna
answer the door, Carey?
Child, this year
has been, like, the most.
Hi!
It's good to see you.
- How are you, my dear?
- My goodness.
Starting the year planning a wedding,
and planning a marriage,
ending my engagement,
getting sick,
thank god
recovering from COVID.
And now here
comes Linda with more good news.
I just can't wait.
Alright, so you had tested
at Ancestry DNA,
and ultimately, your DNA
results were enough for me
to then determine
that there are three candidates
for your father.
They're all brothers.
So, it's from
the same family line.
So, wait. One of
these three men is my dad?
- Is that what you're telling me?
- I am almost certain of it.
What?! Wait, wait.
She's like,
"Don't graze over that."
Wait, I need to just -
give me a second.
Process, yeah.
This is crazy.
It's exciting, yeah.
- And these men are alive.
- Yes, they are.
Holy sh...
- I know.
- I have a dad.
Yes, you do!
Oh my god. No, this is nuts,
y'all. This is so crazy.
So, the man who I believe to
be, out of the three brothers...
Oh, so you have one that
you think is...
I do, just based on his age.
He's born in 1957.
Your mother's born in 1960.
- OK.
- That's very close.
Yeah, the other
brother is born in 1951.
- OK.
- And then the other brother,
- he's born in 1939. So...
- Oh, it's probably not him.,
No. We would've been...
If she's anything
like me, it might be.
- That's true.
- That's a good 20 years older.
Yeah, see, in ,
he would've been 44,
so that's not out
of the realm of possibilities.
- Definitely not.
- And the one who I believe
is your father, he is married
and he has two daughters.
Oh, God!
This is just a lot.
Yeah, no. It is.
I don't even think
I was prepared for this.
I told Natalie before you came,
I was like, "Maybe some cousins,
maybe at best,
like an aunt or uncle."
The youngest daughter bears a
very strong resemblance to you.
As does your dad.
Who I believe is your father.
I think I hadn't
allowed myself to, um...
entertain the possibility that
I had a dad who was still alive.
And wow.
Thank you.
I'm so so happy
that I can help.
Oh god.
This is a lot.
And it's all
extremely wonderful.
This is literally the best case
scenario that could've happened.
She found him. He's alive.
Amazing. And a half-sister!
I'll show you his picture.
Yeah.
I do see the resemblance.
He's cute.
He's an attractive man.
He even has that roundness
to his face, like I do.
You know, those cheeks.
This is crazy! I'm sorry.
But I wanna
sit with it for a beat
before I start
opening up a million new boxes.
I wanna just be really
happy that I have a dad.
And just kind
of bask in that truth
for the first time
in my entire life.
It's beautiful,
and like the fact that
this man who is my
dad is alive
and after the new year
I get to do the exciting work
- of potentially...
- That's what I was telling her.
2021 will be a year of renewal.
Amen.
Thank you, sis. Yay!
Next time on The Real Housewives
of New York City.
In high school if I hadn't
gotten mixed up with clubs,
I could've been a star athlete,
I could've gone to a probably...
That's what happens when you get
involved with drugs and alcohol.
- Mom.
- Mm. These are good.
Sonjarita! How are you, honey?
You look so pretty.
We did a test last night for
COVID, and...
She's so fine
that she was totally wasted
yesterday when I spoke
to her on the phone.
- Are you serious?
- Good to see you? Bye!
Oh my god, I speak
so much sh... about Luann
- and I love her so much.
- I can ****ing hear you!
You ready to
play pin the tail on...
Harry!
Oh sh...!
Oh my god.
I feel this is disrespectful
to Harry, he's my friend.
He's not your friend,
he's my ex-boyfriend
who cheated on me
and ****ed all my friends!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/8qbws
Help other users to choose the best subtitles