Previously on Homeland...
I hereby resign
the presidency
of the United States.
Vice President Warner will be
sworn in as president.
You're here
to leverage G'ulom,
but you're asking
about Russians.
Jesus, Mike, not you, too.
What the hell'd they tell you?
That you tanked
the polygraph.
Jalal..."We don't want
to stop the war.
We're winning."
That's his son, Haqqani.
"But we never do."
That's the head of the Taliban
saying, "Enough of war."
Haqqani is tired
of the fight, aba.
Direct talks with Berenson
could lead to a breakthrough
Well, any breakthrough
must be controlled by us
and not the United States.
Or prevent it from happening
in the first place.
Pakistani intelligence
may know we're here.
They're gonna
hit the convoy.
Thank God, you're alive.
Get back, get back!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
The World Trade Center,
Tower Number One
is on fire!
I missed something
once before. I won't...
I can't let that happen again!
An American prisoner
of war has been turned.
You're a disgrace
to your nation,
Sgt. Nicholas Brody.
You're a traitor
and a terrorist,
and now it's time
to pay for that.
Are you accusing me
of something?
You really do not remember?
Remember what?
We may be dealing with
a compromised officer here.
You had a relationship
complicated enough
to lie about.
Yeah, it's complicated.
I lost seven months
of my life.
To my Russian handler?
Is our strategy working?
And you will become
the focus of an investigation
that will define
the rest of your life.
That not every problem
in the Middle East
deserves a military solution.
Because this whole country
went stupid crazy after 9/11.
Carrie, you're not yourself.
I'm still putting
the pieces together.
Please, God,
tell me you have it.
Is there no fucking line?
I believe you.
No one else will.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
I thought you
were going to thank me.
For what?
Handing you Samira Noori.
That was you?
Come on, don't play dumb.
Why are you
looking at me like that?
- Stay.
- I can't.
- Please don't leave me.
- I have to go.
Stay.
Don't go.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No! No!
You can't leave me here!
Don't go!
No, don't!
- Mr. Vice President.
- David.
Just catching up
on this Berenson mess.
Anything new?
We'll find out
when the president
finishes talking
to General Ryan.
What a clusterfuck.
Yeah, you leave Washington for
36 hours, look what happens.
You were just
in Columbus, right?
Watch OSU play Michigan...
The Game.
Frank Gillette and I
haven't missed one
since we graduated.
We may not have gone
to Princeton,
but we know how to have
a good time.
Thank you all
for getting here
on such short notice
at such a late hour.
General Ryan
has been in contact
with the Taliban delegation
in Doha,
and they've confirmed
that Saul Berenson
is their prisoner.
Despite our intel
implicating the I. S. I.,
Haqqani is convinced we were
behind the attempt on his life,
and he's threatening
to kill Saul
at the first sign of a rescue.
Well, I realize, uh,
I was out of town
when all this was decided,
but what in the hell
was the National Security
Advisor thinking?
He was trying to facilitate
a breakthrough
in the negotiations.
How many red lights
we gonna let this guy run?
He's a Keane holdover anyway.
I say fire his ass.
Well, I don't know, Ben.
Shouldn't we try
to get him back first?
HQ wants to keep
a low profile.
Nothing that
will draw attention.
Uh-huh.
Come in.
Glad you're not leaving
without saying good-bye.
I'm not leaving.
Not yet anyway.
I'm fairly certain I signed
a travel memo.
You're due back in Germany
this evening.
Hey, Alan, give us a minute,
will you?
Sure.
Yevgeny Gromov...
is here
in Kabul.
Aren't you at all curious
what he's up to?
Whatever it is,
we can't touch him.
Orders from on high...
no contact,
no officer access,
not even at arm's length.
I'm aware.
He contacted me.
Last night at the club,
he put himself in front of me,
said he was the one who gave us
the lead on Samira Noori.
Any idea why he would
do something like that?
It's hard to say for sure,
but I think we're obligated
to find out, don't you?
You realize we're gonna
need consent from headquarters
to follow up.
Not necessarily.
Not if we wait for him
to reach out again.
Are you so sure he will?
He already has,
twice in secret.
Clearly there's
something on his mind.
Since when is this
even a debate?
Russian intelligence
is knocking on our door.
It's more complicated
than that, and you know it.
Yeah, it's complicated!
I lost seven months of my life!
You look me in the eye
and tell me
I don't get a shot
at some operational payback.
I guess I could fail to report
the contact last night
and call the next one, if it
happens, a chance encounter.
That's a good plan.
You're finally getting
the hang of this job.
48 hours.
If he's not in touch by then,
you're on your way
back to Germany.
Fair enough.
It wasn't us.
If it was, you'd be dead.
Arrogant as ever.
I was on the street
trying to save you.
Your men saw me.
My men are dead.
They were murdered
by the I.S.I.
Who couldn't have known
about our meeting
because I did not tell them.
Well, someone did.
Someone you confided in.
Someone you trust.
You have a traitor
in your camp.
- Enough.
- You read my letter.
I took as big a risk
coming here as you did.
Enough!
Your death would have
served me no purpose.
The opposite.
Don't worry.
Any doubts
about your leadership
will be resolved
at the Shura.
What makes you so sure?
They remember
what your father forgot.
That without me,
there is no Taliban.
Hello.
Jalala.
Speak English
so we are not understood.
Amadullah said there was an
assassin sent by the Americans.
He told me you were dead.
My men went ahead
as a precaution.
Four are murdered.
Thank God you're alive.
The danger isn't over.
You must come at once.
Where are you now?
With our cousins,
north of Peshawar.
I'll be there
as soon as I can.
He wants me by his side.
Then you must go to him.
What if he thinks it was me?
You have to convince him
otherwise.
He'll figure it out.
Not if you keep
your wits about you.
You and I are
the only ones who know.
And what
about this meeting...
the one we're having
right now?
He'll find out
about that for sure.
Then tell him the truth.
Tell him I came
to talk to you
about consolidating your power
in the wake of his death.
Your time will come, Jalal.
Until then, you need
to be your father's son.
Change keywords.
National Security Advisor.
Hostage.
Ransom.
Search.
- Hey.
- I got him.
Don't fight it!
Just let it happen!
Let it happen!
- Chill the fuck out!
- Get the fuck off of me!
- The shirt!
- I got it, go, go!
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
You fucking freaks!
- Is that all you got?
- Hey, Max, chill out!
Chill, chill.
He's going up to the firebase.
He just needed
a hardcore hit.
Sorry, man, I had to.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I'm not your fucking Buddha!
Don't say that.
You're gonna jinx it.
Oh, yeah?
I just got my boss
taken prisoner.
How fucking lucky is that?
I'm Carrie Mathison.
I was told something
was dropped off for me.
Of course, ma'am.
Contact was made
the same way as before...
kid on a bike
passes the message
to one of the contractors
guarding the perimeter.
- Just an address?
- And a time.
Zero six thirty
tomorrow morning.
Fifty-two hundred
Asmayi Road.
That's the Abdul Kahn Mosque.
Just across the street
from the Ministry of Finance.
The handwriting's a match.
There's no reason to believe
this is anybody but him.
It's an odd choice
for a rendezvous, though.
Not if you're considering
coming over to our side.
Is that what you think?
That Yevgeny Gromov
is recruitable?
I'm beginning to.
I mean, first, the unsolicited
help with G'ulom.
Now this.
Huh.
It's Kabul, Carrie.
You're gonna need backup
regardless.
What do you think,
three teams on foot?
Minimum, plus a rotation
of vehicles.
You might as well put me back
on the plane to Germany, then.
Come on, Carrie,
you know I can't let you
hunt alone on this one.
He'll be watching.
He'll make our people
in two seconds,
and if he's
the least bit skittish,
the chance will be lost.
Hey, it's your station, Mike.
It's your call.
You know what I would do.
If we think she was
compromised in Russia...
Why would we give her
the go-ahead
to meet with a Russian?
I think I just answered
my own question.
To get her to incriminate
herself, right?
Right, which is how come I was
pushing so hard for backup.
We need eyes and ears
on her the whole time.
- What about a bug?
- What about it?
Any chance you could
slip one into her purse?
- Carrie's purse?
- Yeah.
Uh, highly unlikely.
Not buying
the friendship routine, huh?
No, she is, we're just not
braiding each other's hair yet.
Parabolic it is, then.
Tell her one team in a van
parked where no one can see.
- Hello?
- Tasneem.
- Who's this?
- It's Jalal.
- What the hell are you doing?
- We have a problem.
You're on an open line.
I told you never to call me
on an open line.
Tasneem?
Mind if I join?
Not at all.
You ever sleep?
Is it that obvious?
You're never in your room.
I'm right next door.
Walls are like paper.
So, uh, what happens tomorrow?
Your guess is as good as mine.
Let's say Yevgeny
asks to defect.
What's the procedure?
That he won't do.
Why not?
I thought you said...
I said he was a candidate
for recruitment, not defection.
The last thing a field guy
like Yevgeny wants
is a new identity
and a condo in Scottsdale.
You know him better
than anybody, I guess.
Is that what Mike told you?
No, I just assumed.
Don't assume.
What has he told you?
Not much.
Come on.
Your long stay in Russia
raised some flags.
Are you spying on me, Jenna?
Mike send you up here
to take my temperature?
No.
I've met Yevgeny Gromov
exactly five times in my life.
Two of those times have
happened right here in Kabul
over the past few days.
For all I know...
he's staging this whole event
just to throw more shade on me
and do what he does best...
spread rumor and innuendo,
divide us against ourselves.
Why even agree
to meet with him, then?
'Cause I could be wrong.
He could just as easily
be the genuine article.
How you gonna know
which it is?
That's the thing...
you never really do.
Not 100%, anyway.
You're free to go.
No one will stop you.
Wait!
Wait.
What's happened?
What is this place?
Badonbaay.
It means
"where the clouds end."
My father used
to bring me here.
There, that's where I grew up,
at the end of the valley.
Afghanistan.
My unlucky country.
It was Jalal who tried
to have me killed.
He's the youngest
of my four sons,
the only one
who's still alive.
Yes, I know.
I was hoping for something
more for him
than war and death.
It's not too late.
Anybody else
would be dead already.
Surely you can make
an exception
for your own child.
Not without compromising
my command.
No, the only other option
is to step down.
Don't do that.
Maybe it's time.
Some have said as much.
There are many
who would take my place.
None who have the power
or influence
to end the war.
You overstate my standing.
Is that why they call you
"the Arrow of God"?
I'm...
just a man.
Then you are a man
like Faisal was to the Saudis,
Kemal to the Turks.
Where the fuck is he?
Still no sign.
He's 15 minutes late.
Any chance he made you?
We're pretty hidden up here.
Any chance she made you
and warned him?
I don't see how.
We've been on her since
she got out of the taxi.
Hasn't even looked up
in our direction.
Stand by.
Standing by.
Listen to me.
Another Islamic Emirate
of Afghanistan
will be never won
on the battlefield.
You don't know that.
How can you say that?
The West won't allow it,
no matter what the I.S.I.
is telling you.
Then we will outlast them,
Father.
We will outlast them.
No.
We are just strong enough
never to lose
and just weak enough
never to win.
So you've decided.
What choice do I have
but to accept your decision?
You could do it
as a good soldier...
and a good son.
At the end of a rope?
With a gun to my head?
What do you say now, Jalala?
Will you join me
on this new path?
I will try...
Father...
for you.
Come.
We have much to discuss.
Another ten minutes,
and I'm calling it.
Copy that.
Well?
I don't buy it.
Why make the whole thing up?
Because she didn't want
to go back to Germany.
Look at her.
She's just as bummed
he didn't show as we are.
It's an act.
She must know
we're watching her,
or at least suspect.
That doesn't make her
a liar.
She reported the contact,
didn't she?
What the hell?
Mike, look.
Right on cue.
You knew?
The minute I read
the time and place.
Your people,
do they know?
They do now.
Are you getting this?
I can't make out
a word they're saying.
Negative, problem is we're
aimed right at a wall of sound.
- Fix it.
- We're trying.
Where are we going?
We'll talk by the fountain.
I want to make double sure
they can't hear us.
What's so amusing?
Just admiring the tradecraft.
What do you want?
Come on, admit it... you're
a little pleased to see me.
You know, "pleased" isn't the
first word that comes to mind.
Okay, look, I'm sorry.
Apology is in order.
I didn't mean to leave
your life like that.
Well, it was crowded.
I assumed you didn't want
to be seen.
No, not... not at the bar.
In Moscow.
At the asylum.
I'm sorry I left you alone
in that place.
So... so what was
Samira Noori, then... penance?
Yeah, sort of.
And Roshan Shadman?
Who's that?
Tied to a truck
and dragged through the streets
of Ghazni to his death?
Sorry, I don't know
who that is.
Tell that to his widow,
to his 12-year-old child.
I can see you're angry, but
I had nothing to do with that.
Well, forgive me,
but you're full of shit.
Don't think I don't know
what you're really doing.
You're wrong.
I really was trying to just...
just pick up
where we left off.
Right, whatever that means.
You really do not remember?
Remember what?
I saved your life...
for one thing.
You were trying
to hang yourself
with a rope
made from your bedsheets.
I hadn't seen you in months,
I got there, and by pure luck...
If I was there a minute later,
just a minute later,
you would have been gone.
And after that,
I managed to get you
back on your meds
for a couple weeks.
There was a birch forest
right near the hospital.
You really liked
walking there.
It's true.
Turns out we had
a lot to talk about.
Really?
Like what?
Like your relationship
with Nicholas Brody.
Tell me something you didn't
just read in my file.
You had a daughter with him.
Franny.
You slipped her head underwater
in the bath.
There was a moment
when you actually considered
drowning your own child.
Shh.
And now they aren't
saying a word.
Fuck.
I have to go.
How much of what they did say
are we gonna be able
to recover?
I'm not sure.
I'll get the techs
working on it
once we're back
at the station.
Make it a first priority.
- David.
- Mr. President.
We may have caught a break.
Haqqani released Saul
a little over an hour ago.
What happened?
It turns out Haqqani's son
was an I.S.I. asset.
They promised him
keys to the kingdom.
If he killed Daddy?
Something like that.
Does this mean Daddy
might be willing
to negotiate after all?
Looks that way.
I need you to talk Saul
through some
of the stickier points
of the deal just in case.
He's got to know
where he can compromise,
where to hold the line.
He's expecting your call.
What is it, David?
Last night I asked
the vice president
about an unscheduled trip
to Columbus.
He said he was there
for a football game
with Frank Gillette.
So?
So he neglected to mention
that every other major donor
in the country
was also there.
It was a who's who
of heavy hitters.
He's fundraising for his side.
Not much we can do about that.
Or positioning himself.
Positioning himself?
Well, you're aware Ohio voters
approved a proposition
to move up the state's primary.
They're now number two in line
after the Iowa caucuses.
No vice president
has ever challenged
a sitting president, David.
No vice president's ever been
from the opposing party.
Not for 150 years, anyway.
Look, the country
was tearing itself apart.
You reached across the aisle
to bridge the divide,
but those fault lines run deep.
They're still active.
And Ben Hayes is in the perfect
position to exploit them.
Has he put a poll
in the field?
Not yet.
Well...
let me know when he does.
Everything we've talked about
so far falls apart
without a timeline
for Taliban disarmament.
We disarm when there are
no more foreign troops
in Afghanistan.
National Unity Government
will never accept
that order of events,
and neither will
the United States.
If you're serious
about a political settlement,
first you must agree
to a mechanism
for decommissioning
your weapons.
- What do I get in return?
- A lot.
Amnesty for your fighters,
guaranteed positions
in the new government,
and a clean break
from the Pakistan military,
who's held you hostage
all these years.
You also gain the power
of legitimacy.
No longer identified
as a terror organization,
you can start
to enjoy the comforts
of political privilege.
Your good friends
in Saudi Arabia
looking to fund the movement
can do so legally.
Your wealth and influence
will actually grow and expand.
Sometimes I'm thinking...
I just want to go home
while I still can.
That too.
Okay.
Okay?
I agree.
We have a deal, then?
You and I...
known each other
a long time.
I'm counting on you
to make sure
America lives up
at its end of the bargain.
It will.
Then, yes, we have a deal.
And you'll declare an immediate
country-wide cease fire
as we discussed?
Starting tomorrow morning.
What's wrong?
I'm worried I made a mistake
with Jalal.
By letting him go?
Hmm.
By not putting
his head in a bag
and sending it to his fighters
in the field as a warning.
Hey, what's this?
What's it look like?
You seeing this, Sarge?
Christ sakes,
leave the man alone.
You can't be serious, bro.
I'm on a chopper back
to Bagram in a couple hours.
No way.
What about the Pakistan border,
patrolling the airwaves?
It's all on automatic
collection now.
What about your boss?
He's still out there somewhere.
You can't... you can't just
give up on him.
- He's been released.
- When?
This morning.
That's fucked up.
Soto, relax.
You're gonna give
yourself a stroke.
- Get over it.
- You get over it.
Haven't you noticed?
Dude's been here a week.
Not a single IED, RPG, mortar,
rocket, sniper, nothing.
I'm not saying it ain't weird.
It's weirder than weird.
We shouldn't even
be talking about it.
Well, nobody's going
anywhere anyhow.
How's that?
We got some weather coming in.
What?
Yeah, it's gonna get nasty.
All air traffic in
the mountains is grounded.
Usually takes
a couple days to clear.
Oh.
Thank you, God.
Thank you.
- Come on.
- Where?
Berenson's been
waiting for you.
Saul's here?
In the SCIF
talking to the president.
Apparently there's
been a breakthrough
in the negotiations.
...our government
to the process.
Without that,
we wouldn't even be here.
Is that you, Ms. Mathison?
Um, it is, sir.
Glad you could join us.
And it's nice
to finally meet you.
Thank you, sir.
- Hello, Carrie.
- David.
We were just
discussing next steps.
To catch you up,
Haissam Haqqani has agreed
in principle to the terms
and the timelines
laid out
in the Doha Framework.
Not only that,
he's committed to a ceasefire.
That should buy us some time
to hash out
the outstanding issues.
One of which is to sell this
peace to the American people.
Well, I think the prospect
of ending our longest war
would enjoy broad support.
Well, not when it's twisted
into a partisan issue
made to look like we're
capitulating to terrorists.
Seeing as you were one of
the architects of the policy,
we thought you might
have some ideas.
Well, I can tell you
what Elizabeth Keane
was planning to do.
Get out in front
of the debate.
Come here to Afghanistan
and make the case
directly to the men and women
who put their lives
on the line every day.
You're talking about
taking a secret trip,
making a surprise announcement?
Followed by
a joint press conference
with President Daoud
at the Arg Palace.
Hmm.
I'm just saying,
win over the military,
and you're halfway there.
It also has
the benefit of good optics.
Flying into a war zone,
rallying the troops,
and not looking anything
remotely like surrender.
Sounds like you've made
this argument before.
I have, sir.
Well, I appreciate
the bluntness.
Now, if you don't mind,
I'd like a few minutes alone
with my
National Security Advisor.
Yes, sir.
Saul, Carrie...
Thank you, David.
Talk to me, Saul.
Well, sir, the best part
you've already heard.
Hey, slow down.
What's the hurry?
I want to write up
the contact with Yevgeny
while it's still fresh.
Where'd you disappear to?
I'm sorry?
If you're so eager
to write up the contact,
where'd you go afterwards?
You were off the grid
for more than 90 minutes.
I was walking.
Walking?
It wasn't so easy
seeing him again,
if you must know.
I went up to the university
to clear my head.
You said he was recruitable.
Is he?
Just give me an hour,
and you'll have the entire
conversation verbatim.
It's a simple question, Carrie.
Yes or no?
He's feeling
underappreciated, okay?
He and Mirov were demoted
for letting us
get Simone Martin
out of Moscow.
We made them look
pretty damn silly.
He said that?
Not in so many words,
but he did call Afghanistan
the penalty box.
Well, that doesn't sound
unpromising.
Provided it's not all
some grand deception.
- Where'd you leave it?
- In his court.
Either way, I don't think
I should be getting
on a plane anytime soon.
How about we talk
after I read the report?
Sure.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org