Previously on Homeland...
- Maggie around?
- Uh, no.
Don't call her. She's--
she's talking to a lawyer.
- About?
- Franny.
You can't provide her with a
stable home, so we are going to.
- Carrie.
- Stay the fuck away from my kid.
Dante's missing.
I can't go, then.
This can put the whole
operation at risk.
Then I must plan
to never see you again.
Simone. Simone.
Mr. Allen is
in federal custody, Senator,
charged with violations
of the Espionage Act.
And he's talking.
So far, he's confirmed
a devastating account
of Russian interference
in our democratic process,
including feeding you
and your committee
a steady diet
of manipulated information.
You've been played, Sam.
- Sorry, can you help me?
- Sure.
I need to pull my daughter out
a little early today.
- Hey, sweetheart. You ready?
- Yeah.
- Hey, Dante?
Can I call you back
in, like, five minutes?
Yevgeny's here.
Lock down the hospital.
Dante! Fuck.
Hey, you need to go
back to class.
I love you, baby.
I'll see you after school.
- No, Mommy. No, Mommy. No.
- No, I gotta go. I gotta go.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hey!
What did you do?
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
He saved our lives.
Yeah.
What was his name?
Carrie, you're not yourself.
But you don't have
my condition.
I'm dealing with it.
I-I've been dealing with it
since I was 22.
She said no one at work
could know. She's bipolar.
The mood of the country,
it's not great.
Civil... war.
Madam President, please!
You have to put a stop to this!
It's only getting worse.
Is there no fucking line?
Ridiculous lies and accusations.
The White House
is in crisis mode.
I'm talking
about information warfare.
Our country
is under attack.
The time to rise up is now!
I swore an oath
to protect it.
Just think of me
as a light on the heavens,
a beacon, steering you clear
of the wrongs.
You're doing great. Doc says
this is the last one, okay?
You ready, Carrie?
We're gonna start prepping
for your third
and final treatment.
Same procedure as before.
Let's get started.
Today, we've got
a bilateral application
with dexmedetomidine infusion
for her lithium at 2cc's
and 5 cc's of Succinylcholine.
So far, the patient's responded
well to the procedure,
other than slight memory loss
immediately
following the application.
Just like before, okay?
Counting backwards from 100.
100, 99,
98...
97...
96...
Ready for oxygen.
Giving Succinylcholine now.
Vitals are normal.
Current is good.
EEG is good.
Everyone clear.
Apply stimulus.
Seizure induced.
_
- Yeah, there you go.
- Mm-hmm.
Something wrong, sir?
Uh, no, it's fine.
Tie's too red.
Maybe the wrong kind
of red.
Sir, he's been downstairs
for half an hour.
He's kept me waiting longer
than that more than once.
They both have.
He can wait.
- Sorry to keep you.
- Mr. Vice President.
Want some coffee?
Something stronger?
It's early,
but Kyle can get you
whatever you like.
I'm fine. Thank you.
Ah. Please, sit.
Am I mistaken, or is this
your first visit here?
- Um, my first time.
- Ah.
It was built
for the superintendent
of the Naval Observatory
back in 1893...
until the Chief
of Naval Operations
decided he liked it so much,
he took it for himself.
That rank has
its prerogatives.
I'm usually the one
who's summoned.
Something important
must be happening.
Last night,
the Attorney General
called the President
about a document Senator Paley
wanted the AG to sign.
What kind of document?
Invoking the 25th Amendment.
Declaring the President
unfit for office.
The Senator thinks enlisting
the President's Cabinet
will be easier than
getting Congress to impeach.
He claims four members
have signed on already.
Four short of
the majority required.
Who are the four?
Well, I was hoping
you could tell me.
I wouldn't have asked
if I knew.
So you, yourself,
haven't been approached.
No. In fact, I was under
the assumption
that Paley had eased off
once he saw the Russia file.
He had. Dante Allen's death
put him back on the warpath.
And how worried are we?
Depends.
On what?
You, sir.
Because Congress can't
ratify the 25th Amendment
- without my signature.
- Correct.
Even if he's got
a majority of the Cabinet,
Paley can't get this done
without you.
Must gall her,
that the survival
of her Presidency
could come down to me.
The President trusts
your judgment.
Trusts my judgment?
That's a very generous
interpretation
of our relationship.
You're being a little
sensitive, aren't you?
Maybe.
Still, I can't remember
one time she demonstrated
any real interest in my opinion
or solicited my advice.
But I took an oath
to defend this country
against all enemies,
foreign and domestic.
And I won't let
the President's indifference
interfere with that.
So...
you tell her she's got
nothing to worry about,
at least not from me.
Thank you, sir.
- She'll appreciate it.
- Mm-hmm.
Saul, quickly.
Thanks for coming.
I couldn't think of another
excuse to get out of the house.
He thinks I've been subbing
all this time
for another professor
out with the flu. Please, sit.
So I couldn't get those damn
flight logs out of my head.
- What about 'em?
- Two private aircraft booked
out of the same private airfield
within 24 hours of each other?
Tail numbers
on both planes blocked
by an identical
onboard system.
Let's just say the timing
of Dante's murder
puts Yevgeny
on the second flight.
Question is, who's on
the first flight?
Could be anybody
in his network.
Or Simone.
Simone's at the bottom
of a lake somewhere.
What if she isn't?
If Yevgeny was gonna
kill her,
why not do it on the spot
like he did with Dante?
No, Saul. He couldn't
leave her behind.
It's a love story.
It's always a love story
with you.
11 years ago, they were
both living in Paris.
She, a doctoral candidate
at the Sorbonne.
He, running a small group
of Western residencies
- for the SVR.
- Still, you can't...
you can't be sure the young spy
met the young graduate student.
Actually, I can.
Simone's thesis advisor
at the time
has a vivid memory
of her boyfriend--
tall, dark, and Russian.
- You good?
- I'm good.
- Your lawyer's here.
- Oh, thanks.
Morning.
Hey, Rhonda.
You said there was news.
There is.
There's an offer
on the table.
Tell me.
Your sister's agreed to
a visitation schedule.
Every third weekend
at first,
moving to alternating weekends
after a probationary period.
Okay. Uh...
This is a giant step forward,
Carrie.
It means that
you're guaranteed
to see your daughter
every month.
That wasn't the case
yesterday.
This is assuming
Maggie and Bill win
- the custody hearing tomorrow.
- No.
This is in lieu of the hearing.
I-I don't understand.
It's an agreement
between parties
in exchange for signing over
sole physical custody.
Me signing over custody
to them.
Yes.
And no hearing?
I don't even get a chance
to argue my side
in front of a judge?
Carrie, I think your sister
wants to avoid
a protracted legal battle,
which will be hard
on everyone.
Right now,
that gives you leverage.
After the hearing,
not so much.
If they want Franny, I'm not
just gonna hand her over.
They're gonna have to
take her from me.
I thought
you understood that.
As long as you understand,
if the court awards Maggie
and Bill sole custody tomorrow,
even temporarily,
you stand to lose
any and all access
to your daughter.
Is that what you think's
gonna happen?
I really don't know.
In your professional
opinion, then.
Look, I've done this
long enough
to tell you that there are
no certain outcomes.
But you said courts
bend over backwards
to keep children
with their parents.
Yes. They do.
Come on, Rhonda. Quit hedging.
Tell me what you think.
I think you should seriously
consider the merits
of the visitation offer.
As most of you know,
my ex-husband was
an anthropologist.
About politics, he used to say,
mankind was not descended
from peaceful arboreal apes,
but from a cruder, earthbound
type who hunted in packs
and crushed the skulls
of his prey with gloves.
Ladies and gentlemen...
we are under attack,
as radical as it sounds.
Senator Paley must now be
considered a witting participant
in a massive
Russian influence operation,
designed to paralyze
our democracy
and to diminish our role
on the world stage.
If you don't believe it,
and I gather that
some of you don't,
ask yourself this--
What of the people's business
have we, any of us,
managed to get done
in the first 100 days?
All our high hopes
in pieces on the ground.
If there was ever a moment
to stand together,
it is now.
So...
the next time the good Senator
comes calling
with his schemes
of invoking the 25th...
and he will come calling,
know two things.
One, that there is no daylight
between me
and the Vice President
on this matter.
None.
And two...
feel free to
beat his head in with a club.
- Okay. Are we ready?
- Yes, Madam President.
- Let's get into character, then.
- Madam President...
- Thank you.
You'll come
through this, Madam President.
With your help, I will.
Good morning.
Doesn't sound
like Rhonda's exactly...
brimming with confidence.
Well, she's a lawyer. She wants
to prepare me for the worst.
And?
Are you? Prepared?
I don't think you are,
Carrie.
You're in a knife fight
without a knife.
- Well, what do you suggest?
- I don't know.
Maybe a little
opposition research?
- On my sister?
- Or her husband?
I'm sensing some moral confusion
here. Should I shut up?
No, not at all. I-I was just
wondering what kind of dirt
you could actually dig up
on those two.
Well, you tell me.
What,
Supermom and Saint Bill?
It's not exactly
a laundry list.
Come on, Carrie.
Everybody has something.
- Well...
- What?
She was my unofficial doctor
for years,
treated me under an alias,
ran my blood tests,
wrote my lithium prescriptions.
To avoid you getting
flagged by the agency?
Yep.
Well...
That's her medical license
right there.
Good to go.
Moscow's on
the secure uplink, sir.
- Talk to me.
- Good morning, Saul.
This is crap, Jim.
It's been over a week.
It's fuckin' amateur hour.
Well, to be fair,
finding Yevgeny
was only made
a priority yesterday.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say I'm being slow-rolled.
Am I being
slow-rolled, Jim?
The long answer is
the President hasn't
exactly banked
a whole lot
of good will with HQ.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, after what she said
during the campaign,
nobody on the seventh floor
is much in the mood
to throw her a lifeline.
Fuck them.
You don't seem happy, Saul.
Is the President
really that vulnerable?
Yeah, she is.
If we don't produce
some hard evidence
that screams Russia,
and soon,
I don't see her making it
to the end of the year,
much less
the end of her term.
Tell me what to do.
Start by sending a team
to Sergiyev Posad.
Why there?
I hear it's a beautiful town.
Plus, Yevgeny goes on and on
about it
in an unpublished novel
he wrote at university.
Describes
an idyllic summer there
at a baronial dacha
on the river.
Shouldn't be hard to find,
if it exists.
In the novel, a rich uncle
on his mother's side
- owns the place.
- I'll have people there
- first thing in the morning.
- Good.
Jim, while you're there,
keep an eye out
for Simone Martin, too.
I will.
Good.
_
- Can I come in?
- Of course.
Saul, you didn't have to.
They're beautiful.
Where do you want them?
I was here on Monday.
You were sleeping.
I didn't want
to disturb you.
Yeah, Anson told me.
How are you?
Better. I'm much better.
I'm starting a whole new
drug protocol.
Is it true you also did another course of
electroconvulsive therapy?
I did. I know they scare
the hell out of you,
those treatments, but for me,
they're a miracle, really.
What happened, Carrie?
Can you tell me?
Um, wh-what happened is...
what always happens
when I don't listen
to the people around me,
when I think I can keep all
the plates spinning by myself.
I swear, I should've
seen it coming.
That makes two of us.
No. In no way is this
your responsibility.
I feel responsible.
Don't. It was a complete
psychotic break.
They had to hit me with
a massive dose of Haldol
and take me away
in four-point restraints.
Waking fucking nightmare.
And now I'm in the middle
of this ugly, ugly
custody battle with Maggie.
Hearing's tomorrow, huh?
- Yeah.
- What can I do?
Nothing.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
Come on, Saul.
I-I appreciate the visit, but...
why are you really here?
Yevgeny slipped the net.
Best guess is he made it
back to Russia.
- Fuck.
- Yeah.
There's also some institutional
resistance on our side
to finding him,
if you can believe that.
Oh, I believe it.
So what do you need?
Next best thing to you,
Carrie-- people I can trust.
- I need your team.
- To do what? Repatriot him?
Him or Simone Martin.
Turns out she might
be alive after all.
Of the two of them,
she'd be the easier
to exfiltrate.
What's the timeframe?
Soon as we can locate
one or the other,
which we're hoping happens
in the very near future.
I'll reach out
right away, then.
The boys will jump
at the chance.
Who leads the team,
Anson or Bennet?
That's a tough call.
I...
Bennet's steady, but Anson
can think outside the box.
Either one run an operation
in Eastern Europe before?
Not that I know of.
Really should be you,
Carrie.
I can't.
I'm talking about
in a purely supervisory role.
Really, I-I can't.
I'm sorry.
You'd be in the field
three days. Week at the most.
That's not about days
or weeks, Saul.
This is about
the rest of my life.
Tomorrow, I walk
into a courtroom
to fight for my daughter.
If I'm ever gonna
convince anybody
I deserve a second chance,
first I have to convince myself.
That means putting the job
behind me once and for all.
You tried that before.
Didn't work.
It will this time.
- James.
- Good to see you.
- Mr. Vice President.
- Sir.
You asked me to review
the defense budget
over a working dinner.
Last I checked,
the Senator wasn't on
the Appropriations committee.
You're wasting your time, Sam.
Whatever differences I may have
with the President are overstated.
Look, none of us
wants to be here,
but it's on all of us to hold
that woman accountable.
You know, your indignation
might be more convincing
if it weren't
quite so covered in crap.
Crap? You mean like, uh,
this, uh,
Russian bogeyman
she keeps talking about?
Have you seen any evidence?
Any actual evidence?
I've seen the same
intelligence you have.
Right, those photographs
and timeline.
It all looks real enough,
I'll give 'em that.
I almost bought it myself until
that FBI agent turned up dead.
Murdered
by Russian operatives.
Dante Allen was
in federal custody,
just like General McClendon,
just like Simone Martin,
Fool me once, shame on you.
But... three times?
The President is covering up
one crime with another.
A majority of the Cabinet
concurs.
What are you talking about?
Eight Secretaries are ready
to sign a document, if you are.
We gave her the chance
to step down,
and to do so with dignity,
but she refused.
So that leaves you,
Mr. Vice President.
Like it or not,
it's up to you to end
this national nightmare.
Please.
At least hear us out.
It's the most important decision
you'll ever make.
Okay, what are
the classification parameters
so I can sign off on them?
No, consider it a go order
until you hear otherwise.
And good luck.
Saul Berenson.
He's working a lead with
our station chief in Moscow.
- Sounds promising.
- We'll see.
So far, so good today.
Nothing to worry about,
but I thought you should know--
Senator Paley just reached out
to the Vice President.
No surprise there.
Well, only that
it's taken this long.
Warner had
a dinner scheduled
with Secretary Mullen
in Georgetown.
Paley ambushed him there.
So... Mullen was in on it.
Looks that way.
He was sitting next to me
in the Cabinet Room,
looked me right in the eye.
Besides Mullen, who else
might be wavering?
Warner find out?
I actually haven't
spoken to him yet.
So how do you know
this dinner happened?
Is happening, right now.
There's a bartender
at the restaurant
I keep on retainer.
How long have they been
in there?
Over an hour.
What the hell are they
talking about?
Get me the Vice President,
please.
I wouldn't read too much
into this.
I can't afford not to.
Voicemail.
Ralph?
I know where you are,
and I know who you're with.
Please call me back
when you get this.
Elizabeth, you talked to him
this morning.
Trust me, he's solid.
I talked to Mullen, too,
and he lied to my face.
I'll be here late tonight.
Let me know
when he calls back.
Hello?
It's not here.
- What?
- The file.
There's no one by the name
of Jessica Field.
F-I-E-L-D.
Nope. Nothing.
You sure?
Look, I'm looking at the F's now--
Feddermen, Feld, Fuchs.
- Maybe she shredded it?
- Not Maggie.
- She keeps everything.
- Fraudulent prescriptions?
It wasn't
just prescriptions.
She monitored my dosages,
my blood work.
It was an important
medical record.
She wouldn't have
just tossed it.
Oh, wait.
What?
Fuck.
It must be at home. She has
an office there, too.
- Where?
- Above the garage.
So what do you want me
to do?
Is there an alarm?
Yeah.
Do you know the code?
So are you gonna
give it to me or what?
Thank you.
Olivia.
- Didn't see you on the schedule.
- I asked her here myself.
What's going on?
Madam President, if you'd like
a minute alone with David--
What I need is for
my White House counsel
to deliver these before
the Vice President
invokes the 25th.
Before he does what?
- What exactly did he tell you?
- Nothing.
He didn't return my calls
last night or this morning.
His office is saying
he is unreachable.
Well, if-- if he's
not returning your calls,
- there must be a reason.
- Yeah, there is.
He's thrown down
with Paley and Mullen.
- You don't know that.
- Why do you doubt it?
The plan is to deprive him of
the signatures Congress needs
- to open debate.
- Deprive him? How?
Let me see that.
You're firing your Cabinet.
Only those who caved.
Besides Mullen, you have
no idea who that is.
Well, I can
damn well guess.
The ones I didn't
hand-pick.
The ones
whose portfolios
intersect with
National Security.
Is this even legal?
It's unprecedented,
but the law's clear.
The President can dismiss
Cabinet members at any time
- for any reason.
- You do realize
that you are playing
right into their hands.
You don't think
I know that?
Warner is
a human weather vane,
- but Paley and Mullen...
- No, no, no, no, not them!
- ...are smart as--
- The Russians!
You are giving them
the very Constitutional crisis
they've been trying
to instigate for months.
What choice do I have?
Wait any longer,
and I could be removed
from office this afternoon!
Temporarily. Even if Warner does
deliver those signatures,
it's just the first round.
He still needs Congress
to declare you unfit,
and by a two-thirds vote
in each house.
If I let them march me
out of here today,
they are never
letting me back in.
The press will crucify you,
Elizabeth.
Articles of impeachment
will be drafted.
This will make
the Saturday Night Massacre
look like a dress rehearsal
for the real thing.
Please...
I'm begging you.
Reconsider.
I did not bust my ass
to get elected.
I did not survive
an assassination attempt
just to fold up my tent
and go home.
Send 'em.
Don't.
Hey. Carrie.
Any issues?
No. In and out
in five minutes.
It's all there.
Thanks.
Good luck.
Franny always loved
when Aunt Carrie was around--
played with her,
fixed her breakfast.
Stuff like that.
Does your Aunt Carrie
spend a lot of time with Franny?
Not really.
Can you speak up, please?
No.
It always seems like Aunt Carrie
is going somewhere,
and my mom couldn't
depend on her.
Do you know what kept
her out of the house so much?
I think she's trying
to save our democracy,
which is a pretty good thing,
if you ask me.
Josie,
have you noticed any changes
in Franny recently?
Some, yeah.
Can you give the court
an example?
She's gotten really quiet.
I've noticed that.
Anything else?
At night, she crawls
into bed with me.
Most times,
she cries herself to sleep.
It's a terrible situation.
Mr. Quinn was a close friend.
He was homeless and suffered
from PTSD, so she took him in.
It wasn't, uh, the wisest
decision on her part,
but it was
an act of compassion.
Unfortunately,
things got out of hand,
and there was an incident.
More than
an incident, correct?
Didn't he hold Franny hostage
at gunpoint?
According to Carrie, he thought
he was protecting her.
Ms. Lonas, do you
think it's sometimes necessary
to separate a child
from her parent?
I hate to see it happen.
Research has shown that children
suffer life-long damage
when their bond with
the primary caregiver is broken.
Is there any exception?
Yes, when a child has suffered
repeated trauma.
Apparently, she had been
in a man's house.
Someone she called
Mommy's friend.
Then she said some bad men
broke in. They had guns.
They fought with Mommy
and her friend
and took the friend away.
She said
Mommy was screaming,
and somebody
was screaming at her.
We didn't press too hard
for details
because it really agitated her
to talk about it.
She would literally
start trembling.
No more questions.
The witness may step down.
Our next witness is
Dr. Margaret Mathison.
- Good morning, Dr. Mathison.
- Good morning.
- You're Franny's Aunt?
- Yes.
And the sister of her mother,
Carrie Mathison.
Yes.
And you and your husband are
petitioning the court
for sole physical custody
of your niece. Is that correct?
- That's correct.
- You have a lot of experience
taking care of Franny,
don't you?
I've been taking care of her
on and off since she was born.
And Franny lives with you now,
doesn't she?
Yes, Carrie and Franny moved in
with us about three months ago.
Was that difficult
for you and your family?
Not at first.
Um, Josie's always loved her
Aunt Carrie, so she was happy.
And Franny's a delight.
It was good to have them.
But it didn't last.
What happened,
Dr. Mathison?
What always happens.
Uh, Carrie became
obsessed with something,
started staying out
all hours,
forgetting to pick up
Franny from school.
I found strangers in the house
at night in her bedroom.
And she was racking up
thousands of dollars in debt
on her credit cards
and lying about it.
- Did you confront her?
- I did. Finally.
At first,
she denied everything,
and then she said she was
working on something
but couldn't say what.
That's typical.
And the whole time
in the middle of it all
is this little girl, desperate
for her mother's attention.
Was there something specific
that prompted you
- to petition for custody?
- Definitely.
It was the incident
Mrs. Shepherd was talking about.
But what she didn't
tell you is that
the man who was
arrested that night,
he was an FBI agent who Carrie
suspected was dirty.
- Dirty? How?
- I have no idea.
But your point is, your sister
thought this was a bad guy,
and still, she allowed him
near her daughter?
- is that correct?
- It's worse than that.
She deliberately
put Franny in harm's way
in order to collect evidence
against him.
Is that the only reason
you're petitioning for custody?
No, there's more.
Your Honor,
Dr. Mathison would
like to read a statement
to the court.
I'll allow it.
Is it okay if I just
speak to her instead?
I mean, directly,
is that okay?
Yes, go ahead.
Carrie, the last thing I wanna
do is take Franny away from you.
- Then don't.
- Please don't interrupt
the witness, Ms. Mathison.
You'll get your chance
to respond.
From the day you were born,
you've had a mind of your own.
You never listened to anyone,
even when you were little.
You used to wave at planes.
Remember?
And I would say, "Who are you
waving at? They can't see you."
But you would just
keep on waving.
You were always so fearless,
too, my God.
I hated you for that.
Why was I scared
all the time?
How come you got to be
the brave one?
And Dad going around
to everyone,
calling you
his little daredevil
until I could scream.
I am not...
...extraordinary
like you, Carrie.
I don't run CIA stations
in Afghanistan
or disrupt terrorist plots
in Berlin.
I don't advise the President
of the United States.
My job doesn't require me
to risk my life.
I'm not a hero.
But as it turns out,
safe has
its advantages, too.
A family...
A stable home life...
These are the things that
I can offer Franny...
things that you can't.
It's a chance to be normal.
No. I-- Maggie, that's what
I've decided, too.
I have to give it up.
All of it. I swear.
I'm seeing this
very clearly now.
Carrie, you're my sister,
and I love you, I really do,
but I don't believe you.
In six weeks,
the ECT will wear off,
and Saul will come knocking
with some new crisis,
and the whole crazy orchestra
will start playing again.
I'm sorry. I really am.
That's all I have to say.
Mr. Schroder?
No more questions,
Your Honor.
I think this would be
a good time for a short break.
Court is adjourned
for 15 minutes.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just gonna-- I'm just
gonna sit here for a while
- if that's all right.
- Sure. Take your time.
Talk to you for a second?
Before you say anything,
and just so you know,
I wanted to come see you
in the hospital.
- I was advised not to.
- It's fine.
Listen, is that visitation
agreement still on the table?
What?
If I sign over sole custody
to you and Bill,
do I still get to see her
every third weekend?
Of course.
How about
every other weekend?
I think we can make
that work, yeah.
We should get the lawyers,
then.
Oh, my God.
Are you sure about this?
I am.
- Carrie.
- Quick. Before I change my mind.
Okay.
The White House has yet to
respond to what one source
has characterized as
a major purge in the administration.
According to that
unconfirmed report,
President Keane will dismiss
at least four
Cabinet-level Secretaries
effective today at 5 PM.
While three of the four
are unknown at this time,
the source did name
Secretary of Defense
Terry Mullen as one of
the potential...
- They're piling on.
- ...to be dismissed.
And it's happening a lot
faster than I thought.
...are directly tied
to Senator Sam Paley's
investigation...
The Vice President is here.
- He's asking to see you.
- Now?
He's right outside.
Well, if he's carrying
an olive branch,
tell him he's a day late
and a dollar short.
He won't say what he wants
except that
he'll only talk to you.
If you like,
I can get rid of him.
No. Now I'm curious.
Bring him in.
Thank you, David.
Madam President, when you
asked me to stand with you,
I was grateful
for the opportunity.
Whatever bad blood existed,
I was happy to put it behind us.
- I truly was.
- Until you weren't.
Until you let Paley
turn your head.
- Well, you're wrong there.
- How do you mean?
It's true. After I saw him,
I-I had some second thoughts.
I... I found myself wanting
more time to think it through.
Once I did, though,
I came down on your side.
You mean...
You signed no document
invoking the 25th Amendment?
I have not, and I won't...
on the one condition that you
immediately walk back the firing
of Secretary Mullen
and the others.
Power without authority
is tyranny.
That's the line I'm trying
to keep you from crossing.
Okay.
Okay, what?
What assurance can you give me
that if I rescind the firings,
you won't just go ahead
and sign the document anyway?
I guess you'll just
have to trust me.
When you're one signature away
from sitting at this desk?
After you ignored my phone calls
knowing full well
- what I was going through?
- I needed the time I needed--
time I knew you wouldn't allow
without browbeating me somehow
into pledging my loyalty.
Which, now, all of a sudden,
you're willing to do.
In good faith, as long
as you do the right thing.
I don't like being
dictated to.
I'm defining the limits
of my support.
There's a difference.
Without a majority
of the Cabinet,
which you do not have,
as of now,
that document is invalid.
You are pointing
an empty gun at my head.
Before I came here,
I spoke
to three separate lawyers.
Each one confirmed that
firing close to a third
of your Cabinet
under these circumstances
is probably unconstitutional.
The White House counsel
doesn't share their opinion.
I'm giving you a simple choice,
Madam President.
Plunge this nation
into crisis
or defend it
from its real enemies.
Madam President--
The answer is no.
Then you leave me no choice
but to deliver
to the President pro tempore
of the Senate
and the Speaker of the House
a document declaring you
unfit for the Office
of the Presidency.
It doesn't have to be
such a snake pit, Elizabeth--
the world.
It really doesn't.
- I miss the service?
- Just ended.
What happened in court?
Franny's gonna live
with Maggie and Bill.
Sorry.
I'm okay.
Really?
Yeah.
It's the right thing.
Did you find Simone?
At a dacha on the outskirts
of Moscow.
Yevgeny's with her.
The clock's ticking.
- What do you mean?
- Warner signed on
- to the 25th Amendment.
- Fuck.
- So Keane has to stand down?
- Not yet.
She preemptively fired
four members of her Cabinet.
Warner's petitioning
the Supreme Court
to rule on the legality
of her action.
- So what's your plan?
- At my request,
the President's demanded
immediate and high-level talks
with my counterparts on
the Russian
national security council.
As the pretext for an operation
to grab Simone?
Delegation leaves tonight.
Is it too late?
For?
Me to join?
I think I could be useful.
Fucking kidding? Can you
be ready in four hours?
If I hustle.
Text me the details.
I gotta say something
to Dante's parents first.
- What do they know?
- Medical examiner found
a congenital heart defect
that was never diagnosed.
Here you go, sweetie.
Hey.
Find your bag?
Yeah. Yeah, I got it.
- Hi, Mommy.
- Hi, sweetheart.
- What kind of cookies are those?
- Chocolate chip.
Mmm.
Did Aunt Maggie make 'em?
No, she bought them
from the store.
So, um...
Sweetheart, you know how
Mommy goes away sometimes?
And you stay
with Aunt Maggie, right?
Are you going away?
Yeah. Yeah,
I have to go to work.
And while I'm gone,
you're gonna live here
with Aunt Maggie
and Josie and Uncle Bill
just like you have been.
Where are you going?
Um, I'm going to Europe.
Remember?
- Where we used to live?
- Not really.
I showed you on a map once.
Across the ocean.
You showed me,
but I don't remember.
Well, that's where
I'm goin'.
Are you coming back?
Of course I'm coming back.
I'm going to work,
and I always come back
when my work's over, don't I?
Hey, Franny.
I always come back.
And while she's gone, you and I
are going to what?
Make pictures for her every day.
- Are you?
- We are going to draw a picture
of something we've done that day
and then when Mommy comes home,
we're gonna give her
all the pictures
so she's going to know
what we've been up to. Right?
- Right.
- That's an amazing idea.
Did you think of that?
Ah. You're so smart.
Come here. Give Mom a hug.
Can I go play
with Josie now?
Yeah, of course you can.
She's going to be fine.
Yeah, I know.
Thank you.
Come here.
Now go.
Go do what you were born to do.
Thank you.
Stop saying that.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN