Previously,
on Homeland...
We have to buy time,
40 minutes, maybe an hour,
till they're in the air.
- I'm not leaving you.
- I agreed with Saul.
If things go wrong,
this is the plan.
What, to allow them
to fucking catch you?
speaking foreign language
It was you.
Carrie Mathison, you're just
going to leave her here?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Ms. Martin, what was
your most recent operation?
We tried to compromise
your president
and push her out of office.
Your medication.
How do you wanna spend
the rest of your days here?
Reading nice books
that Alexander brings you
and exercising in the yard...
or going mad,
locked up in an asylum?
No one back in Moscow
is much in the mood
to negotiate, anyway.
Maybe it's better
if you wait a few months.
I can't wait a few months.
I don't even know if she'll be
alive in a few months.
Go.
You all right?
No, no, no, no.
Not the coat.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't be scared.
No, no, no, no!
Rough ride?
You need to sleep.
I'm trying.
It's been almost six hours.
You can have another lorazepam.
No, I wanna wean myself.
Maybe a half.
Blood work?
Tomorrow.
Sorry.
No, come on in.
Have a seat.
Is Doug...
I'm sitting in for Doug.
Jim Turrow.
You're his supervisor.
Is that right?
You want anything to drink?
Uh, no.
No, I'm good.
Okay if I ask you
a few questions?
Sure.
You were detained in Russia
for 213 days?
Yes.
And you were interrogated
for the first...
Uh, 30ish...
Who was your interrogator?
Um, a colonel named
Sergei Tobokov,
most of the time, anyway.
GRU.
Why'd he stop?
All of this is in the file.
It's a big file.
Can you tell me why
he stopped interrogating you?
I think because
I threw my feces at him.
And was that strategic?
No, no.
I... I... I was in the midst
of a florid psychosis.
They withheld my medication
and it took about 20 days
for me to devolve
into a not
very helpful subject, um,
but they kept at it
for another week or so.
I can't give you
an exact figure.
After that,
it's all either blank
or a series of images
that don't much comport
with reality.
Um, if we're doing this
the slow way,
may... maybe I will take
some water.
Doug informs me you'd like
to be reinstated at the agency.
Yes.
Yes,
I would like that very much.
A security clearance
isn't an option
with upwards of 180 days
unaccounted for.
Yeah, I know that.
That's why I've been
working so hard
with Dr. Foley and Doug,
just trying
to fill in the gaps.
Did they give you
the impression
that wasn't the case?
No.
Did they tell you
you failed your polygraph?
Deception indicated.
So you're gonna have
to bear with me.
Um... which questions?
You said it was usually Tobokov
but not always.
I'd like to know
which questions, please.
Quite a few, actually.
Such as?
Have you ever conspired
with a foreign intelligence
officer or service?
Wh... so... so what does that mean?
Are... are you accusing me
of something?
Could mean a lot of things:
giving up sources
and methods,
working for the enemy.
You tell me.
My memory doesn't distinguish
between what was real
and... and what wasn't.
You get that, right?
The polygraph doesn't care
if you were delusional.
It says you were lying.
I edit my answers,
because I don't trust
my own brain.
That's what it's picking up.
Maybe.
We expected that
going into this.
Dr. Foley and Doug both said
it was a possibility.
Why is he acting like
this is incriminating?
We expected it.
You wanna jump in here?
Sit down, please.
You did admit to giving up
the location
of a safe house in Beirut.
Yeah, one that hasn't been
active for decades.
I believe at that point
I had been kept awake
for 96 hours.
- What about assets?
- What about them?
Did you ever reveal
the identity of an asset?
No.
Maybe somebody who died
ten years before.
No, assets have families.
I wouldn't do that.
You sure?
How much more clearly
can I say this?
I did not.
Ms. Mathison,
how can you be so sure
if there's 180 days
of your life
you don't remember?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Parties are prepared
to work through dinner tonight.
Should we take that
as a positive sign?
Just getting the Taliban
to the table
has taken nine years.
So the fact
they're sitting down
with the Afghan government
at all is a positive.
Come on, Saul, make some news.
It's been three weeks.
At least give us a sense
of how it's going so far.
It's going;
from what I understand,
there's a nice lamb kabsa
on the menu tonight.
- Ha.
- Okay.
How 'bout off the record then?
Sure.
Well, the list
of missed opportunities
for peace in Afghanistan
is long.
What do you see as the main
obstacles to a deal?
Well, for one thing,
America hasn't got
a whole lot of good options.
We're not staying forever.
President's made that
abundantly clear.
We can't just walk away either.
Why not?
Well, our forces out past
a critical point,
Kabul falls in six weeks.
General Edwards
told me six months.
Trillion dollars spent,
more than 2,000 lives lost...
it's a U.S. surrender
any way you look at it.
Other issue is
the Taliban itself.
It's not clear they have
anything to gain
by a political settlement.
What do you mean, exactly?
Only reason to cut a deal
is to get us to leave
sooner than later.
Which you just said
isn't an option.
Not without serious
security guarantees in place
before we go.
And what's wrong with that?
Nothing, if you think
the Taliban will abide
by the terms of an agreement.
And will they?
Your guess is as good as mine.
President Warner
seems confident enough.
Well, the President's
an optimist.
Me, I'm a spy.
And his
National Security Advisor.
Don't remind me.
G'ulom's making a statement.
Sorry, I gotta go.
More later.
What's he gonna say?
Do we know?
No idea.
His office only just announced
that he was doing
the press conference.
This can't be good.
But we are
lions, brothers and sisters.
Other animals in the jungle
are afraid
of even a sick lion
and stay away from him.
We are lions.
The United States
should treat us
as lions.
And we demand nothing less.
Instead, our president
and foreign minister
have been tricked.
Tricked into promising
to release
more than 1,000
Taliban prisoners of war,
12 of them responsible
for the bomb...
hidden inside an ambulance
and killed nearly
100 citizens last month
in Kabul.
I want you to know...
I am in charge of these
prisoners,
and I will never agree
to their release.
Never.
Not even a single one.
Robin, talk to me.
Phones started going off,
and you can imagine
what happened next.
Where's Agha Jan?
He threw down his credentials
and he stormed off
with the rest
of the Taliban delegation.
I don't think
he's coming back, Saul.
- I really don't.
- Which way they go?
Um...
Agha Jan.
Agha Jan!
We told you,
no prisoners, no talks.
I'm aware.
The very first thing
we agreed to
and now it is broken.
I understand you're angry.
I'm angry,
but nothing is broken.
We agreed
to a prisoner exchange
upon successful completion
of an agreement.
We are not there yet,
not even close.
You heard G'ulom.
Vice President doesn't speak
for the government.
You know that.
What is done is done.
Too bad.
Agha Jan.
Leave now
and it'll be years before
we get back to this point,
if ever.
I'm sorry, I truly am.
I have an idea.
What if I was able
to accelerate the release
of some of the prisoners
in U.S. custody?
Say, 5 of the 32 at Guantanamo?
Would that change your mind?
You could do that?
I could try.
I would consider it
if we get to choose which five.
Okay.
Then we'll stay
for one week,
but you still have to get
G'ulom to change what he said.
speaks foreign language
I'll call you back
from the office.
Give us a minute, will you?
Of course.
You look peeved.
What's happened?
You know damn well.
I warned you.
It was only a matter of time
before things fell apart.
There's falling apart
and then there's pushing 'em
off a cliff.
Pakistan had nothing to do
with this.
We're not leaking details
of these talks to anyone.
Please.
It wasn't me, and it wasn't
anybody in my delegation.
You know, you almost
make me believe you.
Then I remember Islamabad,
the embassy,
the two hours you stood down
your response team,
while 36 Americans were killed
in cold blood.
Colonel Jefrani.
Yes, ma'am?
Show Mr. Berenson out.
You got a lot of shit.
I'm Gonzales.
Piotrowski.
Huh?
Max!
Squad's out on patrol.
Nobody gonna be back
till morning.
Anything I should do
in the meantime?
Stay low, try not to get shot.
Doug.
Hey.
Jim Turrow,
counterintelligence.
Hi, Jim, good to meet you.
And you know Dr. Foley.
Hi.
Where are we?
Physically,
she's in good shape.
Sleep is still an issue,
but it's better than it was.
Her thyroid hasn't quite
leveled out.
That's from?
The malnutrition.
It improves when she eats more
or treat it with a pill?
Medication.
We're playing with the dosage.
That and the sleep
both have an impact
on mood regulation
and memory access.
So we are hoping
that her recall will improve
as we go.
There are still
significant gaps in her story,
but that's par for the course.
She's recovering
more information every day.
It's not the gaps
I'm concerned about.
If you're worried
about the polygraph,
I would take it
with a grain of salt.
It's not something
we can ignore.
Polygraphs are unreliable.
"Deception indicated"
can mean she's nervous
or lying to herself.
Or it can indicate deception.
We have a long way to go.
This is just one data point.
Look, I... I don't wanna dismiss
your misgivings,
but bringing in Mr. Berenson
may have been premature.
He didn't call me here.
Oh.
I misunderstood.
I'm here because
I need Carrie in Kabul
for a week or two.
- When?
- Right away.
We're making progress here.
Put her in a war zone,
we could be back to square one.
Terms of debriefing timeline
or her mental state?
Both.
She unstable?
Not now.
It's an important mission.
I'm okay with a setback.
We may be dealing with
a compromised officer here.
You know, she has a kid.
Mathison?
Yes.
You know,
she signed away custody
and walked into a bear trap
in the middle of Moscow
to stop an attack
on our presidency.
Yes.
Everyone breaks
under interrogation,
especially
Russian interrogation.
They're good at it.
That's why our sources
were protected
and procedures changed
after she was captured.
It's more complicated
than that.
I'm well aware.
What I wanna know is,
do you have anything
other than a jumpy polygraph?
Hey.
How are you?
Color's better.
They're big on fresh air
around here.
It seems my vitamin D level's
not great.
Also, I'm a Russian agent,
apparently.
So I heard.
Ridiculous.
You won't mind, then,
if I pick your brain a bit.
Only if you think it's safe
to be seen talking to me.
I'll take my chances.
Your old friend
Abdul Qarid G'ulom
just fired a broadside
into the peace talks.
Yeah, I saw that.
I need him to
publicly walk back
his comments about the POWs.
Agreeing to their release
is what got the Taliban
to the negotiating table
in the first place.
I assume the ambassador's
already taken a run at him.
And the chief of station,
got exactly nowhere.
Who's the current COS?
Mike Dunne.
What?
You need an alpha to deal
with an alpha.
- Mike's not that.
- No.
All right, give me a few days.
I'll come up with some options.
You don't have a few days.
Putting you on
a military transport
to Kabul tonight.
If you're up for it, that is.
You kidding?
Hell yes.
- Saul...
- Don't thank me yet.
Kabul isn't the place
you knew before.
It's ten times more dangerous
just walking around,
and you'll be without
any of your old assets.
Pulled from the field, huh?
The minute you were
arrested in Moscow.
Everybody?
Ones you reported
to headquarters, at least.
Saul, I report all my assets
to headquarters,
no matter who they are
or how sensitive.
Of course you do.
Come on, let's get you
packed up, ready to go.
Hey, Mike, it's Turrow.
You heard from Saul Berenson
by any chance?
No, what's up?
I could be wrong,
but I think you got
a bad situation
coming your way.
Bad how?
A compromised officer.
Who is it?
Your old boss,
Carrie Mathison.
Piotrowski's doing
hardware maintenance.
We're gonna provide support
so he can repair or replace.
The unit's on Sar Ridge.
We're gonna loop around
north of Decup.
We're going over the six-one?
If the trail's intact,
we'll take it two clicks west.
If the rain last week
washed it out...
What is he, NSA?
We're doing this
for a cable repair guy?
Back me up, Gonzo.
We already know
how this shit goes down.
He's right, LT.
At least tell us
what this is about.
Mission's classified.
- Oh, great.
- Hey.
We leave at 22:00.
Whole thing will be done
under cover of darkness,
which should afford us
a measure of security.
This is bullshit.
Show him where
the riverbed's at.
Okay, look, every time we cross
the six-one, we get hit.
Last couple of times,
we lost a guy.
We'll take it slow
'cause you're not used
to the altitude,
but we're gonna cross
the riverbed
right about here
that's fairly exposed.
You just gotta haul ass
till you get
to the trees
on the other side,
about 25, 30 yards.
So when we get
to the riverbed...
Run.
Can you unlock the window?
They don't open.
speaking foreign language
Thank merciful God.
The cavalry's shown up.
Is it just me or is that
chip on your shoulder
bigger than the last time
we saw each other?
Fuck off.
Hey, I want you
to meet somebody.
This is Jenna Bragg.
Jenna, Carrie Mathison.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
Jenna's the newest member
of the team.
She's gonna be looking
after you.
Come on, Mike,
you know how I roll.
Don't waste your time.
Not at all.
She wants to do it,
don't you, Jenna?
Happy to.
Any word on the G'ulom meeting?
Set for Friday morning.
I figured you'd want a few days
to see what you could dig up.
Saul told me I could get a look
at the latest 201 file on him.
Loaded onto the laptop
in your room,
and if you need anything
run down, just ask.
Thanks.
Glad you're here, Carrie.
I mean that.
Glad to be here.
I'll show you to your room.
Hey, Carrie, um, truth is,
she's a little stuck
in the starting gate.
I've only been here a month.
Sorry?
How am I supposed to get
out of the starting gate
if he won't let me leave
the station
without an armored vehicle
and a security detail?
I might as well have
"CIA" tattooed on my forehead.
How bad is it out there?
It's bad and getting worse.
Foreign workers are
definitely a target,
but isn't this exactly
what I was trained for?
Here.
- Insist, then.
- Excuse me.
You're in a hard place,
trying to do hard things.
Don't whine and don't take no
for an answer.
Who's it to?
Berenson.
What makes you think
she's gonna have
any more luck with G'ulom
than we did?
G'ulom trusts her.
The two of them made
a pretty good partnership
back in the day.
Killed a lot of bad guys
together.
Shh.
What's that?
A call code...
prearranged between asset
and base.
Two pings for this,
three for that.
Old-school.
Now find out
who owns that number.
Got any questions?
'Cause this is the time.
Only about the riverbed.
You'll let me know?
You'll know,
'cause we're fucking running.
You don't need to worry
about it on the way out.
There's just spotters
when we head out.
It's the way back
that's the problem.
So they'll have eyes on us?
Starting now.
Where the road ends,
the Taliban begins.
Should we walk
or would you rather go inside?
Let's walk.
I was emotional before
and rude.
I apologize.
Apology accepted.
I've been meaning to ask
about your father.
How is he?
Stepfather, and poorly,
I'm afraid.
The MS is starting to affect
his vision.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Must be proud of you, though,
getting the job
he always wanted.
I think he'd have
preferred grandchildren.
You said you needed to see me.
Frankly, I'm at a loss.
I don't know what to do.
- About what?
- You.
Me?
Well, Pakistan.
I was hoping for another
adult in the room.
Seems all you're interested in
is making
what's already a difficult
situation impossible.
I'm sorry.
Am I missing something here?
Weren't you just apologizing
30 seconds ago?
I was, now I'm imploring.
Really?
Because that's not
what it sounds like.
I know we want
the same thing here.
- Do we?
- Yes.
Fair and durable peace
in the region.
Don't lecture me
about peace in the region.
You abandoned the region
after the Soviets
were sent packing.
Then 9/11 happened
and you're back.
We've all seen this movie.
We know how it ends...
in chaos and civil war
on our border.
That's exactly what
we're trying to avoid.
How?
By announcing timetables
and benchmarks?
By unilaterally drawing down
your combat troop levels
to zero?
The Afghan state you've built
is a house of cards,
its army a joke.
You want real resolution,
then show some real resolve.
At least make the Taliban think
you aren't running
for the exits.
Policy's the policy.
No way that is changing now.
Then peace isn't what you want.
You just want out.
speaking foreign language
All right, we're here.
You see the kid?
Where?
By the caves.
Come on, get a move on.
We don't got all night.
They sent the fucking A-team.
Carrie!
Arman, how are you?
Good, good, prosperous.
Yeah, I can see that.
23 in the fleet now.
This one, it is brand-new,
10,000 gallons.
Beautiful.
All thanks to you.
Hardly.
You built this yourself,
Arman, from nothing.
One rented truck,
and who helped me rent it?
This is for Daria.
I tried to get the Lancome,
but I couldn't find it.
Never mind.
She will love
whatever you bring.
So who's driving me tonight?
I am.
- You are?
- Yeah.
But I thought you don't
drive anymore.
I do for you.
Nothing has changed:
bribes, extortion, murder.
It is criminal enterprise,
this government.
And G'ulom himself, where does
he fit in these days?
Oh, he's at the very top
of the pyramid.
He's more powerful
than the President.
Then I need to find an enemy,
someone willing
to bring him down.
Maybe one
of the other ministers.
Don't bother.
They don't have the guts.
What about Faqiar?
I read somewhere he was running
an anti-corruption campaign.
G'ulom paid him off.
I hear he's in Dubai now.
He's living like a king.
The law in this country,
it is only for the poor.
Taliban?
Most likely pro-Taliban
kochi nomads.
They are very brave
to be fighting Sunni in Kabul.
I thought Ghazni was as far
as they'd advanced.
That was last month.
Today, they make attacks
on Afghan army positions
almost anywhere.
That was closer.
I give them free gas
in exchange for safe passage.
I think we'll be fine.
Ghazni.
Ah, right, checkpoint.
All clear.
No checkpoint, huh?
- No.
- What's that mean?
I don't know.
How long will you be?
An hour at the most.
I'll text you when I'm ready.
Okay.
speaking foreign language
Are you Sheena?
Do you speak English?
English study, Pashto.
Good.
I'm so sorry to disturb you
at night.
Your husband has told me
wonderful things.
It's really an honor
to meet you.
I met Zarawar
when he was this high.
He's so big.
Uh, is Roshan here?
No.
Okay, do... do you know
when he'll be back?
No.
I really would like to see him.
Would you mind calling him
for me?
No, I'm sorry.
You should go.
I understand it's uncomfortable
having a strange woman
speak to your husband,
but it's... it's very,
very important.
And I'm not gonna leave
your house
until you contact him.
Can you please pick up
your phone?
I said no.
speaks foreign language
Tell me what?
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
I didn't know.
They killed him.
Who did?
The Taliban, because of you.
Because of the CIA.
No, no, that's...
that's not possible.
They said,
"This is what happens
to a traitor
for the Americans."
They pulled him from the house,
ropes on his hands, feet...
tied him to a truck,
dragged him
through the streets.
Oh, Sheena, I'm so sorry.
Zarawar...
Don't speak to my son.
You have to believe me.
I never told anyone
about my meetings with Roshan,
not... not even the people
I work for, nobody.
Is it... is it possible he had
another American contact?
Only you.
When did this happen?
Five months ago.
I don't... I...
I... I... I... I wasn't
even in Afghanistan.
I was in prison.
I never told anyone his name.
Please... please believe me.
I'm s... I'm so sorry.
You should go now.
Get out of my house.
Did you ever reveal
the identity of an asset?
No.
Maybe somebody who died
ten years before.
No.
Assets have families.
I wouldn't do that.
Ms. Mathison,
how can you be so sure
if there's 180 days
of your life
you don't remember?
No, stay.
Don't leave me.
Stay.
Stay, stay.
shouting in foreign language
Fuck!
speaking foreign language
shouting foreign language
speaks foreign language
speaking in foreign language
shouts foreign language
Are you done yet?
No.
How much longer?
I don't know.
I thought I could fix
the switch box,
but it's not working.
I gotta swap it out.
How involved is that?
Fuck this, man.
Well, it's gonna be light
in an hour.
You're gonna have to
wrap it up.
You go ahead.
I'll find my own way back.
Come on, huddle up.
Hey, we're going.
I'm not leaving until I'm done.
Just pick up
your fucking bag and walk.
We don't have
a functional listening device
in 14 miles
of the Pakistani border.
We're in negotiations
with the Taliban in Doha.
Our people don't know
if they are having
a real conversation
or if it's just bullshit
designed to get us to release
1,000 Taliban fighters
from prison.
Hasan Hakhami is
down there somewhere.
He's the one calling the shots
in a hideout in Pakistan
that we can't find,
on a phone that we can't tap.
He's the guy that slaughtered
36 of our people
in Islamabad.
I watched him do it.
You were there, at the embassy?
It's not that you went out,
it's that you went out
without informing anybody.
Mike...
And don't give me any bullshit
about source protection
or "better to ask forgiveness
than permission."
I don't need anybody's
permission.
I'm here on behalf of
the National Security Advisor.
God damn it, Carrie.
There are three teams
out there right now
risking their lives
to find you.
Well, I didn't ask
for that either.
Well, for your sake,
I hope it was worth it.
Wh... what's that supposed
to mean?
That you got what you needed,
because G'ulom's office called.
Your meeting's been
rescheduled.
- For when?
- This morning.
Six hours from now.
- Fuck.
- Yeah.
Jenna will be here at 8:45
to pick you up.
Hey, Mike.
I need to ask you something.
What?
About Russian cooperation
with the Taliban.
How real is it?
Real enough.
What does that look like,
exactly?
Military aid, advisors?
Both.
What about intelligence?
Are they sharing intelligence?
You bet,
anything to piss us off.
It's what the Kremlin
lives for.
I see.
Why do you ask?
I don't know.
I just... I'm trying to get
the lay of the land, I guess.
Where were you tonight, Carrie?
Well, maybe you can tell me
how it relates to Russia, then.
How what relates?
You're here to leverage G'ulom,
but you're asking Russia.
Jesus, Mike, not you too.
What the hell'd they tell you?
That you tanked a polygraph.
I was in Ghazni, okay,
meeting a guy
who used to run against
the insurgents.
He mentioned a GRU contact
in the area.
- Who?
- Well, he wasn't naming names,
was he?
Okay.
You look tired.
You should get some rest.
Big day tomorrow.
Yeah.
All right, I'm pushing up
with Stout.
Cover till we're behind
the boulders.
Durkin, you and Soto got
rear security.
Remember what I told you about
that path at the riverbed?
Watch out.
This is it.
Remember what to do?
Haul ass.
Wait till I tell you.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Move.
Stay down.
Set.
Okay.
Your turn.
Hey, tell me when.
When.
Look, they're right there.
Okay?
Go, go.
Motherfucker.
Come on.
On the wall.
We got him.
Where the fuck are they?
Some patient motherfuckers.
Fuck this place.
You ready?
- No.
- Let's move.
Move, move, move!
Now!
Coming in, coming in!
Everybody okay?
- Yeah.
- Brace for a second attack.
Viper zero-two,
troops in contact.
I say it again.
Troops in contact.
Viper
zero-two is two mikes out.
I'll give you a ten-second...
Negative.
We need close air support.
I repeat, close air support.
Roger,...
What the fuck is that?
Am I hit?
Shit.
Just your CamelBak.
What?
It's water.
Ha.
I thought that fucker hit me.
It's water or piss.
It ain't blood.
I thought that motherfucker
hit me.
Hey, get down!
This ain't over.
Where the hell are those
air assets?
One minute out.
Coming down from Sar Ridge,
where else?
In broad daylight?
Nobody got hit?
My pack got hit,
blew my fucking water open.
You pissed yourself?
No, my actual water pack.
He fucking pissed himself.
No, I didn't.
One casualty:
water transport apparatus.
Cable Guy, he's like a... he's
like a lucky fucking charm.
Cable Guy.
You're like a frosted
Lucky Charm, man.
You're all right.
Look at his face.
He's still freaked out.
You good, pal?
It's working.
Heh.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Ms. Mathison,
this way, please.
The Vice President is
completing another meeting.
He will be ready in a moment.
Thank you.
You okay?
Mike told me you were
out late last night.
I'm fine.
You know you're not going
in there with me, right?
I'm sure you're smart enough
to realize
the Vice President's
not opening up
with some female in the room
he's never met before.
Don't leave me.
Stay, stay, stay, stay.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No!
You can't leave me here!
Don't go!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org