www.Team-NCIS.com
Previously on Damages...
I don't know how to tell you this.
Somehow Ellen's in jail.
She was arrested for killing David.
David doesn't love you anymore.
I've been sleeping with him.
Clearly the woman is nuts.
There's always a solution.
What kind of a solution?
A permanent one.
My name is Gregory Malina,
and I want to make
sure my story gets out.
I got a letter from Greg Malina.
It's over, Art.
The photos link Ray
Fiske to Gregory Malina,
and the documents prove that
Fiske's guilty of insider trading.
You should be able to use that.
You can have your job back.
I don't want it.
Gregory?
You're blackmailing me, Patty.
I'm sorry.
We really have to wear
these for the rest of our lives?
It's kind of terrifying, huh?
I don't know.
Maybe we're making a big mistake.
Excuse me?
About the rings.
Maybe we should've gone gold.
What are you smiling at?
You're gonna look sexy when you're bald.
Bald?
No way.
I'm going toupee all the way.
No, no, don't.
- Why?
- It's bad luck.
We should put them away,
you're making me nervous.
We should lock them up.
They're not insured yet.
Who's gonna take them?
No one, if they're hidden.
Please, babe, it'll put my mind at ease.
All right.
Do you have your key?
It's on the desk.
Put them in our hiding place.
Hello?
What's wrong?
I'll be there right away.
Who was that?
It was my sister.
She's in the Village.
They had another fight.
Patty?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
He shot himself.
I need your help.
Have you called the police?
Not yet.
Who else knows about this?
Just us.
Take this.
Put it somewhere safe.
No one...
can ever know what he was doing here.
I understand.
Not even David.
Ellen?
I can trust you?
Yes.
Damages Season 1 Episode 12
There's No 'We' Anymore
Capture: Swsub.com
Synchro : Gaillots.
Parsons.
Got a roommate.
What's a matter, rich girl?
Daddy won't post bail?
Lower bunk's mine.
Bitch, don't even.
I ripped off a convenience store
and a bodega before they busted my ass.
I killed my fiancי.
A WEEK EARLIER
Babe?
How's your sister?
Oh, she's fine.
You know, Carrie...
it's always a crisis.
You're leaving?
Yeah, I just got called in.
I'm gonna see you later. Okay?
Okay. Hey.
I love you.
I love you, too.
How do you know Raymond Fiske?
Patty?
We were opposing counsel on a case.
Is it common practice
to conduct business this late?
Ray called me at the last minute,
he said he needed to see me urgently.
What happened when he got here?
He'd proposed a settlement offer.
When...
I told him that my clients didn't
accept it, he got upset.
Did he threaten you?
No.
He just got up and left. I...
I thought the meeting was over.
But then he came back and...
did it.
There are no powder burns on the woman.
Blood spatter, angle of the trajectory,
position of the body.
This was a suicide.
Okay.
Can I take her home now?
Yes.
You're free to go, Ms. Hewes.
But we'd like you to stay available
in case we have any other questions.
Of course.
Hello?
What? No, slow-slow down. What...
You're... What?
Where?
Jesus Christ.
How long have you
been standing out there?
No, no, hold on. Hold on a second.
Jesus.
These are Detectives Wright
and Fleming. They have a few questions
they need to ask you.
Nah, excuse me. But where-where's Ray?
Why don't we come inside.
- Nah, where...
- This is about Ray.
What do you mean?
What happened?
Last night, he took his own life.
We have reason to believe
that they were meeting
to discuss your latest settlement offer.
That's entirely possible.
We're in negotiations.
Were you aware that there was
a meeting scheduled for last night?
No. No, I wasn't.
Has Mallory been told?
Amos is there now.
We should be with her.
Mr. Frobisher,
when was the last time
that you spoke to Mr. Fiske?
Yesterday on the phone.
George Moore is dead.
I heard.
I don't even really remember
what we were talking about.
Some... probably details
about the case.
Did Mr. Fiske give any indication
that he was distressed or...?
No.
It's over, Art.
What is?
Are you aware of anything
in Mr. Fiske's life
that could have driven
him to take this action?
No. No, there was nothing.
You all right?
I'm fine.
Why did he do it?
I don't know.
Must have been horrible.
I'm sorry.
I want you to shut down the office.
Send everyone home for a few days.
Okay.
There's going to be
a hearing with Judge Toomey.
I want you to take it.
I'll, uh, I'll-I'll handle it.
I'll be gone for a while.
Sure.
Anything you need.
Thanks, Tom.
Come on, boy. Come on.
I think I should cancel my flight.
Phil, go to your conference.
Not if Michael's going upstate
tonight with Henry's family.
I'm happy to bail, Mom.
Henry and I can go up anytimewe want.
No, no, I don't want
you two changing your plans.
Patty, you shouldn't be alone.
I prefer to be alone.
Really.
You sure?
You know I'd tell you otherwise.
I want to go to the beach house.
I want to get away.
I knew Ray Fiske
well over 20 years.
He was a great lawyer.
A WEEK EARLIER
And a friend.
We're all devastated, Your Honor.
You have my sympathies.
Something like this happens,
it gives us all pause.
Needless to say,
we've been forced to regroup.
New attorneys are just beginning
to familiarize themselves with
Mr. Frobisher's case.
I appreciate that.
The trial was set
for the end of next month
and I see you're requesting
a six-month extension.
Mr. Shayes?
Well, first of all,
let me express my condolences
to the entire firm.
We respect the difficult position
Mr. Phillips finds himself in.
We understand the challenge of getting
new team members up to speed, but...
our responsibilities lie with
Mr. Frobisher's 5,000 employees
who can't pay their bills.
For them, justice delayed...
-  is truly...
- I'd have to agree, Mr. Phillips.
You have a proposed order?
A one-month continuance.
Mr. Phillips,
the court empathizes with your position.
Thank you, Your Honor.
But after one month,
we press on.
Ray left something for you.
It's on the desk.
Take your time, Arthur.
Thank you.
In case anytihing happens to me, I made
a videotape explainning every thing.
I wanted you to know. There's still time
to do the right thing. Gregory.
Ray Fiske killed himself last night.
It's all over the news.
I heard.
David, what is it?
Your sister called
to see how you were doing.
She said she hasn't spoken
to you in three weeks.
Where were you last night?
You told me that you were fired.
I was, but Patty needed me
to meet with George Moore.
You didn't think you should tell me?
I didn't want you involved.
These people are dangerous.
I thought the less that
you knew, the better.
This information that
you got from George Moore...
Shows that Ray Fiske is
part of the whole conspiracy.
So Patty used it as
leverage against Fiske.
Is that why he killed himself?
I don't know.
Patty was blackmailing him.
- Fiske was guilty of corruption.
- Enough, Ellen!
David, listen,
these men killed Gregory Malina.
They probably killed George Moore.
They do whatever the hell they want,
and they'll keep doing it
until somebody stops them.
Frobisher has to take responsibility.
Winning this case is the only
way that that is going to happen.
And then what?
What do you mean?
Are you going to go back to Patty?
This is the kind of work
that I want to do, David.
Patty may be a horrible person, but...
these guys are ruthless.
I don't know what you are doing anymore.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
Really?
A man's dead now. Was that the plan?
You of all people should understand
after what they did to Katie.
I don't care about them;
I care about us.
This is what it takes.
I don't want this life.
Someone has to hold
these guys accountable.
You decide right now:
do you want us or do you want this job?
- Please don't do this.
- Right now.
Right...
now!
You can't decide, can you?
- David...
- No.
We're done, Ellen.
Hello?
Stop, stop it, just stop. Listen to me.
Damn it, will you just... no!
Lila, you need to stop calling me!
I'm sorry to disturb you.
What do you want?
One of your neighbors called and said
they heard a bit of a commotion earlier.
I just wanted to make
sure you two are all right.
Yeah, we're fine.
Is your fiancיe here?
She went out.
But everything's okay?
We're great.
- Have a nice night.
- Hey, you, too.
Malina made a goddamn videotape.
Where is it?
I don't know, I don't know,
but right now that tape is my life.
When he came back into the country,
Malina went to the chef.
Katie Connor?
Do you still have people on her?
Of course.
All right,
all right, good, good, good, all right.
Just do anything you have to do,
but get me that tape.
Hey, it's me.
I... I'm so sorry.
Just please...
Just please call me back.
Okay?
Jesus Christ.
Katie.
Can I come in?
Of course.
I just saw Ellen go. She seemed upset.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, everything's fine.
Good.
You're back in town?
You didn't call.
What are you doing here?
What is this?
Gregory left it with me.
Give it to Ellen. She needs to see this.
Okay.
I gotta go.
Wait a minute. That's it?
You're leaving?
I haven't seen you in months.
I don't want to be
here when she gets back.
I'll call you tomorrow.
You okay?
Yeah, I...
I just came by to grab some stuff.
I thought it would be
better when no one was around.
You heard about Fiske?
Yeah, it's awful.
Doing it in front of Patty.
How is she doing?
She's pretty shaken up.
Have you seen her since she...
let you go?
I don't think Patty wants to see me.
Yeah, what you said was pretty...
Stupid?
I was going to say ballsy,
but, yeah, stupid... stupid works.
So, you know, we should...
we should get some coffee sometime.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Okay.
- Take care.
- You, too.
- Who is it?
- Mallory Fiske.
Oh, shit.
Ray was...
medicated, you know.
For the last several years.
He could just get...
so depressed sometimes.
Hey, do you want a...?
Do you want a drink?
- No, no thank you.
- No?
Well, he probably didn't
want you feeling
obligated to solve his problems.
You know Ray.
He'd bend over backwards
to help someone he cared about,
but God forbid any of us
should worry about him.
God forbid, right?
How was the case going?
Well.
Exceptionally well.
Arthur, the night Ray...
He...
told me to pack my bags.
Said he wanted to leave the country.
He said that?
Why?
I don't know.
But, Arthur, if this had
anything to do with the case...
No, no, no, no.
I would have known that.
Maybe if...
I'd understood him, I could have...
Why did he do it?
Arthur, you knew him better than anyone.
Mallory, you were married to him.
I mean, if you... if you don't
know why he did this, no one does.
- Oh, sure. I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry to take your time.
No, no, it's me.
Can you just hold on one second?
Listen, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on, Mallory.
Look, you know,
don't-don't beat yourself up.
You can't blame yourself.
You know what I mean?
Good night.
Yeah.
Yeah, no. Good. Send 'em up.
Ah, yeah.
Oh, Jesus...
- Good evening, Miss Parsons.
- Good evening, Perry.
Thank you.
Yes.
He called off the engagement?
I'm so sorry, Ellen.
Maybe we went too far.
Do you regret what we did?
Because I do.
You do?
We crossed a line.
How could we know that Ray...?
Is the folder in a safe place?
It's locked up...
in my apartment.
We'll deal with it on Monday morning.
While I'm gone,
you're welcome to stay here.
The guest room's all made up.
Thank you.
You and David can work this out.
I wouldn't be surprised if you were...
together again by the time I get back.
Shortly after, Mr. Fiske sent me
to Florida to help set up a meeting./i>
I didn't know what
this meeting was about,
but I know that Arthur Frobisher
was in contact with a member of
the Securities and Exchange Commission.
The name of that member is...
George Moore.
If anything happens to me,
George Moore and Arthur Frobisher
are responsible.
So, there's bourbon in the kitchen,
and remember to walk Corey.
Where can I reach you?
I'll be at the beach house.
Tom has the number.
Storm cleared Montauk last night.
Should be a perfect weekend.
Thank you, Perry.
Everything's going to be all right.
Hey, Ellen, Ellen, it's me.
Look, there's something
here that you really got to see.
Katie brought you a videotape
that Gregory Malina made.
It's about the case.
Gregory confessed everything
about what happened in Florida.
Look, I got the early shift,
but I'm going to leave it
in our hiding place, okay?
You scared me.
Sorry.
Where's my mom?
She went to the beach house.
She said I could stay here.
Cool.
I'm just grabbing some stuff.
Don't tell my mom you saw me.
Sure.
If anyone asks,
I wasn't here.
- I'm sorry, David.
- Ellen?
Jesus.
- Ellen's gone.
- What are you doing here?
- I'll run you a bath.
- Just get out of here.
- Enough of this shit.
- Don't do this.
Just get out!
You don't know what we had.
I'm calling the police.
You really should lock your door.
Jesus! Patty,
where the hell have you been?
Visiting family.
Well, you need to get back here.
Ellen thinks you tried to kill her.
I'm coming home.
Parsons.
School's out early.
What's going on?
Your bail was posted.
By who?
You know a Patricia Hewes?
All right, sweetheart,
all you've got is a set of keys.
And your attorney sent you
a change of clothes. Sign right here.
Maybe I should go
in and get your things, huh?
No. Thanks.
I think I just want
to be alone for a while.
You really should lock your door.
Where is it?
Where's the videotape?
Check the bedroom.
What have you got?
Bring him in here.
Where... is the goddamn videotape?
I don't know.
All right.
I think I got something.
Jesus Christ.
What about the tape?
It wasn't there.
What?
So we went to Patty Hewes' apartment.
And?
Things got a little fouled up.
What the hell is that supposed to mean,
"things got a little bit fouled up"?
Let's just say we didn't find the tape.
Where the hell have you been?
Ellen...
no matter what you think,
I didn't have anything
to do with any of this.
I know.
But Tom told me that you
accused me of trying to kill you.
How else was I supposed
to get you back here?
So this videotape...
implicates Frobisher?
Yes.
You have one new message.
Ellen, it's me.
Katie brought you a videotape
that Gregory Malina made.
I'm going to leave it
in our hiding place, okay?
That's why Frobisher
had someone try to find it.
But Frobisher's people didn't
find the tape in my apartment.
So they went to mine.
But they didn't know
that I would be there.
That's when they tried to kill you.
If they never found the tape,
where is it?
I have it. It's safe.
Good.
- Then we...
- There's no "we" anymore.
I've had some time to think over
the past few days.
The only reason you hired
me was to get to Katie.
- Ellen...
- Don't bother.
I had that figured
out pretty early actually,
but then you had Tom
convince me otherwise,
and I was stupid enough to believe him.
At the time, I didn't realize
he's a scared, weak, liar
who would do anything to please you.
- I would never...
- Bullshit.
And then you tried
to break up me and David,
you trashed Katie as a witness,
and you fired me for no good reason.
But you did teach
me one valuable lesson.
I'm glad.
"Trust no one."
Well, I don't anymore, Patty.
Least of all you.
I see.
I'll give you the tape...
but you're going to
do something for me first.
What?
Be my lawyer.
I've been accused of murder
and you're going to exonerate me.
I need your power and your connections.
Clear me of this, and then help me find
who killed David.
If you do that...
then I'll give you the tape.
Ellen Parsons is out on bail.
You know where to find her.
www.Team-NCIS.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org