www.Team-NCIS.com
www.seriestele.net
Previously on damages...
Someone tried to kill me.
And, uh, where is this body?
I've been trying to reach patty.
Go to the beach house.
Patty, where the hell are you?
Ellen wants to use your beach house.
Be my guest.
I am trying to settle this case.
Try harder.
Katie, katie, it's me.
Start by looking into arlington.
Arlington, Virginia.
Some girl was killed in a car crash.
It was Frobisher's car.
The girl's family went from living
in a trailer park to being
the biggest landowner in arlington.
I'm sorry,
Gregory, for everything.
It's done.
Watch free HD Movies and TV Shows at
StreamingSites.com
What's the matter, david?
Where's Ellen?
I'm right here.
What's wrong?
I could get used to this.
What are you doing with her?
What do you mean?
Look, I like her.
She's smart, capable, but...
Come on...
she's not your type of lawyer.
How long you going to keep her around?
Ellen brought us Katie,
Katie brought us Gregory.
Right.
So as long as Gregory's still in play,
so is Ellen.
Simple as that.
- It's katie.
- Oh, yeah?
What's the matter?
Gregory Malina's dead.
Damages Season 1 Episode 10
Sort of Like a Family
Capture: Swsub.com
Synchro: Gaillots
www.Team-NCIS.com
www.seriestele.net
Patty was at the beach house.
- What did you tell her?
- She was there.
By the time I showed up, she was gone.
Looks like she left in a hurry.
Look, Ellen,
I want to help you.
I want to get you out of here.
But I don't know what
to believe anymore.
Someone tried to kill me, Tom.
It was a hit-and-run.
Gregory Malina died at the scene.
1 MONTH EARLIER
So we move on...
to Frobisher's deposition.
Here's the game plan
with one major addition.
Arlington, Virginia, 1983,
Frobisher's jaguar crashes,
killing the girl he's with.
Frobisher denies he was driving,
but he was drunk at the time.
He's never charged, so
there's no wrongful death suit
but last week...
we received a tip that
Frobisher gave the girl's parents
stock in his company.
It's hush money, so we're going
to use it to show Frobisher's
history of obstructing justice.
If we can crack his slick facade
in the deposition
and get him to show his true colors,
it'll be a victory.
Thanks, everyone.
Thank you.
Hey, there she is.
Do you really have to go, dad?
Yeah, I'm afraid so.
Daddy's lawyer's helping him prepare.
This way he can focus better, not
be distracted by all of us.
Mohammed Ali used to hole
up for six weeks before a fight.
Who's that?
Greatest fighter of all times after me.
I'm not going to have
time to do that, sweetheart.
Thought you could use this.
Look at you.
What's that for?
The night before
your stepmom and I got married,
I was staying in a hotel
room nervous as shit.
Dad!
You're old enough.
Anyway, I was cooped up,
sweating bullets and holly
sent me my three iron.
Why?
It's your dad's good luck charm.
You're my good luck charm now.
What are you doing?
Come on, it's just another deposition.
Everything's going to be okay.
We're going to be fine,
trust me.
How ugly is this going to get?
We're reasonable people.
Yes, we are.
No video camera.
- Unreasonable.
- Patty...
What are you worried about?
Your client is a matinee idol.
Unless his herpes has
flared up, he'll be just fine.
Nonnegotiable.
- I'll give you home-court advantage.
- Not interested.
But since we're on the topic...
how many sessions?
Seven.
Two.
Five.
I have a lot of questions.
That's what wikipedia is for.
Okay,
three.
But I get the video camera.
That's a big concession.
So is three days.
Deal.
Gregory Malina's dead.
Oh, my...
Hit-and-run.
That's horrible.
I guess we'll never know
what really happened.
Maybe the police will find the guy.
I won't hold my breath.
And, Ray...
shame on you.
What's the matter with you, Ray?
You look a little green.
Listen, I got it down to three days,
but she's going to have a camera.
That's okay, right?
We've prepared, I'm ready.
Yeah, but, Art,
listen...
What?
You're going into this
deposition exposed.
How so?
Well, I don't know what to do about
this arlington business, I'm sorry.
She's going to attack you with it
and there's no clear way
I can see to stop her.
I'm not settling, Ray.
I don't know how to protect you.
I'll just have to protect
myself then, won't I?
How are you going to do that?
You wanted to see me?
How was the beach house?
Amazing. I've been meaning to thank
you all day, but it's been so busy.
David and I would love
to take you and phil to dinner.
Oh, forget the dinner, Ellen.
I've decided to take
you off the deposition.
I would like you to report to felicia.
She needs some work done
on a pro bono she's heading up.
Vacation's over.
Get back to work.
Yeah, I'll do that.
What are you doing?
Patty's making me do all
this paralegal bullshit.
For the deposition?
No, it has absolutely nothing
to do with the deposition.
Then put that shit away, huh
Oh, wait.
In 1983, shortly after the tragedy
of their daughter, cindy's, death,
I gave the Lambert family
stock in my company.
Holy shit.
There's some people who might think
that that act was a sign of guilt...
or worse, an attempt to obfuscate
a crime and to buy the...
Lambert family's silence.
To respond to that,
I'm going to turn this part
over to cindy's father, Carl.
Thank you, Arthur.
Folks, for my wife and I,
the particulars of this tragedy were
put to rest almost three decades ago.
Now this is the police
report from the accident.
It documents the angle of impact
and the numerous injuries sustained
by both Cindy and Arthur.
Now, this report...
convinced us at that time
and we remain convinced,
that our daughter was driving that car.
Unbelievable.
Arthur Frobisher provided financial
support to my family because
he loved my daughter.
The fact that it wasn't made public
is to his credit.
Character is what you do in the dark.
Isn't that what christ teaches us?
Oh, Jesus.
Thank you, Carl.
And thank all of you for coming today.
I just want to say
I'm relieved and grateful
that this issue can
finally be put to rest.
1 MONTH LATER
I don't know what to believe anymore.
Someone tried to kill me, Tom.
Come on, Ellen.
When I left patty's apartment,
there was a dead body.
There was blood on the floor,
a window had been broken.
You've got to go there.
You've got to go to patty's apartment.
The police didn't find anything!
Then someone's covering it up!
Look, without any evidence,
what can I do?
Let's go, Parsons.
Get me bail. I'll do the rest myself.
Okay, boy, okay.
There's a good boy.
Yeah, good boy.
Patty?
We were set up.
Or there's a leak in the office.
I don't want anyone in
the deposition but you, Tom.
We're going into lockdown.
Miss hewes, I'd like to meet
with Mr. Moore and question him.
No.
He could be the source of the leak.
This thing was buried for 25 years.
I said no.
Call George Moore, set up a meeting.
What the hell was that press conference?
It was Art's idea, he did it on his own.
And you let him? Your job
is to control your client.
He won't listen to reason.
This incompetence is staggering.
Listen, asshole, this
arlington fiasco's on you.
I warned you from the start
this was a jackass move,
and now you've exposed
yourself to patty's people.
Now just lay low and let me do my job.
Clearly, you can't.
Maybe I'll tell him about
you and Gregory Malina.
You don't want to do that.
You gave that kid stock and
told him when to sell it.
Arthur finds out the full story,
he'll have to settle.
You better be careful.
I can take you down at any moment.
Go ahead.
You'll be taking yourself down as well.
You can't touch me, Ray.
Arthur needs me.
So do you.
Which one do you think looks best?
I like this.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Use a windsor.
It's assertive and formidable.
You know, I never learned
how to tie that, actually.
Can you believe that?
Billionaire doesn't know
how to tie a rich man's knot?
Here, sit down, I'll do it for you.
Holly usually helps me with this.
Yeah?
I want to thank you, Ray.
For my invaluable sartorial assistance?
No, for everything.
The last 16 years.
Especially the last five.
I mean, I know it hasn't been easy.
I know I can sometimes be kind of A...
Bull in a china shop?
This life is so full of people
trying to screw you, you know?
You shake hands with them one day, the
next day they're trying to stab you.
But you...
you may be the only
one I can trust, Ray.
You're a good friend.
Let's go show 'em what we got.
SPE stands for special purpose entity.
I'd like to mark as exhibit seven...
a chart entitled
Frobisher value analysis
dated march 4, 2001.
Do you recall seeing
this exhibit seven before?
It's important to establish that
it wasn't me personally
that set up these entities.
They were incorporated under
the direction of...
the chief operating officer.
Despite running the company,
you take no responsibility
for these entities that
your COO created?
Insofar as I was his superior,
yes, a certain
amount of responsibility
must be inferred.
But as far as direct
responsibility, no.
I don't believe that I can be
held personally responsible.
Mr. Frobisher, you were...
intimately involved in
founding your
company, running your company,
bankrupting your company,
and yet you sit here today
wanting us to believe that you...
have no idea where the money went.
Objection.
One more of those, counselor, and we're
going to have ourselves a problem.
Look,
all those SPEs and-and hold co's
every company has them.
I know when you see them up
there on a big chart
with all those colors and arrows
and unrestricted this and
offshore that, you...
you think they've been designed
purposefully...
to confuse the heck out of you.
And you know what?
It works,'ause it
confuses the hell out of me,
which is probably why I'm a
CEO and not a CFO
or a COO.
So,
you don't consider it
your duty as chief
executive of your company
to understand its
financial underpinnings?
A chief executive's job is to set
his company's agenda.
You're like A... you're like a coach.
Sometimes even a cheerleader.
You-you provide goals.
You lead by example.
I always believed
that it was my duty to...
to inspire my employees so that...
so that together we
could build something...
remarkable.
Hello.
Mr. Moore, it's Ellen parsons.
She spent the day lobbing
me softballs, loosening me up.
It's going to get a lot tougher.
But Ray says the day went well.
Good, I'm glad.
Is there anything you need?
Anything I can do to
make this easier for you?
No, just talking to you helps.
I love you, Holly.
I miss you guys.
We miss you.
Night.
Good night, Arthur.
He's going through so much.
It's been hard for you, too.
Don't forget that.
I'm so grateful I found you.
I don't know how I would...
Hey, we'll get through this.
It'll be easier once you tell him.
We have to wait until
after the deposition.
Miss Parsons.
I put my ass on the line for you.
Mr. Moore.
I trusted you with Arlington,
and your camp leaked it.
Why would we do that?
You don't understand how
Frobisher operates, do you?
Someone in your office...
is in his pocket.
Or you are.
Grow up.
I could get killed for what i told you.
You people had the opportunity to
take down Frobisher,
and you blew it.
The case isn't over yet.
Well, we are.
You get nothing else from me.
And tell Tom Shayes to stop calling.
Mr. Moore?
If there's a connection between you
and Arthur Frobisher, we will find it.
Watch yourself.
George Moore is full of shit.
He's saying we leaked arlington.
What have you found?
Moore was one of five SEC
commissioners appointed.
By who?
The president.
Moore headed up a team of investigators
to look into possible
fraud in Frobisher's company.
Who's Laura Watkins?
One of Moore's investigators.
But, in 2002, just before the
government trial, she was fired.
Moore said her methods were unsound.
After the trial, Watkins
did this interview.
She said that Moore removed her
for investigating too aggressively.
It was the first and last
interview she ever did.
You think Moore shut her down?
Now she works for an accounting
firm here in the city.
Have you told patty about this?
No.
And I'm not going to until I'm
absolutely sure I have something.
George Moore made a big show
of going after Frobisher.
- But you didn't believe he was?
- No.
Behind the scenes, Moore did nothing.
He forced us to keep investigating
Frobisher's stock broker
months after it was clear
that it would be a dead end.
Did you ever figure out Moore's agenda?
No.
But, the weekend before
Frobisher dumped his stock,
we were getting ready to expose
the accounting fraud in his company.
The same weekend Frobisher
was in palm beach.
Yeah. Exactly.
And you know where George
Moore was that same weekend?
No. We had no reason to look into that.
Well, he was in jacksonville, florida,
less than four hours away,
at an SEC commissioners'retreat.
George Moore chose
that location himself.
He said he wanted to play
the 17th hole at sawgrass.
Good morning.
Arthur Frobisher.
I know who you are.
I probably shouldn't
be talking to you, huh?
How's the coffee here?
You know, when I was your age,
I used to run from moments like this,
standing two feet from
somebody who hates your guts.
Now I live for this shit.
Was your trip to palm beach
in june 2002
primarily business or pleasure?
Business.
I was there to deliver
a speech at a luncheon.
That's where you met katie connor?
No, we never met in florida.
I was told later that she
was one of the caterers.
And, afterwards, you approached
her about financing a restaurant?
My attorney contacted
her on my behalf, yes.
Why such interest in a novice chef?
Objection. Vague.
At the luncheon,
an herb-encrusted pork loin
made quite an impression.
I was told later that it
was ms. Connor's creation.
Yet your financing of
Miss Connor's restaurant
halted shortly after she agreed
to testify in this case.
Why was that?
Ms. Connor went through a series...
of personal struggles.
Exhibit 41.
Please mark as exhibit 41.
Do you recognize this man?
No, I don't.
Let the record reflect that exhibit
41 is a photograph of
Gregory Malina.
Were you aware that Mr. Malina was in
Palm Beach the same weekend you were?
No. I've never seen him before.
So you didn't know he was
romantically linked to Ms. Connor?
No, I did not.
Or that he owned a thousand
shares of stock in your company?
My stock was publicly traded.
A lot of people had it.
Or that in june, 2002,
he sold his stock the very same
morning you sold yours?
No. No, I didn't know that.
Are you aware Mr. Malina is dead?
No. No.
but, like I said, I've
never seen this man before.
I'm very sorry to hear that.
I think that will be all for today.
Did you give Gregory Malina
stock in my company?
Absolutely not.
Then who the hell tipped him off?
I have no idea.
It doesn't matter, Art.
Malina can't hurt you.
You know what I think?
I think...
George Moore engineered
this whole hit-and-run.
Well, George is capable
of a lot of things.
What does that mean?
What do you mean?
I think he leaked Arlington.
Well, for christ...
Why would he do that?
Save his own ass. Get you to settle.
No, don't...
Senior partners wanted to meet with you.
We'll talk about this later.
Hey, Marshall, come on in.
Amos, good to see you.
Arthur, you remember Marshall
Phillips, amos denninger,
my superiors in everything
but shortness and baldness.
Come on in. Sit down.
Amos, you look good.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Frobisher, we just want
to assure you
that every one of our firm's
resources is at your disposal.
Well, marshall, i appreciate
that, but I'll tell you something.
With Ray, here, I never
felt more confident.
Can I get you fellas a drink?
No, nothing for me, thanks.
Ray? I'm going to freshen
myself up here a little bit.
I'm fine thank you
Why do I would this pleasure?
Ms. Hewes, I found a way to help.
- I went back to George Moore, and he...
- You did what?
I spoke with George Moore.
Who told you to do that?
It was my initiative.
I thought we should follow...
Thought?
Who told you to think?
You are in this office
to wait for instructions.
You don't have license to think.
You have jeopardized...
the only serious lead we still have.
How could you be so...
stupid?
Just get out of my office.
I'm so sick of your bullshit.
What did you say to me?
You heard me.
Get out.
And don't bother coming back.
Give this to patty.
What you looking for, boy?
You a good boy?
Excuse me.
Jeez...
Does Ms. Hewes know you're here?
She gave me an extra set of keys.
How did you get in?
Service elevator.
Ms. Hewes had a water delivery.
Make sure you lock up when you go.
Will do.
I was just fired.
What happened?
The thing is, I'm fine.
Seriously, I feel great.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Let's go out.
Let's get drunk.
We still have some friends, don't we?
- Hey, there he is.
- Art, come here.
I tried to head you off.
I've got some bad news.
She's divorcing me.
I am so sorry, Art.
Where did you get this?
The papers were filed this morning.
God...
who else knows about this?
Well, it's just us and the
court, it's not public yet.
Look, I'm going to
reschedule today's session.
I've prepared for this.
Art, listen to me.
You are distracted.
I cannot have you in that room
in anything less than top form.
I'm fine.
Put this away.
Come on.
Mr. Frobisher, two days after you
returned from your trip to florida,
you gave a speech to your employees.
Yes, that's correct.
Exhibit 67.
It's a transcript of mr.
Frobisher's remarks dated...
june 21,
2002.
Were you aware
that your company was being investigated
by the sec at the time?
Yes, I was.
And yet you still told your employees
that the company was
on sound financial ground?
I was confident that we were.
I firmly believed that the
sec investigation would turn up
no financial irregularities whatsoever.
Exhibit 68.
This is an e-mail you sent
your CFO, is that correct?
Yes, it is.
It's a rough draft of the...
speech you wrote, the one you intended
to give your employees?
Yes, it appears to be that.
In the margin, you wrote the words,
too rosy,
followed by a question mark.
Too rosy.
I think I was...
wondering about the tone of the speech.
I was debating whether or
not to acknowledge the...
the climate that we were in at the time.
By climate, you mean the SEC
was about to expose
your accounting fraud.
Objection.
For me to ignore the pending sec report
would have threatened my credibility,
so in my final speech,
I decided to mention the investigation
and even a...
possible action against us by the sec.
But...
you also continued to insist that
your company was financially sound?
- Yes
- And your employees trusted you?
Absolutely.
For almost 35 years, they knew
that I was fully committed to them.
There's nothing more important
to the well-being of a company
than the relationship
between its workers...
and its management.
That's...
sort of like a family, isn't it?
Yes, it's very much like a family.
And you were the head of the household?
You might say you were both husband
and father to your employees.
Objection.
You could say that, yes.
And was it your job to
hold the family together?
Yes, it was.
- And you failed.
- Objection.
I'll rephrase.
I mean...
was it...
very painful for you when you failed?
Objection.
I'm warning you...
- I'm merely asking Mr. Frobisher...
- counselor.
about his commitment to his company.
Would you agree...
that the crumbling of
that relationship is nothing less,
really, than the
dissolution of a marriage?
You watch what you say.
Your position...
is that the collapse of your company
wasn't your fault, is that right?
Yes, that's correct.
I was misled by the accountants.
I take full responsibility
but not the blame.
I understand, it's like marriages.
Companies just fail sometime.
Irreconcilable differences.
No one is to blame.
Is that your position?
One more like that,
and we will walk out.
Is that your position, Mr. Frobisher?
Or is the failure of this relationship,
as you call it,
- your failure? Your breach of trust...
- Patty, I'm warning you.
- your infidelity...
- You are out of line...
This is bullshit!
- This is bullshit!
- Art...
I'm done here. This is bullshit.
This is absolute
bullshit, and you know it.
No, I'm done.
- No, I'm done.
- Arthur...
I'll see you in court, you bitch.
Are you kidding me? Divorce?
You blindsided me, you know that, holly?
We'll talk about this later.
Did you want patty hewes
to use this against me?
- Of course not.
- Is that what you wanted? Then why now?
- Why now, Holly?
- This isn't
- about the case, it's about us.
- Bullshit!
You screwed me!
You screwed yourself,
too, you know that?
This is our money. We're
talking about our money here.
- I'm sorry, Arthur.
- Look at this.
I gave you everything you ever wanted!
Stay away from me.
I could've ended this
anytime I wanted, you know.
I could've made this go away months ago.
- What are you do... Come on.
- Move the car.
Did you even think about the kids?
You ever think about that?
You move that car, I will kill you.
Open the window; let's talk. Come on.
Holly, come on, open the window...
Open the...
Holly, talk to me, will ya?
Talk to me, will ya?
Stop the car!
Stop the damn car!
The hell with this.
I can't take any more of it.
Just make an offer.
How's my favorite divorce attorney?
Men and women still hate
each other, so I'm good.
Oh, boy, thanks for the tip.
I hope it didn't get you
in trouble with your client.
I just blamed it on
the clerks at the court.
High-profile divorce like this...
Yeah, they would have leaked
it to the press anyway.
Besides,
this thing's going
to be about custody...
and infidelity.
I owe you one.
Very nice.
Ellen, where are you going to work now?
I don't know. I have
no idea! I don't care.
Do you know where I can
work? Where can I work?
You could a sushi photographer.
Raymond.
- 500
- 500?
You heard me, patty.
I daresay, it's as much
as you could've hoped for.
More than fair.
Let's wrap this up.
Patty?
Oh, it's tempting, Ray.
I could use a vacation.
You deserve one.
But I've still got work to do.
- Patty...
- No deal.
If Gregory Malina was worth killing,
he must have known something.
If he testified, my guess, we'd
be talking ten figures.
not so chatty now, are you, Ray?
You won't get more than
500 out of my client, Patty.
Evening, Ray.
It didn't matter, grades were in, and
she goes, what would I do in that case?
I'll tell you what I would do, Calder,
I'd... let me tell it.
I'll tell you what I would do.
I'd sub-penis'him.
she said sub-penis!
She said penis in law school.
And he was, like, who do you think
you are, Ms. Parsons?
Calder with his silver streak,
right? Calder?
I didn't know what I was
saying. He was so sleazy.
He kept asking me out on dates.
Who the hell is this guy?
where is that guy?
Who is it?
Oh, it's my mom.
He wanted to take you to
a drive-in of viva zapata.
This is Ellen Parsons.
You can leave a message here or
reach me at my office:
212-752-4708.
This is some pretty
interesting stuff you found.
I don't even want a goddamn centerpiece.
Sorry, I didn't realize
it was the honeymoon.
I'm sorry. I hate that shit.
You were right.
Whoever tried to clean up
the body missed something.
What?
Blood. I saw... the blood.
Look, I got to take
this to the police.
Did you get any word from patty?
I've left messages.
I've told her that she's
got to come back here.
She doesn't want to come back.
Why not?
Patty is a lot of things, but
she's not a murderer.
I know things, Tom.
Things that could destroy her.
You think patty tried to kill you
to protect herself?
Well, the only way that I'm going
to find out is if I talk to her.
Face-to-face.
So call her.
Tell her I know she wants me dead.
www.Team-NCIS.com
www.seriestele.net
Surf the internet with browser of future
osdb.link/brave