My God.
Ellen.
What happened?
I didn't kill David.
Someone tried to kill me.
Arthur Frobisher told his
employees to invest in
the company and then
sold his own stock.
We don't have a case
unless we can connect
Frobisher with his broker.
You're my sister.
How do you know
Arthur Frobisher?
You and I, we meet at some
boring luncheon down in Florida,
and the next thing you know,
we're-we're partners.
Katie, this whole case
turns on one weekend,
and you were there.
You're stepping into
the spotlight now.
Details of your life
are going to come out.
I think Katie's lying about
the guy she met in Florida.
His name is Gregory Malina.
Do you remember we actually
saw him down in Florida?
If you do know something,
you should come down
and speak to the
lawyers with me.
The only time I saw
Frobisher was with you.
If Patty Hewes gets that
girl in front of a jury,
all bets are off.
Ten years, one box, one trip.
You didn't deserve this.
I miss seeing you around
the office, Tommy.
Everyone thinks you
were actually canned.
What is it, Tom?
Following Katie Connor?
I'm a lawyer, Patty.
I miss it.
Hey, everybody wants to know
when you're going to get here.
I have no idea.
The decision's yours.
Ellen was still there
when I left at 9:15.
Well, interesting choice.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Palm
Beach
Florida
Can I just say what
a bad idea this is?
Gregory.
Katie.
What the hell was that?
Come on, follow me.
Wait, wait, wait.
How many drinks did you have?
The two, with Gregory,
and then...
before that maybe another beer.
And no drugs?
No drugs.
And you never caught
his last name.
We have been over this.
It's no like it
was a formal date.
I love Florida!
Let's go to another
club.Come on.
Oh, I can't.
I got a big day tomorrow--
I've gotta be up early. I can't.
Who doesn't?
If you don't go to sleep,
you don't have to wake up, right?
Huh? Huh?
Oh, God.
Okay!
Wait for me!
And you didn't see
Frobisher in the nightclub?
No, I didn't even know
what he looked like
until the parking lot.
No shit.
You live in Brooklyn, too?
"It's better in
the the boroughs."
I live in Williamburg.
Isn't that crazy?
You come all the way to Florida
and meet someone who lives,
like, five minutes away.
What are you doing down here?
Business. You?
Oh, shit.
Friends of yours?
I wish.
That's Arthur Frobisher.
The guy's got more
money than Trump.
Huh!
You think that guy eats beef?
I think that guy eats
small cows for breakfast.
I'm catering a function
for him tomorrow.
Ah, you're a cook.
We prefer to say "chef."
I'm a waiter.
I guess that means
I'm beneath you.
Not yet.
You want me to keep going?
We still don't have enough
unless you can identify the
man who got in the limo.
I only saw him for,
like, a split second.
Is there anything
you can remember?
Was he tall, short?
Young, old?
It was five years ago.
But I can tell you that he
wasn't any of these people
you showed me from
the government trial.
And what about your
one-night stand?
Greg lived in Williamsburg.
He was a waiter.
He was staying in
his friend's condo.
Which we can't find
because you don't remember
what part of town you were in.
Why don't you try hypnosis?
It helped me quit smoking.
Still stuck in the parking lot?
Afraid so.
Hmm. Well,
you know what's going to happen
if we don't come
up with anything?
The clients are going to
accept Frobisher's settlement.
Unless Katie turns out
to be a viable witness.
What is this?
A Ding Dong.
A what?
It's delicious.
Go home. It's late.
Try again tomorrow.
It tastes like a Ho Ho.
Ms. Connor,
is that your brother?
Y... Yes!
Oh, my...
Oh, God!
¾׳ײִ»½צ¹©ׁ§ֿ°½»ֱק£¬ֿׁ½׃ֳ׃ֹּׂµ׃ֳֽ
¾׳ײִ»½צ¹©ׁ§ֿ°½»ֱק£¬ֿׁ½׃ֳ׃ֹּׂµ׃ֳֽ¾
=ְֳֶֶ׀׳ײִ»׳י=- ·­ׂכ:
׀£¶װ: ±¼הײב:״»₪ּל¹
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- ְֳֶֶ׀ְײװ°
ֱׁ÷ µׂ»¼¾µ4¼¯ Resynch/Corrections:
Travis - forom.com
Hewes, Michael.
His mother.
What?
Why not?
He's been there a week.
He's entitled to
phone privileges.
Listen...
I've waited seven days
to talk to my son,
and now you're
telling me I can't?
Fine.
I said fine.
I'll call again next week.
Mr. Frobisher's case
is fully staffed.
We're billing roughly
$550,000 per month.
And the payments?
Always prompt.
Our client's aware of
all the exigencies one
encounters when trying a
case against Patty Hewes.
Ray, what does she have that
she has not accepted Mr.
Frobisher's settlement offer?
Nothing.
Ms. Hewes has been unable to provide
even one significant witness.
She's failed to
produce any evidence
that Mr. Frobisher breached
his duty to his employees,
or participated in the
alleged fraud that she...
Ray...
Yes, Amos?
You know how much Mr.
Frobisher's case means to this firm.
Get it done.
Yes, sir.
Roughly 5,
200 employees are involved in the suit.
Arthur Frobisher-- he wiped out
our whole retirement account.
$1.4 billion.
Gone.
So, you know, most of us,
we just lost everything we had.
You have to stop
torturing yourself.
You're doing
everything you can.
Am I?
Yes, Katie, you are.
Patty needs to know who got
in that limo with Frobisher.
And she keeps
asking about you--
my one-night stand.
What if I can't keep this up?
What if I slip, or they back
me into a corner or something?
You're going to be fine. Okay?
Maybe you should come in.
Why won't you just
talk to them?
And tell them what?
I saw the same thing you did.
Maybe you'd remember something
if you saw the pictures.
Hey, if I go in there,
then my wife is going
to find out about us,
and then we'll be over,
and I don't want that.
It's not about us.
It's about Frobisher and those
people whose lives he ruined.
Patty is the only one holding
him responsible for this.
You really think Patty
Hewes cares about you?
Here is the complete
dossier on Katie Connor.
Is she still seeing Gregory?
Almost every day.
You think she knows anything?
I'm not sure.
Keep an eye on her.
If she's going to
give us something,
she's going to have
to get it from him.
My guy says he can get Greg's stock
portfolio by the end of the week.
Good.
No. No, it's not good, Patty.
This kind of thing
could get me disbarred.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you still on the board of the
Jazz Society at Lincoln Center?
Why?
Well, the head of the Trilling
School is on it, too,
and I was wondering if you'd
put in a word in for Megan...
Tom, wake up.
People think I fired you.
Find another connection.
What is it?
I guess it's a rite of passage.
What is?
It was the ICU.
I assisted on my first
bypass yesterday,
and the patient's
not doing so hot.
Oh, baby, I'm sorry.
The family looks at
you like you're God.
If they only knew...
Ugh!
Shit.
So much for exercise.
What?
What are you doing tonight?
I got a couple hours.
So?
Catch a movie?
I'm in.
Movie, tonight.
You got your
saxophone, sweetheart?
I'm holding it.
Daddy, I'm going to
be late for assembly.
Okay, okay.
You look bellisima.
Bye, Dad.
Bye-bye.
Good luck with the solo.
I'll be thinking of you.
You didn't tell me
she was a musician.
Martin, twice in one week.
We got to stop
meeting like this.
I was hoping we could
finish Monday's chat.
I appreciate the offer.
I've been doing some
soul searching--
I'm just not ready
to start work yet.
Bullshit.
I know what's going on
between you and Patty.
Excuse me?
The whole world sees it.
She treats you like
dirt for ten years,
won't share the spotlight,
then she refuses to
make you a partner.
You don't know what you're
talking about, Martin.
Sure, I don't.
You're not a battered wife
defending her abusive
husband to the end, huh?
Oh, geez.
Yeah, that's it.
No, you got it.
That's me.
You know, your little girl--
she's terrific.
She's the best thing that's
ever happened to me.
She serious with the music?
Yeah, she's pretty serious,
considering she's ten.
I ask 'cause I know that she's
got an application at Trilling.
How do you know that?
Well, I'm president elect
of the parents' board.
You guys have put together
an outstanding app.
Good, good.
Megan's got her heart
set on Trilling.
All her friends are going.
Got to say, it's...
it sure is tough though
to accept an applicant
whose father checks
the "unemployed" box.
Martin...
Don't do this.
Come on, take it easy, Tom.
There are other schools.
Some of them even pretty good.
But, at Trilling, we've got the
music department in the entire city.
Harvard, Yale, Princeton--
without Trilling,
they don't have orchestras.
I'd love to see Megan get in.
Comedy or drama?
I'm sorry?
I heard you telling
that other doctor
that you were going
to go see a movie.
Oh, I'm sorry you overheard
my personal conversation.
Oh, I shouldn't have
been listening.
I want you to know that
we are doing everything
that we can to make your
grandfather comfortable.
I know. Thanks.
And I really appreciate all
the time you take with him.
You've been great.
So...
comedy or drama?
Uh, I don't know.
I was thinking maybe the Cassavetes
retrospective at Film Forum.
I've never heard of that.
Is it funny?
No.
It's pretty serious.
'70s stuff.
I guess I'm more
the drama type.
Oh, not me.
I love comedies.
You know,
they're just so funny.
Oh, oh, check it out.
My grandpa got me into
these old radio shows.
Here.
Who is this?
It's Jack Benny.
It's good.
Grandpa loves the guy,
so I downloaded it for him.
That'll be nice.
Yeah. Well...
Enjoy your big night out.
Thank you.
And have some popcorn for me.
'Cause I'll be here.
Sure thing.
Oh, and Dr. Conner...
Be a little naughty.
Excuse me?
Get something chocolate.
You got it.
Ellen?
Hey, can you come in tomorrow?
I pulled more photos
to run by you.
Minor players,
but we should check them out.
Okay, I can try.
Cool. I'll be in
the office at 8:00.
Look, I got to go.
What are you doing here?
I know who he is.
The guy in the limo.
With Frobisher?
Katie, I don't want to get
involved in any of this, okay?
But you saw his face.
I didn't know who he was
when we first saw him.
Then I recognized
him on Court TV.
They did this thing on Frobisher's
broker during the criminal trial.
And who is he?
Katie...
What's his name?
His name is Luke Richards.
Luke Richards?
He was one of the
broker's assistants.
But Ellen said all of the
assistants had alibis.
Well, Richards must be lying,
because I definitely saw him.
Gregory, if you could have
linked Frobisher to his broker,
why didn't you tell me?
Because I'm not going
to get involved.
What?! Why not?!
I don't want to be
another Kato Kalen.
Let 15 minutes of bullshit
ruin the rest of my life.
Gregory, for Jes...
No, no.
Maybe I'm an asshole,
but I'm not going to let these
people use me and throw me away.
Which is exactly what
they're going to do.
Okay, well, forget about them.
What about me?
I have risked everything I
have to put this guy away,
and now you're just going...
Going to be a
selfish prick? Yeah.
And you should, too.
Think about it, Katie.
You're going to lose
your restaurant,
your privacy,
any shot at having a normal life.
I do care about you.
I don't want to
see you get hurt.
Stay out of it.
Just stay out of it, okay?
Katie...
Darrell Goldstein interned
at Frobisher's company.
No, not him.
Paul Ordell-- he was a temp.
No.
Luke Richards.
Katie, what is it?
Hi, there.
I'm Arthur.
Oh, my God.
Katie?
You want me to be a
witness against Frobisher?
Yes, if you know something.
She's going to be screwed.
She will lose everything,
won't she?
Nothing. Keep going.
Stephen Gilbride.
No, not him.
Jason Raber.
You and I,
we never really spoke when we
were down in Florida, did we?
No, no, that's right.
I want the straight story,
and until you tell me,
you're worthless to me.
I don't give a shit about you.
No, go back to that other guy.
No, before him.
Yeah, him.
You recognize him?
When was this picture taken?
Last year. Why?
Yeah, he was younger,
but...
But what?
It could be Luke Richards.
I think this could be the guy.
The guy you saw get in
the limo with Frobisher?
Yeah.
But a second ago you
said it wasn't him.
Because he looked familiar,
and...
Yeah, this is definitely him.
Katie, are you 100% sure?
It's okay if you're not.
Our fates are
intertwined, Katie.
Isn't that remarkable?
I'm sure.
Who is he, anyway?
Richards was an assistant
to Frobisher's broker.
You're kidding.Seriously?
You farted in your
sleep last night.
David!
You're on speaker.
Classic.
My bad.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's a great day,
David.
Oh, yeah?
Why's that?
Your sister really
came through today.
We're moving forward.
Oh, God.
David?
We're going to prepare
Katie's testimony.
What?
She made an ID.
Babe, are you busy?
Uh... yeah, kind of.
Can I, um...
can we talk tonight?
Yeah, sure.
I don't think he's
getting much sleep.
getting laid.
Hey, okay, too far.
R-I-C-H-A-R-D-S, Luke.
Find out where he was on
the Frobisher weekend.
All right, Patty,
I'll look into it.
Martin, Tom Shayes.
Make me an offer.
I'm ready to listen.
Bad news, Ray.
Looks like they got a witness.
Such a sweet girl.
I was hoping it wasn't
going to come to this.
A mock deposition is
just a tool to see where
you're at in your testimony.
Patty's brought
in Roger Kastle.
Who's he?
Big name in
medical malpractice.
He's kind of a legend.
Is he a sleazeball?
Patty's asked him to play
the role of Ray Fiske.
Perfect.
And you're certain this
is the man you saw enter
Mr. Frobisher's limousine?
Yes, 100% certain.
Okay.
Good.
So, Ms. Connor,
how would you characterize your
stay at the Maxwell Clinic?
What do you mean?
I was simply wondering
if your stint in
rehab was successful.
You had an extremely
difficult time
overcoming your drug addiction,
did you not?
Eyes on me, Ms. Connor.
How is this relevant?
Blurred vision,
paranoia, auditory
hallucinations, unfortunately,
are all documented long-term side
effects of serious cocaine abuse.
I did one line in
the parking lot.
But earlier that evening,
how many lines did
you do in the club?
And more importantly,
how much cocaine had you
consumed prior to that night?
I don't know.
Enough not to remember?
No, I didn't say that.
And this mystery man who
supplied you with cocaine,
what was his last name?
I don't remember.
I'm better with faces.
Oh, so yours is more
of a visual memory?
Yes.
Was he circumcised?
Was he circumcised, Ms. Connor?
You're kidding, right?
Well, now you said you
went back to his condo.
So what?
So I assumed you
had intercourse.
No.
did you schedule a procedure
at Hudson General to
terminate your pregnancy?
Jesus Christ.
Ms. Hewes,
maybe we should take a break.
I thought we had
an understanding.
Ms. Connor,
would you characterize your life
as one big blur of
narcotics and intercourse?
Would you characterize
yourself as an asshole?
Let the record reflect that
the witness is refusing...
Somebody shut this guy up!
Katie, sit down.
Wow, she's not ready.
You signed their
medical release waiver.
Go on, sit down.
I told you that the truth would
have to come out eventually.
I also warned you
that the spotlight
is a pretty goddamn
awful place to be.
And Mr. Kastle's right,
you're not ready for it.
Because this deposition
isn't about the facts.
It's about Katie Connor and do
we like her and is she credible.
Yes, you saw this
man in Florida,
but it's your word
against theirs.
And if Ray Fiske
can embarrass you,
piss you off,
rattle you in any way, it's over.
He's done what he's
set out to do--
neutralize your testimony
and weaken our case.
Katie, why don't we go
outside for a moment?
No, I want to keep going.
Good.
Try again.
Oh, my God.
Can I talk to her?
Not until her
attorney gets back.
You really think she
killed my brother?
They were due to get
married in two weeks.
Katie, you didn't know they
called off their engagement?
No. No.
We had a falling out,
we haven't spoken in months.
Katie, why didn't you tell me?
What,
that I got pregnant
and ended up in rehab?
Isn't it obvious?
I wanted to forget it ever
happened and then... this case.
What about Gregory?
He never even knew you were...
No, I never had a chance
to tell him the truth.
...the whole truth, and nothing
but the truth, so help you God?
I do.
Ms. Connor,
thank you for joining us today.
And many thanks to the
plaintiff's attorney
for the use of her
conference room.
Now, as for the subject
of today's deposition,
I've been instructed
by the court to limit
my questions to the 18th
and the 19th of June, 2002.
Those dates ring
a bell for you,
Ms. Connor?
Yes, sir.
I was in Palm Beach,
working for a catering
company at that time.
We were doing a business
event for Arthur Frobisher.
Ms. Connor,
do you recognize the
man in this photo?
Yes, that's Arthur Frobisher.
And the man in this photo?
Luke Richards.
Thank you, Ms. Connor.
Let the record reflect that the
witness has correctly
identified both men.
Now, Ms. Connor,
if you permit me to
cut to the chase...
you claim that
you saw these men
together early
morning on June 19,
do you not?
Yes, I did.
And where did this alleged
sighting take place?
In a parking lot on the
200 block of Ocean Avenue.
Mr. Frobisher was
in a limousine
and Mr.
Richards got into that limousine.
And where were you
when this happened?
I was in that same parking lot.
Alone?
No, sir.
With whom were you
in this parking lot?
With a man I met in a club
earlier that evening.
If these next few
questions make you blush,
Ms.Connor,
I apologize.
To screw.
I'm sorry?
That's why I was in
an empty parking lot
in the middle of the night.
And later on a couch
and then on the floor.
Do you find cocaine
is like Viagra?
Or are you more of a tantric
breathing kind of a guy,
like Sting?
If these past few answers
make you blush, Mr. Fiske,
I apologize.
So you saw Mr.Richards get into
a limo when it was parked,
what, 25, 30 yards away?
I got my best look at
his face as he left.
He turned his face
toward the window.
I couldn't have been more than
ten feet away at the time.
And this was when exactly?
Between 1:15 and 1:45 a.m.
You checked your watch.
Gunshots forced us
to leave the club.
It's my understanding that
the police report documents
this at approximately 1:15 a.m.
So, you saw Mr.
Frobisher with Mr. Richards
some time after 1:15 a.m.
Saturday morning June 19, 2002.
I remind you,
you're under oath, Ms. Connor.
Yes, that's when I saw them.
Would you agree that a man
can't be in two places at once?
Objection to form.
Vague and ambiguous argument.
Noted.
Go ahead, Katie,
you can answer.
Yeah, I'd agree.
A man cannot be in
two places at once.
So, when Mr. Richards told
investigators he was at the
Jersey shore with a college buddy
pulling cod out of the Atlantic,
it's your contention
he was lying.
Yes, sir.
Mine, too.
Let's not get cute
here, Counsel.
Ms. Connor,
can you identify the
man in Exhibit 15?
Objection.
This exhibit was not made
available to us during discovery.
We've only just discovered
this ourselves.
We have every
intention of producing
it to Ms.
Hewes at the close of this deposition.
Noted.
You can answer.
The man in the picture,
Ms. Connor.
Luke Richards.
And the text there...
what does that say?
Out loud, Ms. Connor.
But this isn't true.
Ms. Connor,
I'm not asking for an opinion,
I'm asking you to read.
Now what does it say?
"June 19, 2002, 1:37 a.m."
Let the record reflect
that Exhibit 15 shows
Mr.Richards withdrawing cash
from an ATM located at 333 Casino
East Boulevard, which is where,
Ms. Connor?
I'm telling you Luke Richards
was in that parking lot.
Can you read the last four words,
Ms. Connor?
I am not lying, he was there.
The last four words.
"Atlantic City, New Jersey."
But I swear to God,
he was in that parking lot.
Luke Richards did lie,
Ms. Connor,
but I suspect it had everything
to do with that woman
standing next to him with the
muscular arms and Adam's apple.
He wasn't hiding Arthur
Frobisher's transgressions,
he was hiding his own.
Why are you lying?
Objection.
Argumentative.
This is bullshit!
I think we're finished here.
You hear that, Patty?
That's the sound of the zeroes
dropping off of Mr.
Frobisher's revised offer.
I heard everything went well.
The threat's gone.
She lied under oath.
I want you to know,
we ruined her life.
If you kept your
dick in your pants,
we wouldn't have had to.
It's been five years.
Starting today,
I want you guys to
leave me alone.
Just let me live my life.
I don't think that's
going to happen.
I don't even think
she remembers you.
Did I ask what you think?
Let's go to another
club.Come on.
Oh, I can't!
I got a big day tomorrow!
I can't!
Who doesn't?
If you don't go to sleep,
you don't have to wake up, right?
Right? Huh?
Okay!
Wait for me!
Five years from now,
what is Katie Connor doing?
I'd like my own little
restaurant in Brooklyn,
but that is not
going to happen.
Why not?
Because I have got the biggest
gig in my life tomorrow,
and I've got to be at
work in five hours,
and I am,
like, totally wired.
Oh...
Relax.
Hey, hey, relax.
Here, try one of these.
You'll be out in ten minutes.
I'm going to hit the shower.
Okay...
Only the white ones, okay?
Hmm.
You were right, you know?
Gregory turns out to
be our missing link.
Gregory Malina owned
Frobisher stock?
Guess when he cashed out.
June, 2002.
Katie Connor never
knew what hit her.
But you had the
photo before anyone,
so why would you
let her be deposed
if you knew she wouldn't
hold up as a witness?
Because now Ray Fiske thinks
we don't have anything.
And watch, his next step will be
to pull the settlement offer.
Which is what you
wanted all along.
Why? Why would you
do this to me? Why?!
Katie, Katie, come here.
Don't touch me.
You lied to me, asshole!
Hey, hey, hey...
Greg, are you cool?
Yeah, yeah, we're fine.
You lied to me!
Why did you lie to me?!
Answer my question!
Why don't you just
call me later, okay?
Yeah, I'll call you later.
I'll call your wife later.
Dude, you're married now?
Katie...
Why would you do
this to me, Gregory?
I'm sorry.
Go to hell.
Katie.
This is your solution?
Katie, what about
the restaurant?
You can't just run
away from this.
I know. I tried.
You wouldn't let me.
What?
This is my fault?
I only tried to help your case.
Katie, you perjured yourself.
People go to jail for that.
There was an answer you wanted,
and you hounded me
until you got it.
That is bullshit.
You know,
you are not mad that I lied.
You are just pissed that I got
caught and made you look bad.
I only ever wanted the truth.
No, Ellen,
all you ever wanted was
to impress Patty Hewes.
Katie? Katie!
From day one,
I never wanted her
involved in this!
I'm so sorry, Miss Hewes.
I thought I knew her.
I trusted her.
Katie's a very
good liar, Ellen.
She had me fooled, too.
You're a lawyer,
lies come with the territory.
Will the clients accept
a settlement now?
I assume so,
which is too bad because I think
we could have gotten them more,
but Frobisher's in
the driver's seat now.
It just doesn't make any sense.
Fiske had pictures.
He was right there waiting
with Richard's alibi.
Ray Fiske is a brilliant lawyer who
made us look very foolish today.
It happens.
Ellen, I understand how
it must hurt right now--
what happened with Katie--
but... there's a very important
lesson to be learned from all this.
Which is?
Trust no one.
Hey.
Listen, I don't want
to be presumptuous.
I'm not available.
I'm engaged.
We can play this
any way you like.
I don't even think
she remembers you.
Palm Beach 2002
ְֳֶֶ׀׳ײִ»׳י
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
Resynch/Corrections: Travis - forom.com
Surf the internet with browser of future
osdb.link/brave