Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
What up, Power?
What up?
Yo, we gonna need a re‐up soon.
Word.
You know where Sha at?
There he go.
A'ight.
Peace.
Where the hell you been, Sha?
Yo, my bad.
I told you I was pickin'
you up at your crib, yo.
Yo, cool.
We still talkin', man? Let's go.
All right, whatever, yo.
‐ There's gonna be
mad Stapleton niggas
out there waiting, son.
‐ I don't care how many
we gotta go through, son.
We dropping Dennis tonight.
Know what I mean?
And if there's one thing
I'm sure of,
it's that drugs destroy your
mind and destroy your home.
‐ I l‐love this s‐shit, nigga.
Hey, yo, you love that shit
too much.
How many times
you gonna watch it?
I got you.
They're filthy drug peddlers...
Hey, yo, turn
that shit off, son.
It's time to eat. Come on, yo.
- Shit. Come on, man.
- Shut up.
This shit mine, man.
- Y'all hungry?
- Y'all ready for this oatmeal?
This my comic?
Took my comic from me?
This is a old one.
This is right before
Tony Stark got paralyzed.
He was in a wheelchair too,
just like y'all,
but he was still a superhero.
‐ W‐what... h‐happened?
What happened.
He got shot.
Yeah, his ex‐girl
put one through him.
See, this nigga fucked up
all the bad guys,
the Hulk, whoever,
but in the end, all it took was a
crazy‐ass bitch to lay Iron Man down.
Fuck!
Yo, don't move! Don't move, son!
- Yo, come on, move.
- Get the fuck up out of here.
Yo. Yo, you hit?
Yo, you okay back there?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Shit! The cops came mad quick!
Pull over right there.
Let me stash the TEC.
Right here, right here!
What's the deal, Sha?
Yo, what up, Bobby?
- You okay?
- Nigga.
You almost killed me.
Yo, my bad, son.
Shit, son.
Ma!
What is it?
Is it morning already?
Wake me in an hour.
Where you going?
Where you coming from?
Niggas had to put in work.
Yo, Bobby, I need you
to stash this shit for me.
Hey, yo, this shit is still hot.
Yo, what the fuck?
Yo, play that beat again, son.
Yo, D‐Love.
- Let me get two for five.
- I ain't working.
Come on, man. Bless a nigga.
Yo, I said I ain't fucking working!
A'ight, yeah, nigga.
Red tops in the Hill is better
than your bullshit
blue tops anyway.
Fuck a Stapleton nigga!
Hey, yo, throw
an extra wing in there,
some of that spicy red shit,
you know what I'm saying?
Make my hair curl
like James Brown!
‐ One dollar more.
‐ Come on, sister Lee.
You know I love you.
You don't love nobody.
‐ What up, son?
‐ Shit just got real.
‐ Hey, this‐‐
this is what you should be
putting your work into.
Fuck the streets, nigga.
Nigga gotta eat.
Ain't making no bread
off of no music, son.
This is a hobby we picked up
in the lobby,
- you know what I mean?
- Hey.
I told you
in Miss Hoover's class.
We gonna make it big.
‐ Get the‐‐look, son.
Niggas is not in third grade.
Come on now.
Hey, yo, this shit crazy, Sha.
What did you say?
Fight, damn it!
You're lucky ain't no one
got hit,
but what'd you expect Power
and Sha was gonna do?
I can't let that shit
slide, Divine.
Look, Dennis.
You know I'd hit Power back
for you,
but we need to leave it alone
for right now.
We only a few grand away
from getting these bricks.
‐ Nah, 'Vine.
Fuck Power.
Fuck that bitch nigga Sha.
Fuck Park Hill.
Fuck all them niggas.
What about our rep?
‐ No, it's better to have
a rep in the streets
than a rep in jail.
‐ Hey, yo, pass the hot sauce,
Look, D, we gonna get
them niggas.
Trust me.
But business is first.
Yeah, them keys are coming
to Staten Island next week.
You know, no more having
to go Uptown
for our re‐up?
‐ Yeah, I heard that.
Well, hear me on this.
We focus on that cream,
then we let off that steam.
I want you and Ason
to do the pick‐ups
and the drop‐offs
with my brother tomorrow.
A'ight?
‐ You gonna finish
that beef and broccoli, yo?
‐ Yeah, nigga, I'm gonna finish
my beef and broccoli.
I'm just saying... you just ate up
all that fucking chicken.
What the fuck you want
beef and broccoli for?
God damn it.
Eat my beef. You done fucked
up my whole appetite.
Nah, nah.
Nah, can't just be about me.
Fighting over
the same dollars...
Yeah, I like that shit.
Yeah.
Bobby, you still here?
Little bro.
Bobby, you're supposed
to be out there doing pickups.
Shit.
Hey, yo, what time is it?
No, never mind all that.
You're so focused
on your records,
you don't even know
what happened last night.
So what happened last night?
Dennis got his crib shot up.
Wait, what?
Yo, is everybody good? Is...
Yo, everyone was lucky.
A'ight, good, good.
Y'all figure anything out?
That track you were just playing...
who's running on it?
It was Sha.
And when'd y'all record that?
A while ago.
Why?
Go do your fucking pickups.
I'm going to bed.
Ooh, I'm telling Mommy!
You need to mind your business.
And make sure
you don't waste them eggs.
But I want Frosted Flakes.
You know better.
No sugar in the morning.
I'll ask Mommy.
She's sleeping
'cause she worked a double.
Do you really wanna wake her up?
Hey, what's going on over here?
Let me see
what this tasting like,
'cause you know
you ain't eating this.
You don't want that.
Hey! ‐ Hey.
Well, you know
Shurrie's the best cook.
‐ - I wish I had me a plate.
- ‐ It's on the stove.
- Thank you.
Y'all hurry up
and get to school, all right?
Y'all gonna be late.
Divine said you already are.
‐ Fuck.
Yo, Power, we gotta hit Dennis
before him and Divine hit us.
He ain't gonna hit us.
Not yet.
That's not Divine's way.
He on his suit‐and‐tie shit.
That nigga want
to be a businessman,
but the problem is, what we do
ain't no fucking business.
Know what I mean? It's a hustle.
‐ What's the difference?
‐ All niggas got
an expiration date.
We ain't here to build no business.
We here to beat the clock,
and you're a fool
if you think otherwise.
‐ We're all out.
‐ Indeed we are.
Where you headed?
‐ Home.
‐ Yo, I got you.
‐ No, I'ma walk it.
Peace.
The uniformed crew members
located on each deck.
‐ So how the fuck y'all know
Sha was with him
in the first place?
I mean, he ain't
the only shooter on P's team.
You know that sneaky bastard be
everywhere with Power. Come on, cousin.
‐ Hey, yo, w‐when the last time
you seen him?
‐ I don't know.
It's been a minute.
‐ Yeah, well, I don't care
if y'all motherfuckers
go all the way back
to eatin' cupcakes
and fucking playing G.I. Joe
and shit.
I'ma peel that nigga's cap back.
It'd be done already if your
brother ain't pumped the brakes.
‐ Enjoy your trip. ‐ Thank you.
You rocking
that fake crown, son.
‐ It's just work shit.
‐ You some old chocolate deluxe‐type
sugarplum yum‐yum mama.
Shit, I'd love to rub your ass
in the moonshine.
When I look into those pretty
eyes, I can read your soul.
Says you're descended
from an Egyptian queen.
‐ All right, come on.
You're holding up my line‐‐
‐ Yo, I'm not leaving
until she give me her number.
Ready to handle this business?
This supposed to be 1,500.
‐ Shit was slow.
I mean, it should pick up
over the weekend.
‐ Come on, son. We ain't got
no time for games, nigga.
Where the fuck the money at?
Where the money at, son?
- Come on, Bobby.
- What's wrong with your man?
‐ Hey, yo.
Bobby D, what it do?
‐ Shit, what up, Shotgun?
‐ Hey, yo, fam,
whatever y'all niggas
is doing here,
you can't be doing that.
This is a place of business.
‐ Yeah, our business.
‐ This ain't Stapleton.
‐ Yo, it ain't Park Hill
either, nigga.
‐ Relax.
‐ Check this out.
I live in Park Hill,
but I'm good everywhere.
I'm not with none of this
petty neighborhood bullshit.
So like I said, y'all got to go.
‐ Yo, who the fuck is you?
‐ Assistant manager.
‐ Yo, a'ight, a'ight, all right.
All right. Hey, chill out.
Hey, Shotgun, let me holler
at you for a minute, a'ight?
Let me talk to you for a minute.
- ‐ Yeah, a'ight.
- Yeah.
Let us just have five minutes.
Laying some new beats.
Just come by the lab
and maybe you can record
some of that heat, nigga.
‐ Lunch break over
in two minutes, man.
‐ Hey, yo, you better have the
rest of that cheese by Sunday.
A'ight?
You gotta stop letting
niggas slide all the time.
Yo, what you buy?
‐ Some pussy!
Hey, yo, she gave me
a few rolls of film for free!
Nigga, you don't even got
a camera, bro.
A man must
attain knowledge of himself
in order to survive here in the
wilderness of North America.
Black people
are the original people
and the fathers of the universe,
and we out here teaching
everything other than our word!
So.
‐ Hey, yo, I can't believe
you let the assistant manager
punk us like that, son.
‐ Yeah, whatever, yo.
‐ Man, whatever? ‐ Yeah.
‐ Your brother need
all his money
if he gonna cop that brick,
know what I mean?
Don't be talking to me
about my brother, yo.
Hey, Bobby!
I'ma catch y'all niggas later, man.
‐ What's up? ‐ Yo, you serious?
Trying to stop
and play games and shit?
Ain't you got Monopoly
at home, nigga?
Yo, I wanna be
the thimble piece.
Hey, yo, chill.
I told y'all niggas
I'ma catch y'all later.
A'ight, son. Yo.
Been a while since I took
your money, youngblood.
‐ You ain't taking nothing
from me today.
A'ight? ‐ Well, well.
Let's get it on.
Yeah.
‐ Yo, homeboy,
let me get a dime bag.
‐ What?
‐ Weed, man.
‐ Hey, wrong homeboy.
Yo, can you believe that shit?
‐ You sure
you ain't that homeboy?
‐ That ain't me.
‐ Who are you, then?
‐ There's stuff I gotta do,
for my family,
but I do be having
other shit on my mind.
‐ Clearly.
‐ I be hearing music in my head
all day long.
And I get lost in that shit.
I love it.
And I get pulled out
'cause of, you know,
business...
‐ Like a splash of cold water
on your face.
‐ Yeah, man.
Something like that.
‐ Well, it's nobody else's job
to chase your dreams for you.
Sounds to me
like you're out here,
doing somebody else's business
and not your own.
Speaking of business.
Checkmate.
- What up, 'Rie?
- Hey.
What up, Ran‐D. M. C.?
Hey.
What happened?
‐ School.
‐ Yeah?
Was somebody messing with you?
You take them out like Mike?
‐ Nah, Shurrie did.
Clotheslined him
like Rowdy Roddy Piper.
The whole schoolyard laughed.
‐ Hell, yeah.
Who is, ‐‐
who's Mom talking to upstairs?
‐ Jerome.
Something about putting
more money on his commissary.
Bobby, is that you?
Yeah.
‐ Well, what do you
expect me to do?
I got my hands full here.
Baby, I need you to hurry
and put my numbers in.
They close in 20 minutes.
Here.
Play, um, Randy's‐‐
‐ Randy's birthday.
Straight.
What about your mother?
Fucking ass over here!
Give me the... where is my shit?
‐ No! No!
Where's my money?
Yo, yo, yo. Chill out.
‐ What the fuck you doing?
Mind your fucking business.
Better watch who the fuck
you talking to, nigga.
Yo, walk that fucking shit off, nigga.
It's okay.
No!
‐ Mother‐‐
Damn it!
Why do I have to go?
Don't make Mommy cry.
It's for the best.
No! No! No! No! No!
‐ Hey, who's that DJ, Kid Capri?
I don't know.
‐ Hey, what is this?
‐ It's an SP‐1200 drum machine
with a built‐in
ten‐second sampler.
This thing never makes
a timing error.
‐ How much?
‐ 2,000 bucks out the door.
I gotta try this shit out.
Yeah, fuck all that, son.
Yo.
Look who decided to show up.
‐ I need to ask you something.
‐ About?
‐ I need an advance.
You come up short on pickups,
and you asking for an advance?
A'ight, so how much?
- ‐ 2,000.
- You're fucking with me.
The fuck you need $2,000 for?
‐ It's for
this new beat machine.
Look, I'm telling you, this
shit is a fucking game‐changer.
I mean, the‐‐
the quality of demos
I can make off of this shit
is fucking...
Hey, yo.
My little brother
needs 2 Gs for a drum machine.
Who got 'em?
Hey, yo, fuck you need
a drum machine for, son?
You got the human beatboxer
right here!
Hey, yo, check it out. Hold on.
Yo, check it.
And all that costs you
is a 40 of Olde E.
- Shit.
- Here comes Jah Son.
This nigga tripping.
- Bobby D, what up?
- Yo, what up, Jah?
‐ Nigga, I just got me
a quarter uptown,
all feeling
like motherfucking Scarface
in this bitch, nigga.
This shit fucking... fucking weigh a ton.
Hey, yo, move your fucking car!
No, they not fucking honking me.
- They wanna play with me?
- Yo!
‐ They wanna fucking play
with me?
Let's show them some fucking
play rough, motherfucker.
Shit, what's good?
Nigga, what's up?
‐ Nigga, I know
this motherfucker.
Damn, I almost blew
your fucking head off, B.
Stop fucking around, nigga.
Seriously, you too, nigga?
Man, you wild, Jah.
You're burning it.
Shurrie, you hear me?
Divine likes his skin crispy.
‐ All right, I'ma be late
for my shift.
‐ Don't forget your purse.
Hey, Mommy.
If you got the rent, I can drop it
off on my way to the Rib Shack.
‐ No, no, I already paid it,
all right?
Wasn't Cross Colours, even.
The nigga Jah Son
came out the whip
like Rainbow Man,
like one of them clowns
in the circus or some shit.
‐ Yo, like, ‐‐like, ‐‐
like Ronald McDonald.
‐ Yeah!
‐ Happy Meal.
‐ All he needed
was the red afro.
You know?
‐ Eat your food.
You save me a plate?
‐ ‐ On the stove.
He was bullying him.
He need to learn how to fight
for himself, don't he?
He gotta learn right now.
Whoo, this is that shit.
Shit.
‐ Turn it off.
‐ Yo.
Yo, why you bugging?
‐ Go finish your homework.
‐ I did already.
‐ Come on.
I'll see y'all. I gotta
get home to my brothers.
I'ma catch ya.
- ‐ All right.
- Later, D.
‐ Kilos are coming
to Staten Island
for the first time in whenever.
Now, you know how long I've been
stacking up my chips for this.
We get our hands
on a whole key and flip it.
Now, that's some life‐changing
shit right there.
‐ Right, so what?
So you flip that shit,
and then you give me the money.
‐ You want more money to buy
your little music machine
or whatever, then bro,
you need to put in work.
‐ I put in work.
‐ No, you‐‐
you put in part‐time.
This work we do‐‐
it's all for family.
Now, you only family part‐time?
Is that what you're saying?
Now, we out there at war
with Power and Park Hill
while you down in the basement
with Gladys Knight.
They tried to wet D.
You think they won't try
and touch you?
‐ I don't know.
I don't roll like D.
‐ Yeah, that's right. You don't.
See, I remember when you and Sha
were shorties,
chewing Bubble Yum together.
That's the only reason I've been
giving that little nigga a pass.
But if he had anything to do
with that move on D,
yeah, it ain't gonna be his bubble
that gets popped. Know what I mean?
‐ Yo, Sha ain't have nothing
to do with that shit.
All right?
Right, we just trying
to make music, yo.
It must be nice to have dreams?
But they ain't real.
This house is real.
That food on your plate,
the money that pays
for all of it,
is real.
‐ Your way ain't
the only way, 'Vine.
‐ You know the other thing
about dreams
is that they're there
for you to wake up from.
You wanna make it in this world?
Then put in the fucking work.
Tomorrow, when I page you,
it's on you to go get the re‐up.
Hey, yo, going to North Carolina
was the worst thing that
could've ever happened to you.
Travel time
is approximately 17 hours...
Thirty minutes...
‐ Bobby?
You remember me?
I'm your Uncle Hollis.
Welcome to your new home.
Where we're at,
you speak when you're spoken to.
You say "yes" and "sir."
Understand?
‐ Yes, sir.
‐ All right.
This is my sister Goldie.
She looks over my properties.
‐ Hello.
Hello, ma'am.
‐ We're happy
to have you, Bobby.
I'ma feed y'all
after I feed the chickens.
‐ Did you brush your teeth?
‐ Yeah‐‐yes, sir.
‐ Turn that off.
Good night, Bobby.
This thing never‐ver‐ver‐‐
never makes a timing error.
Yo, we sold out.
Shit was popping last night.
‐ Yo, that ain't gonna fit, man.
You put it back now, I won't
report you to the manager.
Otherwise, he gonna ban you
from the store.
All right?
I told them niggas,
they need to stay
near their fucking‐‐
their fucking beepers, man.
That's what I fucking told them.
Telling you, if you don't re‐up
in the next 30,
these fiends'll go over
to the Hill
and cop them red tops.
‐ Yo, fucking Bobby
ain't call me back.
Hey, I'ma‐‐I'ma hit D up.
A'ight.
‐ Hey, yo, where Randy at?
‐ At his friend's,
like I told you already.
Come on.
My mom's gonna be home soon!
We don't have much time.
- My...
- Fuck.
Fuck.
‐ Yeah.
- Fuck.
- Yeah.
‐ What's up, baby?
‐ Yo, you seen where D at?
I paged him an hour ago
and he ain't hit me back yet.
Yo, head back to the spot,
a'ight?
‐ You bet.
‐ Hey, you sure you want this
fiend looking after the spot?
‐ Fuck you, old
Grimace‐looking motherfucker.
You know I ain't no fucking fiend.
Okay, nigga.
You can't take
a fucking joke, nigga?
‐ Man, fuck you.
‐ Nigga, it's a fucking joke.
Fucking take it. It's not
a fucking dick, a'ight?
‐ Come on, man. You know I
ain't no fucking fiend.
‐ Hey, maybe so, but you looking
kind of fiendish to me.
Look at him, nigga.
That's a crackhead.
‐ Come on, man. Fuck what
he talking about, man?
Who making the drop,
Bobby or D‐Love?
‐ I'll do it my damn self.
‐ Hey, you want me to
come with you? Nah.
‐ Nigga, sit your ugly ass
down, bro.
Nobody need your shit no more.
Fuck you, Grimace!
‐ Stay off the crack.
Visit your mom, nigga.
I know she fucking miss you.
She told me that shit
last night.
I spoke with Haze, and he said
Cressy and his team
is all set up.
A'ight, Bricks is on the Rock.
‐ Word.
Shit, it sound
like we all good, then.
‐ Yeah, but yo,
I wanna settle
that other problem first,
know what I mean?
I don't want
these Stapleton niggas
making a come‐up.
Hey, fucking Haze is cool
with Divine,
so I'm assuming he'll be
setting up business with him.
Where you stash the TEC?
‐ The chick house. She good.
‐ Go on and get that back.
I want Dennis in the ground by
the end of the week, my nigga.
A'ight? Take these
niggas' strength away.
‐ Shit.
Fuck.
Shit.
‐ Sheba, stay.
‐ I thought Bobby was coming.
‐ No, instead you got me.
‐ Okay.
Yo, you got this
for you little brother
but you can't hook me up
with one, too?
‐ No, I gotta go.
‐ Yo, let me hit it again.
Your bonbons still hard.
‐ Get out of here. ‐
‐ Yo, Shurrie‐‐
‐ My mom gonna be home soon.
‐ Come on.
Okay. Okay!
All right, I'll see you later.
‐ Bye.
‐ For real?
‐ Nia, I'll be right back.
‐ You promise?
‐ Yeah, yeah, sure, dear.
I promise.
Okay.
If New Jersey
would've won that boat race,
then this rock
we call Staten Island
would be a part of New Jersey,
and all the micks from Bayonne
would've moved in here,
and that's a fact.
Hey, Cocoa Puff!
Get the hell out of here!
I catch you playing
with that again,
I'm gonna break
your little fingers!
How do you expect them
to learn that way?
‐ When are you gonna learn
to listen to your doctor,
quit smoking?
‐ Yeah, yeah. Hello, yeah.
Yeah, she's here. Yeah, hold on.
‐ Hello?
Divine, baby.
You okay?
‐ Yeah, Mom. I'm okay.
Yeah.
Put Bobby on.
‐ Divine, I'm sorry, man.
I was‐‐I was just trying to‐‐
There ain't no time for that.
Yo, you and D
can apologize to me
after you get me out of here.
All right, well,
your bail is 250,
and we still gotta get that 10%.
You know, Ma's trying
to get you a lawyer, so‐‐
No, we can't afford to have our
cream tied up in the system
or with no lawyer.
Now, we need to use that money
on that cake.
You know what I'm saying?
‐ Yeah, but we‐‐
we gotta get you out.
No, we need a roof over our head
and food on our table first,
so don't talk to me
about bail or no lawyer.
You need to put that money
to work.
You, Bobby.
You need to do that,
or we ain't gonna have no house.
We ain't gonna have nothing.
You gotta be the man now,
whether you like it or not.
A'ight?
‐ Yeah.
Yeah, I hear you.
‐ Yo, money,
Dougie Fresh time in here.
Six minutes and off.
Hang it the fuck up!
‐ Hey, yo.
Put D on.
‐ Yo.
‐ Yo, fam, you good?
Them BK niggas
trying to press hard?
- It is what it is.
- Listen,
we continue with the movement.
Fl‐zip that cake fast,
and then we can talk
about b‐zail.
Six minutes is up.
‐ Yeah, my brother
can have his head
up in the clouds,
so I'ma need you
to be my boots on the ground.
You know what I mean?
- ‐ Word is bond.
- A'ight.
‐ Six minutes is up, Staten!
‐ Yo, 'Vine.
Yo, 'Vine.
‐ What's happening?
‐ Yo.
'Vine. What's
happening to my baby?
‐ 'Vine.
‐ What's happening to my baby?
No, please, Auntie, no!
Are you gonna forget
to turn the lights off
in your room?
‐ No, ma'am!
No, please, Auntie, no!
That's right.
Now, what's this I hear
about you keeping
the light on all night?
Goldie sleeps
with the window open,
and those mosquitoes
be feasting on her.
‐ There's demons in my room.
They be there in the dark.
‐ Okay, no more horror movies
for you.
‐ If God made light,
why does darkness still exist?
‐ Actually, Bobby,
light is always shining.
It's just that we turn ourselves
away from it
and end up in the shadow
of something that blocks
the light.
Sometimes, it's our own shadows.
Look around the room, Bobby.
Y‐you see the bookcase?
‐ Yes, sir.
‐ See the closet? ‐ ‐
‐ What's in the dark
is also in the light.
It's just your perception
that changes.
See?
Everything the same.
‐ So the demon in my closet
was just my imagination?
Yep.
The largest nation
is the imagination.
It can be your greatest enemy,
but if you have control of it
and you understand
how to use it,
it becomes your greatest weapon.
‐ You're saying
your imagination
is like a superpower.
Well, that's one way to put it.
Now, get you some rest.
‐ Yes, sir.
Boo!
‐ HOLLIS: Good night, Bobby.
‐ Night, Uncle Hollis.
Love you!
Can't believe 'Vine
gotta do a bid
right before the keys are finally
coming to Staten Island.
‐ Hey, stop saying that shit.
He might get off.
‐ Yo, with what he had on him?
Ain't no way he walking,
unless he snitching,
and Vine ain't no snitch.
Hey, yo, h‐how many years
you think he gonna get?
I don't know!
I look like a fucking lawyer?
Use your imagination, nigga.
Hey, yo, it coulda been
me or you that got picked up.
‐ Maybe.
Maybe, or if me and you
were around,
no one would've got bagged.
‐ Hey, yo, when y'all get this?
‐ Shit, yo.
That's...
I be having that for a minute.
‐ From where?
‐ My cousin Gary's man
out in Brooklyn.
Repo man was coming for his car,
so I got it for cheap.
And you ain't never
shown me this shit, son?
This shit fire!
‐ Yeah.
Let me see that shit, nigga.
‐ Nah.
This exactly
what I been needing.
‐ For what?
‐ To hit back at Power
and your boy Sha.
‐ I thought Divine said
to deck that shit.
Well, 'Vine ain't here
right now, is he?
We in charge,
and the first order of business
is we getting them niggas back.
Attempt to fan our rivalry!
I don't give a damn.
‐ So you do want us
to kill each other.
‐ That's right.
I want you to fight
till one of you dies.
Take you on
this lyrical high real quick.
1993 exoticness.
Know what I'm saying?
Let's get technical.
Where's your bone at?
Get up on that shit, a'ight?
Get on the line.
It's Staten Island...
Against the world.
I told you, Bobby, you got
to step up and make decisions.
We in charge now.
‐ When there's a war in the
streets, nobody makes money.
‐ But when that war is over,
it's winner take all.
‐ Truth.
When y'all gonna start
making more music together?
‐ Nah, I'm good.
‐ He shot at my crib where
my moms and my brothers stay.
When I catch up with Sha...
‐ You got Divine's bail?
‐ We don't have enough yet.
‐ Where you been at lately?
Hey, yo, I'm out here
putting in work.
‐ What would Bobby think?
‐ You want to tell him?
‐ Yo, battle on the island, son.
The winner
of the battle gets $5,000?
‐ Let the battle begin.
- Here we are again...
- ‐
Another mother's son
has been taken from us.
‐ I'm sick of this. ‐ What?
You got to tell her.
You can't just be trifling with it.
You're looking at 20 years.
‐ It's not just you up in here.
It's us.
I'm gonna step it up, Ma.
‐ You control your fate.
‐ Them tapes swarming in the
hood like killer bees and shit.
‐ Damn, son.
Put on a good show. It doesn't
matter if there's two people today.
Tomorrow there's gonna be 200
and then 2,000.
We coming together.
‐ Wu‐Tang sword style. ‐
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6ynuf
Help other users to choose the best subtitles