Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
This day wasn't
particularly a good one for him.
He was 10 minutes late for the train,
and as a result, he had
to take the next one
that left an hour later.
The schedule that he had
meticulously planned for the day
fell to the wayside, but
it didn't matter to him.
He knew that if he had to live his life
by times and rhythms, that
he could never achieve
what it was that he wanted.
At least, not in any satisfactory way
that he could wake up the next day
and felt that he had
achieved enough to move on.
He nevertheless had achieved
what he had wanted that day,
and felt that he could
take a breath and sit.
Tomorrow was another day, and the dread of
and responsibilities of tomorrow
would keep him up this night.
This day was very different for him.
He vowed every night that
he would change his ways.
He told himself this every night,
and truly believed that he could change.
Yes, he wanted to change,
he wanted to be different.
- You like that, don't you?
Love those old-fashioned tape machines.
We don't sell much of those anymore.
I gotta be honest with you, you know,
it's all landfill now,
those old tape machines.
- My baby.
- The other advantage
is jerkin' off to porn,
you know the digital
stuff runs a little fast.
I've still got my old VHS
stash to jerk off to.
You interested?
- Yeah, yeah, I'll take it.
- Cool, 150 bucks.
But the impulse was too strong
that it overtook him.
Once he had crossed that
line, there was no going back.
He had done this before,
but day 11 was different.
Day 11 was significant
because he had felt something
for her, something genuine.
He remembered how he first met her.
This was the decision that
would change his life forever.
That's an old one, isn't it?
- Yeah.
That's tape, right?
You know, like Betamax or VHS?
- Yeah.
- My dad has stacks and
decks sitting in his closet.
Hasn't used it in many years.
He has a lotta cool stuff.
I used to see his tapes
scattered on the floor.
- You still close to your dad?
- Yeah.
Yeah, he's saved me a lotta times.
No!
- Saved?
- You know.
How old are you?
- 17.
Well, I don't mean he saved me like Jesus.
I just mean that
when I fell down during times,
you know, like difficult
times in the past?
- But you're only 17.
- And?
Well.
My father's been the only
one I can look up to.
He has saved me, he has rescued me.
I have no faith in anyone else.
My friends are all backstabbers.
- So you don't have real friends?
- Real?
No.
- Nobody you can count on then?
- I give too much,
and they let me down.
- How does that make you feel?
- How would you feel if
your bestie fucked your BF
and didn't give a shit about you?
- Yeah.
Now, a friend is someone you
can just confess things to.
Like, I can say I want to kill my mom,
or fuck my brother, and that's that.
It's like I can't say
anything to anyone anymore,
and I don't even have any feelings.
My friends reject me because
I don't go to church.
Sometimes I wish I could just
fly away.
Brandon knew he had found her.
- I beg you.
Why are you doing this?
No, don't do that.
Please.
Stop!
- Your dad, he isn't doing too well.
- You spoke to him?
- He called from Memphis.
I guess all that drinking and
binging finally got to him,
the bastard.
He needs dialysis.
That's the least of it.
He asked about you.
He hopes you find something to do,
something on your own,
without me enabling you.
He says you're a failure,
and you need to accept that.
And do something.
Hey, you.
Hey.
So my mom,
she's such a fucking bitch, you know?
It's just this disconnection.
I don't think she
understands anything anymore.
I'm doing the best I can, you know?
- Yeah.
I don't have any friends.
I just need
someone to talk to some time.
I don't have anyone.
- Yeah, I know.
- Yeah, I don't think Mom wants
me to finish school at all.
I don't think she wants me to stay here.
Dressed like as a fucking
whore, all her life.
I don't know what she
sees in those track guys.
- Track guys?
- You know, the guys
that run in their shorts
for miles and miles.
I don't really know
the point of it anyway,
to run all those miles and
wear off your body like that,
yeah, only to say you're the winner.
Like, what is winning anyway?
I won, well, I sorta won
the spelling bee one year.
I was second place.
They gave me a plaque.
I don't even know where it is anymore.
Mom wasn't really proud of it.
She said the judges cheated
and that Chinese girl
from Monrovia should have won.
She didn't like that I had won.
Hmm.
Jesse's texting me now,
wants to know where I am.
Wanna be at that star there.
That star
is the furthest one away.
- Mm-mm.
That's the closest one.
Furthest one is the big one right there.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Huh.
- I mean, why be far away when
you can be close by, right?
Kinda skip everything, you know?
♪ Once upon a time,
there was a man I knew ♪
♪ Used to be a servant
in the land we grew ♪
♪ Then the evil ego came
and changed his tune ♪
♪ Now he's evil too, now he's evil too ♪
- What do you mean?
Like, I can't escape
from my shitty parents?
♪ There is somethin' that I gotta say ♪
♪ From my head to my mouth
to my knees and toes ♪
♪ This is somethin' that you gotta know ♪
Off me!
♪ I don't really like you ♪
♪ You really like yourself though ♪
- Anyway.
We'll all die.
- Die?
- We just all die.
You know, like really die?
♪ This world is under your rule ♪
♪ Down, Mr. Evil Ego, down, Mr. Evil Ego ♪
♪ I've been thinkin' lately ♪
♪ You're actin' kinda crazy ♪
♪ A silver-corked baby ♪
♪ Down, Mr. Evil Ego, down, Mr. Evil Ego ♪
♪ If I wanted somethin',
I would let you know ♪
♪ The king of the castle
in the town we've grown ♪
♪ I'm not sure who voted,
but it's time to go ♪
♪ Time to go, time to go ♪
♪ Take what I'm about to do lightly ♪
♪ But there's somethin' that I gotta say ♪
♪ From my head to my mouth
to my knees and toes ♪
♪ This is somethin' that you gotta know ♪
♪ I don't really like you ♪
- Shit.
Dahlia, I wanted to call you.
It's been too long.
I know I should have reached out sooner
but this week has been incredibly insane.
You have no idea.
I wonder, how's Ophelia doing?
I miss her, is she okay?
How are her grades?
Is she eating okay?
I know, I'm asking too many questions.
I'm really sorry, my dear.
I love you, you know that.
I don't know.
Do you think that we could
attempt to be together again,
at least for Ophelia?
Maybe we can make it work out.
My job's promoting
me to a big case now,
and things will be better financially.
I've amassed quite a bit of savings,
so no more excess anymore, my love.
I just wonder
if we could give this another chance.
After all we've been through.
Come on, man!
Why don't you do a seizure for once?
Shut up!
- Well, well, well,
look what we have here.
- Right, nice, that'll buy you
a few years, won't it, huh?
All the evidence we need.
Shut up!
Keep gettin' him.
Fuck you, cock sucker!
Fuck you!
Hey, hey!
- Yeah, fuck you.
Bugger off, wanker!
I said shut up!
- Who are you calling a wanker?
- Detective, here's your papers.
Is there anything else you need?
- No, that's great, thank you, Samantha.
- How's your boyfriend?
- Good.
This is a new prototype.
Even the gangs and the Chinese
haven't been able to get
ahold of this one yet.
Pretty soon, we'll be using these on duty.
- Come off it, Tim, really?
- Yeah, anything's possible, isn't it?
I mean, would you have predicted
any of this that's happened,
cars that drive themselves,
phones that know what you wanna eat next,
what music you're gonna listen to?
Guess no real reason for
any of us to exist, right?
I can't even predict this kinda thing.
That's great.
- It was really catching
that pervert last week.
- Which one?
- The woods are lovely, dark and deep,
but I have promises to keep
and miles to go before I sleep.
- The wood are lovely,
dark and deep.
And I have promise to keep.
- These woods are lovely, dark and deep.
And miles before.
- It's over, you're caught.
It's over!
You know the crank caller,
the one jerkin' off over the phone
and blind-calling in girls.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Where were you on the night of April 13th?
- I told you, I was in bed, sleeping.
- Right, and somebody
can corroborate this?
Yes.
- You killed John Gaines.
We have three key witnesses
who saw you rob that liquor store,
and kill this guy in cold-blooded murder
when it all went wrong.
- It wasn't me.
- It wasn't you.
You piece of shit.
- Poor girl.
Coroner thinks it may have only
taken her two hours to die.
With all the markings on her throat,
there were at least a dozen
attempts to strangle her.
My guess is two hours
for it to all go down.
- This is a terrible situation.
- It is.
- Not yet.
Not yet.
You're quiet today.
I'm leaving this town.
Next week, in fact.
No, I did not find religion,
but I'm just turning a new leaf.
I'm moving back up to my mom's in Oregon.
I'm going to start a jewelry business.
Oh, no need to be so heartbroken.
There is a very special girl,
very special, and she will
take my place, you know?
It's not like I'm leaving forever.
It's just a thousand miles away.
I'll come visit you.
I have a four p.m. client, I
think you should leave now.
Dahlia, day 289.
Without you, it's not the same.
I've begun writing again.
Well, not actually writing.
I've been keeping a journal,
but it's a journal based on
my recollections and dates.
For example, and I know
I have the date wrong,
but do you remember the
time you slapped me?
I have it written down in my journal
as occurring on June 16th.
You'll need to correct me
if I'm wrong about this,
but I remember distinctly that the 15th
was a Sunday that year,
and Monday's paper, I went
to fetch that morning,
and then you slapped me that evening.
It didn't hurt, but I
was stunned for sure.
I'd never seen you as physical
as you were that night.
The force of your hand, there
could have been nothing more.
♪ I stand beneath ♪
♪ Your sun, your moon ♪
♪ The night will pass ♪
♪ My darling ♪
- Not too hard.
♪ Though while those sparks ♪
♪ The flame stands still ♪
♪ The chase you doubt ♪
♪ Don't kill ♪
♪ The grass is crying ♪
- Okay.
♪ The bright shade ♪
♪ Of your bluest light ♪
♪ You say everything, everything ♪
♪ Everything is perfect ♪
♪ Everything, everything ♪
♪ Everything's fine ♪
♪ You say everything, everything ♪
♪ Everything's just perfect ♪
♪ Everything, everything ♪
♪ Everything's fine ♪
♪ From day to day ♪
♪ I see it more ♪
♪ Up in the clouds ♪
♪ Down on the floor ♪
♪ How fleeting was ♪
♪ What we once had ♪
♪ Our tears, the rain ♪
♪ Your pain ♪
- We've been talking about your fears,
what it is that's troubling you,
and how we can get to the bottom
where the root of what's causing
this imbalance you're experiencing.
- So, there's this girl,
this incredible girl.
- How old is she?
- 21, maybe 25.
She seems to know how to play
older when she needs to be.
- You mentioned she was murdered.
But isn't murder part of our DNA now?
We've discussed all of this yesterday,
we've been over all of this.
Anything else you wanna tell me?
For one brief moment,
no matter how much we fought,
no matter how much we hated each other...
Yes!
Pass out, baby.
No matter how much
we wanted to kill each other.
Motherfucker, you!
You motherfucker!
The one brief moment,
that one moment when hate turned to love,
it was fleeting, but it was there.
- So, I'm gonna see you tomorrow, right?
You're not seriously thinking
about going back out there
and finding that whole
lolita crowd again, are you?
Because you cannot, Robert,
not anymore, it's dangerous.
Oh, my God, you are!
You're contemplating
jeopardizing everything
and going back out there, aren't you?
You can't, do you understand me?
Like, no fucking way can't.
- Stephanie, I must do...
- You must.
You psycho.
Yes, yes.
Pass out.
Yes!
What was the first thing you felt?
The room became darker,
like watching the lights go down
as the theater program begins.
And do you
remember when you blacked out?
No, it was
like a switch turned off.
No, more like a fade.
It just dimmed out.
What do you
remember when you woke?
I remember
this intense euphoria.
You got it, baby.
No one ever experiences
that the first time.
I'm so impressed you got to that level.
The mind needs to be there
to bring us to full realization.
Day 335.
Dahlia, I need you.
Nothing seems to make sense anymore.
I wake up and don't want to wake up
unless you're next to me.
The coffee I make in the
morning isn't even the same.
I can't smell you as I
shower in the morning.
Time just seems to pass by in its own
fleeting butterfly-ous way,
and I can't catch on to it.
I can't grasp it in any
way that's meaningful.
And I've been making the wrong choices.
I can't stand what I've become.
Timothy, I know you still
get a thrill out of this all,
but I'm gonna call it quits soon.
- You will, for what?
After being nice guys for so many years?
We busted our asses all these years,
did everything above the board,
only so those fucks could get promotions
for the cases that we solved.
I have no regrets in
what we're doing, Robert.
- Well, it's just enough for me.
If there ever was a thrill,
there isn't one anymore.
- What are you gonna do,
go after your winery then?
Assuming they give you
a good enough pension
if you stick it out long enough.
What if I became
the good guy for once?
Good luck, pal.
Can't change a horse's stripes.
- They're zebras.
- Same difference.
The zebra is a horse,
or whatever they say.
We're in too deep, buddy, and you know it.
You have to play this out.
You.
- Okay, we if that makes
you feel any better.
Stakes are high, you just
gotta roll with it, baby.
So I think I found her.
Oh?
I was at the coffee place
ordering my usual black chai,
and then I saw her.
Same eyes as your girl,
same facial structures.
It's crazy, the resemblance, uncanny.
Her face was like porcelain,
like those antique porcelain dolls.
Her eyes dark, deep blue,
just like your girl's.
So what did you do.
I was literally
frozen, I couldn't move.
I wanted to walk up to her,
but I just couldn't
believe the resemblance.
We spoke.
She admitted she made some
wrong choices early on,
and was just looking to get
back on track with her life.
She's broke, as you might have guessed.
That's where you come
in, if you wanna do this.
Okay.
- I saw you.
And, well, you were alone, so.
I was alone too, and well,
I was hoping to talk to you
because I was alone too.
I just said that, didn't I?
- Yes, you did.
- Yeah.
- You could really
benefit from my sessions.
Here.
Call me.
Are you hesitating?
She said she's done this
type of thing before.
You're sure?
Baby, look me in the eye.
Tell me you don't trust me after all
that we've been through.
I don't think you're going to
believe what you see, baby.
It's almost like she came
to us from another world
or something because
they knew we wanted her,
like some cosmic gift.
Oh, we sound like sci-fi nuts now.
Well, at least I do.
Anyway.
I don't know what
I'm doing anymore, Stephanie.
Robert, it's
too late for this now.
From the moment you
stepped into my office,
I knew that we'd get to this level, baby.
We said every step of the
way, no matter how hard
or how fucked up it was going to be,
we said we could and would just move on.
Am I right?
Do you remember this at all?
Or do you only remember the fucking?
There's no regrets, understand?
Do you understand me, baby?
Baby, are you there?
Yes.
If you like her,
then she must come to
Stanton's teachings next week.
Oh, give her 500 bucks, please.
She needs rent money.
Where's she staying?
Do you really wanna know?
I guess not.
- A lot of what you experience in life
is completely related
and directly inherent
to these preconceived notions
that we have about our lives.
how to live it.
How much of it do you live?
How much are you willing
to live and not hold back
and accept the energy of all
of these incoming forces?
Therefore, we like to stress
that this will be a highly individual
and personal experience for you,
'cause it takes time, it
takes years of living life,
perhaps, to be in full balance,
to experience the ultimate,
the right mindset,
the right body, touch your nerves.
Touch them.
We're all circuit.
Feel it!
Feel yourselves.
Feel the physical.
Feel the emotional.
But what is emotion?
Because what we think, it's
psychological, isn't it?
And this psychological force, this energy,
these cosmic lines
combine and are created
by a physical entity,
a brain,
a goddamn brain!
- We are late.
- I'm sorry.
- We are already conscious
above what they already know.
And we strive to go to places
with our physical bodies
where are physical bodies cannot go,
unless we are one, one with the universe.
Love is the answer.
Love is one continuous
endless dream.
Everyone needs love.
Movement number one, raise your hands.
Raise them.
Higher.
Higher still.
Reach for the sky.
Movement number two.
- I don't think I can do this.
- The mind blocks us,
but there will always
be a metaphysical path.
The mind knows.
Our perceptions of reality
are based upon what we see
and what we read.
But what about feelings?
Feelings is truthful
and do not let them dictate
to you what you feel.
Four!
Feelings are your own experience,
and you take with it
whatever is inside of you.
4.5!
All these molecules that are
trying to insert themselves
into you and bang you all to hell...
- I know I know can do it.
- Five!
- Please!
- I ask you, you have the right afterwards
to morph with that.
Six!
I can!
- Reject that cosmic sperm if you choose,
and be whatever it is
you want to be.
The moment she
picked up the vial, she knew.
The crystals melted into her hand
as if they had existed for centuries.
A single salt crystal, a grain harvested
as far as the beginning of time,
what was the basis of life and of love.
♪ It's early in love and ♪
♪ Watch the sunrise ♪
♪ The crystals in the air ♪
♪ The poison in the spring ♪
It's hard to tell.
♪ Revolutions falling ♪
♪ We don't hear a thing ♪
♪ Everything you wanted ♪
You bit me.
What is wrong with you?
♪ Hell is in the hallway ♪
♪ What were you looking for ♪
- So,
my fucking mom hates me.
Says she'll kick the
shit out of me to Hades
if she finds out I'm doin' somethin'
she don't want me to do.
But I want her to.
♪ I still remember ♪
♪ The night that we hit it off ♪
♪ I was going crazy when we charged you ♪
♪ With arson to the room ♪
♪ Only you go to a show ♪
♪ In a skirt of silver sequins ♪
♪ The whole room felt the
heat when you walked in ♪
♪ So you pick up your thoughts ♪
- What?
♪ Try to call up your friends
as I say, hey there, girl ♪
♪ Let it go to message ♪
♪ Hello, I'm not in ♪
♪ Baby, take me out to the discotheque ♪
♪ Down where we go to party
and we're dressed to impress ♪
♪ All the boys and girls
on the dance floor ♪
♪ I was down on my knees, tryin' so hard ♪
♪ When I met you ♪
♪ La ♪
- You know, like, two
years ago at my school.
And screw those mothers.
But my school changed their lunch menu
for all the popular
people, like James Steven
and Linda Kendall.
- They changed the lunch
menu 'cause of popular kids?
- Yeah, you can change a lunch menu.
Well, for the elite few, you know,
the real ones in the know,
we were able to special
order in the morning.
You know, like tell the
teacher in the morning
you didn't want what
everyone else was having,
like the penis dogs.
- What's a penis dog?
- You know, it's like a corn dog,
breaded corn dog?
- What's a breaded corn dog?
- Yeah, it's like the
penis is in the middle
and the breading's the condom!
Well, anyway, when it came
time for us to go to our lunch,
well, we lesbies went
off to the annex portion
of the building where
we'd eat our sub sandwich
and chicken salad.
But hear me out here.
So, since only a handful of
us were sent to the annex
to have lunch while the rest of those
Mr. and Mrs. Populars went
off to main cafeteria,
we on the other side were queens.
I remember that V, Veronica,
always tasted like chapstick,
but she had the most amazing lips.
It always matched room
temperature, as I recall.
Meanwhile, Haley was a cold fish.
We had good lunches.
Kinda wish I was back in school again.
Least I had a place to go
to every day at 12:30 p.m.
I don't even know where to go to now.
Mom's such a mess.
♪ Don't you sit there, baby ♪
♪ Come and pet my body ♪
♪ 'Cause my feelings go in ♪
♪ Well, now climb my mountain ♪
♪ Rock me ♪
♪ Put my favorite song on ♪
♪ Got all my senses ♪
♪ Be my refuge I love, yes, yes ♪
♪ You chose my station ♪
♪ Now we are surfin' the
channels, fast forward ♪
♪ With all your forces ♪
♪ You might receive
every motion, yes, yes ♪
♪ Nothing's the matter ♪
♪ We are climbing the ladders, baby ♪
♪ Mixing the colors, we
never thought we'd fly ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ Leavin', oh ♪
♪ It's better for you ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ Leavin', oh ♪
♪ Just as I would ♪
♪ Free, free from pain ♪
♪ Free your mind ♪
- On the street that I
live, well, years ago,
there was this ice cream truck
that used to come by our house.
And you could hear the chimes, the melody,
it goes so far, far away.
I remember that feeling, you know,
like the anticipation
of what it all meant.
Before I knew it, my brother and I
were at the front of the truck,
'cause it arrived at our house.
Sometimes it came by too quickly though,
and the satisfaction wasn't quite there.
Like, you know when you were
wanting something so bad
that the build-up is
the best thing about it,
and the actual feeling
in the end isn't as much?
You know what I mean?
Like, it wasn't the orgasm you
thought you were building up.
Like it was a letdown.
I wish I could...
I wish I could just shut up.
- Say it, whore, say it!
Get motherfuckin' whore money!
I earned every goddamned dollar
of my fuckin' life honestly!
Never in my life, never think
my daughter would be a whore,
a cock-suckin' whore!
Whore, say it, say it!
Motherfuckin' whore!
Never in my life!
Daughter does this to me!
Never in my life would I think
my daughter would be a whore.
Cock-sucking, common, drinkin' whore!
- It didn't really hurt.
I don't know if it's
that I'm just used to it,
or that I got stronger,
or tolerant,
or numb.
I still feel,
I feel you still.
Know what I mean?
It's like that guy on TV,
that Indian guy that
says you can conquer all,
your pain, your everything that hurts you,
ails you, bothers you, and
with one push on your head
with his hand, you are
cured and you feel nothing.
Give me a countdown.
- What?
- Give me a countdown.
You know, like 10, nine, eight.
- Okay, 10, nine, eight.
- No.
Not so fast.
Do it slow, please.
- 10,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five,
four,
three.
- Say it, please.
T-t-t-two.
- Two.
- Say it!
One.
What he wanted to say then,
he clearly couldn't say.
He couldn't even form the
words that would describe
what would become an incredible hatred.
Not a hatred directly against her,
but for whoever made her
become what she became.
He called these the
horrible, the awful elements,
the ones that would ruin everything.
But the forces who could
take anything that was good,
anything that ever meant
anything meaningful and good,
good he kept seeing, and
then just ruin it all,
just ruin the happiness,
and that's all whatever the
forces that he had reckoned
and struggled with.
These were the ones ruining his happiness,
and so the rest had to go.
But he was very humble.
He never stole anyone's happiness.
He was only selfish to a point.
But he said "thank you" whenever he felt
he had received the correct
service at a diner, for example.
And even though he didn't
really show his appreciation
to any man or god, he felt the reverence.
Time seemed to stand still for Brandon
and operated at a slow crawl, increments,
decibels, micro ions.
He didn't know what it all meant.
For Jeanie, it was the start of a life.
And for Brandon, while
it had the joy of a life,
the beauty, while it
all stood still for him
whenever he was with Jeanie, it just ended
when she came to his world,
because she hadn't come from there.
She was a gift, as
Stephanie had told Robert,
but the gift was actually
meant for Brandon.
He'd waited all his life for
someone who would look at him,
just acknowledge his existence.
He never knew when the
person he was next to
knew if he was even there.
He just wanted to know he was there,
and Jeanie told him he was there.
Hi, it's me, leave a message.
- Day 301.
It's a big number, isn't it?
I thought about the
first time we went out,
and me being crazy when I was back then,
I asked you out for a midnight date,
and you accepted, to my surprise.
Do you remember that?
No, you looked so beautiful.
You didn't say a single word,
but I knew it in your eyes.
You really believed in me.
I could see the love.
I saw your smile.
It was late and you had no makeup on,
and I saw you.
You, that's what I
remember of you the most.
I just don't want to lose those memories.
Now I don't even know if
you have them anymore.
Was I there?
I don't even know if it
was, but I know I saw you.
You existed and you were there for me.
And I, I was a...
For Brandon, it was easy.
He knew who did it, who corrupted Jeanie.
This elite group, they
controlled everything,
the media, banks, state
parks, commercial real estate,
ecology, the environment, technology,
and everything that he had ever missed.
It wasn't even intuition,
because Brandon knew.
He had felt this woman,
the woman who had destroyed
every feeling he had
ever felt in his life,
a woman so selfish, so
absorbed, so charmed
with the immediacy of
being accepted by anyone,
even the homeless, wig-less, thief scumbag
taking a shit on the curb.
His acceptance meant everything to her.
It was obvious the way
Stephanie had corrupted Jeanie.
She had done it so expertly.
- So today, we're gonna start
with the basic principles
of what we're trying to achieve.
And by that, I mean we're
going to try to blend
the metaphysical with the physical,
and that way, we can get
to that level of euphoria
that's so important for mental health.
- Cool.
- So we're gonna begin
with the basics.
- Okay.
- Just sit up straight with me.
And we're gonna start by
facing our thumbs together.
Beautiful, and now you're just
gonna wrap around your neck,
and just, I like to kinda ease into it.
Beautiful.
And now we're gonna find
that beautiful sweet spot.
You got it.
Why again, Steph?
Haven't you learned by now it's
not about being insatiable?
You want too much, and
now you're using others
to do it for you.
Don't sacrifice this girl, please.
She's young, she's innocent.
Just let her live her life for once.
Let her find love,
disappointment, let her live.
Will you give her a chance?
I see her eyes, her eyes
show that she has a chance,
unlike the others.
How do you feel?
- Good.
- There you go, perfect.
Yes.
A little more.
Oh, yes, yes!
Yes!
There you go.
Yes.
You got this.
♪ All give or take till I carry the pain ♪
♪ Your walls between us keep me far away ♪
♪ There's no way back ♪
♪ Your heart is full of bricks ♪
♪ I'm trying to move on ♪
♪ Raise my head to the horizon ♪
♪ Wanna know what's to come ♪
♪ I'm scared to be alone ♪
♪ Stuck at the same
place that we've been ♪
♪ But I cannot get out ♪
♪ Doors open, doors
close in my heart again ♪
- So, who did you say
recommended me to you again?
- Jeanie.
- Right, Jeanie.
I saw you after hours
because of her referral.
I don't normally do that.
Brandon, I can only help
you if you talk to me.
Why did you contact me?
What is troubling you that was so urgent?
How is Jeanie?
Is there something you want
to tell me about Jeanie?
Are you in a relationship with her?
- Like a little sister.
- She's like a little sister.
That's all she is to you, a little sister?
You seem to be upset about
something relating to Jeanie.
- I lost somebody.
- Did something happen
to Jeanie because of you?
- No, no, I'm.
- I can't hear you, what did you say?
Brandon, you have to talk
to me for me to help you.
Did something happen to Jeanie?
We've already gone over the hour allotted,
and I don't think I'm helping you
because you're not telling me anything
to give me a chance to help you.
Brandon, I don't think I can help you.
I think you need to call
a different therapist.
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
- No.
- It's getting late.
- Sit the fuck down!
- There's no need to get upset.
You can tell me what's bothering you.
That's what I do, that's
what I can do for you.
I can help you get through this,
but you have to talk to me.
All right, now this is starting to make me
feel a little uncomfortable.
I have to go.
I really mean it...
- Sit down.
- It's time to go, I
really want you to go.
- Sit the fuck down!
You sit and stay the fuck right there!
- All right, I'm staying.
Okay.
- But I want you to leave.
I want you to get the help you need,
and I don't think I can do that.
- No, start.
- Please leave.
No!
Where is she now?
You know.
I'm so sorry.
You did it nicely?
No.
♪ Mountains towering again ♪
♪ In your mind ♪
♪ Aren't they the hardest ones to climb ♪
♪ Darling, look how far we've come ♪
♪ Simply by taking ♪
♪ It one step at a time ♪
♪ Oh, I want you to know ♪
♪ You're not in this on your own ♪
♪ Oh, because darlin' ♪
♪ I would never let you go ♪
♪ Oh, and I'm willing to lose ♪
♪ Anything if I have you ♪
♪ Darling, no matter what it takes ♪
♪ We'll make it through ♪
♪ No matter what it takes, we'll make it ♪
♪ I don't have many fancy things ♪
♪ To my name ♪
♪ Aren't they fleeting anyway ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org