Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Subtitles by explosiveskull & EVO
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hello?
Nai Nai, hi!
Billi!
It's the middle of the night,
why aren't you sleeping?
Sleeping? I'm only 12 hours ahead!
Isn't it 7AM in China?
It's almost 7:30!
Is it cold there?
Are you wearing enough?
Are you wearing a hat?
I'm wearing one.
Don't worry about me, Nai Nai!
You have to be careful.
I read that...
in New York, people
will steal your earrings.
They'll rip them out!
And then you have to go to
the hospital for surgery.
I'm not wearing earrings.
Ah. So you heard too.
What's that sound?
Where are you?
I'm at your great aunt's house.
What are you doing?
I'm going to Mom and Dad's...
Do you have a second to save marine life?
Hold on a second, Nai Nai.
Alright.
I was gonna say something snarky, but...
I used to work this job.
Ooh, what happened girl? You got fired?
I quit!
Because I was about to get fired.
Who was that, Billi?
Uh, no one, just a friend.
What's that?
It's nothing.
I'll call you back later, OK?
OK.
Yeah, call me back, Nai Nai...
Nai Nai?
Where's my sister?
She's with the doctor.
OK Sis. Let's go.
Did you talk to the doctor?
Yep. You're in full health.
Really?
What about the CT scan?
What about the spots they saw before?
It's all clear.
Turned out to be nothing.
They're just benign shadows.
Benign shadows? What's that mean?
That's just what the doctor said.
You're fine. Let's go, Sis.
So one day the wife goes out of town.
And when she returns, the husband says...
honey, the cat is dead.
And she says "How can you
tell me so abruptly like this?"
You have to ease me into bad news."
Like honey...
the cat, he got on the roof.
So...
now...
a few months later the
wife goes out of town again.
And she returns, and the
husband greets her again.
But this time he learned his lesson.
And as the wife comes
through the door he says,
"Honey, your mom, she got on the roof."
How did you get in here?
- Nai Nai?
- Billi!
I'm sorry I hung up earlier.
It's OK. What happened?
Nothing. I'm good.
You're spilling.
You're spilling!
Ooh!
This old man. He's so careless!
You mean Mr. Li?
I never should have agreed to be with him!
Nai Nai...
He can't hear me anyway.
He's practically deaf.
Why are you still with him?
It's been so many years.
It's better than living alone.
At least there's a live body in the house.
Otherwise, when you get
up to go to the bathroom...
all you see are your own shadows.
Child...
do you have a friend yet?
I have a lot of friends, Nai Nai.
I mean a special friend.
You're all alone. I worry about you.
New York is such a big place.
Billi?
Are you OK?
I'm fine...
I'm just tired.
If you're tired, go to bed!
OK.
I love you, Nai Nai.
I love you. I love you.
For what month?
For this month, May?
And what happened to April?
My mom says you didn't pay April yet.
You know if you moved out
right now, we could literally
double the rent?
So what, you're broke again?
Are you always going to live like this?
Poor but sexy, I hope so.
Why you not try to save, huh?
You should change your expensive lifestyle.
Mom, if you're going to
give me shit every time
I come home, I'm not coming home anymore.
Lower your voice. Dad's sleeping.
Sleeping? It's 6:00 PM.
What's wrong with him?
Nothing. He's just tired.
Is he okay?
He's fine, we're just busy that's all.
Busy with what? What's going on?
Hao Hao's getting married,
so we have to go to China.
What? Since when?
Hasn't he like just
started dating that girl?
You don't need to go.
No one's expecting you to go.
I mean, he's my only cousin.
Don't you think I should be there?
OK, OK.
Do you think he knocked her up?
How many wontons you want?
Five.
Five? That's not enough.
Make a dozen then.
Ten's good.
OK.
What's wrong, Dad?
Nothing.
You and mom got in a fight?
You've been drinking?
Please tell me what's going on.
You're scaring me.
Something's going on.
Just tell me what's going on.
Your Nai Nai's dying.
She has stage four lung cancer.
The doctor says she has three months.
Could be faster, you never know.
- I need to call her.
- You can't do that.
- I need to go see her.
- Can't do that.
She doesn't know.
The family thinks it's
better not to tell her.
So you can't say anything.
I don't understand.
She doesn't have a lot of time
left, she should know, right?
There's nothing they can do.
So everyone decided it's
better not to tell her.
Why is that better?
Chinese people have saying,
"when people get cancer they die."
It's not cancer that
kills them, it's the fear.
OK, when were you guys gonna tell me this?
How could you let me find out like this?
How should I have told you?
Oh, your grandma's on the roof?
What about the wedding?
The wedding is an excuse
so everyone can go see her.
We leave first thing in the morning.
I need to go.
Billie.
Everyone thinks it's better if you don't.
Look at you.
You can't hide your emotions.
If you go now, Nai Nai
will find out right away.
♪ Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday dear Tony
Who's that?
It's me, Billi.
Who?
Mr. Li?
Billi.
Billi?
Child, how come you're here?
Quick, come in!
Pass that to me.
- Billi!
- Huh?
Billi came back...
Billi, you stupid child!
Come, let me look at you.
Oh you're not that skinny!
Your mother said you got skinny
but you're not that skinny!
Oh, my granddaughter.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I've been calling you all week.
But you didn't answer!
Your mother said you were too busy to come.
What's wrong?
Why aren't you talking?
I've missed you.
I know.
How'd you get here? Did you fly?
I swam.
Should have called first.
Stupid child, teasing me!
This little round butt
hasn't changed at all!
I've always loved to touch
your little round butt!
Little Nai Nai.
Billi!
I'm making meat pies. You must be starving.
I remember these were
your favorite as a kid.
This is Mrs. Gao.
Hello.
You're the granddaughter!
You're back home too.
- Yes.
- Great.
Last time you were here,
we still had Mrs. Jin.
I remember Mrs. Ma?
Mrs. Ma? That was four maids ago!
Has it been that long
since you've been back?
Stop fooling around, oil is hot.
Don't be mad, Mom.
Where'd you get the money to buy a ticket?
Credit card, right?
Mom, I'm fine.
Look at my face, look at my
face, look at my face, look.
Take to table.
It's been too long since we've
all been together like this.
Has it been over 20 years?
At least!
Haiyan went to America 25 years ago.
Billi was only six!
And Haibin left for Japan right after.
That's a long time.
Time flies.
These just came off the stove.
Eat them while they're hot.
Look at these wonderful
grandchildren of mine!
Billi is very strong. Independent.
Not someone who just follows everyone else.
Hao Hao's always been sensitive.
Now he's all grown up.
And getting married!
I've been looking forward
to this day for a long time.
Too bad neither speak Chinese well.
Hao Hao's Chinese is
good, he's just being shy.
Hao Hao, talk to your grandma in Chinese.
We don't need a big wedding banquet.
We came to spend time with you.
Nonsense!
You came home to get married.
We must have a proper banquet!
Ma, let's just keep it simple.
We don't need to go overboard.
Stop it!
Everything's already booked.
I sent invitations out last week.
My only grandson's getting
married, we can't look cheap!
Hao Hao, eat!
Aiko.
Have a meat pie.
Why aren't you eating?
I'm not hungry.
How can you not be hungry?
You've been on the road all day.
Take a big bite!
It's good, right?
Everyone says I'm adorable.
What's wrong?
Not feeling well?
I'm fine.
It must be jet lag. I'll
take you to the hotel first.
Hotel?
Why can't I stay here?
With so many people visiting, it's
easier if we all stay at a hotel.
I'll walk you there.
Don't worry. The hotel is
very nice. It's newly built!
Go get some rest. There's
lots to do before the wedding.
I spoke to a cancer specialist in Japan.
I bought her some medicine.
From the Japanese doctor?
From the Internet.
Nai Nai...
Nai Nai loves you very much, you know that?
I know.
Nai Nai is very sick.
She doesn't know anything
about her illness.
I know.
You have to be very
careful not to tell her.
I know!
Dad told me!
You will feel sad.
But...
no matter how sad you feel...
you cannot tell her.
I know.
She doesn't have long left.
We're not planning to tell her.
I know.
No matter what, you cannot tell her.
What do you mean the elevator's broken?
Isn't this a newly opened hotel?
I'm so sorry, sir. It's under maintenance.
This way please.
I'll carry the luggage. I'm sorry.
- Billi.
- Hm-mm?
- You OK by yourself?
- Yes.
- I'll head back.
- OK.
- Rest well.
- I will.
- We want the same room as last time.
- No problem.
Are we almost there?
Almost!
Are you visiting from abroad?
Yes.
Which country?
America.
America?
You don't look like an American.
What'd you come back for?
A wedding.
Who's getting married?
My cousin... my "tang di".
Oh your cousin.
He's also from America?
No, Japan.
Japan? What are they doing in Japan?
I don't know.
My uncle paints.
Thank you.
And what does your father do in America?
He's a translator.
Do you have water? For drinking?
Yes! You can use this boiler.
OK, got it.
That's fine, thank you.
So what do you think's
better? China or America?
It's different.
What do you mean different? It
must be much nicer in America.
It's just... different.
But I guess you're more
used to America, right?
I guess.
OK, if you need anything, just tell me.
K, thanks. Bye.
Thank you.
Ha!
Ho!
Ha! Ho!
Come do it with me!
Ha! Ha!
Be serious!
Try harder.
This will clear out all the bad toxins.
Ha! Ha!
Then you inhale to take in fresh oxygen.
Understand?
- Yes.
- Let's do it together.
Inhale.
Ha! Ha!
Ha. Ha.
Make it stronger!
Open your eyes! Lift your chest!
OK got it.
- Do you get it?
- I get it!
You can also slap your arms.
Slap your back.
Slap my butt?
Stupid child!
Slap your legs, get the circulation going.
- Understand?
- Understand.
Now you can practice this on your
own when you return to America!
It's good for you! Trust me!
Try again!
Inhale...
Ha! Ha!
It's OK. I got it.
I go up and down by myself every morning.
Doesn't that hurt your legs?
Even so, I have to keep exercising.
It's the reason I'm so
healthy. Even at my age!
- I heard you came back!
- Hi Auntie!
- You remember Bao?
- Bao, say hi!
Little Bao, you've gotten so big!
I'm not little Bao!
I'm just called Bao!
Oh, Bao's here!
YuPing, come sit come sit!
Jian.
Something's off about
Haiyan. Have you noticed?
His face is all puffy and discolored.
He seems very unhappy.
He's fine, Ma.
He looks so tired.
Is he still drinking?
You can't let him drink.
Alcohol can ruin a person.
I know so many men around here
who drank themselves to death.
He barely drinks anymore.
Is everything OK at home?
Everything's fine. Really, Ma.
I know you guys have
had issues in the past...
At our age, what issues
could we still have?
They're just vitamins.
Your uncle bought it for me from Japan.
He says they're expensive.
So they must be good.
The Japanese really know how
to take care of themselves!
Mr. Li, you finished?
Don't mind him. That's just how he is.
He eats and leaves.
Doesn't care about anything
that doesn't concern him.
Listen to me...
I know everyone's excited to see me.
But let's not forget why we're here.
The wedding is the big event!
If anyone asks
nobody say Hao Hao and his bride
have only been dating 3 months.
Ma, I already told you,
Aiko's not pregnant.
It's about appearances.
You know how people think!
I don't want people
talking behind our backs.
If anyone asks
just say they've been dating 6 months.
Why 6 months? Might as
well say a year then.
Great idea.
A year's better. We'll say a year!
Listen...
the wedding's in 3 days.
Someone needs to come see
the banquet hall with me.
I'll come!
No you can't be much help anyway!
Ma, I'll go.
No, you rest.
Look at your face. It's not right.
Ma, why don't you rest? I'll
go check on the banquet hall.
I have to go myself.
You don't even know who to talk to.
What can I do?
You don't need to do anything.
You don't look good either.
Must still be the jet lag.
Ma.
I'll take them to the massage parlor.
Oh great!
You guys go relax.
You better not get sick before the wedding!
Eat eat eat!
When I booked the wedding
you guys told me it'd be lobster.
Now you act like you don't
know anything about it?
I don't know anything about that.
The menu says crab, not lobster.
I know it says crab, but I ordered lobster!
Fine. Let me ask.
Little Ping! Little Ping!
Go get the chef!
Hurry up!
Let's take a look at the alcohol options.
We have baijiu, red
wine, white wine, beer...
We're bringing champagne.
Champagne?
Your brother bought it.
Looks very nice and expensive!
Chinese people won't drink that stuff.
Order baijiu!
Mrs. Zhao says she was told the
meal would have lobster, not crab.
It's not lobster, it's crab.
What kind of scam is this?
When I booked, you guys
told me it'd be lobster!
We already paid a deposit!
Now it's 3 days before the wedding
and you change the menu without telling us!
I don't know anything about
that. I was told to make crab.
Ma, don't get all worked up over this!
I'm fine. I just need to rest a bit.
So what's going on with the fellowship?
Nothing.
You still haven't heard anything?
No.
Well, when are they gonna let you know?
I don't know, Dad.
How are you doing with money?
I'm fine.
Can you afford this trip?
Yes, I'm fine.
You need help?
No, I'm fine.
All set. Let's go.
This way please.
"Mei nu", what treatment would you like?
Her Chinese isn't great. Give
her the full body massage!
- Cupping too?
- The whole package.
- Same for you, "mei nu"?
- I don't need cupping today.
What is "mei nu"?
It means beauty.
Always "mei nu, mei nu."
Everyone in China's called "mei nu."
Old or young. Beautiful or ugly.
All beauties! So stupid!
Sir, what about you?
You can call me beauty.
I mean what kind of
treatment would you like?
I recommend our bath and massage treatment.
The tub is filled with herbs.
What do you think?
Why are you asking me?
Ask yourself if you want to take a bath!
- Can you show me the tub?
- No problem, this way please.
Ow!
Auntie, I thought this was a massage!
Suck it up.
A little pain is normal,
otherwise it doesn't work.
Auntie.
Hm-mm?
Don't you think we should tell Nai Nai?
Tell her? What for?
Ow that hurts! What's going on?
This is the sleeping point.
You haven't been sleeping well.
Have you been stressed
lately? Try to relax.
What if she has things to take care of?
She doesn't have anything like that.
What if...
she wants to say goodbye?
Say goodbye?
That's too painful.
Why would you want her to go through that?
She seems totally normal right now.
If you tell her, you'll
ruin her good mood, right?
"Mei nu", get closer to him.
Get closer! He told you to get closer!
Come, lay your head on his shoulder.
Hao Hao, wrap your arms around her.
Your arm...
hold him.
Now smile.
What's wrong with this girl?
Can't they act like a
normal couple in love?
That girl is unaffectionate.
Nothing like our family.
I have to yell at her just to hug him!
Makes me wonder what they do in
the bedroom when I'm not here.
Nai Nai, she seems really nice.
She's dumb. I don't like her!
She doesn't understand anything!
She doesn't understand because
she doesn't speak Chinese!
No, she's dumb. She's dumb!
Billi.
Look at you.
Smart. Beautiful.
You must find someone to take care of you.
I take care of myself, Nai Nai.
You're still young, child.
As you get older, it's good to
have someone to take care of you.
Does Mr. Li take care of you?
It's also good to be independent.
A woman should be self-sufficient.
Stupid child.
Too lovable!
I'll never forget...
when your parents brought you to my
house, you were barely two years old.
You were skinny as a twig...
because of that horrible
nanny who stole your eggs!
And she'd take you all over the city
and only feed you popsicles!
- Do you remember this?
- No. Why did she steal my eggs?
Eggs were rationed back then.
Your parents saved theirs to give to you.
These last few days, there's
been too much going on.
We haven't been able to talk much.
Oh, sorry. We're lost. Sorry.
You know...
the wedding is very important.
A lot of friends and family are coming.
They haven't seen you
since you were little!
I know you have a lot on your mind,
but you can't be weird at the wedding.
You must be generous in
spirit. And be courteous!
When you see people, you should loudly
say, "Hello uncle! Hello auntie!"
Don't be "nio nio ne ne."
What's "nio nio ne ne"?
- You don't understand?
- No.
Watch me.
Understand?
If someone asks you to sing, don't say
I can't sing, I won't sing.
That'll make the whole room go cold.
OK.
Promise me you won't act like that.
When you get married
I'll throw you an even
bigger wedding banquet.
It's so rare for us to be together.
Just look at your mother's face.
I'm happy.
Come, let's toast.
Billi, you ever think
about moving back to China?
A lot of foreigners are
moving here to get rich.
In America, how long would it
take to make a million dollars?
A long time.
Really?
It's very easy in China.
It's true.
Life is not all about money.
Money can't buy everything.
But money doesn't get in the way.
You can still enjoy the
stuff money can't buy.
If it's so easy to get rich here,
why are you sending Bao
to America for college?
For more opportunity.
What kind of opportunity?
Maybe after going to America,
Bao won't care about money.
Just like Billi. She'd
rather do what she loves.
You guys don't have to worry,
Billi will make big money when
she becomes a famous writer!
You're investing in her talent.
So raising a kid is like
playing the stock market?
What's that mean?
They say you're a stock
investment and you're gonna make
us a lot of money.
Well we can't expect that from you, right?
You are the losing stock.
You know...
when we first moved to America,
a friend took us to a church.
As we were leaving the service
Billi suddenly stopped in front of a piano.
She reached her hand out to
play, and Haiyan stopped her.
The pastor came over
and Haiyan quickly explained that
Billi used to play the piano in China.
After we moved, we couldn't
afford it so Billi stopped playing.
The pastor walked away
without saying a word.
When she came back, she
handed us a key and said
this is the key to the church.
Bring Billi to play the
piano anytime you want.
Really?
They really just gave you the key?
That's America.
Mom, that church is not
representative of all America.
We have a lot of problems.
Guns. Health care.
If you think China that
good, why don't you move here?
China has its benefits!
We're not totally useless.
Of course. The roast
duck is still delicious!
That's enough!
No matter what, you can't criticize China.
Don't forget, you're still Chinese!
Technically, we're American.
I mean, we have American passports.
I'll always be Chinese.
No matter where I live
or what passport I hold.
You all may think the moon
is rounder outside China
but have you considered your mother?
Growing old without her kids around.
Alright, alright!
Everyone's home, let's
talk about happy things!
But YuPing...
you're still sending Bao
to America for college?
He'll be back. He won't stay there.
You can't guarantee that.
But even with the risk that he won't return
you'll still send him away, right?
So how's your piano, Billi?
I don't play anymore.
Go home, I'm fine.
How can I leave when
you're coughing like this?
There's nothing to worry about!
I just haven't gotten over the cold I had.
Don't tell the children.
- They'll be worried for nothing.
- I won't say anything.
- Lock the door.
- Sure.
Go home, Sis.
OK Auntie. I'll meet you there.
What's going on?
Nai Nai went to the hospital.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
Billi, it's the wrong way.
This way is fine.
- We have to go around.
- He says it's fine.
Which way are we going?
Dad, do you know where we're going?
- This way.
- My umbrella...
- Is this the right way?
- Yes.
Are you sure?
Ma?
Why'd you all come?
You told them?
I told you not to say anything!
You always blame me!
You can't disappear
without telling any of us.
I'm fine!
I'm going to find the doctor.
What? Why are you all so serious?
I just came to change my medicine.
It's no big deal!
Nai Nai.
Do you not feel well?
I just have a bit of a cough.
I didn't fully recover from
the last time I had a cold.
I just wanted to change my medicine.
Maybe it'll work better.
Doctor.
Let's have a look.
Inhale.
Exhale.
Cough.
You have some infection.
I'm already on antibiotics!
You gave me bad medicine.
Give me a better one, so I can heal faster.
This is my grandson. He's
getting married in two days!
Really? Congratulations.
This is my granddaughter.
She's back from America.
Visit from America?
I went to school in the UK for many years.
Oh, that's cool.
Where do you live?
Uh, I'm in New York.
New York. I always
wanted to visit New York.
It's a very beautiful city.
Yeah, it's very beautiful...
Uh, question...
do you know about my grandma's condition?
What are you guys talking about?
He studied in England so he speaks English.
Really?
It's true.
Dr. Song, let me ask you...
are you married?
Not yet.
The young man's so handsome, and a doctor
and he speaks English!
Not married? Impossible!
Ma!
How bad is she?
But you can tell me the truth.
The cancer is quite advanced.
Shouldn't we tell her?
In her situation, most
families in China would
choose not to tell her.
When my grandmother had cancer,
my family didn't tell her.
Isn't it wrong to lie?
I mean if it's for good,
it's not really a lie.
I mean, it's still a lie.
It's a good lie.
How's your grandmother?
She passed away, a few months
after she was diagnosed.
Mrs. Zhao, you had
pneumonia a few months ago.
I suspect that your cough
is left over from that.
Let's do an X-ray
to make sure the infection isn't spreading.
That's not necessary. I just
want to change my medicine.
We can change your medicine.
But I still recommend an X-ray.
Maybe we should tell her now.
We can start making plans.
When the time comes
who will take care of her?
We don't need to tell her to make plans.
You know, in America, we couldn't do this.
We wouldn't be allowed to.
It'd be...
Illegal. How do you say illegal?
Illegal. In America, this is illegal.
This isn't America...
It's not time to tell her yet!
How do you know?
I just know.
If Nai Nai knew we were all
lying to her, wouldn't she be mad?
What does she have to be mad about?
She did the same thing herself!
What do you mean?
When your grandpa had cancer,
Nai Nai lied to him too.
When she knew he was close to the end
that's when she told him.
When your Nai Nai reaches that point,
I'll tell her too.
Ellen!
Ellen, Little Ellen!
Sing for us!
Ellen, sing another!
Mr. Li, go get the Maotai we saved!
Ma, there will be plenty
of alcohol at the wedding.
Why don't you save your Maotai?
What am I saving it for?
You know your two sons!
They don't know when to stop.
Haiyan already has a fatty liver.
The doctor told him not to drink!
- Where is it again?
- On the kitchen shelf.
These two rarely come back together.
If they want to drink, let them drink!
We're celebrating. Drink!
Your mother's always telling
me to take care of you
but if she gets you drunk herself,
she doesn't worry about your health.
Mom, can we not do this right now, please?
Every time you drink, you drink too much.
Mom!
Who's drunk? I'm not drunk.
Can we not right now?
My ma gave it to me. I drink for my ma!
Alright, alright.
Just leave him alone.
Billi, the key.
Nai Nai should not be
organizing this wedding.
If she enjoys it then just let her do it.
She's sick.
She should be resting or in a hospital.
Not stressing about a fake wedding.
You really don't know your Nai Nai.
You know she enjoys
bossing everyone around.
Makes her feel important.
Makes her feel in control.
- Mom.
- It's true!
That's why she hated to
stay in America in our house.
You know?
Because she could not
tell anyone what to do.
Whatever I do, never good enough for her.
But she can't say anything
because it was my house.
Mom, stop!
What? What did I say?
You have always had issues
with her, but right now...
Oh, I don't have a problem with her.
She's the one that have a problem with me.
She's dying.
Can't you be a little more sensitive?
What you want from me?
To scream and cry like you?
You know when my father
died, I was also very sad.
But I don't act like you.
When I went back to China for the funeral,
everybody was watching me.
They were all expecting me to fall apart.
And they think if I don't
cry, I don't love my father.
No one's asking you to cry!
Too loud!
I don't like, you know, put
all my emotion on display,
like I'm in the zoo.
But in here, if you don't cry,
you don't put on a show they
think you don't love your family.
You know in here, they even
hire some professional criers.
Just to show how sad they are.
It's just so ridiculous. I hate that.
Your grandpa loved bananas.
Give him some bananas.
You have to peel the oranges!
I don't think they need to be peeled.
Yes, peel them!
Otherwise he can't eat them.
Should I drink it?
Pour, just pour.
Yeah, pour, very good.
Billi, put these cookies out.
You have to open them!
- They need to be opened too?
- Yes, open it!
- Rip the flowers too!
- Why do we have to rip the flowers?
To prevent thieves.
Some people steal offerings to
put on their own family graves.
This way they won't steal it!
Don't give him cigarettes! He quit!
He didn't quit.
He did!
A few weeks before he passed, he quit.
Dad just told you he
quit, but he never quit!
Ma, let the man smoke.
He's already dead, what else can happen?
Enjoy the cigarette, Dad.
Burn the paper jacket for your grandfather.
That way, he won't be cold in the winter.
Old timer, we all came to see you.
Our grandson's getting married tomorrow.
We came to get your blessing.
We ask you to bless Hao
Hao and his new bride.
Bless them with happiness.
Bless their children
with health and strength.
One bow.
Two bows.
Three bows.
Old timer, you left us too soon.
Why did you have to leave so early?
Wherever you are...
we hope you're happy and peaceful.
One bow.
Two bows.
Three bows.
Bless both our sons with
success in their businesses.
One bow.
Two bows.
Three bows.
Who else?
Bless Billi.
Bless her with a happy future.
One bow.
Two bows.
Three bows.
Still bowing?
We're all getting dizzy!
Bless my little sister. Bless her...
Bless me to win big money in Mahjong!
Bless your niece, YuPing.
And Bao.
Bless him to do well on his exams.
Bao, keep up!
When the time comes, just
spread my ashes into the ocean.
No one's ever home anyway.
What are you talking about? I'm here!
Just scatter me into the ocean.
Then you won't have to travel
back and forth all the time.
Into the ocean? Nonsense!
- You don't agree?
- Certainly not.
We're Chinese.
Humans must return to
the earth we came from!
Wait! This looks so familiar.
This is NaiNai's old neighborhood.
Do you remember that house?
You used to love to play in the garden.
Where is it?
We already passed it.
Can we go back? I want to see it!
There's nothing to see.
That neighborhood is long gone.
Even I don't recognize it anymore.
OK, OK, that's enough.
- Enough?
- Yes.
Careful, don't burn yourself.
Dad?
Huh?
Are you smoking?
Hm-mm.
I thought you said you quit.
I did.
I will.
Stop giving him cigarettes!
Don't control him.
He's your father. You
shouldn't try to control him.
Go to bed, Billi.
Forget it.
What're you guys talking about?
Nothing.
Are you going to tell Nai Nai?
I can't, Billi.
I won't go against my family.
Billi.
There are things you must understand...
you guys moved to the West long ago.
You think one's life belongs to oneself.
But that's the difference
between the East and the West.
In the East, a person's
life is part of a whole.
Family.
Society.
You want to tell Nai Nai the truth...
because you're afraid to
take responsibility for her.
Because it's too big of a burden.
If you tell her...
then you don't have to feel guilty.
We're not telling Nai Nai...
because it's our duty to carry
this emotional burden for her.
Billi, don't just stand there.
Come help find Aiko's earring.
Where did she drop it?
Not far.
Hao Hao.
Where's Aiko been?
The earring is light, so it
could have jumped farther away.
- Mom?
- Yeah?
I want to stay in China and
help take care of Nai Nai.
What?
You stay here, to do what?
You can't cook, you can't clean.
You don't even speak good
Chinese. What can you do?
Is this it, Hao Hao?
Thank you!
I'll figure it out, Mom.
So you just stay here.
And what?
Wait for her to die?
What about the fellowship?
Just forget about it, huh?
You're 30 years old, you
can just stop your life
and stay here?
And every day she has to look at
you, with that sad looking face?
That's not nice for anybody, right?
You know, one of the few
good memories of my childhood,
were the summers at Nai Nai's.
They had that garden.
Ye Ye and I would catch dragonflies.
And then we just moved to the States.
Everything was different.
Everyone was gone.
And it was just the three of us.
I know it was hard.
It was hard for us too.
I wanted to believe
that it was a good thing,
but all I saw was fear in your eyes.
And I was confused and scared constantly
because you never told
me what was going on.
And then Ye Ye died.
You didn't even tell me he was sick.
So it felt like he just...
vanished suddenly.
And you wouldn't even
let me go to his funeral.
You were at school.
We didn't want you to miss school.
We did what we thought was best for you.
But I never saw him again.
And every time I came
back to China, he just
wasn't there anymore.
And I come back and he's just gone.
The house is gone, A Die's gone,
our Beijing home is gone and
soon she'll be gone, too.
Guests first!
Strive for excellence!
Make romance!
Become history!
Witness happiness!
Move your whole life!
We welcome your visit!
Billi!
Hello Auntie!
Did you get the X-ray results?
No, I'll get them tomorrow.
Tomorrow's Sunday! Now we'll
have to wait until Monday!
So I'll get them Monday! Stop worrying!
Welcome back to Changchun everyone!
It doesn't matter if
you're from America or Japan
or anywhere else in the world.
What's important is that
we're all one family.
All citizens of the Earth.
Of the solar system.
Of the Milky Way.
Just remember this!
You'll always have a home in Changchun.
We will always, always welcome you.
Yes. We will always, always welcome you!
Everybody raise your glass, let's toast.
When you come home to Changchun
you will eat well, drink well and be happy!
That way, you'll remember
to come back often!
- Cheers!
- Bottoms up!
Everyone keep eating, keep eating.
Don't let me interrupt.
As the oldest son, I'll say a few
words on behalf of me and my brother.
My brother and I...
have not been home at the
same time in over 25 years.
Today, I'm very happy.
We're welcoming Aiko to our family.
Perhaps the next time we return
we'll bring a little baby with us.
Since my brother and I have been away
we're grateful to you all
for taking care of our mother.
YuPing...
all these years, you've
been by my mother's side.
Treating her like your own mother.
I'm very grateful to you.
Really, very grateful.
But...
the person I want to thank the most...
is my mother.
Ma...
forgive me.
All these years, I
haven't been by your side.
Everything...
all of my accomplishments...
are because of you.
Ma...
you're the best mother in the entire world!
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm just too happy today.
Happy thank you.
Does everyone know?
I think most people don't know.
But I'm not sure.
Billi?
Eat more.
She says
"Thank you for attending
our wedding ceremony."
She says
"I'm very happy to celebrate with you all."
"Hao Hao is a very nice, good man."
The battlefield in front
of us. Hoards of enemies!
There were only a few of us left.
And then, let me tell you...
I used my martial arts skills.
I killed five at once!
This is my granddaughter!
She's quite pretty!
Married yet?
Not yet.
Career first, then marriage!
These three grandpas
were in the army with me.
They're all important
government officials now!
Yeah, right!
We're long retired!
Little Ting...
I see you're still limping.
Is it from that bullet you took in the war?
You still remember that?
How could I forget?
At the time, I had a plan.
After the war...
I was going to make you my wife!
But then you got injured.
And Comrade Wang carried you off.
That was a lifetime ago!
You're confessing your love now?
If I don't say it now,
I'll take it to my grave!
You've had too much to drink!
It's good I'm telling
you, right Little Ting?
Little Ting? I'm OLD TING!
This time home
you should talk more with your grandmother!
You've had too much to drink.
What are you talking about?
Billi, go up and say a few words.
Hi everyone.
As you know, I was very
young when I left China.
My Chinese isn't very good. I'm sorry.
It's great! Keep going!
Thank you.
I almost didn't come back.
I was busy with work.
But...
I still came back.
In America
we don't have a lot of family.
I've missed all of you.
I'm very happy to be back.
I'm very happy
to celebrate with you all.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, how do you say congratulations? Dad?
Gong xi!
Gong xi Hao Hao Aiko! Thank you.
♪ And so I came to see her ♪
♪ And listen for a while ♪
♪ And there he was this young boy ♪
♪ A stranger to my eyes ♪
♪ Strumming my pain with his fingers ♪
♪ Singing my life with his words ♪
Auntie?
It must be tough taking care
of your sister all these years.
In the future, you have to
think more about yourself.
You don't have to worry about me.
I've already figured it all out.
After she's gone...
I'll go to Shenzhen to be with my husband.
He's been out there working
alone all these years.
It hasn't been easy.
I haven't been able to be by his side.
When he retires soon, we'll
be able to travel together.
You can come visit us in America!
Right! Definitely! I've always
wanted to see your house!
If you come, we'll drive you around.
We'll take you anywhere you want to go!
Great! That's fantastic!
See, you don't have to worry about me.
I'm totally fine!
Everyone stand up straight!
Look into the lens!
Why are you crying? Did you drink too much?
You can't take a wedding
photo with the groom crying.
What are you crying about?
He's fine. They're tears of joy.
Isn't that right, Hao Hao?
Will you take one with my camera too?
Sis, where's my camera?
I gave it to Mrs. Gao. It's in her purse.
Where is she?
I sent her to the hospital
to pick up my test results.
Everyone say "eggplant!"
One, two three!
Eggplant!
- Test result pickup?
- Upstairs.
Mrs. Gao!
What are you doing here?
- Did you get them?
- The test results? Yeah.
What's the matter? What's it say?
I don't know. I can't read Chinese.
Didn't you read it?
I can't read. I never went to school.
How am I supposed to change this?
What do you want to me write here?
Just change it to benign shadows.
Benign shadow? What's a benign shadow?
It means it's not fatal!
Fine.
You see
I told you I was fine!
Don't give me money!
Take it.
Just take it.
I gave one to Hao Hao, so
I have to give you one too.
I didn't get married.
Even more reason!
You're all on your own.
And I can't be much help.
Take it, my child.
And don't spend it on
practical things like rent!
Buy yourself something nice.
I don't want to leave.
You'll be back.
I know you're always thinking of me.
But I've been taking my new medicine...
and I'm all better!
You have work to do.
You still have a long road ahead.
I'm very proud of you.
I didn't get the fellowship.
Really?
You just heard?
Last week.
I didn't tell you because
I didn't want you to worry.
I'm not worried.
You'll be fine, child.
I've walked the path of
life and I must tell you
you'll encounter difficulties,
but you have to keep an open mind.
Don't be the bull endless ramming
its horns into the corner of the room.
Life is not just about what you do
it's more about how you do it.
Your mind is very powerful.
You will succeed.
Are you really OK?
Yes, really!
Why would I lie to you?
Stupid child!
Let's go, you'll miss your flight!
You don't need to come down!
I'm fine! I'm coming!
Don't cry, Nai Nai.
I'm not, I'm not.
Stupid child! I'm not crying.
- You don't cry.
- I'm not crying.
I'll visit you again.
I know. We'll see each other very soon.
Go on, let's not drag this out anymore.
Otherwise I can't take it. Hurry up!
Go on, get in the car!
- Take care, Ma.
- I know, I will.
- Go back inside, Ma!
- I'll go after you get in the car!
- Go upstairs, Ma! It's chilly!
- Hurry up, you'll miss your flight!
Be good, my child.
Ha!!
Ha! Ho! Ha! Ho!
Subtitles by explosiveskull & EVO
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Stream Securely & Hide from Your ISP
with www.PureVPN.com/isp at 86% OFF