Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
Mr. Rusk?
Mr. Rusk.
Boss, are you there?
Mia, out of curiosity,
what part of "hold my calls"
couldn't you wrap your head around?
I'm in a meeting.
I'm sorry. It's Harold, and think
that there's something wrong.
Harold? Uh...
Put him through.
Richard.
Harold.
What happened, buddy?
Why didn't you come back
with me and Elaine?
Richard, I've been taken!
Taken?
Elaine, Elaine,
I've been kidnapped.
- Turn it down. Turn it down.
- They have a gun to my head!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
What are you doing?
Calm down and explain, as clearly
as you can, what's going on.
I am somewhere in Mexico
with a gun to my head!
- I don't know how much clearer I can be!
- Holy fuck!
Harold, it's okay.
We're here.
- Um...
- Ask what they want.
What do they want?
They want five million
wired to an account.
Or they're going
to hang me from the bridge!
Five million what, pesos?
Peso... Dollars!
We're so fucked.
Harold?
Walk Riley.
...and snow continues to linger.
Everyone in Chicago
is complaining,
and I say let's turn it around.
Here.
- I love you.
- Mmm.
- Say hi to Stu.
- I will.
Maybe the beach holiday
will have to wait.
But I must get a second car.
- Bonnie keeps bringing it up.
- Shit.
Bonnie is the one
that's killing you.
I mean, look, don't get me wrong.
I know you love her and all.
But your wife's the reason that
that's all fucked up, okay?
The loans.
The insane office space.
She's got one client. She should
be working out of your garage,
not leasing space
at the damn Franklin Center.
Listen, as your accountant,
I have to tell you,
she's dragging you in some deep
water, Harold, like bankruptcy-deep.
So, you're saying
that I am cash poor?
No, I'm saying
you're poor-poor, nigga.
Plus, word on the street
is that Promethium
is about to be gobbled up
by Powell or AFT.
If there's a merger, you could
be looking for another job.
What?
I... I haven't heard
anything about that.
Look, man, I do taxes for half the
Powell brass, and this shit is real.
Stewart, Richard
wouldn't do that to me.
He's my friend, okay?
Richard has a vanity
license plate, Harold.
He does push-ups
in his goddamn office.
Richard would
do that to you.
Good morning. Promethium
Pharmaceuticals. How can I help you?
Harold!
Man, it's 9:20!
You're late again!
What do you call this?
- I think that's all, Mr. Rusk.
- All right.
- I'll see you at the game.
- Sure.
Come.
Get in here.
I had to do that.
Everybody knows we're friends. I
can't give you special treatment.
Sorry, Richard. Lake Shore
was crazy this morning.
Sit down.
Hey, Mia,
I'm thirsty.
All right.
You ready
for this game tonight?
Those Benson-Smith cocksuckers
are begging for an ass kicking.
I am gonna
give it to 'em.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, and then tomorrow,
you and me are gonna have
a little fun in Mexico.
What?
Elaine and I are gonna
join you on this trip.
You're not the only one who
could go for a little sunshine.
This is because
of the missing inventory.
Look, I plan to speak to Sanchez
to get to the bottom of that.
No, Elaine and I will
speak to Sanchez.
We just wanna check
on a few things down there.
Uh, I need you to put
all the Mexico files in this
and give it to Elaine.
Yo, thanks, buddy.
Richard.
Is everything okay here?
It's just
I heard a rumor,
something about
a possible merger.
Harold, listen.
When-When you needed a job
and you came to me,
I said if you stuck with me, your
life is gonna look like a rap video.
Right?
And haven't I always
looked after you?
I give you an incredible position
as operations supervisor.
Yes.
I handed you
the Mexico assignment.
Yes.
I give Bonnie a job
designing my loft,
and she has fuck-all
for experience.
That was generous.
Trust me.
Fucking be patient, man.
And everything's
gonna get revealed.
Why don't you
reveal it to me... now?
Have I told you
about the two gorillas?
All right.
I read it in this book.
Two gorillas, right?
And every day
they get fed carrots.
they eat the carrots.
No problem. Chomp, chomp, chomp.
So delicious.
Except, one day, the handler, he
gives one of the gorillas a banana,
and the other guy
still gets his carrots,
and he doesn't wanna eat
the carrots.
You know why? 'Cause he's seen
the other guy eat the banana.
You know what I'm saying?
Harold.
Eat your fucking carrots.
'Cause I have your back, right?
And then you're gonna be dick-deep
in bananas before you know it.
Right?
Rap video.
Mia.
Hungry.
Receipt's in the bag.
- Thanks.
Stop.
Wow. All of that without
professional training.
Whoo. That's good, man.
You don't have to be a dick about it.
All right.
Spunky. I like it.
You'll get far.
Hey, stranger.
Nelly.
What you doing here?
You disappeared on us.
Thought about
Monty's offer yet?
Yeah, you can't come in here
talking about that, all right?
I'm, uh... I'm working.
Yeah.
You seem... super busy.
Yeah, well these babies don't
polish themselves, all right?
So, are you in or out?
I can't. It's too dangerous.
Oh, come on, Miles.
Don't be a pussy.
You can do this.
Really not that hard.
Right. I really appreciate the pep
talk, but it ain't happening.
Look, it's just
a couple of pills
from Monty's friend
at some lab
so he can figure out
what's in it and make his own.
All you gotta do is bring 'em back.
It'll be easy.
Plus, it's a free trip to Mexico.
What more do you want?
Right, so I'll be like
a little drug mule.
Perfect. I'll write you a
"thank you" note from prison.
Okay. Fine.
You don't want 20 grand,
that's your business.
Twenty grand?
You said it was ten.
Yeah, it was.
It's 20 now.
For real?
- For real.
- Hmm.
Oh, and you can bring
Guitar Shop Barbie with you.
Sh, sh, sh.
- What was all that about?
- What?
That.
Oh, nothing.
Ever been to Mexico, babe?
Richard.
Hey, listen. My lunch
meeting ran a little long.
I'm not gonna make it back to
the office before the game.
So do you mind grabbing my bag
for me before you leave?
It's under my desk.
Uh, okay.
All right.
I'll see you at the gym.
Hey. Sorry.
Just had to deal
with something.
Uh, Mia, Richard asked me
to grab something for the game.
Yeah.
I know, but not everything
needs to make sense, Tony.
Scotland Yard is in England.
Who the fuck
can explain that?
Now you're just
fucking boring me.
Hey. Ask you
about something?
Listen. I'm gonna give you some advice.
You listening, Tony Tones?
Good.
Stop crying.
Go down to unemployment.
Start acting
like a fucking man.
Kenny!
It's a foul.
Foul!
Oh.
You're kidding me!
All these underclassmen
have really paid their dues
coming off the bench.
How's it going
at Richard's?
Fine.
Do you have any leads
on other clients?
Stu's a little worried.
He was saying that your office space
might be costing a little too much.
What?
Nothing.
It's... It's fine.
I still don't understand
why she gave us her tickets.
I told you,
she's going on tour.
She needs me to pick up something
for her mum. This way.
What band is she in?
Please. Just be happy we
got a free trip out of it.
- I'm happy. Of course I am.
- I need to piss. Hold this a sec.
Look, relax.
It'll be fine, all right?
- Fucking hell, mate.
- Sorry.
Easy, tiger.
Harold!
Passports and boarding passes...
There it is again.
What... What is that smell?
Fat Willy's barbecue.
I always bring it for Angel.
Angel.
There you go.
Allow me to introduce
our co-presidents,
Mr. Rusk
and Ms. Markinson.
A new app. Amazing.
You know what else is amazing? Is
actually learning a foreign language.
Yo quiero
Taco Bell, huh?
That's sensational. Can we
get the fuck outta here?
Harold.
Welcome back.
This is Celerino Sanchez,
our plant manager,
and Roberto Vega,
his right-hand man.
All right, so you,
we need to talk to.
- Okay.
- Uh, you, we don't.
My office is this way.
Right.
- Sorry.
- No problem, Harold.
Please have a seat.
- Oh, uh...
- Thank you.
Harold, just sit
this one out,
and I'll come
get you after, okay?
Holy fuck.
Do they not sell condoms
down here?
Okay, Sanchez.
Do you wanna tell me
what that is?
It's an
inventory report.
That's right. What do you
think it's telling me?
Sir, you have
to understand...
Oh, just answer
the question, Suarez.
- Sanchez.
- Okay.
The report is telling you
that the inventory is light,
as I am still selling your
product to Señor Villegas,
as you requested.
We told you to cut him off.
With all due respect,
that's not the way it works.
Uh, that's exactly
how it works.
I make a product. I decide
who to sell it to. Right?
You get to decide if you want
a future with the company...
Again,
con todo respeto,
if I don't continue
to deliver,
I will have
no future at all.
When you needed money,
you asked me...
When we needed money, we asked you to
sell some product off the books...
and not say anything to Harold.
Now, we don't need money.
We're telling you to stop.
I really don't see what is so
difficult to understand-o.
- It's a sensitive time for the company now.
- Yes.
We're gonna have people coming down here,
and they're gonna look things over,
and we wanna make sure
that everything is in order.
I understand, but Señor Villegas
is expecting his usual shipment.
The Black Panther is
not someone to mess with.
You can't scare me with tales
of the big, bad cartels, right?
I know how things work.
Not in Mexico.
Well, as far as I'm concerned,
we are not in Mexico.
This is an American company
making an American product,
and I'm telling you,
in American,
to make sure
that the inventory's right.
Yes. I mean, if you can
take care of 35 kids,
I think you can handle
one drug dealer.
- No?
- ¿Comprende?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Gracias.
Adiós.
Have a nice day.
Harold, let's go.
Harold, just so you know,
the inventory thing
worried us.
That's why we came down here
to speak to Sanchez,
just to make sure everything
was on the up-and-up.
It's no reflection
on you.
No, certainly not.
You know we value your work.
- I was starting to think it might be something else.
- Well, you're hearing things.
He's hearing things.
Harold, when I was
in junior high,
a rumor went around
that I let the lacrosse team
pull a train on me
in the Dairy Queen parking lot.
I hated the lacrosse team.
They were the biggest
bunch of Waspy,
turtle-dicked ass pirates
I ever met in my entire life.
- Here you are, señor.
- Thank you.
And I'd rather give that waiter a rim
job than eat at a fucking Dairy Queen.
- What's a rim job?
- It's when...
Don't believe
everything you hear
is probably
the point here, right?
Exactly.
You're gonna be fine.
We're not selling
the company.
All right?
I'll be right back.
I don't think
he knows anything.
- I almost feel bad for the guy.
- Right.
Someone should put him
out of his misery.
Seriously.
No, I mean literally.
Someone should literally put
him out of his fucking misery.
Angel.
You can go.
I will see you mañana.
Okay.
But when they married each
other, she was a fatty.
She was 50 pounds heavier
than she is today.
I was like,
"Don't do it."
Fat people are so funny.
Gracias.
You wanna come
to my room tonight?
Yeah,
I'm really tired.
- Hey, buddy.
- What did I miss?
Uh, I'm gonna check some e-mails
and maybe hit the sauna
after I punch out
a little CrossFit.
- Then I'll see you guys in the morning.
- You sure...
Do you...
You know,
I'm gonna crash too.
It's gonna be
an early flight, so...
- That's it then.
- Good night.
What is your problem?
You just fucking left me.
Right.
Someone should
put him out of his misery.
No, I mean literally.
Someone should literally put him
out of his fucking misery.
Well, when the sale
goes through,
that's the last you're
gonna see of Harold Soyinka.
He is on the 86 list.
Maybe they're gonna
give him severance,
but I just think they're
gonna fucking clean house.
His wife must be a real winner.
Actually, she is.
But when they married each
other, she was a fatty.
She was 50 pounds heavier
than she is today.
Okay.
Richard
is supposed to be my friend.
It's unbelievable!
Just unbelievable!
You have
every right to be upset.
I swear...
I know I'm not supposed to touch the
minibar, but I'm going to do it.
I don't even care anymore. I'm doing it.
I'm having the merlot.
I feel horrible.
I should've told you
to your face.
What should you have
told me to my face?
- The e-mail.
- What e-mail?
- Just go ahead with what you were saying.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Wha-What should you
have told me?
You know...
You know the invisible
gorilla experiment, Harold?
Why is everyone talking about
gorillas all of a sudden?
There's this video, right?
Some people in black shirts.
Some people in white shirts.
And you have to count
how many times
the people in white shirts
pass this ball back and forth.
This person in a gorilla suit walks
into the middle of the group.
The experiment is whether or not
you're so focused on the ball
that you miss the gorilla.
You would've been part
of the group that missed it.
Missed what?
I'm having an affair.
I'm leaving you.
That's what the e-mail says.
You didn't notice the gorilla.
So, the affair is a gorilla?
Yes.
Wh-What is the ball?
The ball?
Is that our marriage,
the ball?
I don't know what the ball is.
I'm-I'm not
supposed to be...
looking for gorillas,
Bonnie.
I'm supposed to be
watching the ball.
That's my job.
I'm sorry.
Why am I always getting
screwed for doing my job?
Tell me who it is.
I want to know!
- Who is the gorilla, Bonnie?
- I'm sorry.
Bonnie.
Bonnie!
You have
reached the voice mailbox of...
- Bonnie.
- At the tone, please record your voice message...
Ahh!
Oh!
No.
No?
No, no! No, no!
No, no! No! No!
- Still not answering.
- What?
Not like him at all.
I'm not waiting
for this dipshit.
Can you just get
in the car!
No wait-o for dipshit-o.
Yeah, we...
We're gonna... We need...
¡Ándale!
I... I go to look?
- Yeah. Can you?
- Okay.
- Okay, señor.
- Perfect.
Butler!
Room?
- You want a room.
- Yes. Yes.
With TV?
Uh... Uh, fine. Yes.
Uh, 300.
Gracias.
Come, come.
My name is Ronaldo, and this
is my brother, Ernesto.
Just... Just tell us
if you need something.
Okay. Uh, actually, uh, do you know
where I can buy a cheap phone?
Uh, yeah,
just across the street.
- I just don't get it.
- There's nothing to get, babe.
Seriously. I told you,
Nelly's just a friend.
You gotta let it go,
all right?
No.
Live life to the fullest
and leave setbacks behind.
Together, we can lead
pharmaceuticals into the future.
Alleviate.
Initiate.
Innovate.
With Cannabax.
Medical marijuana is already
a multi-billion dollar industry.
It's already up and running
in 20 states
and the District of Columbia.
If you've got a card, you can legally
rip a bong in the Lincoln bedroom.
Wow.
All right, look, guys,
now, legally speaking,
isn't this
right on the line?
Well, it's on it.
It's not over it.
There's a reason why we
set up the lab in Mexico.
You could be operational the
moment the laws open up.
Marty, you-you-you really wanna
let AFT take this from you?
You're gonna be staring at their
taillights for the rest of all time.
The future of marijuana
is this pill.
You know this product
is revolutionary.
You know that by the time
everybody else catches up,
we will have established a brand
that can never be usurped.
- Think Pfizer and Viagra.
- Yeah.
They got there first.
There ain't no second.
Look...
most people will tell you
Buzz Aldrin walked on the moon.
But even a complete retard
will tell you
Neil Armstrong did it first.
And do you know
why he went first?
- He was mission commander?
- 'Cause the hatch opened on his side?
He went first because he pushed
Buzz Aldrin the fuck out of the way
and seized history
by the ball sack.
That's the story schools are afraid
to teach, but that's what happened.
I'm satisfied.
Jer?
I'm still not sure
about this.
Oh, Jerry!
The club is closing.
We've been dancing all night.
It's time to go home
and fuck.
Easy, Elaine.
What, Richard?
Nobody dances all night
unless they wanna fuck.
And Jerry here wants to.
He's just being shy.
I have a gun to my head.
I have a loaded gun
to my head.
Richard.
Richard!
I've been kidnapped!
I have a loaded gun
to my head!
So...
you guys understand
what to do?
- Yes? ¿Comprende?
- Yes, yes.
Does he comprende?
Okay. Good.
Richard Rusk's office.
Mia! I need
to speak to Richard!
Harold?
I need to speak to Richard!
Mr. Rusk?
I said hold my calls.
Mr. Rusk.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- Yep.
- Fuck yeah.
Mr. Rusk.
- Oh, my God.
- Right, right.
Mr. Rusk?
- Boss, are you there?
- Oh, shit.
Mia, out of curiosity,
exactly what part
of "hold my calls" couldn't
you wrap your head around?
I'm... I'm in a meeting.
I'm sorry. It's Harold, and I think
that there's something wrong.
Harold?
Uh...
Yeah, put him through.
Harold?
Richard!
Where are you? Why didn't you
come back with me and Elaine?
Richard! I've been taken!
- Taken?
- Elaine? I've been kidnapped!
They have a gun to my head!
I have a loaded gun to my head!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no, no! No! No!
Try and breathe and calm down and explain,
as clearly as you can, what's going on.
I'm somewhere in Mexico with a gun to
my head! How much clearer can I be?
Harold, it's okay.
We're here.
- Um...
- Ask them what they want.
What do they want?
They want five million
wired to an account.
Or they're going to hang me
from the bridge!
Five million what, pesos?
Peso... Dollars!
Harold, how exactly
did they arrive at a number
like five million dollars
for a person in your position?
You didn't tell them about
the K&R policy, did you?
They came to the hotel
and kidnapped me.
I had no choice!
God-fucking-damn it!
We're so fucked.
- Jesus Christ!
- Shh.
The number-one rule
about having
the fucking insurance policy
is never tell anyone we have
the fucking insurance policy!
Did you not attend the seminar?
He set up the seminar.
Aah! No!
Aah! Aah!
No! No more!
- Aah! Aah!
- Yes! Yes!
No!
Really fucking hamstrings our bargaining
position. You know that, right?
Bargaining? I just told you
they're going to kill me!
Yes. Bargaining. I'm in business.
That's what I do.
You walk through warehouses,
put little check marks on boxes.
- That's what you do.
- Don't be mean.
What about the policy?
You're gonna have to tell him.
Harold, I'm just gonna spit this out.
There is no policy.
What?
We had to make cutbacks.
Uh... Fuck.
There was a lot going out. We didn't have a
lot coming in. I had to let the policy lapse.
You kept sending me
down here with no insurance?
Yeah, but just
for a little while.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- What a fucking crybaby.
There's not enough time
in every day
for us to tell you all the things
we do not need to tell you, Harold.
No! No! No!
Nada! No!
Oh!
Aah!
- Aah!
- Fucking Mexicans.
- Harold?
- Richard!
All right. Hey, listen.
Harold, I am gonna get you
outta there, I swear to God.
Harold,
listen to me right now.
You tell whoever's got you
that there is no deal unless
they come way down on the price.
- What?
- Yeah, la cuenta...
Just... Harold,
can we call you back?
- What?
- You got a number?
- Richard. Richard.
- No, I need to speak to legal.
Richard.
Richard, don't leave me...
I'm gonna get somebody
in here who speaks Mexican.
No, Richard, don't leave me here!
Richard!
- Can you call us back?
- Richard!
Richard!
Gracias, guys.
Vamos.
Shit.
Five million dollars for
someone in middle management.
Do me a favor.
Just shut the fuck up.
You with your whole fucking, "Hey,
Elaine, I got the perfect guy for us.
My good buddy, Harold Sinka."
- Soyinka.
- "He's gonna fucking be perfect for the job.
He won't ask any questions, not
gonna cause any fucking trouble."
This is
a fucking clusterfuck!
Just stay focused.
I am focused.
What do we do now?
Do we call the cops?
Would it be such a bad thing
if he didn't come back?
What are you talking about?
We are not leaving Harold in
fucking Mexico. That's crazy.
You're the one who said
put him out of his misery.
I say crazy shit all the time.
I don't mean it literally.
But you said, literally,
put him out of his misery.
Oh, my fucking...
I meant not literally literally.
"Literally" is
something people say now.
- It doesn't mean a fucking thing.
- Okay.
They're going to be inspecting
the plant tomorrow,
and if they find anything off,
this whole deal is shot.
I don't need to tell you
what's gonna happen
if the feds catch fucking
wind of any of this on any level.
We are completely fucked.
I know a guy.
Here we go again.
You know a fucking guy.
No, I know a guy who might be
really good for this kind of thing.
Extraction.
- Jesus Christ.
- Special ops type things.
Boy.
This is really bad timing.
Fuck this. We've got this.
Richard,
we fucking got this.
We're a team.
Look, why don't I come over
to your loft tonight.
We'll just...
I'm not in there yet.
I'm still at that...
boutique hotel.
You told me last week
you moved in.
Did I tell you that?
Did I tell... I'm
gonna make this call.
I... I'm gonna just get
this thing sorted out.
Um, except that
if I change my mind,
I'm gonna give you a call,
which I probably will.
But I'm, you know,
maybe just, uh...
Whew!
Yeah, so...
Yeah, I'll read that.
Good meeting.
- Mia.
- Hmm?
Get my brother
on the phone, now.
Allô?
Oui.
Oh, yeah. Mitch?
Yeah, one moment.
Mitch.
Okay.
Hey, Rich!
- Mitch!
- How you doing, bro?
How's, uh... How's Nepal?
Uh, Haiti. I'm in Haiti.
Haiti. No, I knew that.
How... How... How is it?
It's a fucking mess
is what it is.
Uh, we're doing what we can.
Well, you're doing
God's work, so...
No, the earthquake
was God's work.
This is something else, man.
You're seriously all, uh,
religious-y and stuff?
It's not religious.
It's spiritual.
And I don't mock your
dirty little money-grabbing,
back-fucking-stabbing
corporate life.
No, it's not...
Dude, I'm not, I swear to God.
It's just... I hear through Mom that you've
turned over a new leaf, and it's great.
Mom's right. I've been good.
I've been doing good things
with my life.
I have a new path now. My mercenary
days are over. Look, what...
What do you want, Richard? You only
ever call if you want something,
so let's get to that part... the
greedy part, the selfish part.
All right.
You wanna help people, right?
You wanna help people. Help me, and
I will make it worth your while.
And then you can build
these people a schoolhouse
or a fucking GAP,
whatever the fuck they need.
You know, might I remind you that
you were sent there six months ago
to make a diplomat disappear.
You want me
to fucking kill somebody?
- Have you lost your fucking mind?
- Hey, man...
Did you not hear anything
I just fucking said?
I... I don't want... want you
to take anybody out for me.
I'm just... No, I need you
to bring somebody back.
- What phone is that?
- Hmm? Work gave it to me.
Hey, look. That's that guy
from the room next to ours.
Nice suit.
Why would somebody wearing a posh
suit be staying at our shit motel?
Miles, he has that, like, shoulder
holster gun thing under his arms.
Maybe he's a cop.
Or he's like a FBI guy.
Or, no, a DEA guy.
Yeah, he's a DEA guy,
on the trail
of some big drug thing,
and he's about
to bust somebody.
Oh, yeah,
somebody's going down.
All right,
let's go, shall we?
- But I haven't finished my margarita yet.
- You can get more later.
Babe, we're in Mexico. They brush their
teeth with tequila. Let's do it.
Amigo!
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Are you crying?
I'm sorry.
Did you not smoke every girl
in every fucking pageant
you ever entered?
That's what I thought.
You're a winner, Elaine.
You've always been a winner.
Who is Daddy's blue-ribbon girl?
Hmm?
That's right.
I am.
I'm the blue-ribbon girl.
Now, get your shit together.
Go handle your business.
Richard, it's me.
No. No, no, no, no. Shut up.
Shut up and let me
do the talking.
Hola. Hola, amigo.
Hola, shithead.
Better.
Hola, shithead. It's me.
Shut up. Now, I know
what you've been doing.
And I know about all these people are
going to lose their job, including me.
And I know that you
and Elaine are having sex.
Richard,
you are a bad person.
You know what happens
to bad people?
Bad things.
Bad things happen
to bad people.
So you can...
you can take your... carrot
and shove it up your
motherfucking lying buttocks,
because I can have bananas.
Harold Soyinka can have
all the bananas.
I'll have my bananas.
Oh, God. Phone.
It's that weird number.
Don't. Don't touch it.
You think it's him?
Just don't think about it.
God, I'm such a shit.
Bonnie, stop singing
sad Harold songs.
I mean, how many times do I have
to tell you? Guilt is for losers.
Now, you want something,
you go after it.
You fucking
make it happen.
Harold? He just...
He never understood that.
Now, I'm sorry.
He is a nice guy, but,
you know, he never
fucking grew a pair.
So it's that simple.
I know.
Thank you.
Mmm! Mmm! Mmm!
Who could that be?
I don't know.
- Surprise.
- Oh. Elaine.
Uh... Okay.
So I see you moved in
after all.
Uh, yeah.
Who do we have here,
Richard?
Hmm?
Do you have a name?
It's a deaf girl.
She's adorable.
Hello, deaf girl.
Bonnie, Elaine.
Elaine, Bonnie.
Bonnie is my...
She...
My interior decorator.
That's interesting,
because I thought you said
Harold's wife was
your interior decorator.
Yeah.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Now I see why you wanted
to leave him in Mexico.
What?
Elaine.
Ooh. Would you show me
your stomach?
'Cause I am
super curious.
Excuse me?
Richard here told me you were a
little fatty Patty back in the day.
Isn't that right,
Richard?
You know,
I've always wondered
what do they do
with all that... extra skin?
Ugh!
Listen, I don't know
what is going on...
That's right.
You don't know anything.
And you certainly
don't know this guy.
And I bet you don't know
what I had on the plane
to Mexico yesterday.
I don't care what you
had on the plane.
The petite filet.
Four glasses of champagne
and Richard's cock in my mouth
in the first-class bathroom.
Oh!
It's... Bonnie, she...
Come on, Riley.
Now, what do you say we
christen this fucking place?
"Live by the rules."
That is
what my father said.
"Work hard, respect the boss,
and you become rich in America.
Then you can come back home
a great success."
Bullshit.
- One hundred percent bullshit.
- Bullshit.
Just the other day, Richard invited
me into his office to play chess.
He wanted to show me how much he had
improved since we were at college.
So, he's playing white,
and he begins with f3.
Naturally,
I respond with e5.
Huh? What does
this crazy man do? G4.
Can you believe it? G4.
All I have to do
is move my queen to h4.
Checkmate.
But did I do it?
No. Why?
Because I had my father's
voice in my head.
"Respect the rules."
As a rule, you do not
defeat your boss,
especially when you
want a promotion.
That is the story
of my time in America.
Play by the rules?
Bullshit.
Are they your friends?
Ah.
Friendly.
Where...
Where is this other bar?
Señor, donde...
donde the, uh...
the other bar?
I need the bathroom.
Amigo.
Amigo, I need the bath...
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Monarch butterflies go through
four generations each year.
The first three generations hatch from their
cocoon state and live for up to six weeks,
but the fourth generation continues to
live on for up to six or eight months...
so that they can migrate
to a warmer climate
and birth a new generation
in the spring.
They are one of the great
miracles of nature.
- I've gotta go, baby. Sorry.
- What?
Babe.
- If you want to take pictures, you can do it.
- What the fuck?
Babe, how many butterflies
do you need to see? Really.
- What are we doing?
- What?
- Why are you with me?
- Here we go.
I'm serious, Miles.
Why are you with me?
I don't know, Sunny.
Fucking hell.
That guy looks like
he needs help.
- Well, hopefully someone will pick him up.
- That's the guy from the plaza.
- The one with the shoulder holster?
- Stop the car.
- I'm not stopping the car for a fucking DEA agent.
- Stop the fucking car, Miles!
Please.
Sunny.
You okay?
- Sunny!
- Oh, my God!
Are you all right? Sir? Sir,
can you hear me? Please?
- Sunny, don't touch him!
- Oh, God, he's... Help me, Miles.
This is good. This is good.
Right, we're here.
- Mr. Rusk?
- What?
I was just wondering
about Harold.
What about him?
Well, he didn't sound so good yesterday,
and he didn't call in today. Is he okay?
Mia, a simple quiz. The job of a receptionist
is to A: Make calls or B: Answer them?
B?
B, yeah. Is this everything?
All company policies contracts,
leases, travel and insurance riders.
Okay, great. Hey, great
game the other night.
Uh, I'll be
in the conference room.
No more interruptions.
Yes, sir, Mr. Rusk, sir.
Keep that up, you'll
passive-aggressive yourself
straight to the unemployment line, then you'll
have plenty of time to worry about Harold.
Asshole.
- Hello.
- Rich, it's Mitch.
Oh. Mitch.
Hey. Oh, thank God.
Yeah, t-t-tell me
you found him.
I've tracked down dictators
in caves, Richard.
I can find a guy
in middle management.
Miles will be back soon
with your painkillers.
Those are gonna make you
feel a lot better.
Listen, you are very kind, but,
really, I will be okay on my own.
I think you ought to have someone
just keep an eye on you.
You're really beat up.
I'm Sunny, by the way.
I've never met anyone
named Sunny before.
Well, I never met a Harold.
So we're even stephen.
You know, if you
google the name Harold,
it's the most common name with the least
amount of famous people associated with it.
Well,
why don't you go by Harry?
There are a lot of famous Harrys, like
that magician with the water tank.
- Houdini.
- Yeah.
And Harry S. Truman,
the president.
And lots of singers.
Harry Potter, obviously.
I love Harry Potter.
I've read every single book.
Harry.
- Harry Soyinka.
- Yeah, I like that.
Okay, it's official. I'm gonna
call you Harry from now on.
I've got Jerry on line one.
Hey, Jerry.
Elaine.
I heard AFT was crying
when they got the news.
Guess they felt like they
danced with you all night too.
- Someone's gotta go home alone, right?
- Unless you're into threesomes.
Uh, Elaine, so, uh, anyway,
been going over our departments.
A lot of redundancies.
Fire whoever you want.
Well, the problem might be
right at the top.
With me and Marty, we're not
gonna need both you and Richard.
Have you guys talked about this?
Hey, Jer, how about you and I get
together for a drink tonight?
Bat a few ideas around.
I don't know.
Well... Well, yeah. Okay.
I'll let my secretary
get you all the information.
- That's great.
- Great.
Hey, Elaine...
Hello?
Fuck!
Relax, Richard. It's under control.
This is a midnight run.
Well, let's just talk about
the money later, okay?
Richie, we'll talk about
the money now, all right?
You tend to have a faulty
memory where money's concerned.
None of your business bullshit.
One million for the ransom, 200
grand for me and the Haiti kids.
A million dollars.
A million dollars
for Harold Soyinka.
That's like paying a thousand
bucks for a Whopper Jr.
Yeah, well, think of it
as karma for banging his wife.
Great, just... just a million!
Just go do whatever you do.
All right. He'll be on
the next plane to Chicago.
Thank you.
I... I know that whatever happened
to you is none of my business,
but is there anybody
that you need to call?
Uh...
no.
My wife just left me.
But what about friends?
There's no one to call.
Well...
I like the way you talk, Harry. You have
a really cool accent. Are you Jamaican?
- No.
- Oh.
I'm Nigerian.
I don't know much about Nigeria, except
once I got an e-mail from a Nigerian prince
saying that he would give me a ton
of money if I helped him out.
You didn't send him
the money, did you?
'Cause you might have been
sending it to my uncle.
Your uncle does that?
Like, try and steal
from people like that?
Yes, he's one of those people.
He tried to get my father
to join him, but he would not.
Now my uncle has lots of houses,
land, sports cars, and a yacht,
and my father is a poor man.
The world is upside down, Sunny.
I don't think it pays
to be a good person.
I mean, look at you.
You seem to be a good person.
Do you have a sports car?
Do you have a yacht?
I don't need
a sports car or a yacht.
Well, I'm glad you didn't
help my uncle pay for his.
I think you're wrong, Harry.
I think the world is just fine.
I think it's some of the
people in it who are wrong.
Trust me.
I have good instincts.
I make bad decisions,
but I have good instincts.
You'll see, things are gonna
start to get better for you.
Harry!
What's going...
Wait!
Okay, okay, okay.
- Put it on!
- What-What? I don't understand!
In your face!
In your head!
- Your head!
- In your head!
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Put it on!
Put it on!
Harry!
Harry.
Sunny?
So I couldn't get
Paracetamol, but I did...
- Uh, oh! Ooh!
- Shh. Richard sent me.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
What about the ransom?
Why didn't they pay the ransom?
Who gives a fuck
about the ransom?
I'm gonna have you back in
the States in time for dinner.
Mm.
- Sunny.
- Miles?
- Miles!
- Sunny?
Miles?
Miles.
- Sunny!
- Miles, I'm in here!
- Oh.
- Are you...
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What time is it?
What? I don't know.
- Oh, no.
- What?
Uh...
Oh, fuck.
- I've gotta go. Um...
- What?
I'm really sorry, babe.
Go to my room.
Lock the door.
Where are you going?
I'll be back soon.
- Ah.
- Beginner.
Ah.
Ah, sí.
No.
Hmm?
Harold.
Harold!
Uhh!
Ohh!
Harold, come back here!
Harold!
Stop! Shit. S-Stop.
Stop!
Stop! Shit!
Sorry.
- Excuse me.
- Hey!
Hey!
Okay.
Ah, the genius wakes.
So...
riddle me something,
shithead.
Why does a man run away from
someone who's saved his life?
Hmm? You don't know?
All right.
Harold, who are these two?
They are tourists
from the motel.
Really? You sure?
What about
those two assholes?
They-They run the motel.
They run the motel?
Mm.
You weren't kidnapped,
were you?
You set this up yourself.
On the one hand, I am
surprised you had the balls.
On the other...
this shit show can only be
the work of a fucking amateur.
Why'd you do it?
Money?
Revenge 'cause he was
banging your wife?
You-You didn't know?
Ah, shit.
Try not to take it
too personally.
I thought he was my friend.
Remember the, uh, story
about five years ago,
a woman in Pennsylvania
kept a black bear as a pet.
She looked after it, fed it. And then
one day, it mauled her, you know?
She's shocked.
I mean, she-she thought
they were friends.
But it's a fucking bear,
Harold.
Yeah.
We're gonna need
a couple of new passports
after, uh, that incident
at the airport.
Who'd you wanna be? I'm gonna
let you choose your own name.
You're forging passports?
This is a magic box, my friend.
I've been 25 different people
in my life,
and the 200 grand
I'm getting for your ass
is going right
into my little account
in the Grand Caymans.
- Two hundred thousand?
- Yep.
Is that all I'm worth?
No, no. I was authorized
to go as high as a million.
Richard's gonna be so happy
that he doesn't have to pay it.
He's such a greedy fucker.
So they do know
you have me?
No, not yet.
Why would you settle for 200 thousand
when you can make more than double that?
Oh, Harold.
You wanna go for the ransom?
Why not? You've already
done the hard part.
You have me, you have
the offshore account.
Look at me.
I have no job to go
back to, no wife.
Why do you think I ran?
I cannot go back to Chicago.
My life there
has been a complete lie.
You're waking up, Harold.
I like that.
That's a lot of food packs.
Medical supplies.
All right. Done.
You have a deal, my friend.
But you can forget
about a 50-50 split.
I could kill you right now, tell
them that you're still alive
and blow off
with the whole million.
But I'm not gonna do that,
Harold. I've changed.
Freedom, huh?
Eighty-twenty...
'cause I like you.
You got an underdog thing
going on, Harold.
Reminds me of the Haitians.
- What is that?
- It's an injectable microchip.
- I need to keep track of you.
- I won't run again.
- I promise I won't run again.
- Harold. Harold, I can't take the chance.
No, no! Aah!
I don't like needles!
- Just give me... Look away. Look away.
- No, no, no! No, please!
It's over. It's over.
- Motherfucker!
- It's over, man. Shit.
Elaine,
this is really fun.
So glad you made that call.
You called me, Jerry.
You're right.
Hey, here's a toast.
To Neil Armstrong.
Yeah, it's been
a great night, Jerry,
but we should probably start talking
some business, don't you think?
Oh, let's relax, Elaine.
Business isn't going anywhere.
I was thinking maybe
we keep it personal tonight.
Dance till the club closes,
if you catch my meaning.
You dirty dog.
Okay.
All right, well,
let's have a look at it.
What?
Let's see what
you're working with.
I am catching
your meaning, right?
I'm not gonna... I'm not... I'm not.
I'm not... I'm not...
Go on, Jerry.
Just toss it against your thigh.
No one's looking.
Look, you take that baby out,
and if I like what I see...
I'll let you take me
home tonight.
But if I don't think that's up to snuff, then,
well, we start talking business right now.
What do you say?
Let me tell you why
you don't need Richard.
This is fantastic, Mitch.
Really impressive.
Well, it's not
my first rodeo.
- Oh.
- It's Richard.
Get out of the frame.
Don't say a word.
Hey. Hey, Rich.
Uh, listen, man,
extraction's looking iffy.
I don't want
an extraction anymore.
Good. Good, 'cause
the deal's the way to go.
- There's not gonna be a deal either.
- What?
What do you mean?
It seems that while we dropped
the kidnap and ransom policy
there was another policy that we
overlooked: corporate life insurance.
Overlooked?
If Harold were to...
end up dead while conducting
business in a foreign country...
this would pay out five million
dollars to the corporation.
Hmm. Yeah.
Yeah, well, that... that's
not a deal I'm willing to do.
Don't start with any of this, "I'm
not gonna take anyone out for you!"
Okay, just relax.
Just relax.
And I will give you one million
reasons to kill this guy.
Really?
One million?
It's not enough.
- What about two million?
- You fucking pig, Mitch!
Oh, come on,
it's for a good cause.
Think of someone other
than yourself for once.
Just wire the money, shithead,
and you have a deal.
- Did they double it to two million?
- They did!
- Great!
- Yeah.
- Great.
- Yeah!
- You are very good at that.
- Yeah.
What do you say we, uh,
hit the town to celebrate?
- Yes! Yes, we need to celebrate. Fiesta!
- Huh? Yeah?
Fiesta!
- Come on, dance.
- No, I'm good. I don't dance.
- Come on!
- No, Harold, I won't. No, Harold.
No. Harold.
I don't... I don't...
I don't... I don't dance.
- Come on!
- Okay.
Okay. All right.
- Whoo!
Look.
I'm here to see Mr. Vega.
Hey, gringo, you're late.
Oh, fuck,
that was too good.
Oh.
Oh, man.
You know, I really feel like
things are turning around for me.
Yeah?
Thank you, Mitch.
Thank you.
Sure.
All right. Harold, there's
something I have to tell you.
Uh...
Richard's my brother.
Yeah.
Richard Rusk?
Yep, unfortunately.
- Fuck!
- Ah.
Can't fucking do it.
Why... Why have you got that out?
What are you doing?
It seems Richard's company wants to
claim the insurance policy money.
No, no. No, no, no. Richard
said they have canceled it.
- They have canceled the policy.
- No, your life insurance policy, Harold.
So...
- But I thought you liked me.
- I do like you.
No, no, no. But you-you-you said
you liked my whole underdog thing.
- I love your underdog thing.
- So, Mitch, please.
Look, I made a deal with Richard that
if I sacrificed you, I can help...
Sacrifice...
You want to sacrifice...
- ...thousands... hundreds of thousands of underdogs.
- You want to sacrifice me. Hey!
You understand? Harold.
Oh, Lord Almighty!
Shh.
Harold. Shit.
Please, God,
save me from this man.
Please, I beg you. Help me in my
moment of need. Please, Jesus. Please.
Harold, nobody's coming
in your moment of need.
You really believe in God?
Of course I believe in God. What kind
of person does not believe in God?
Me. I... I don't.
Well, I mean, I...
I guess I kind of do,
but not... not in a life-or-death
situation, Harold.
You know, I... I'm looking for
something, but something more...
more reliable, you know?
Yeah, I mean, sure, I tried reading
the Bible a couple of times, but...
I mean, the Old Testament, Harold.
You can't take that shit seriously.
And the New Testament, I mean...
- You take the Bible seriously?
- Of course.
Really? Like the whole thing
with Peter and Judas.
Remember? So-So Peter
denies Jesus three times.
Three fucking times, man.
Now, Judas, on the other hand,
yeah, I mean, he fucked up.
He sold Jesus out, all right?
But he felt bad about it.
He hung himself, man!
He felt guilty!
He had a lot more fucking
character than fucking Peter.
I mean, Peter.
How do you get behind a religion
that demonizes a guy like Judas
and makes a saint
out of a guy like Peter?
Well...
one was a man
who had a crisis of faith.
The other one sold his soul
for his own gain.
So you have to ask yourself,
which one are you?
Well...
Put it on!
Ah.
Okay.
Here.
Nelly said it'd be easy.
It is. Getting
out of here isn't.
There's one exit
and security checks everything.
Mate. Mate! How the fuck am I
supposed to get out of here?
It's okay. I have a little plan.
Come on.
Nelly, you fucking bitch.
Alto.
Ah.
Come on.
Let's take the sad song
and make it better.
Hey.
Oh.
Hello, Harold.
Put this on.
When you get outside, you go to
your car and don't look back.
Follow me.
Let's go.
Okay, this way.
Sunny said you were fucking DEA.
The-The-The gates!
The gates!
Where are you?
What the fuck?
Angel!
What the motherfuck?
Harold, I need you to be very calm
right now. You understand me?
My name is not Angel. I'm Victor Cruz.
I'm with the DEA.
I infiltrated Villegas, and then your buddy
Sanchez showed up, so I infiltrated Promethium.
You know, you work
for bad people, Harold.
You speak English?
Yes, I speak English!
Fuck!
Go, go, go, go!
Aah!
What is wrong with these people?
On the side! On the side!
He's coming up on the side!
I don't think
he can survive that.
Ohh!
Hey!
Harold!
You okay, buddy?
Are you okay?
You saved my life,
Harold.
I need your help.
I can't go back home.
There's nothing
for me there. Nothing.
Please.
You know, people disappear
all the time, Harold.
You died here tonight.
You understand me?
I understand.
This has everything you'll need
to bring down Richard Rusk.
Aah.
Have a great life, Harold.
Babe.
What the fuck?
It's a tough situation, but these were very
dangerous people you were dealing with.
And I was so scared.
You did the right thing
here today.
Go!
Richard Rusk?
- Yeah.
- I have a warrant for your arrest.
Give him the ball.
After an intense six-month trial
which saw longtime business partner Elaine
Markinson turn state's evidence against him,
president of Promethium
Pharmaceuticals, Richard Rusk,
was given a 15-year sentence to be
served in Genesee Federal Prison.
The verdict, which took the jury less
than four hours of deliberation,
brings an end and perhaps
a small measure of justice
to the shocking and tragic tale
of Harold Soyinka.
You know, my dear friend,
Harold, would still be alive.
I mean, Nigeria,
Chicago, Mexico.
I'm... I'm surprised the guy
lasted as long as he did.
Richard Rusk!
Adam Riley!
Michael Clone!
John Axelrad!
Anthony Lynch!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-