USRCS
employees are advised to avoid
prolonged physical contact
with Bad Batch inmates.
This includes eye contact.
Bad Batch 5035 to 5040,
step into the room.
USRCS employees
are advised to limit eye contact
with Bad Batch inmates
- to no longer than 10 seconds.
- All Bad Batch,
once you are tagged,
go to the left side of the room
and get your rations.
Single-file line, please.
USRCS
employees are never to inquire
- details regarding fittings.
- Come on, folks.
Let's keep 'em moving.
Bad Batch Inmate 5040,
Arlen Mae Johnson?
Take a seat right there, miss.
I need your right ear, please.
USRCS
employees are reminded
to clearly differentiate
between personal view statements
and views, statements,
positions made on behalf
of the agency or association.
Bad Batch 5039,
you can move out.
USRCS
employees are advised to avoid
prolonged physical contact
with Bad Batch inmates.
All right 5040,
you can move out.
Step through.
Stand back from the gate.
You wanna radio it in?
It's hotter
than the devil's a-hole out here.
Whoo! Get me back to that AC.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ Oh, she leads a lonely life ♪
♪ When she woke up late
in morning light ♪
♪ And the day has just begun ♪
♪ She opened up her eyes
and thought ♪
♪ Oh, what a morning ♪
♪ It's not a day for work ♪
♪ It's a day for catching sun ♪
♪ Just lying on the beach
and having fun ♪
- Help me! Help me!
- ♪ She's going ♪
♪ To get you,
all that she wants ♪
♪ Is another baby
she's gone tomorrow, boy ♪
♪ All that she wants ♪
♪ Is another baby, yeah ♪
♪ All that she wants
is another baby ♪
♪ She's gone tomorrow, boy ♪
♪ All that she wants ♪
♪ Is another baby, yeah ♪
♪ So if you are in sight
and the day is right... ♪
No.
No. No!
♪ It is a night for passion ♪
♪ But the morning
means good-bye ♪
♪ Beware of what is flashing
in her eyes ♪
♪ She's going to get you ♪
♪ All that she wants ♪
♪ Is another baby ♪
♪ She's gone tomorrow, boy ♪
♪ All that she wants ♪
♪ Is another baby, yeah ♪
♪ Is another baby ♪
♪ She's gone tomorrow boy... ♪
♪ Uhh ♪
♪ This one's dedicated
to all the haters out there ♪
♪ Jealous of us
because we're better than you ♪
♪ Yolandi Vi$$er,
bring the sparks? ♪
♪ Jou ma se poes
in 'n fish paste jar ♪
♪ D. D. J-J-J ♪
♪ Jou ma se poes
in 'n fish paste jar ♪
♪ Hi-hi-hi Tek ♪
♪ Moenie kom kak
praat nie my bra ♪
♪ Yolandi Vi$$er ♪
♪ Fresh and depressed
vat 'n picture ♪
♪ Jou ma se poes
in 'n fish paste jar ♪
♪ He was the wrong ninja
to fuck with ♪
♪ Yo, I am the ninja
in charge over here ♪
♪ But no fear when I scope
a rhyme in your ear ♪
♪ Fuck with the wrong ninja ♪
♪ This time
what's the matter with you?
♪ Should've known better ♪
♪ Than to fuck with a ninja
with a attitude ♪
♪ I wasn't mad at you but now
you mad at me and jealous ♪
♪ Little spunk poofy rappers
like Anthony en Dennis ♪
♪ Let me help
to make you famous ♪
♪ Jissis but you rap cock ♪
♪ When you rap
you actually sound like ♪
- ♪ You're having a fat cock ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Why you
so obsessed with me? ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Jesus Christ you should
see how these boys stalk me ♪
♪ Follow my every move
like a Sea Point moffie ♪
♪ Fuck you ♪
♪ And all your ♪
♪ Maak klaar met die spiff quote
from the licks ♪
♪ Yo, there's not a rapper
out there who can touch me ♪
♪ If you don't believe me
run up and try to punch me ♪
♪ Jou ma se poes
in 'n fish paste jar ♪
♪ D. D. J-J-J ♪
♪ Jou ma se poes
in 'n fish paste jar ♪
♪ Hi-hi-hi Tek ♪
♪ Oh oh vat's it yuketa? ♪
Help, somebody!
Hey!
Help! I just want to go home!
Please, somebody!
Oh, my God! Please!
Huh? Goddamn.
Come on.
Be right there.
Okay, come on in.
Is it ready?
Tore her ass up.
Homegirl got fucked up!
Fuck, homes.
She stink, man.
Right.
I'm surprised
she's alive, homes.
I can't find
my fuckin' shoes.
Where are my shoes?
Hey, y'all seen my shoes?
It's all rusted out.
Doesn't even fuckin' work.
If you forget
everything else but not this,
you have nothing to worry about.
It's the one thing...
Keep walkin', motherfucker.
Keep walkin'.
There's one thing
you must never forget.
Never forget.
Never, never, never,
never, never, never, never,
never, never forget
this one thing.
If you remember
everything else,
if you forget this one thing...
Whoo!
If you remember everything else
and you forget this one thing,
you will... you will have
done nothing in your life!
Nothing! Nothing!
This is the one thing,
the one thing
you must never forget!
Give me some fucking noodles!
One dollar!
- Demon!
- One dollar!
She's a goddamn...
she's a goddamn demon!
You no pay, no noodle!
No noodle for you, no pay!
Thank you very much. Huh?
- Hey, what's the thing?
- Shut up, motherfucker!
The thing?
The thing.
How should I know?
Find out for yourself.
You find out for yourself.
No one is gonna tell you.
You have to figure it out
for yourself.
You have to figure it out.
Forget everything else
but this one thing.
You have nothing
to worry about.
Just one thing.
Must never forget.
All right, get up! Get up!
Ohh!
♪ If I listen to your lies ♪
♪ Would you say ♪
♪ I'm a man ♪
♪ Without conviction ♪
♪ Who doesn't know ♪
- I can't do it again.
- ♪ How to sell ♪
- ♪ A contradiction ♪
- Please don't do this! Please!
- ♪ You come and go ♪
- Please! Please,
I'm begging you!
Please don't do this!
- ♪ Karma, Karma, Karma... ♪
- I can't do this again!
I can't do it!
- ♪ You come and go ♪
- Please don't do this!
I can't do it again!
I can't do it. Please.
Oh, God, please.
Please don't make me!
Please just let me go! Please!
I don't want any...
please don't do this!
Please, please, please,
I'm begging you!
Please don't do this!
Oh, God! No, please! Please!
Please, I can't! No, no, no.
♪ That my love ♪
♪ Was an addiction ♪
♪ When you... ♪
So sick of this shit.
Sick and tired of this shit.
Hmm.
♪ That's how it feels to you ♪
♪ Just to be next to you ♪
♪ I'm like a firefly ♪
♪ Trapped in the spotlight ♪
♪ I try to get alone with you ♪
♪ And then I don't know
what to do ♪
♪ I don't know what to do ♪
♪ I'm calling
when I'm around you ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Come on, turn ♪
♪ Come, come, all right ♪
♪ Just walk towards the light ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
There. Push, push.
Ohh!
Ohh. Ohh.
Ohh.
Mm.
Where do y'all come from?
You come from Comfort?
Look, I ain't got no problem.
No problem with you.
You're a Bridge person.
We're just out here
looking for plates, that's all.
That's right.
Looking for plates.
Honey, stay back.
Does your kid eat people, too?
I'm just trying
to live out here,
same as you.
Ain't easy for me neither.
Look, we the same, we are.
No, we ain't.
We ain't the same.
We both Bad Batch, right?
We ain't the fuckin' same!
Do you hear me?
Please.
Just let us go.
Yeah, I did that.
Begged.
Pleaded.
Just like you're doing.
Tell me what you want.
I'll do it.
So, tell me
what you want me to do
- and I'll do it.
- Shut up.
Just tell me what you want...
There's fuckin' nothing
you can do.
You kind of stink, kid.
You want me to take
your socks off?
My name's Arlen.
What's your name?
Look, no one cares
about you now.
I could have just left you
out there in the desert.
Is that where you wanna be?
Hmm?
Now, you like this bunny,
don't you?
Do you wanna keep him?
Then, you got to do
exactly what I say.
That dead woman over there.
There was... a kid was with her.
Did you see this kid?
Did you see her?
You better start talking,
old man.
Did you see her?
What you want?
Keep it steady.
Nice straight line.
Let me see.
That's good.
A little bit more down here.
Yeah, baby.
Come on, baby! Do that move!
Move it down.
Dang, baby!
People of Comfort,
good evening!
Give us The Dream!
Make some noise
for the one and only!
The Dream!
Come on, Dream!
Change my life!
He looked at me!
- We love you!
- I love you, too.
Heal my life with The Dream!
I've been wanting
to dream all my life!
Come on now, Dream!
I love you, Dream!
I've got a question.
Why are we out here?
Just what are we doing
in the middle
of the goddamn desert tonight?
Jimmy! Jimmy!
That's right. That's right.
You want that music
only Jimmy can make.
Let me tell you
something about Jimmy.
You know why Jimmy's here?
- Why?
- Jimmy!
- He's Bad Batch.
Yeah, yeah!
Bad Batch, fucker!
Nonfunctioning
member of society.
That's what they told him.
That's right.
All of us here,
we weren't good enough.
Smart enough.
- Yeah!
- Young enough.
- Healthy enough.
- You're right!
Wealthy enough.
Sane enough.
Freaks.
Parasites.
Bad Batch!
Motherfucking Bad Batch!
This here is the Bad Batch.
Bad Batch, bitches!
We ain't good. We're bad.
Yeah, yeah,
that's right, Bad Batch!
Yeah, Bad Batch.
That's right.
We're bad, baby!
Now, there's only one rule here,
and it's this.
It's time to wake up.
It's time to find... The Dream.
The Dream!
All glory to The Dream!
We're a Bad Batch,
motherfuckers!
Bad Batch, motherfuckers!
Yeah!
Yee-haw!
- Yeah.
- What's wrong with that?
Is this your rabbit?
Where is she?
She was just right here?
That kid.
She was right here a second ago.
She's got to be here somewhere.
Where did that kid go?
I lost her.
That kid. I hope she's okay.
What did I do?
She's got to be here.
I know she's got to be here.
She's got to be here somewhere.
What did I do? What did I do?
Where did that kid go?
Hey, you guys seen a little girl?
Hey, you seen a kid?
What am I gonna do now?
I hate this place.
What is this place?
This place.
Here's what you do.
Okay, here's what you do.
Go somewhere. Go far away.
You go far away.
Somewhere. Leave Comfort.
Leave Comfort.
Just go for a walk.
Somewhere. Anywhere.
Wow.
It's so big.
So big.
Wow.
It's so big.
Wow! It's so big.
It's pretty, so pretty.
Is that what
it always looks like?
Doesn't always look like that.
Wow.
Thought it was
pretty at first, but...
now, I'm not so sure.
I don't even really know
what it is.
Do you?
You're big.
Strange, isn't it?
Here we are
in the darkest corner
of this Earth,
and we're afraid
of our own kind.
Hmm.
You know where you are?
You are a long way from Comfort.
And without this,
you go nowhere.
Did you see a kid
look like that?
Did you see her?
No.
I'm going
to take you to Comfort,
and you will go inside
and find her for me.
Listen to me good.
I don't care
about nothing or nobody
except that little girl.
And I'm going to kill you
if you don't find her for me.
Comprende?
Mm.
Vámonos!
I'm thirsty.
This make you more thirsty.
We got guns at the wall.
They'll shoot if they see you.
Mm.
So what?
That's your kid?
What if I can't find her?
You will find her.
Trade you for that leg.
I'm being friendly, dude.
I can just keep it all
for myself.
It's up to you.
Wait!
No!
Mm!
Fuck.
Mm-hmm.
No.
No, no, no, no! No!
Let me go!
Aah!
Vámonos!
Would you turn around,
please?
What's your deal?
How come
you're in the Bad Batch?
Gang related?
Drug related?
Illegal.
No papers.
You a Mexican?
Cubano, from Havana.
I heard of Cuba.
That's in the tropics, right?
Near Hawaii?
Here is Cuba.
I am born here, in Havana.
I come with a boat to America
when I'm 16.
To Miami.
Miami.
What did you do there?
Like, what did you do in Miami?
A lot of thing.
I make tattoos,
construction.
I do this, that.
No big deal.
I got this one when I was 13.
And this.
See this one?
It's from the first boy
I ever loved.
He was a musician.
We both got matching ones
at the same time.
And this one,
5040.
What's your number?
Come on.
What's the big deal?
Just show me your number.
Your kind,
you're evil.
That's what you are.
Evil.
You don't see things
how they are.
You only see things
how you are.
I don't care.
I hate you.
Get it?
I hate all of y'all.
No problema para mí.
It's okay.
Doesn't change nothing for me.
Doesn't change nothing for you.
Ohh.
Ohh!
Come on. Come with me.
Come on.
Let's go, man. I'm getting
the fuck out of here.
Come on.
Hurry the fuck up.
Let's go now.
Open up.
Close it up.
- What's up, man?
- Hey, what's going on?
What's your number, fool?
5828.
Been out in the desert
two days, man.
I need some food.
Are you guys gonna help me
out or what?
What's up
with the white girl, man?
Found her ass out there
with one of them Bridge people.
All right, kick back, homey.
- Thanks, man.
- Welcome to Comfort ese.
Yeah, welcome to Comfort.
♪ I woke in the dark ♪
♪ Called out
into the cold night ♪
♪ A voice from outside ♪
♪ Drew me away ♪
♪ From the light ♪
♪ Follow me now ♪
♪ And never return ♪
♪ To your dawn ♪
♪ I'm drawn to the light ♪
♪ Nevermore, nevermore ♪
♪ Nevermore ♪
♪ All the colours of the dark ♪
♪ You will find ♪
♪ Will remind you ♪
♪ Of someone who ♪
♪ Once was you ♪
♪ But madness ♪
♪ Is all you'll find ♪
♪ He walked in front ♪
♪ And found he was lost ♪
♪ In the dark ♪
♪ I drew him through the night ♪
♪ Away from the call ♪
♪ Of the light ♪
♪ I followed you here ♪
♪ And now can return ♪
♪ To my door ♪
♪ I'll go to the dark ♪
♪ Evermore, evermore ♪
♪ Evermore ♪
♪ All the colours of the dark ♪
♪ You will find ♪
♪ Will remind you ♪
♪ Of someone who ♪
♪ Was once just you ♪
♪ But madness ♪
♪ Is all you'll find ♪
♪ You'll wander ♪
♪ Through your mind ♪
♪ You won't be coming back ♪
♪ Nevermore, nevermore ♪
♪ Never ♪
Excuse me.
Have you seen this kid?
No.
You seen this kid?
Excuse me, sir.
Have you seen this kid
anywhere?
Uh-uh.
No?
Can you look out
for her, please?
Oh, he ain't
ever gonna be wasted.
Hey, have you guys
seen a little girl?
I ain't seen shit, man.
I wish they'd stop
making pennies.
I hate pennies.
I hate 'em!
Hey!
- I keep losing things.
- Hey.
Don't wanna be a loser.
I wanna be a finder.
Finder finds things.
Loser loses them.
Yeah. I need to find a kid.
A little girl.
Yeah.
- She's about this tall.
- Yeah.
- You've seen her?
- Where?
- Hey, you wanna play
with my puzzle?
You wanna play?
No, I'm not gonna play
with your puzzle.
- Thank you.
- I'll call you later.
Yeah, baby!
Woo!
It's happening!
Yeah.
Yeah, baby.
♪ Moonlight sets ♪
♪ Feels like seven years ♪
♪ Since I left ♪
♪ Can't you see
behind this love ♪
♪ Tell me you don't know ♪
♪ If you don't like
what you see ♪
Take a good look there.
That's the economy of Comfort
sitting right in front of you.
Right beautiful.
See, you can catch
more flies with honey.
But who wants flies?
Remind me your name again,
Sweetheart.
It's Arlen.
Let me ask you
a question, Arlen.
When you shit here in Comfort,
your shit goes away.
That accurate?
I guess.
You shit.
It leaves.
You know why it leaves?
Um...
because the toilet
takes it someplace?
Yes, it does.
Takes it where it takes it...
because of me.
'Cause I hate the idea
that my sons and daughters
would have to stew
in their own shit.
Cows stand in their shit.
They stand in their shit...
'cause they're cows.
Pigs stand in their shit...
'cause they're pigs.
Some misbehaving humans
been making hamburgers
out of my sons
and daughters.
We are not cows.
We don't stand in our shit.
Reason we don't...
is because
I won't let that happen.
I got each and every toilet
in Comfort
taking that shit
from all your little asses
and sending it down the pipes
till it reaches a place
where no one thinks about it
and no one smells it.
Ain't that nice of me?
But you don't like it here,
do you?
No, I just...
Costs a lot to be here.
Cost you an arm and a leg.
Where would you rather be?
It's all right.
You know what I see
when I look at you?
A sailboat out in the sea...
with no wind.
What is it you want, Arlen?
If you could have one thing,
anything,
what would it be?
Anything?
Anything at all.
A time machine.
Why?
So I could go back.
Fix things.
Make it better.
All the things you've done
have put you right here,
on this couch,
in this room,
with me.
Close your eyes.
Close them.
What do you really want?
I wanna be the solution
for something.
You know what this is?
It's a tomato.
First,
it was a seed.
You take care of a garden,
and it takes care of you back.
You feed it,
it feeds you.
Few things in this world
operate like that,
fair and square.
It just needs a place to grow.
It grows and grows.
Then it comes out
and it's part of the world.
Because you know what
The Dream really is?
It's life.
Life is The Dream.
The only dream.
I want The Dream.
What dream is that?
This one here.
Like they have.
Make up a room for our guest.
Is everything okay?
Hey. I'm sorry.
I guess I'm just a bit nervous.
That's okay.
Can you come in for a second?
Yeah, of course.
Is this really necessary?
Come here, kid.
We're going.
Bring her down!
You wanna see it all over
your fucking walls?
Come here.
Promise me something.
Take care of this rabbit.
Come on.
Yeah.
When we're out
and clear of the wall,
I'll let her go.
Come here.
Let's go, kid.
I'm real disappointed
in you, Arlen.
Real disappointed.
Once we're out,
I'll let her go.
I swear.
Yo, check this shit
out right here, homes.
- Open it, Nacho.
- Open the gate, homes.
Open it!
Come on.
Bye, guerita.
Don't come back,
you crazy bitch.
♪ Better go and get ♪
♪ Better inside ♪
Get in the front.
♪ Here inside ♪
♪ I told you I would get you ♪
Come on.
♪ The back of the house ♪
♪ I told you I would find you ♪
♪ Paper trails on a mountain ♪
♪ And fruits on a table ♪
♪ A wooden house to live in ♪
♪ A baby; take care of ♪
♪ The grass is green ♪
♪ But the... ♪
♪ The sun is slow ♪
♪ Better find a way ♪
♪ To get through to you ♪
♪ Where are you
when I need you? ♪
♪ Where did you go? ♪
♪ How can I find you
when I need you? ♪
♪ Where should I go? ♪
Miel.
You good? Okay?
♪ Paper trails on a mountain ♪
♪ And fruits on a table ♪
♪ A wooden house to live in ♪
♪ A baby; take care of ♪
Hey.
Wait.
What are you doing
right now?
Do you wanna hang out
or something?
You are very confused, no?
Not really.
What you think I am, gringa?
What if all these things
that happened to us
happened to us
so the next things
that gonna happen to us
can happen to us?
You brought back my kid.
You done now.
You can go.
Go back to Comfort.
I'm not going back there.
In this place
is only death for you.
Is like that.
Well, I like it here.
What do you like?
Where is here?
Look around.
Is nothing.
I want spaghetti
because the other man
gave me spaghetti.
I want spaghetti.
I'm hungry. I want spaghetti!
I want spaghetti!
♪ On the cusp of vessel 18 ♪
♪ A look of terror in our eyes ♪
♪ The moonlight licked
the face of danger ♪
♪ Innocence made us
like soldiers ♪
♪ Untouchable and golden ♪
♪ The quilt of darkness ♪
♪ Dotted with our teardrops ♪
♪ I know you're sad
I'm leaving ♪
♪ So this may hurt a little ♪
♪ But, girl, look from your window
late tonight ♪
♪ You think my heart is frozen ♪
♪ While yours
is slowly grieving ♪
♪ You'll see the boy you loved
start burning in the sky ♪
♪ We were a dozen
to the project ♪
♪ With a galaxy of questions ♪
♪ And all we heard was lies
about the truth ♪
♪ No choice but be obedient ♪
♪ Like prisoners of war ♪
♪ Caught on the wrong side
of morality and youth ♪
♪ We thought about
our loved ones ♪
♪ Tallied 50
on our foreheads ♪
♪ With the pen your mother
gave me in the spring ♪
♪ The sun beat at the windows ♪
♪ Within an hour
James had cracked ♪
♪ Left the ship and died
still clinging to the wings ♪
♪ Start burning in the sky ♪
♪ Late in the night ♪
♪ When the darkness is deep ♪
♪ Come to my home ♪
♪ Let me offer you tea ♪
♪ Sadness may go ♪
♪ Like the sails on the sea ♪
♪ Lay down your love ♪
♪ Lay down ♪
♪ Lay down your sorrow ♪
♪ Lay down your love ♪
♪ Stay till tomorrow ♪
♪ Let yourself go ♪
♪ Lay down your sorrow ♪
♪ Lay out your love ♪
♪ Stay till tomorrow ♪
♪ Open up ♪
♪ Sadness may go ♪
♪ Like the sails on the sea ♪
♪ Come to my home ♪
♪ Let me offer you tea ♪
♪ Late in the night ♪
♪ When the darkness is deep ♪
♪ Lay down your love ♪
♪ Stay close to me ♪
♪ Sorrow ♪
♪ Lay down your love ♪
♪ Love ♪
♪ Stay till tomorrow ♪
♪ Open up ♪
♪ Lay down your sorrow ♪
♪ Lay out your lie ♪
♪ Come see the new dawn ♪
♪ Dawn ♪
♪ Break through the night ♪
♪ Sadness may go ♪
♪ Like the sails on the sea ♪
♪ Come to my home ♪
♪ Let me offer you tea ♪
♪ Late in the night ♪
♪ When the darkness is deep ♪
♪ Love will arise ♪
♪ And the stars kiss the sea ♪
♪ All the words lost is found
in the final round ♪
♪ Deepest ♪
♪ Darkest hour ♪
♪ Open up your coat ♪
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/49vaw
Help other users to choose the best subtitles