Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
On afull moon night
On the roof of the Forbidden City
A sword from the west
Flying fairy
You Fa Moon-lau and me, Luk Siu Fung
would be so glad to watch
the duel of 2 great swordsmen
Yes. Sai Mun Tsui-suet &
Yip Koo-shing's swords
haven't been shown yet
but we can smell it
This sword is made by finest steel
its length is 3 feet 3 inches
weight 6 catties and 4 taels
This sword is very sharp
Its length is 3 feet 7 inches
weight 7 catties & 1 3 taels
Sai Mun Tsui-suet, do you have
confidence to face my stance?
Mr. Yip, I'm ready
Fly...
Flying...
Fa...
Fairy!
Who are you?
How dare you fight on the roof top of
the Emperor's house? Tell me your names
I'm Yip Koo-shing
Master of the White Cloud Castle
Yip Koo-ching?
And... I'm a cool swordsman
Sai Mun Tsui-suet
And me, Fa Moon-lau, the Blind Superman
And me, a lovely hero with
4 eye-brows. Luk Siu-fung!
What? Luk Siu-fung?
Lovely hero?
You know you're bothering
2 great swordsmen to have their duel?
Who are you?
Secret Agent Ling Ling Fat
I'm responsible to protect
His Majesty and his properties
Listen, you old folks!
You are charged of breach of close
You're charged of illegal gathering, too
And haven't behaved
yourselves in public area
Hey, don't call us old folks!
Great swordsmen may not
always be handsome
Handsome heroes are just
the expectations of ordinary people
Yes. Heroes will have bald head too
But not as ugly as you are!
Please give us a chance!
This is a precious secret
scroll of Kung-fu
Take it. Uncuff us at once
You want to exchange your freedom
with such poor book? Stop dreaming
Haven't you heard of my name?
Of course not!
You're not that famous. Get lost
Young man
better give us face. I'm Sai...
I don't care
I won't give you face, anyway
Bastard! You'd respect the blind
Since you're blind, don't climb up!
Or, you'll fall to death, old man
You've gone too far!
Once I attack with my Wonder Fingers...
Wonder Finger? I have one too. Got it?
Better learn it
All of you, on the floor
put your hands on your heads
I think you'll be put to jail
not less than 1 0 years
I won't let you go this time
What a shame!
Pals, let's forget this ignorant guy
Let's choose another day for the fight
So powerful!
Members of the Secret Agent
Ling Ling Kung
Ling Ling Hei
Ling Ling Fat
Ling Ling Choi
We'll be your
Majesty's loyal servants forever
Iron Clothe!
It breaks Yes...
Great!
Unbreakable Armor
Five Shapes Fists
Dragon
Snake
Tiger
Panther
Crane
Bravo!
What's up?
These 2 stones are
found in the very North
There are 2 sides, with amazing power
If positive side face the positive side
they'll reject each other
They can't stick together
If the positive side faces the
negative side, they'll stick together
Very amazing!
It's a great discovery
I'd like to devote it to you
What's the use of it?
Girls, you need not sway
the fan so hardly from now on
That two aren't attractive
how about this?
Put these 2 leaves together
and move it with great speed
So strong wind will be created
If the weather is hot
this new product would be wonderful!
Is Your Majesty interested in being
a sole agent of my product?
Your Majesty, I've not given my
subordinates good guidance
I'd be blamed!
Ling Ling Fat, behave yourself
I've got a way to
defeat your lron Clothe
Fat-yan
I'm coming
I've discovered that
if I put carbon
Nitre and sulphur in a small space
say, inside one's mouth
And, one tiny steel ball is put in
When an explosion is happened inside
solid becomes gas form
and the expansion creates great power
So the steel ball will be pushed out
The power is so great that
it can break stone and metal
Iron clothe will become a mess
What did you say?
Great! Come here
Fat-yan, are you ready?
The only demerit of this weapon is...
high temperature will be caused
So Fat-yan's mouth must be
under series of special training
say, eat hot dumplings
as training step no. one
Or, drink very hot soup
Now, Fat-yan's mouth can
stand temperature of 1 00oC
I tell you, he can eat hot
shark-fin soup faster than anyone else
so, he can eat much more than us
But...
Kids should not learn this
Make it or not?
It's almost successful
I feel that my mouth has had gone
No, it becomes bigger only
How big is it?
Very big, don't worry
It's almost done!
Give me some time to amend it
I think I can...
Shut up!
Please don't get angry
Fat, what are you doing?
Doing minor things
I'm asking you, what are you doing?
Just some inventions
Say! What're you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
The Majesty is asking you
What're you doing? Say!
I just want to make new inventions
Come up!
I want you to come up and tell me
Hurry up...
I'm coming soon
If your post wasn't from heritage
I would have fired you!
Now, get lost!
I let you cover yourself
by acting as a doctor
But he chose to be a gynecologist!
What a shame!
You seldom practise Kung-fu
I don't know what you're doing at all
He didn't come for a meeting last night
Where were you last night?
I caught thieves on the roof top
What thieves?
I caught Yip Koo-shing
Sai Mun Tsui-suet and Luk Siu-fung
Although they escaped
I got a secret scroll of Kung-fu instead
What's that?
A stance named Flying Fairy
Have you practised?
Yes, I did a bit
Show me now
This is called Flying Fairy
He is fooling you, Your Majesty
Get up! Now! Quick! Stand right here!
I'm coming... Hurry up...
Don't pretend. Come up...
Coming
Come up! Coming!
Get out now!
I tell you
I don't want to see you again
and hear from you either!
Secret agent...
Great!
Doctor, l...
Let me give you some medicine?
Wait, let me tell you my symptoms first
You have to take medicine anyway, right?
Take the medicine
Pay now
Show her to the door
Doctor, I've come a long way here
Please listen to me first
Come on, please!
I'll let you say anything you like...
on your way home
Next
Doctor, I'm sick
Let me give you some medicine
My hands and legs are cold
I feel dizzy too
Sometimes when I stand up after a squat
I'll feel dizzy
Well, no medicine is needed
Go home and prepare for your funeral
Are you kidding me? Isn't it...
because of woman's period?
Or hormone changed after delivery?
What make you think so?
Well, you can tell it
from the color of tongue
Well, how to cure you then?
It's simple
Use 1/2 tael of Tin Nam Sing
0.15 tael of Lily
0.2 tael of To Chow Sing, 0.08 tael
of Si Kwan Chi, one teal of Ha Fu Tsoi
Plus winter flower, cook with light fire
Here they are
boil with eight bowls of water
Drink it, then you'll recover soon
Thank you, doctor
Show doctor to the door
Ne...
Next?
Doctor, my heart aches!
Let me give you some medicine
My nasty husband has a concubine
He always beats me up!
I've suffered enough! Although
a rude man brings extra excitement
I couldn't stand any more!
Doctor, are you rude?
It depends
Sometimes, I can be rude
Alright, my husband fools around
I want to have a secret affair too
Come on!
Let me see how rude are you!
Honey!
What's the matter, honey?
This lady...
she wants my help
You know, I am a kind-hearted doctor
She comes a long way here
just give her a hand
Miss, are you tired?
Do you want some noodle?
I am fine!
Honey, am I a good husband?
I have arrived, that's why you behaved!
If I am not present
will you accept the temptation?
I swear!
I will!
You bastard!
Once again
will you take the temptation! Tell me
Yes
Great
I am not afraid of it! You nuts!
I will not play with you if you bite!
Alright
I surrender! I surrender!
Hands off!
No! Or you will jump over!
I won't! I surrender!
My hand breaks! Honey
hands off me please
I don't believe in you
It really breaks!
Sorry, hubby
You woman!
You are really good at Kung-fu
Master is so pleased!
I won't feel unhappy
What?
Do you know what's in my mind?
I have present for you
Remember you cut the onion few days ago
you chopped and chopped...
At last, you cut your finger
Now, I will give you this hand
So, you can use your
own hand to catch this hand
And use this hand to hold the onion
Even you cut your hand
it'll be a fake hand
Your own hand won't be hurt!
How can you make it?
Thank you, hubby!
Sweetie!
Honey!
You said, it's tough to clean the floor
Yes
Take this pair of shoes
After wearing it
your legs will help you a lot
See, your legs will
become groom & dust pan
And you can clean the floor
while you are walking
Open your mouth
Put all the rubbish inside your mouth
No!
Wait
How do you feel?
Hubby, I think you are a great inventor
What else?
And...
I love you very much!
So...
Let's sleep
But I want to try this!
No, try this
It's rat!
This time, I'll use
rat's movement to release power
And it will push the wheel
to increase the power
then, it's powerful enough to move this!
It can support weight over 200 catties
How about the steam machine
we used last time?
It's good, but when it is dried
it will stop at once
Isn't this better?
You are right
But, something is missing
And this is the greatest breakthrough
I've ever made
Now, we can choose different grade
of speed for different needs
Look!
Honey, am I wonderful?
You are so cheap!
Sure!
Honey, what does that Rear mean?
That's backward!
Let me try
No!
Does it work?
Sure, I cook with
this super turning shovel
Not even a drop of oil can dirty me
Sure, but I mean the air system machine!
That machine?
Show me once
It works, this is effective
And you can take this as practice
Yeah, it's good to health
Hubby
Honey
I'll let you play
Great
The one who is like a ghost has arrived
What's wrong with you?
Doctor...
Just between you and me!
It's enough for you to disguise as woman
It's not necessary
for you to talk like a woman!
Being a member of the
Forbidden City Cops
I should try my very best
to cover my identity
Better be careful
Doctor...
Am I pregnant?
Yes, eat this for abortion
What else do you want to say?
Fat-yan said...
Don't talk like a woman
Lie down, don't let me see your face
There is an important mission for you
go back to the Headquarters
Better say earlier!
Fat, be smart
This important mission is counted on you
We have had banquets
in the headquarters in these nights
if you can't clean
all the dishes tonight
you will be put to jail
Here comes His Majesty
I've got a message that
inside the territory of Gum Kingdom
Something mysterious happened last month
that is
Oh, really?
a creature called Flying Fairy
fell down from heaven
Thus, they called a meeting for
all famous doctors in our country
In order to dissect the Flying Fairy
Dissect Flying Fairy?
Under the great leadership
of Your Majesty
how come such ridiculous thing happens?
I am sure this is
the trick of the cheaters
Do you still want to go?
Only the fool will be cheated!
I do want to take a look
You know it is ridiculous
but Your Majesty still want to face it
you are so brave, so courageous!
Only under the leadership of
such brave and smart emperor
our country will be
prosperous and stable
Long life to Your Majesty
The people of Gum Kingdom are
always cunning, it may be a trap
If you go, it may be dangerous
Forget it
If you don't finish washing these dishes
you'll be more dangerous
But I have duty to remind Your Majesty
Long life to Your Majesty
Bravo
Kung Hei Choi, you will protect me
we will set out tomorrow
Yes
Long life Your Majesty
Fat, cut the crap
His Majesty doesn't want to hear your voice
If you say anything nonsense
your head will be chopped off
Wash the dishes. Don't speak up...
Thank God, you are saved!
You wash my dishes
There must be conspiracy!
China is stable and prosperous
The beautiful women
are specially beautiful
The handsome men are specially handsome
I do hope that our flag of Gum Sect
will be found on their soil
The Chinese soldiers are poor in health
The dissection of Flying Fairy
is to gather the Chinese doctors
then, we will launch an attack
to the Chinese troops
Since they have no doctors
our troops can march from the
North to South with ease
It'll be a piece of cake
for us to conquer China
You bastard, you look like a dummy
especially when you smile!
I don't know why
you are so dummy looking!
Stop it!
I am like a dummy whenever I see you
When I see daddy
I seem to be more foolish!
Don't you like my look?
Your dad ruined his face
because of practising No Face's Stance!
A 2
I four
Got it?
Bingo
D 4 and 7
H 2 5
Got it?
Two Six
Try Two Five again
Two Five
Go back to 2 6
2 & 6
Got it?
Yes
Where do you feel itchy?
C 1 3 4 6 8 plus D 1
And, A 2, E 4
Got it?
You are so stupid!
You won't make it like this!
I am stupid, that's why you look smart
Please don't say I am smart
But your inventions are really wonderful
Who said so?
I said it
What's your name?
Lau
Who are you?
I am your wife
Shit!
Come on, don't scold me
You scolded me first
You are the only one who praises me
but what's the use of it?
I don't care!
I think you are really great
You are great, that's why I praise you!
Don't you understand my words?
What do you want to say?
Don't you know it?
I have had a difficult job
But you will never know it
I don't know how hard your job is
But I believe that
you are doing something good
Just scold whoever offended you
But never blame me as scapegoat
Since you are familiar with me
That's why I should be blamed?
I tell you!
Yes
So, you...
You can blame me instead?
Yeah!
So what? Why not leave home?
How do you know I am
hiding under the table?
You always hide under the table
That's why I know you must be
hiding under the table
Please use your brain to think!
Think a new place to hide!
So, I will have new excitement
But if I don't hide under the table
I am afraid you can't find me
I can't stand it any more
Please don't! I beg you!
Honey, please don't do it again
I am a woman only
but you always scold me
I am afraid I can't tolerate it any more
If you can't tolerate it, just leave me
I'm going to bath
I ask you to leave me alone!
Are you hungry?
I'll do you some noodle
Sorry, it's my fault
I lose my mind
Forget it
But why do you lose your temper?
There is an important medical
meeting held in Gum Kingdom
But I am not qualified to join it
Who said so?
I said, you are qualified
I don't mind others disqualifying me
According to what you said
I can go now!
Stop!
What's the matter?
Some woodmen appear in such remote place
be careful of trick!
Who are you?
We're woodmen
Don't block my way
I am the Emperor
Get lost!
Don't disclose our identities on the way
I don't want others to
know I am the Emperor
Got it?
Yes, Your Majesty
Let's go
The leading guy is having
long and soft breath
He must be a Kung-fu
master who is good at Air Stance
The one with whip is having stable steps
He must be a great Kung-fu fighter
And the one, with strong arms
He must be a great Kung-fu fighter too
I think they must be the
famous Forbidden City Cops
Iron Clothe, Unbreakable Armor
and Five Shapes Fists
Three Forbidden City Cops are all here
the one inside the sedan chair
must be the emperor
We do want to arrest some stupid doctors
God knows, here comes a king!
How lucky are we to
have such good chance!
So what?
Protect me
It's great
So disgusting!
The participants can go
into the hall now
Honey, the meeting is going to start
Let's go
I can't miss this chance!
First, cut the belly
Tear its skin
Pull the intestines out
Then, its shit spitted out...
So exciting!
Honey, there are new clothes for sale
I am going to buy some
How to meet you later?
After the meeting
just go there to look for me
Alright
Don't wander off
Invitation card?
This kind of invitation card
Please let me go, I am a doctor too
Are you a doctor?
Yes, I am a famous doctor
Alright, go in
Thank you, buddy
He doesn't know he is dying!
What?
Doctor... Doctor...
Doctor...
I've discovered that
I can make a medicine with
polycodonis and honey
This liquor is best for chain smokers
It cures sore throat
You will get rich!
I've discovered a new kind of plant
After eating it, you will laugh and cry
the natives call this grass
You will get rich too
You can tell it's drug which harm people
Better keep it yourself
Don't take too much!
You are right
Do you have any now?
Give me some
Later...
This doctor... I haven't seen you before
Your hat is so interesting!
Where do you work?
I am a gynecologist in the capital
To treat women?
You are rich!
Ladies and gentlemen
How are you
Welcome here to watch
the dissection of the Flying Fairy
This is a very precious chance
Now, this is solely shown to you
Where is His Majesty?
In order to let you see clearly
In five consecutive nights
we will repeat, repeat and repeat...
to show you the process
of the dissection
To let you see it clearly
No need...
And, we have invited the farmers
who discovered it to this meeting
Let me now interview...
someone who witnessed
the discovery of the fairy first
that's a dog
Its eye is so big
Will it be clearer?
Where is its wing? How can it fly then?
It's really weird!
Kidding! It is small
or less the same as me
Right, as ugly as you
What are you doing?
I am checking its sex
It must be a girl
It is a girl
I know she is pregnant
What are you doing?
I am checking it's a man or a womam
Don't mess up!
Any gynecologist here?
He is
Move, move now
Why not... Give her some medicine?
Do you know dissection?
I know
Take this cutter and start working
I won't give it a damn
But, may I use this?
Don't move
Do you know how to dissect?
Cut from the throat
let the blood drain out first
I know it already
Come on
In fact, I am not a doctor
I am a butcher
You coward, you needn't find excuse
Let me do it
Have you fixed yet?
Good question, I've just fixed it
Wait
What's up?
His Majesty!
I know it's you!
Who chopped me?
Someone chopped you?
That's him!
But that is his sword
You bastard!
I want to chop you twice
What's wrong?
Why do you hold the sword?
Stay calm
Yes! There is conspiracy!
Conspiracy?
Your Majesty
I, Ling Ling Fat will protect you
My sword is sucked away, so powerful
Come on, one for each one
Your Majesty, you first
Wait
Don't despise us
We earn our living by holding swords too
Yes!
Don't get angry, drink some water first
All dead!
What kind of monster is it?
Try my Lo Chiu's Sword Stance
I wanna kill you! Give me
This is my sword!
Let's attack from both sides OK
So great!
Stop!
Are you kidding?
Why do you always beat me?
Boss
Your feet betrayed you
Don't you think I am a fool?
Hurry...
Watch me!
I know, same sex will reject each other
Fat, how are you?
This magnet is really great
Shit!
Different sex attracts each other
Are you kidding?
Yeah!
Fat, you're really something
Thank you. Your Majesty
we'd better leave
OK, let's go!
Leave now
Honey
Your wife has come too?
Introduce her to me
Go back first, here is so dangerous
Why there is one living?
Is there any
accident happened to my son?
Where is my wife!
Search! Many people are
lying on the floor!
Cut the crap, kill him
No matter where you're hiding
you have to be killed
Kill him
What the hell is it?
Kidding?
Hubby
Same costume! Why?
Honey
Hubby
Where have you been?
I met a friend who
lives in the next village
There is a crazy sale in next village
so I went for shopping with her
What are you doing here?
I am... Iooking for you
Is there a fire?
We have had barbecue here
Barbecue?
Yes, roast chicken wings
Why do they lie on the floor?
They are full, it's nice to have a rest
What's wrong with you?
You ate with violence, didn't you?
What the hell is it?
All people fought for one chicken wing!
I fought with all my might
that's the result
Don't you think I am nuts?
He...
Honey
You...
Where do you get this?
This?
If you like it, just take it
I don't mean it
and I don't want to take your advantage
If I want it
I will ask my husband to buy me one
He is damn rich
I want to tell you that
this doesn't match you
The color is no good
You have a big belly
this kind of clothes doesn't fit you
We may have a look in the shops
of the nearby village
Let's go, let's have a look
My wife
She has fashion sense
Yes, she is nice
Brother Fat
Come on...
Hubby, you have laughed
since you are back
What make you feel so happy?
This morning
I saw a fat woman fall into water ditch
A fat woman fell into water ditch?
What is so funny?
Fat woman!
Water ditch!
Honey
In all these years...
Listen to me
Go ahead
We have had poor living
Don't you mind it?
It depends on you
If you don't mind
eating the food I cooked
I don't mind too
In all these years
other than great inventions
I haven't sent anything
say diamond to you
Why don't you complain against me?
Sure. I have complaints
That super groom
I have to clean the floor with two legs
My hands are free
So, I have to clean
the window with one hand
another hand to wash clothes
It's so troublesome!
You've discovered that!
Yeah...
And your air system
What's wrong?
I don't want to waste time to complain
it drives me crazy
Sure it will
What diamond have you hidden?
Take it out now
Honey
How are you?
Did you rob?
No, I didn't
I cured a man who is damn rich
He paid much money as medical fee
That's why I bought it to you
Honey!
Don't come over. Leave me alone
Are you alright?
I'm too happy, I can't control myself
So pretty
I love you, honey
I love you too
Forever
Fat, I heard that in the
biggest prostitute in town
there is a new girl called
Gum Tso who came from Gum Kingdom
Her name is so beautiful! It fancies me!
Go and check her background
If she is OK, take her to me
Are you kidding, Your Majesty?
How can you let me
carry such nice mission?
You are the fellow I trust most
you know?
And, everyone knows
you are a good husband
You won't take my woman
So, you are the appropriate person
to take this job
May I be frank
Your Majesty
you have many concubines already
Why do you still want an affair?
You... The beauties have arrived!
Now, you understand?
Sure!
Your Majesty, please tolerate
I...
I will fix it as soon as possible
Bastards, who do you think you are!
We're high-class night club
You think we're prostitute?
Members only!
Take enough money if you
want to join our club
Damn it, I've fooled around for years
I haven't experienced
such embarrassing moment
Let's ask someone to ruin this place
Shut up
Damn it!
I am the procuress
Granny, do you wanna
sell your daughter to us?
Let me take a look at her first
She is beautiful
Look
So?
I wanna beat someone up
Can I slap her heavily?
Don't be so mean
you have to give others face anyway
You wanna beat me
I do wanna hit you hardly with rod too
Damn it
how can you talk to me in this way?
The girls here are all
as pretty as angels
Especially the girls from Gum Kingdom
You won't believe it
big eyes, tall nose, little mouth
Ask them to come out for a comparison
She is much more beautiful than you!
Get lost now!
Or, I will slap you! I mean it
She is coming out
The beauty from
Gum Kingdom is coming out
Miss
May l?
What's up?
You stand here without making a noise!
Don't you know dancing
or don't you know talking?
I don't know you
I am Gum Tso
Fat, so many women around!
Fat...
Honey!
Hubby, you're back!
Hubby
I've made a clothe for my birthday party
Isn't it pretty
It's good looking!
I invite many relatives and
friends to have dinner with us!
Remember to come home earlier!
Remember?
Hubby
I can smell fragrance from your body
Wonderful nose you have!
I bought you cosmetics!
Why do you buy me cosmetics?
For your birthday!
Good boy!
Have a bath first!
Alright, let's bath together!
I have bathed. Go bathing now
Better bath again You go alone
I am the procuress
welcome to be our new member
Seeing you...
I have something, very, very...
Strange feeling that...
Say, you feel like slapping me
Right...
Correct
Is Miss Gum Tso here?
Sure!
I want to see her at once
Do you want to see her?
They are wishing to see Miss Gum Tso too
Line up, don't you think a handsome
& smart guy need not line up?
How can you tell I am smart?
I can tell you are sincere
and kind-hearted, too!
It's lucky to have a friend like you
Shit! You can tell it too
I have to treat you dinner!
Sure you have to
Line up!
Bastard!
Miss Gum Tso, I've waited you for ages!
Stay calm...
Miss Gum Tso wishes to treat you a drink
Take a glass over there
I want one
Miss Gum Tso, a toast to you
It's nasty. What's this?
Good wine!
What a nice wine
it makes one lose his mind!
This must be an old wine
of over 1 00 years old
I believe that this is
tribute from foreign country
Isn't it so precious?
Are you exaggerating, Pal?
You are totally wrong!
You drink it without tasting it
Even it isn't wine
you can never tell its taste!
Wine is like woman
you have to try it by some means.
Can anyone lend me his tongue?
Any longer one?
Right
The taste buds are on the
surface of our tongues
Not under
The sweet taste buds are in front
The bitter taste buds
are near the throat
Don't make it too deep
Alright, I'll place it in front
The sour taste bud is
on both sides of the tongue
So, when we taste good wine
roll the tongue
you need more practice
So, you can stop the wine
meeting the sour taste bud
And let the wine floats between
bitter and sweet taste buds
Sweet first, and then bitter...
Just like...
the sense of first love
Congratulation, Gum Tso would like
to meet you in the sitting room
Miss Gum Tso... Don't be anxious
Why don't you...
You seem to have sore throat
Are you missing your wife?
How do you know that?
Chinese people usually
have early marriage
You seem to be mature and trustable
I guess, you must have married for years
You are flattering me
You don't seem to be Chinese
I come from Gum Kingdom
Do you have racial discrimination?
No way, don't be silly
Miss, you seem...
You are fat, and you are thin
You are bored
Give me a surprise
Do you want any surprise?
Do you have any?
Don't despise me
Take it out
Do you want me to take it out?
Come on
This is for you
So pretty! Thank you
You are really different!
Usually, when the girls
see such precious pearl
either they will scream
or, some will die because
of too much excitement
You don't value material life at all
you are really...
Really different!
Mister, do you have time to stay?
To have a long talk?
My wife has prepared dinner
I don't think it's good for me to stay
Why do you come then?
Even cats will be
motivated by such atmosphere!
Do you know what the cat is talking?
That cat said
Don't bother me, mom will scold me
Why do you hurt yourself?
It brings excitement!
So amazing!
There are many amazing things
you haven't tried that before
If you stay
I will try my very best
to make your all eyes
I can't do that
I am married, I love my wife
Although I wish to do it
I have to control myself
Well, I won't give it a damn!
Come on...
A good husband is hard to
find in the world
Since you are thinking of your wife
I won't push you
Send Mister to the door
Yes
Wait... Please leave
No, I've just made up my mind...
Please go back
So bad! I have halfly undressed!
Give me a chance!
Forget it, Mister
Miss Gum Tso
Cheers...
Sweet wine...
Hubby, what's wrong with you?
I haven't been that smart
There isn't any rice in your bowl
Hubby, I've discovered that
the cosmetic you sent me that night
doesn't smell like those
found from your body
Didn't I tell you?
That's made by a thing called Magic Musk
The smell will change according
to different timings
At night, it stinks
No, it doesn't stink
It stinks
On that day
you sent me a very big pearl
I do want to show off tonight
But I couldn't find it out at all
Do you know where is it?
This is life
If you want to find something anxiously
you can never find it
If you are smart, you need not find it
cause it will show up later
Father-in-law, have the chicken ass
I remember
Why did you go to the
prostitute house on that day?
Prostitute house?
Yes, prostitute house
What did you say?
I saw him visiting hookers
Listen to me
Wait
Don't lie to me
I can tell it's true or not easily
Hooker is woman, she will get sick
As a gynecologist
I went there for treatment
It's nothing weird
Daughter, is his heart beating fast?
No
That's good
Sorry, hubby
You are too bad for you
don't trust me at all
It's fragrant! Can you smell it?
Miss, who are you looking for?
I come here to buy herb
Do you have any chiretta
(means home coming in Chinese)?
Are you in urgent need? Come later
I love a man very much
He hasn't come to me for many days
I come to buy chiretta which
means home coming in Chinese
for I really want him to
come back this night
Miss, I suggest you to buy Tu-wo
(means living alone)
Living alone, don't bother others
You have a kind of special smell
I smelt once!
Yes, this perfume is called Hooking Soul
Only I have this kind of
special perfume in town
It is an amazing perfume
to seduce man, right?
But I can't hook the man I love
No matter how hard I torture myself
he just brushes me off and comes here
to have dinner with his wife
So, I come here to see his wife
Today is my daughter's birthday
Don't mess up here
You have seen what you want now
So pretty
Prettier than you
Send her to the door
Madam
Today is your birthday!
I haven't any present
But, why not
take this little thing as my present?
Are you kidding?
Right, when you don't want to find it
it will show up itself
Are you kidding? You sent it to her?
This is your present to me
how I can send it to others?
What is your relationship? Tell me
By the way, it seems to be clear!
You bastard!
How can you treat my daughter like this?
Are you a man?
Granny, don't be angry
Give me back the pearl
Madam, don't be excited!
You bitch, I wanna kill you!
Don't move Don't move
If you hurt her, I will kill you
If you hurt me, I will kill him
None of my business, lady!
Stop her now
Bitch!
Drop the horse down
What did you say, honey?
Drop the horse
You scared my friend
You lied
You said you would love me forever
You lied too
You said you were born
in the year of rabbit
but you were born in the year
of tiger, you are older than me
You lied, you lied!
Drop the horse
Don't throw me while
I am not paying attention
I can tell your trick
Drop it, now!
Are you alright?
I am fine
Sorry to ruin your party
All because I wish to see you very much
I am too bad, I am leaving
I will go with you
It's nonsense for me to
stay in such nonsense family
Go
Hubby
Are you hungry?
Let me cook noodle for you
Wait
What a shame!
Don't get angry
let's go back to my place
I will do that with you
That?
That's what you want
You are inhumane!
Oh my God!
We have become a couple at last
On this stormy night
we will enjoy ourselves!
You look cheap
You haven't seen my cheaper look
Alright, listen to me
I have had hard feeling
Your wife felt so sad
For you, I can sacrifice
my wife as well as my life
Don't say anything nonsense
I don't want to cheat you
I am a Forbidden City Cop
my duty is to protect His Majesty
I came here for
His Majesty is fond of you
He wants me to check your background
You don't check me
you just want to screw me
You are betraying His Majesty
But I can't help loving you
Forget about him!
Ling Ling Fat!
Luckily you have come on time
Did you hear everything?
You!
If she didn't write to His Majesty
we wouldn't have known that
you betrayed His Majesty
You...
In order to trap him
I don't mind risking my virginity
Your Majesty, if you come a bit late
I don't know what will happen!
You...
Ling Ling Fat, your family will have
capital punishment, you know?
Your Majesty, l...
Catch him
Your Majesty, why do you cuff me?
Your trap is really great!
You want me to break my family
Then you make His Majesty kill me
You will kidnap him
to blackmail the government
Then your troop will move from
the North to take over our country
It seem to be a piece of cake
Damn!
But, you remember the pearl
which fancies all women in the world?
When you received that pearl, you didn't
feel excited, that's why I know
you are not a woman
Who is my foe?
And who will undergo such
fantastic plastic surgery?
Only a faceless old folk will do it
King of no face, you bastard!
I hate others to cheat me
by pretending as woman!
Especially disguising as such
pretty woman to seduce me!
Luckily Fat is so smart!
He disclosed your secret
Your Majesty
Don't trust him!
He wanted to screw me
so he brushed his wife off
and he even beated
his wife up in front of me
He isn't a man at all
In order to trap you
my family performed
a show in front of you
Dear audience
The best actress
In the play
she acted very well that
no matter judging from her eyes
or movement
she could express how a sad wife feels
Especially when she threw the horse
it shows a strong protest originated
from post modernism
Let us see how she threw the horse again
Watch! Watch!
Mrs. Fat, congratulation...
Thank you
First of all, I have to thank my parents
Since they have been supporting me
And I have to thank my husband
He gave me chance to act
We had rehearsed many many times
So, this award is yours too
Hubby, thank you
Alright, let's present the
final award of this night
I believe that, you can guess it. Right
The best actor is...
Ah Fat's father-in-law
Wonderful!
This award should go to me
I did see him visiting
the prostitute house!
Please wait. I am sorry
I am the leading man!
You can tell I have done a great job
Why do you present the award to him?
Your acting is quite good
but not mature
Say, when your wife
heard your heart beat
your expression was a bit exaggerated
That's the point of view
of ordinary audiences!
You won't be that ignorant?
No, when I heard your heart beat
I couldn't feel any response from you
I felt that, you couldn't
concentrate in acting
You didn't act well indeed
You...
Be fair
Just one word
You don't know acting
Shut up! Gum Tso's sex
is still a doubtful question
How can you present awards here?
It's a mess
Your Majesty, l...
Be careful of your nostral hair
I am a person who is
willing to die for you
Let me use my body
to check whether Gum Tso
is a woman or not
Get lost
Be careful!
Ling Ling Fat
you killed my wife and my son
Even I can't kill your family
I want to kill you too
Neither of you can go
Protect His Majesty
Fat-yan, take the Box of Treasure to me
Catch it
Why did you ask me to throw it to you?
Game over!
I am sorry
It doesn't hurt!
But the one next to you is in bad luck
That's No-face Stance
It can transfer energy
Pal, are you alright?
I am scared
But I am fine
I feel comfortable
It's not painful at all
So, I won't give it a damn
Let me do it
Pal, didn't you say comfortable?
It's really comfortable
Forget it
You'd better beat that guy
I have to think something else
Forget it, please hit me
It's not predictable
No color, no face, long life to stay!
I am the supreme of the world!
Who is it?
My dear sister
We all rely on you!
Soul Changing Stance
I feel dizzy, I can't stand it anymore
It's cheap! Who do you want to scare?
Don't you think such chain
can lock me up?
It's not for locking you
it's used to connect the lightning-rod
You said, we will enjoy ourselves
on a stormy night
I'll let you try
a wonderful thunder storm
Yeah
Yeah...
Don't move!
Fly...
Flying...
Fa...
Fairy
The thunder hit Fat
So it transform his cells
During the process
he gained extra power
So, he can release
the power of Flying Fairy
At that moment, it seems that
there was a flying fairy in the sky
Isn't it illusion caused by air crash
or am I drunk?
Of course you are drunk
So, you have drunk much more than me
I am drunk everyday
It's strange
why hasn't Fat come to work today?
Brother Fat, where are you?
We can't live without you
Brother Fat, come back!
Hubby, it's so great!
Your new invention can
let us fly freely in the sky
Let us name it...
Helicopter, isn't it nice?
No, this isn't a good name
Why not name it...
Air air air air air O Plane?
You are so smart, honey
If not, how can I be your honey?
Hubby, let's fly again
So romantic! Yes
I want to have a baby with you
Really? Really
Alright, let's go home and make love
No way, I can't wait
Let's do it here!
You can't be serious Come on!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3m2qy
Help other users to choose the best subtitles