Watch free HD Movies and TV Shows at
StreamingSites.com
[dramatic music playing]
[man] You gotta thank me.
I went to five stations
before I found one still selling diesel.
I know what you're thinking.
"Why did that stupid motherfucker
go to all that trouble to find diesel?"
[chuckling]
"Wouldn't regular have done the job?"
There's a reason.
It burns much slower.
["Catamaran" by the Allah-Las playing]
[muffled screaming]
[muffled screaming continues]
♪ Out on the water
Where you're gonna find me ♪
♪ All alone with my mind
Headed for a bounty... ♪
[coughing, retching]
Fuck you, man!
My boys find you,
they're gonna fuck you up!
[grunts]
Careful now.
You gotta try harder to be my friend.
[man 2 grunts]
[breathing heavily]
Your money's gone, Bricke.
And after what you did here today,
the Dumois family
is never gonna stop hunting you.
Who told you?
Okay, okay.
Okay, man, okay! Okay!
Okay!
It was your boy.
What boy?
Johnny Dee.
He gave you up...
for one more taste.
Bad company you keep, man.
[chuckles]
Hey, Bricke.
You don't have to do this, man.
Easy now.
[breathing heavily]
Fuck you!
We don't know how much gasoline
is on your lips...
to light up.
But there's enough in this tub.
So if you stay real still,
maybe this will burn itself out
on your face.
[breathing heavily]
[whimpering]
Hey, Bricke!
Bricke, man!
[coughs]
You motherfucker!
[cartoon character crying on TV]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[loud explosion]
[rock music playing]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[reporter]
The President himself has confirmed
that the US has indeed been involved
in the final stages of deploying
the American Peace Initiative
across the country.
[men grunting]
[men catcalling]
[man] Yo, get your clothes off!
[reporter]
The API is described as a signal
that acts as a synaptic blocker,
making it impossible
for anyone to perform an act
they know to be unlawful.
Once live, the API signal promises
to influence criminal activity
on a national scale.
[gun firing]
[helicopter passing]
[sirens wailing]
[man] Have your documents ready.
No one will be allowed to pass
without proper identification.
[woman] America, one week left
to make your own choices.
One week before the government
climbs into your head and takes the wheel.
In the face of it,
most people just lay down and give up.
Others will still try anything
to get out of this shit town.
Freedom, so close,
just across the bridge. Canada.
[gunfire]
[woman] But most people will die
before they ever see
the red-and-white flag.
[woman] One year ago,
Bricke and his crew were golden.
They hit banks hard and fast,
and they were damn good at it.
Bricke was their fearless leader.
But they didn't run this city.
That honor belonged
to the Dumois crime family.
So long as the Dumois got their cut,
they left him alone.
Bricke's only weakness
was his brother, Rory.
He was the heart of the group,
and he was about to do his first stretch
in prison.
-To Rory!
-[patrons] Rory!
-[cheering]
-[man] Rory!
Gotta keep your head down.
Keep to yourself.
You're out in six months.
Would you relax?
We're supposed to be celebrating.
In six months,
I'll probably be running that joint.
[scoffs]
Yeah? [sniffs]
Prison doesn't change you.
It shows you who you already are.
Don't play tough with me.
Yeah, well,
maybe I'm tougher than you think,
so fuck you.
You listen to me.
We survive...
because we have each other.
Hey, I'm proud of you.
In Dallas, Texas, today,
one of the worst terrorist attacks
on US soil.
[woman] The government had been working on
the API signal in secret labs for years.
Now they decided it was time
to start testing on the real world.
-[man laughing]
-[Bricke] Thirty seconds!
[woman] It wasn't till six months ago
that they got their first taste.
[man] Dude.
[groaning]
[high-pitched ringing]
[moaning]
[ringing continues]
We have a problem here.
[gunfire]
[coughing]
[ringing continues]
[Bricke breathing heavily]
We have to get out of here.
Come on. Take the money!
Let's go.
[man 2 grunting]
[sirens in distance]
-[Bricke] Go, go, go!
-[man 2 groans]
Go! Go!
[woman] The government was learning,
tuning their little box of horrors,
playing Jesus with people's brains,
and we were all their guinea pigs.
The test was short,
but it hit them hard enough
to understand that something was coming.
Something bad.
[man 3] Bricke!
Bricke, Bricke, Bricke.
I got this.
Yeah, I'm talking to you, Bricke.
Where's my money?
Hmm?
[shouting] Where's my money?
[woman] Bricke hid the money and lied,
said he lost it.
Seven million.
Just enough to escape to Canada
before the Dumois
got around to killing them all.
[man] All right, everybody out. Come on.
Get the fuck out! Come on.
Move! All right. Come on, lady.
What's wrong, man?
[grunting]
[woman] It was a good plan
until Rory killed himself in prison,
and Johnny Dee sold them out.
No money. Nowhere to go.
[dogs barking]
[woman] End of the line.
[man] No one will be allowed to pass
without proper identification.
Move in an orderly fashion.
[man 2] I can't see him.
[man 3]
We've been here for an hour. Come on.
[man 2]
I told you I can't fucking see him.
-Fuck you, keep a lookout.
-Yeah, fuck me.
-No, not fuck me. Actually, it's fuck you.
-Shut up.
Jesus, where is this motherfucker?
-Wait, I think I see--
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
-[gunshots]
-[groaning]
[grunts, breathes heavily]
Hey, Bricke.
Remember the rules?
Come on, Bricke.
I mean, everything's just so upside down,
right?
[gasping]
[gunshot echoing]
Well, look who's back.
A couple of Dumois
have been sniffing around recently.
-You might not want to let them find you.
-I know.
[bartender] Joe Hickey...
our very own Dr. Kevorkian.
[Hickey] Thank you very much.
Sit down.
[Bricke] I need something from you.
It's something bad.
And fast.
Bad and fast.
I have things that'll hurt
permanently to death,
if that's what you want.
Uh...
I got...
This is some Soviet shit,
and I'm not talking about
bunny-hugging Perestroika bullshit.
I'm talking about basement-level,
Soviet, melt-your-fucking-brain shit.
I don't know anyone who has survived
the neurotoxin collateral damage.
It's lethal.
It's four grand,
and that's my cost.
Please tell me
that this is not for your own use.
[reporter] Prior to this,
fights have been erupting all day
between pro-API nationalists
and protesters.
A local state of emergency
has been declared...
["Glory Box" by Portishead plays]
[sirens wailing]
[woman] There are some women in the world
who change the way the air is in a room.
There are some women in the world
worth killing for...
and just a few worth dying for.
♪ ...playing with this bow and arrow ♪
♪ Gonna give my heart away... ♪
[reporter]
Police were forced to use tear gas
to try and disperse earlier crowds
in which many arrests have been made.
♪ For I've been a temptress too long ♪
♪ Give me a reason to love you ♪
♪ Give me a reason to be ♪
Have one on me, soldier.
♪ A woman ♪
♪ I just want to be a woman... ♪
[Bricke]
That's some bruise you've got there.
I deserve them.
The shit that I get up to.
Jiminy crickets,
you must have done something
pretty awful to deserve that, Captain.
Made some bad choices.
We all make bad choices.
I've got a to-do list.
Step one: get married.
I tried that.
Yeah, but you fucked around
behind her back, didn't you?
[laughs softly]
Don't cry. We're all dogs.
We all hurt the ones who try and love us.
How's that heart working out for you?
Seems a little cold.
It's not too cold.
Not to touch, anyway.
Let's go check a to-do off my list.
[remix of "I Wanna Be Your Dog"
by The Stooges plays]
♪ So messed up
I want you here ♪
♪ In my room ♪
♪ I want you here ♪
♪ Now we're gonna be face-to-face ♪
♪ And I'll lay right down
In my favorite place ♪
♪ And now I want to be your dog ♪
♪ Now I want to be your dog ♪
♪ Well, come on ♪
[moaning]
Oh, yeah!
[song ends]
[Bricke] Hey.
What did we just check off your list?
Fuck a loser.
So, you never saw this guy before?
Graham Bricke? He's about my height?
He's a little bit shorter, I think.
No.
What are you doing later?
-[gun cocks]
-You know, my wife would really--
[crowd clamors]
Don't worry, I think I found him.
You've got five seconds...
to explain what you want.
[muttering] Five seconds?
Five seconds?
Five seconds won't be enough.
Five words.
I'm going to give you five words
that are gonna...
That are-- They're gonna make
your whole world go upside down.
It's gonna make you
take that gun out of my face.
You ready?
You look ready. All right, here we go.
Word one: Rory.
It's not really a word,
it's more like a name,
but it means something to you.
Rory's dead.
"Suicide," word two.
Something they wrote down
on a little piece of paper,
to tell you
how your poor little brother died,
which leads me to word three,
which is "bullshit!"
Bullshit.
And since word three
is doing such a bang-up job,
I'm gonna move on to word four,
which is,
"I was there. I saw him fucking die."
What's five?
"Revenge."
That's word five. "Revenge."
"Revenge," it's a beautiful word.
They used the signal to kill your brother.
I wanna use it to steal their money.
You help me do that...
you can leave
a big "fuck you for Rory" sign behind.
Revenge, my friend. Revenge.
What do you think, Bricke?
You a guy who can help me
steal 30 million dollars?
Because your brother thought you were.
Who the fuck are you?
Listen, when you get to know me
a bit better,
you're going to realize I'm all about...
timing.
Mr. Bricke, uh...
did I introduce you to my, uh, my fiancée,
Miss Shelby Dupree?
Pleasure to meet you, Mr. Bricke.
"Pleasure to meet you, Mr. Bricke.
Pleasure to meet you, Mr. Bricke."
[Shelby] Sometimes, you get to see
the bullet that has your name on it.
[man] Collins, come on!
[Shelby]
Sometimes, everything is just bullshit.
Home, sweet home.
Oh. Watch that.
Sorry. Sorry about that.
That first step is a doozy.
It's, uh, you know...
security.
Come on in.
[man clears throat]
What can I get you?
You want something? A drink?
Some cocaine? We got some great cocaine.
[Bricke]
What happened to my brother?
Just... let me show you something.
You see that?
That's the money factory.
That's where they make money. That?
That's the great nation of Canada.
And that...
that's the only API tower
covering both this and that.
Look, you're like a dog with a bone.
You see it already?
You see what I'm talking about.
That's a serious score.
[Bricke] What are you gonna do
with the cash? You can't spend it.
[man scoffs] You're so American.
You know, there are so many other places
in this world you can spend your money.
The border is military protected.
Yeah, but most of the city
belongs to the police.
The thing is, on the night of the API,
when they do that whole thing,
the cops, they turn in all their weapons,
and then all the policing is done
by one fat, middle-aged...
Wait.
Baby, what the hell is that guy's name?
[Shelby] Carl Wrightson.
[man] Carl... whatever the fuck.
Wrightson.
He's the systems manager at our tower.
It's insane the things guys will do
for a pretty girl.
I mean, Carl's gonna have a--
[laughs] An extremely intense day.
And we stick this
in the right place at the right time,
and we got ourselves...
30 minutes more than the rest of America.
Thirty minutes, maybe 35, which is tight,
but just enough time
to get from here to there,
and then we're trillionaires.
You don't want a drink?
I got great scotch.
[bottle cap unscrewing]
[liquid pouring]
Hey!
I knew Rory well, man.
I knew your brother well.
I did time with your brother.
[Shelby] Baby, don't.
[man] Yeah.
Yeah, we both volunteered
for the great opportunity
to get our fucking brains... zapped.
[barking]
[man] Give us a little bit more time
in the yard,
some commissary, you know, free ice cream.
Your brother wouldn't--
didn't commit suicide.
[grunting]
[man] He was fucking murdered by a guard.
Beaten to death by a fucking guard.
I watched it.
I couldn't do anything about it.
I mean...
that signal...
freezes you.
Freezes everything.
We should do this for Rory.
You should do it for him.
You got 24 hours.
If you look at your packages,
you'll see that the President has
authorized a 2% increase off your bases,
which means we're getting close
to 75% salary.
Now, in the meantime,
everyone is on full duty
until midnight this time next week
when the API signal goes live.
At which time,
all policing duty will be transferred
to a new branch of enforcement
run out of DC.
[officers groaning]
[sergeant] I'm sorry, guys.
All those who've signed up
for the implant,
you will be notified 24 hours
prior of your status.
Okay, page three.
This is where we're gonna find medical.
And those of you who will be staying on
will have the same co-pay as always.
You okay?
Shit.
Um... just have a seat one second.
[sergeant] These changes
will all go into effect as of next week,
so if this is gonna cause you problems,
don't talk to me.
Bring it to
the Health Services Department.
Uh, excuse me, Sarge.
Uh, there's a lady out front,
looks pretty banged up.
You might wanna...
Okay, page three.
This is where you'll find the medical.
Jesus Christ.
[object clattering]
Hey. Hey, excuse me, ma'am.
You can't be behind there, okay?
I'm gonna have to ask you
to step out from behind--
-What happened to your face?
-Fuck you.
Ma'am, please.
You need medical attention, okay--
[gun cocks]
That's fucking right.
Howdy fucking doody, man.
Oh, you wanna fucking die, man?
You wanna fucking die?
Where's the shit? Where's the shit?
Yeah, that's right.
Right in your fucking house, pig.
While I wait for my friend
to find all that contraband...
[sergeant talking in distance]
Jesus!
-Jesus!
-[gunshot]
[high-pitched ringing]
Fuck.
[sergeant] Sawyer.
He had a gun, Sarge.
Just go home, Sawyer.
Go the fuck home.
[reporter] We're always glad to have
the governor in the room today,
speaking on behalf of the API signal.
[governor] Well, look, we realize
that any amnesty program isn't perfect.
But with API,
any ill-gotten gains would become useless
to those who have them.
So, you're going to pay people
for money they stole.
If that's the way you wanna put it.
[reporter] If the recommendations
are not carried out...
[reporter continues indistinctly]
[Bricke] I met a friend of yours.
[moody blues song plays]
[Bricke] What are you getting me into?
Talk to me, Rory.
Talk to me.
♪ I'm going ♪
♪ Away for long ♪
[camera snapping]
We have a specialist with us today
talking about the inherent problems
with the API signal.
It's difficult to calibrate.
The signal is practically 100% effective.
And while it's true we've seen
an interruption of control
in subjects undergoing
traumatic brain injury,
the level of trauma necessary
to interfere with the signal
is not survivable.
Yes, you can damage the brain
enough to break the connection,
but this is hardly a practical means
to defeat the system.
[reporter] So in theory, an individual
could break from API control...
[Shelby] You're early.
Oh, shit.
Are we gonna do therapy instead?
I get your angle.
I really do.
In case it comes down to your boy or me,
which it often does,
then you're covered.
I get it.
But this score of his...
has a real chance of working.
So don't fuck with me...
or I'll kill you myself.
So romantic.
[man humming]
[Shelby] Can I respond, Captain?
What makes you so sure
that the score was Kevin's idea?
-Hey, baby.
-This place is a total shithole.
So what are we doing?
We all moving in together?
Little ménage à trois?
We're talking about a billion dollars
sitting in a vault right now.
-A billion dollars?
-Wait, even in hundreds,
that's like three tons.
It's 20 cubic yards.
That's--
I don't even know how to move that.
The factory doesn't just handle new money.
It also destroys old bills.
And with all that new cash piling up,
they're working double time
to shred the old stuff.
Every day,
they shred millions,
load up a big dump truck,
and send her across town
where they light it up.
You got the good money and the bad money
in one place at the same time?
What is the fucking plan?
Take the money, drive to Canada, die rich.
Yeah, yeah, but what's the plan?
How do we do it?
We take the money,
drive to Canada, and die rich.
[scoffs]
What's going on here?
-It's my fucking job.
-No, it's not.
It's not my job?
[Bricke] Three things.
First, I need a driver. I have a guy.
[Kevin]
Great, you got a guy now.
Second, five million dollars cash.
-And it doesn't have to be real.
-Yeah.
And third...
I'll need three EFP cone warheads,
like the ones they use against tanks.
No problem.
Thing is
that I can only think of two places
where we can find them,
the US Army and...
I just said no problem.
What are you thinking?
...the Dumois Crime Family.
You're Rossi Dumois's son.
Your father runs
the biggest crime syndicate in the city.
[Kevin] Alleged.
[Bricke]
He alone stands to inherit billions,
and you both live holed up
in a skanky loft, surrounded by landmines.
So... wanna explain?
Explain what?
You don't pick your family.
Look, it doesn't fucking matter
who the fuck my father is, all right?
It's not a secret.
However, I have a question.
[shouting] What the fuck are you doing?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Your father has a hit out on me,
so you better fucking explain yourself.
Listen, Bricke,
this jacket's Armani, man, please.
-[Bricke] Explain yourself!
-[Kevin] Okay, okay.
"Here lies Kevin Cash,
son of a gangster.
Never really did anything."
That's what it's gonna say
on my tombstone.
The moment the fucking signal hits,
making it the last fucking crime
in American history,
that's legacy, my friend.
"Legacy," that's another good word.
So, you want revenge. I want legacy.
Fuck!
By the way, my loft is not skanky, okay?
[sergeant] Hey, Sawyer.
How you hanging in there?
It's a fuck of a thing
that happened to you,
what with two days left to go.
You know about that, I'm...
I wanna go back out.
Put me on a beat, Sergeant.
I don't care which one.
Now, why the fuck
would you wanna do that?
I just, uh...
wanna do it right, you know?
[chuckles]
It's been my whole life, Sarge.
Carillo...
-[Sawyer] Thank you.
-Knock yourself out, supercop.
-[sergeant] Be safe out there.
-Can I have a vest? Thank you.
Thank you, Sarge.
-[man] You wanna drive today?
-[woman] Yeah, I'm good.
["It's Too Late" by Michael Chapman plays]
♪ There's ghosts out in the corridors
Of this broken-down hotel ♪
♪ The place is filled with strangers ♪
♪ Some don't wish me well ♪
♪ And I wake up with a bottle ♪
♪ Of something strong and cheap ♪
♪ And far too many memories
I'm trying not to keep ♪
♪ 'Cause we were kept apart... ♪
-[horn honks]
-Hey! Get outta here.
♪ I never knew I wanted you ♪
♪ Until it was too late ♪
[dance music playing]
[Kevin] What'd you expect?
Daddy's little cokehead.
Excuse me. Fuck you.
Every trust-fund asshole
and Daddy's little coke fiend
are getting ready for the ultimate rave.
They already have all the money.
As soon as the API is on,
they won't have to worry
about anyone taking it from them.
Fucking assholes. Hey! Where's my table?
What was I saying?
I was talking about something.
You were talking about your manifesto.
[Kevin] Oh, yeah, the manifesto
that nobody cares about,
my MIT queen.
Did you know that?
Do you know that this one has gone
to the most prestigious
technological school
in the world, I think.
She has a diploma with her name on it.
Because she put it there
after she hacked them.
And before that, she hacked the... FBI?
That's right.
Look at you. She's, like, embarrassed.
Yeah, it went FBI, MIT, and then you.
My three greatest hacks.
[Kevin]
You ever hear that expression,
"Behind every great man..."?
Yeah, it's: "Behind...
every great man is a woman."
And it's the truth.
Who says that you're a great man, darling?
"Who says that you're a great man,
darling?"
You're so funny.
These fucking jokes, they're so funny.
Why don't you go get us
some fucking champagne, huh?
Woman.
Fuck.
I felt it once.
The signal.
Right there.
A direct...
molecular modulation
of the prefrontal cortex. [sucking]
It's crazy.
You can see all the terrible,
beautiful things you're gonna do.
You can run it
over and over again in your mind,
step by step.
Then when you go do it,
when you tell your body,
"Okay, you remember those things
that we were gonna do? Do 'em."
Boom! You turn into Sammy the vegetable.
[grunting]
It's crazy.
Can you beat it?
-Beat it?
-The signal.
Beat the signal?
Yeah, you could beat it and you could die.
-Come on. Forgive me.
-Here you go, you great fucking man.
-[Kevin]  I'm sorry! I said I--
-Fuck you!
[Kevin] Wait. Now, what?
Baby, come back!
Let's have a toast.
We're celebrating.
To the last days of American crime.
[reporter]
You're saying if these people,
these new federal law enforcers,
you're saying they won't be affected
by the API.
[governor]
No, I'm saying the police have always had
a special relationship with the law.
It's always been legal
for them to use deadly force
if he or she believes it's necessary.
[reporter] But these blockers, that takes
that freedom to a whole new level.
[governor] Well, I disagree.
[reporter] This will result
in a police state on the sca--
[sergeant] Sawyer, what can I do for you?
Um...
I was wondering
if I could still put my name down
for the implant.
Fill that out.
Make sure it's on my desk in the morning.
Okay. Thank you.
You're hard to find.
Guess that's kind of what I do,
though, right?
You never wanna see me again.
"I'll kill myself,"
I think is how you put it.
[gunfire and explosions in distance]
[helicopters circling]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[Shelby] All the rats.
They'd jump ship,
but they can't find the edge.
You should go.
He's gonna be looking for you.
Maybe I don't care.
That's not you.
You're always running your game.
It's not my fault, you know...
that I don't trust anyone.
My mom,
she was alone, and...
then she met this guy,
and he made money, and...
he treated me pretty badly.
He beat me till I left.
And then after that,
there were other assholes,
and then there was Kevin.
Can you do me a solid?
Will you hold me for a little bit?
Is that part of your game?
What do you think?
[man] Still alive.
[Bricke] Still alive.
-How are you?
-[man] Good.
Pretty house.
Pretty neighborhood.
So, do you got an American flag
in front of your house and shit?
You got it.
[Bricke] It's not your dream, Ross.
[Ross] I'm too old for this, Bricke.
So...
why'd you call me?
Because I need you.
One billion.
A billion?
Why didn't we get this before?
Opportunities, man.
Opportunities.
This fucking API...
thing, man, it's...
It creates a gap.
We both know...
that everything's a question of timing.
So...
I really need you on this one, man.
[Ross] I don't know.
Who are you here to see?
[Bricke] Jack Morgan.
[door opening]
My secretary assures me
that you were once quite a big deal
in this town.
Never caught.
The federal buyback
focuses on white-collar criminals,
bankers, hedge-fund managers
who've secreted away large sums,
which if not repatriated now,
will simply go out of circulation
once the signal is active,
which isn't good for anyone.
It's not for purse snatchers.
Five million. Cash.
Five million dollars cash.
How'd you even get it in here?
Filled my trunk with hundreds.
Under the API amnesty program,
I can give you...
$350,000.
You must know you're late.
The signal goes live
in just over 24 hours,
at which point, as you know,
your money will become useless.
Best deal of your life.
All you asked for...
[Shelby]
Totally dying to say "according to spec"
or some shit like that right then,
weren't you?
[Bricke] Maybe.
Let's crime novel this shit up.
It's that easy?
[chuckles softly]
No.
The serials on hundreds are tracked,
so I can't just make them up.
I've hacked the federal database
and got us clean numbers.
Then we have to mix
the right chemistry for the watermarks,
which isn't that hard,
except the printer doesn't accept it
as ink,
so you have to hack the printer.
And when you do that, you're hacking HP,
not the feds,
and that's actually fucking harder.
The only way that you can detect this
is to burn it,
so don't go light a smoke up
on these bad boys, okay?
MIT schoolboys didn't teach you this,
did they?
I'm just a girl
who likes fast cars and big numbers.
[phone buzzes]
[Shelby] Hey.
Yep. I'm at Bricke's.
He's got his dick in me right now,
don't you, Bricke?
[applicator firing]
[woman on PA]
Have your documents ready.
No one will be allowed to pass
without proper identification.
Stop.
[knocks]
You enjoying yourself there, Posner?
Please, can you tell your pet moron
that when he fucks up my face,
I've gotta explain that.
Don't fuck up her face.
Where is she?
Information first, please.
We're going after the main vault,
a lot of money.
-That's where we get Kevin Cash?
-No.
We're switching the load
at the steel works before midnight.
He'll be celebrating.
-I'm just saying, better odds for you.
-Hmm.
So why steal a truckload of money
just before the signal turns on?
He won't be able to spend it.
Oh, Kevin's not in it for the money.
Kevin just wants to be famous.
What about Graham Bricke?
Bricke's just the muscle.
He doesn't matter.
I will enjoy showing these
to your boyfriend.
The official one, I mean,
before putting him in jail
for the rest of his life.
Bricke's part of the plan.
Hey, Posner, I like this.
I guess we could be
a part of this plan, too.
You're right, partner.
Our guest does seem to be
in a generous mood.
Where is she?
[exhales]
Hey.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Did they hurt you?
No?
God, I missed you.
Your sister really loves you.
You know that, girl?
You're lucky.
Hey.
[chuckles]
You take this. [sniffs]
Okay. You know where to go, right?
-[girl] I don't wanna go without you.
-I know, but you have to.
I'm sorry.
But I'm gonna meet you there, okay?
I promise.
If you cross me,
I'll let Posner head up into Canada,
and he'll find her.
And I don't like it,
but we both know that he'll hurt her.
Then we'll find you.
You guys can't do shit anymore.
Oh, we can do that shit.
We're the motherfucking FBI.
We can do all kinds of that shit...
and get through the fucking signal.
[woman on PA]
Have your documents ready.
No one will be allowed to pass
without proper identification.
What is your view on the API?
Let's hear it.
Well, my basic view to begin with
is that we all need change,
and we all know that this is certainly not
the country that I grew up in.
-It's not an America that I recognize.
-[reporter] Mm-hmm.
[governor] We need to return
to those days where we felt safe,
and that is what the API is about.
[reporter] Understood. But, you know,
there's another type of mind control
where, you know-- Okay,
I'm afraid that some criminal
is gonna attack me, and I'm sick of it.
[Kevin]
♪ Like a bomb, baby, boom, boom ♪
[governor] People feel that the API
is all about control, but no.
We have control over the fear
that we have.
We can't all walk out
on the streets at night.
We count on it for the sake of our wives
and our daughters,
the ones we need to protect. The API...
[Kevin] ♪ You make my heart go... ♪
♪ Kaboom, boom! ♪
♪ Like sex in the afternoon ♪
♪ Fucking Looney Toon ♪
[governor]
We are bringing in freedom.
[reporter] But this is still
a level of control, surely.
[governor] It has control
over certain elements in society,
but those are the elements
in our society--
[reporter] But this is why people
are trying to get their voices heard.
[sirens wailing in distance]
[gunfire and explosions in distance]
[rap music playing in distance]
-[woman yelling]
-[gunshots]
Reminiscent of the failed attempt
by actor John Farley last week,
NBA superstar LaMarr Duke and his wife
had liquidated their accounts.
The couple were using
his private plane to exit the country
when the Air Force AC-130 opened fire.
[gunfire on television]
-[gunfire]
-[people screaming]
[Ross] Still alive.
["William Joseph Dean"
by Bror Gunnar Jansson plays]
♪ The devil dwells in the whiskey glass ♪
♪ Black crow cryin' in the tree ♪
♪ Death is waiting on the porch ♪
♪ I know he's been there for me ♪
♪ Now, he's been there for a while ♪
♪ Gonna have to wait longer too ♪
♪ 'Cause I ain't leaving
Not until I'm through with you ♪
[song fades away in headphones]
[Shelby] Hey, John Wayne.
John Wayne?
Fuck John Wayne.
You jealous?
[Kevin] He's dead.
Health insurance.
Oh, is this your guy?
[Bricke] Yeah.
Hi, guy.
Okay, all right.
It's cool.
I can do it sideways, too.
That's a lot of heat.
Yeah, well, my father is a little, uh...
rough around the edges,
so I like a little health insurance
of my own.
Your dad.
So you're setting me up to get killed?
I'm set-- What?
What are you talking about?
-You forgot we have a job tonight?
-You're paranoid.
Look, I told you, if you don't have
a contract on your head in my family,
that means they don't like you.
You still want
your fucking EFP cone warheads?
We're gonna go there and take them.
Why would I want you dead?
I need you.
Get dressed.
-Now.
-Okay, I'm done--
I've been waiting on you.
Jesus.
Bye, guy. Don't eat any of my food.
So, you trust her?
Who?
Who do you think?
So, you and your dad get along?
That's a matter of perspective.
When you go to a shrink,
they say you need to accept your father
for who he is
and avoid the desire to unseat him.
But if you ask me,
my father's just a sociopathic...
control freak...
who wants to destroy anything
that gets close
to his black maggot-infested blood pump
he calls a fucking heart.
So, you two are close.
Super close.
Look, they even threw us
a little fucking homecoming party.
-Lonnie, you look terrible, man.
-What the fuck are you doing here, Kev?
-I just-- I missed you so much, Lonnie.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How you doing, Bricke?
Go ahead, Kevin.
I got business with your friend over here.
No, no, no, Lonnie. This is my new bestie.
You know what that means?
That means he's untouchable.
Didn't know you had any friends, Kevin.
[engine revving]
Up against the car. You know the drill.
Up against the car, both of you.
Okay. All right. Jesus! Armani!
Big toys for a small boy.
I promise
to take good care of your bitches.
This way.
You know,
you watch too many fucking movies.
Come on, Bricke.
Hey, when you want a real job,
let me know.
[upbeat party music playing]
Come on, guys. The guns.
It's like... it's tacky.
[reporter] The US Supreme Court has upheld
an international travel ban,
preventing US citizens
from leaving the country...
until the implementation of...
[Kevin] Okay. All right.
Here's where
the real fucking evil people are.
Here are the real gangsters.
Here's to fucking over the world.
Jesus, tough room. Is this thing on?
-My, my.
-[Kevin] Hey, sis!
-[sister] I've missed you.
-I missed you more.
Where have you been, hmm?
I told you, stop-- Don't...
do that in public.
Where have I been? Where have you been?
Oh, you gained some weight, huh?
Oh, fuck off.
-He'll be happy to see you.
-This is my sister.
What the hell is that skirt?
Shut up.
Sis, I can see your...
fricking...
Oh, Dad! It's me, your favorite son.
Daddy, look who's here.
I thought you were dead.
Sorry to disappoint you.
What's this piece of shit doing here?
That's my lawyer.
And I'm the pope.
I figured you'd come crawling
out of the woodwork sooner or later.
Everybody comes crawling back
to Daddy in the end...
for a handout.
-Where's the good stuff?
-Have a drink.
Kind of disappointed, Pops.
I mean, I thought you would have
some kind of Roman orgy going on
with your fucking sheep.
Nah. I'm 100% American. Legit.
Honest.
I own the bank.
No more busting kneecaps
for 10% on the streets.
We issue credit cards
and charge some fuckhead farmer
from Arkansas 25%.
If he don't pay,
I send in the US marshal
and take his home.
Takes a big man to exploit the poor.
[chuckles]
Who thought it would be so easy?
Still see you're having daddy issues.
Like never before,
Daddy.
-Yeah, we need something.
-Ah.
You come here asking for something?
In the past, you just took.
He's just pissed off
because I fucked his wife.
Not my mother, his second wife.
How is Victoria?
Don't know if you heard.
I shot her.
Well... [sniffs] this is awkward.
You fucking set me up!
You tried to fucking kill me!
What kind of sicko fucks his stepmother?
I introduced you to her.
-I gave you the world.
-You didn't give me shit!
-Now, get the fuck out of here!
-Fuck you!
You didn't give me shit!
You gave her everything!
Oh, grow up, Kevin!
Grow up? Shut the fuck up!
Oh, go to your party!
-Go to your party!
-Do you want my tits?
Do you want my shoes?
-You fucking bitch.
-Oh, is that the best you got?
-You fucking bitch!
-That the best you got?
-Go back to your party!
-Is this okay with Daddy?
-Go back to your party. Go.
-Tell him, Daddy.
-I'm his favorite.
-Go. Your heart is black!
Your heart is black! You're dead inside!
Nah, you don't-- You know what he says?
I get a call,
my father wants to apologize to me.
And you know, I knew it was bullshit,
but I wanted to believe it.
I really did. I wanted to believe it.
I wanted to believe
that he was gonna apologize to me.
I don't know why.
I know I'm fucking crazy.
You know what I got?
I got that.
Two bullets.
That was my fucking birthday present.
You tried to fucking kill me
like you killed my mother.
If you think I'm going to apologize,
you're wrong.
We all use each other.
And we all hate each other.
I'm sorry, Bricke.
-[gunshot]
-[Kevin cries out]
Fuck.
[groaning]
Fucking psycho! What did you do?
I got fucking shot.
-Did you kill your father, you asshole?
-Yes, I did.
Get me up. I got a fucking plan!
[breathing heavily, grunting]
What's the fucking plan?
[Kevin] Just give me a second.
[beeping]
What the fuck is going on?
We gotta go.
-[buzzing]
-[Kevin] Trust me.
Sorry, Pops.
[hand scanner beeping]
Why are you locking the door?
[Kevin] Fucking son of a bitch,
you had to shoot me.
All right?
Come on. Where the fuck are they at?
Fuck.
Yes!
[banging on door]
[Lonnie] Open up!
[Kevin] Trust me.
Piece of shit motherfucker!
Die, you motherfuckers!
It's clear. Blow that fucking wall.
What the fuck? Let's go.
Come on.
[gun fires]
[Kevin] Fuck.
[gasping]
[Bricke] Cash!
Cash! Let's go!
Come on!
-Fucking Connie.
-Come on!
Son of a bitch!
[man] After them!
[gunfire]
If this gunshot doesn't kill me,
your driving is.
[sirens wailing in distance]
[groans]
Lonnie will be looking for you.
Get yourself cleaned up.
See you at the train station.
[car engine starts]
Bricke, you're bleeding.
Not my blood. Your boyfriend's.
I know about the girl.
I can explain.
What?
How you sold us out to the FBI?
She's my sister.
I told you I can explain.
Maybe this is what we both wanted.
-[footsteps approach]
-[thud]
[match lighting]
[Lonnie] Bricke.
[breathing heavily]
[yells]
Listen to me, Bricke.
I have guys all over this town,
anywhere anyone has ever seen Kevin.
So it's just a matter of time.
Something I have, you don't...
[exhales]
Who the fuck are you again?
I'm just a call girl.
[inhales sharply]
Then you won't mind
if I torture this cocksucker to death?
Huh?
You really call this call girl, man?
[grunts, sighs]
This is your last chance, Bricke.
[Bricke] For what?
My lap dance?
[laughing]
Yeah.
I'll be your bitch.
You've just got a be a little more, uh...
comprehensive to me, alright?
Where's Kevin?
I'm not fucking asking you again!
[gun cocks]
[Shelby] Wait!
[breathing heavily] Hmm?
I'm who you want.
[breathing heavily] She's lying.
Kevin Cash.
Calls himself Cash
'cause he can't stand Dumois.
And he's got a fiancée
who he will do just about anything for.
Me.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
[exhales]
So...
take her to the car.
Wait for me.
I wanna ask her a couple of questions.
-[Bricke] No.
-[Lonnie] Yeah.
Yeah, come on! [cackling]
Fucker!
[breathing heavily]
[grunts, pants]
There's someone I'd like you to meet.
Maybe you met him before.
You boys have fun now.
-[door opening]
-[footsteps approaching]
Now, you see,
I thought that you might wanna see this.
Hiya, Bricke.
I thought you'd quit smoking.
You're right, Bricke.
I should quit.
But I had some other priorities before.
Gotta tell ya,
a moment like this,
I've been waiting for it.
I guess you can say...
it gave me a reason to live.
[breathing heavily]
Wasn't much water on the floor.
[sets down gas can forcefully]
It took me a long minute to roll around
and put myself out.
Showed me what I was made of.
You kinda owe me one.
[panting]
-You kinda owe me one, right?
-Yeah.
-You kinda owe me one, don't you?
[growling]
[yelling] Yeah.
[breathing heavily]
[gasping in pain]
Tell me, Bricke.
[breathing heavily]
You got something to live for? Huh?
[Shelby] Bricke!
No! Bricke!
Bricke!
[coughing]
[Kevin] First step is a doozy.
[grunts]
Don't worry, you shouldn't be afraid.
You're worth a lot to me.
Buys you some time.
[Lonnie] Get down!
Fucking animal! You son of a bitch!
You're an ugly-looking motherfucker.
Fuck!
Move, Ross! Move!
-Fuck it up.
-Ready?
-[grunts]
-[Bricke] Are you all right?
[Ross grunts] I'm all right.
Just go and get her.
[grunts] Son of a bitch.
Stop! Get out of the car!
-Quick!
-Hey!
Hey!
[Shelby] Please. Please, no--
I'm gonna give you an experience
you'll never forget.
You can see this as a gift
-for the rest of your pathetic life.
-Please.
-[whimpers] No.
-[Lonnie] Yes.
-[Lonnie] I know you will.
-Please!
-[Lonnie] This is an experience.
-[crying] No.
Be still.
Look, you are Kevin's fiancée.
[breathing heavily]
[choking]
[Shelby] I owe you an apology.
I should've never have called you
a loser.
[Ross chuckles]
[Shelby coughs]
[breathing heavily]
Still alive?
Yeah.
Back at my place, you had an out.
You should have taken it.
Nobody ever do anything just for you,
Bricke?
[Bricke] The FBI.
When will they hit us?
[Shelby] After.
The switch?
Kevin is who they really want.
The FBI nailed me hacking their system.
There's two guys,
and if I don't do what they want,
they're gonna hurt my sister.
That's not gonna happen.
I am done, Bricke.
Believe me.
With you,
it's so hard to know what to believe.
[inhales]
Look, I needed to know
whoever was on top when the smoke cleared.
It's not like that now.
You know that, don't you?
[exhales]
Don't you?
[Kevin] ♪ Oh, baby, you ♪
♪ Oh, baby, you ♪
♪ Why you play with me? ♪
♪ But you say he's just forget ♪
♪ You say-- ♪
You forgot something.
Give me the fucking key.
Can you just give me the fucking key?
[Bricke] After midnight,
we have 30 minutes to cross the border
before the signal resets.
The switch takes six. The drive eight.
There's no room for error.
[snorts]
See you all on the other side.
Come here.
[reporter]
With only one hour remaining
before the launch of the API signal,
local police forces across the country
are preparing to surrender their arms
in the handover of jurisdiction
to federal law enforcement.
[man over PA] The Ambassador Bridge
is currently closed until 6:00 a.m.
All crossing is prohibited.
[gun cocking]
Evening, gentlemen.
[exhales]
All right, give me all your fucking money.
Give me all your money.
You think I'm fucking playing?
You really don't understand my humor.
I dunno, man. I got a bad feeling.
I feel like one of us
is gonna take a bullet tonight.
You go first.
[reporter]
With less than an hour remaining,
tensions continue to rise
as protesters engage in standoffs
with law enforcement across the country.
[crowd chanting] Say no to API!
[reporter] With police absenteeism rates
estimated at close to 90%.
[Shelby] Carl, I'm afraid.
They just came out of nowhere.
I didn't know where else to go.
Can you--
-[crowd chanting] Say no to API!
-Yeah, I'm here. I'm right here.
[crowd chanting]
Say no to API! Say no to API!
[police officer]
You here for Carl Wrightson? Follow me.
It's okay. I'll take it from here.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know where else to go.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
-Just... just follow me.
-Thank you.
[man] Ten.
Twenty-four.
-There's supposed to be two of you.
-Tonight?
Who would come out tonight?
Yeah, okay.
All right.
[trunk closes]
All right. Good to go. Let him through.
[machine whirs, beeps]
[machine whirring]
Sir. Your guest has been red-flagged
for prior history.
You know who I fucking am?
I mean, look at her.
Come on.
[elevator dings]
Randal?
You're not Randal.
Why do you got--
[elevator dings]
[people chattering]
Sorry, you can't go in there.
Oh, I'm sorry.
-[reporter] ...another 300 injured...
-Have a seat.
[reporter] ...during a mass shooting
at a protest over the API signal.
-Would you like some water?
-Yes, please.
[reporter] ...firing from a parking garage
overlooking the protest
and went on to kill himself.
Despite the claims
from international groups...
-Thanks.
-[reporter] ...it is believed this event
-was tied to domestic terror.
-You sure you're all right?
Yeah. I'm so sorry.
I don't mean to be any trouble.
It's okay. My part here is done anyway.
We're just waiting for a go-ahead...
from Washington.
Thank you, Carl.
You just made
this next part so much easier.
Here, I thought Christmas
was a few months away.
[door alert buzzes]
Cutting it a little too close for comfort,
ain't you, Mr. Bricke?
This...
is too close for comfort.
Stop him!
Shut the fucking door!
Shut the door!
Come on.
[alarm blaring]
Stop the lift!
Bring it back up.
[man] I can't.
It's designed
specifically not to be overridden
from the outside.
So no one can take over this office
and do...
-that.
-Let it in.
Ali Baba.
[Morgan over PA]
Congratulations, gentlemen.
You just broke into your own jail cell.
Son of a bitch!
Wait!
[reporter] ...many injured after a bomb
exploded in the middle of the protest.
Prior to this...
Even if you could get out,
which I doubt you can...
in six minutes, you're history.
-No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
-What?
It's live. Don't breathe.
You wanna try one?
-You go ahead.
-You sure?
Yeah.
[officer on radio]
We've got a code 22-44.
Suspicious intrusion at the API building.
[siren wails]
[reporter] Shots were heard.
Upon searching the gunman's property,
more weapons were immediately discovered.
The process of identifying the victims
is still underway.
This, in many ways,
was an all too familiar sight
as both sides of the debate over the API
have resorted to violence.
Hello.
Yeah, I'm busy.
I'm just hanging out with Carl.
[muffled speech]
He says hi.
Shit. I'm gonna have to call you
right back, okay? Yep.
I gotta go.
[reporter]
A state of emergency has been declared.
[muffled yelling]
[reporter] ...disperse earlier crowds
in which many arrests had been made.
[computer] Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four,
three, two, one.
[cheering]
-[high-pitched ringing]
-[groans]
[reporter] Some Americans
have taken to the street today
to celebrate the implementation
of the controversial API.
[alarm klaxon wails]
[high-pitched ringing stops]
Okay.
What now?
Ten seconds, more or less.
More or less?
Where are the fucking cops?
Tell them we're just about to lose
a billion fucking dollars!
Go! Go!
[alarm sounding]
[muffled cries]
What the fuck's going on?
She's in the server room, to the left.
Freeze! Freeze!
Are you alone?
Sir, she betrayed me.
Get out. Get down.
[Carl]
What're you gonna do with her?
I need you to tell me
what the fuck is going on right now.
Six minutes, Ross.
Cover the truck.
[alarm sounding]
-[computer beeps]
-[tech] There we go.
-[high-pitched ringing resumes]
-[groaning]
Call her!
It's on.
-[gun fires]
-[yells]
[gasping]
Oh, shit. Did I just do that?
-What did you do?
-Look at you.
-You're like a lion with no balls.
-What are you doing?
Everyone's at the zoo, staring at him.
Look, it's a lion with no fucking balls.
Don't.
Don't do it, please.
Don't do it. Don't do what?
-Don't...
-Please don't do it.
Please don't do what? What shouldn't I do?
-Please don't do this. Stop!
-What?
-Not kill your best friend?
-Stop!
-No!
-[Kevin] What are you doing? Huh?
What do you wanna do?
-Huh?
-[Bricke groans]
Oh, you wanna dance.
[Bricke screams]
You're never there
for the people you love. [yells]
-[thudding]
-[Bricke groans]
[choking]
Come on.
I got a secret to tell you.
You need to pay attention to this.
[Kevin]
Every Friday, we'd meet in the yard.
They'd yell,
"Fight!"
and get us to do
the nastiest shit to each other.
[dog barking]
[high-pitched ringing]
[Kevin] And then,
they would turn on the brain rape.
[grunting]
-Get in there!
-[Kevin] You ever read William Burroughs?
He had a thing called "the cop within,"
you know, morality, right, wrong.
[high-pitched ringing]
[Kevin] Turns out,
even a sociopathic fucker like me has one.
[groaning]
Motherfucker!
[yelling]
[Kevin]
And I had something else nobody else had:
time to figure it out,
time to practice.
[high-pitched ringing]
[Kevin] And finally,
one day...
I get clarity...
that absolutely nothing meant anything.
[barking]
[yelling]
[Kevin] And Jesus Christ as my witness,
that set me free.
Come on, shoot me.
Fucking shoot me!
You know actually killing your brother
got me out of jail?
Can you believe that?
I mean, motherfucker!
Cruel and unusual punishment?
Human experiments?
My lawyers had a field day with that one.
They didn't realize what a gift it was.
Take Dupree with you.
[Kevin] Um, I'm not sure
if you're listening to me.
I don't feel anything anymore.
Not for you
and certainly not for that bitch.
[laughing] You can have that one.
What are you doing?
Trying to shoot me again?
Come on, try.
Oh, that felt good.
Are we still friends?
I didn't mean it.
[Bricke groans]
[humming]
Pussy. That's your problem.
That's your problem.
You know, I actually like you, Bricke.
I really do.
Bricke.
How about one more? [pumps shotgun]
Huh?
What was that?
I can't hear you.
Speak into my good ear.
Bricke.
Come on, Brickey.
Bricke, wake up!
You know what
the really fucked-up thing is?
In this world...
unfortunately,
that makes me the superhero.
[laughing]
What, are you smiling? [laughing]
Why are you smiling?
Something funny?
You're a tough son of a bitch,
you know that?
[both laughing]
I mean, I'm impressed.
Are you bulletproof?
Am I what?
[yells]
Fucker!
High middle, not bad.
Maybe down a touch.
Three points for the next one.
Fucking-- [yells]
[FBI agent] Ouch, that hurt.
Okay. Take the final one.
I'm getting bored.
But I'm not done playing yet.
I said, end it.
You fucking piece of shit motherfucker!
You motherfucking piece of shit!
You fucking bitch-ass mother--
Bricke, right?
How you doing?
Doesn't look good.
Hey. Thanks for helping with this, Bricke.
You did a great job.
Finally got this motherfucker.
I owe you a medal.
Now all we need to do is find
this three-way thing's girlfriend,
and we can end this chapter permanently.
[breathing heavily]
[Bricke] You promised her.
Yeah, I remember, but you know what?
Things are changing.
Everything's moving like planets.
We're not gonna keep that promise,
are we, Posner?
I'm afraid not. [chuckles]
Sorry, Bricke. [chuckles]
[FBI agent] What about you, now? Hmm?
I mean, I'm no doctor,
but I think he won't make it.
Oh, he won't.
-Should I finish him?
-Uh-uh, don't waste a bullet for a dog.
Let him die, slowly.
One last promise.
I will care for her...
with tenderness.
Yeah.
[grunts]
You know what I could do with now?
Coffee and pussy?
You got the pussy right. [laughs]
[grunting]
[gun clicking]
[wheezing, coughing]
[Sawyer] I'm not gonna hurt you, okay?
I just need you to tell me
what is going on.
You can talk to me. I can help you.
I'm gonna put this down, okay?
I'm gonna put this down.
[yells]
Get off me!
-[grunting]
-[yelling]
Fucking bitch.
[screams]
[growling]
[screaming]
[high-pitched ringing]
[breathing heavily]
[both grunting]
Settle down.
You have the right to--
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you
in a court of-- Fuck.
-Coward.
-You see this?
-Stop fucking around!
-Bitch.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
-[kicks]
-[Sawyer groans]
[panting]
[pained breathing]
[device beeping]
[elevator dings]
-[alarm wailing]
-[tech] Go!
[breathing heavily]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[elevator dings]
[alarm sounding]
[machine beeping]
[security guard] Go! Go! Go!
Stop!
I said stop! Get your ass on the ground.
We will shoot you.
Get down!
Down on the ground.
Hands in the air!
Get down on your knees, now!
We will shoot!
You got five seconds.
Five...
four...
three...
two... one.
[Shelby crying]
[Bricke grunting in pain]
[man over PA]
The Ambassador Bridge is currently closed.
All crossing is prohibited.
[border patrol officer] Hold your ground!
Open fire!
[man over speakers]
You are entering Canadian territory.
Stop, or we will open fire.
If I tell you something,
you promise to forget that I ever said it?
Bricke?
[gasps] Hey, Bricke.
Come on. Hey.
Hey. Stay with me. Come on.
Bricke. Bricke.
Come on.
Wake the fuck up.
[crying]
Stay with me.
What'd you want to say?
That I love you.
I love you so fucking much.
[laughs]
What?
You just crossed something off my list.
[crying]
[sniffs]
[sirens wailing]
He's gone.
["Personal Jesus" plays]
♪ Reach out and touch faith ♪
♪ Your own personal Jesus ♪
♪ Someone to hear your prayers ♪
♪ Someone who cares ♪
♪ Your own personal Jesus ♪
♪ Someone to hear your prayers ♪
♪ Someone who's there ♪
♪ Feeling unknown
And you're all alone ♪
♪ Flesh and bone
By the telephone ♪
♪ Lift up the receiver
I'll make you a believer ♪
♪ Take second best
Put me to the test ♪
♪ Things on your chest
You need to confess ♪
♪ I will deliver
You know I'm a forgiver ♪
♪ Reach out and touch faith ♪
♪ Your own personal Jesus ♪
♪ Someone to hear your prayers ♪
♪ Someone who cares ♪
♪ Your own personal Jesus ♪
♪ Someone to hear your prayers ♪
♪ Someone who's there ♪
♪ Feeling unknown
And you're all alone ♪
♪ Flesh and bone
By the telephone ♪
♪ Lift up the receiver
I'll make you a believer ♪
♪ I will deliver
You know I'm a forgiver ♪
♪ Reach out and touch faith
Your own personal Jesus ♪
♪ Reach out and touch faith ♪
♪ Reach out ♪
["Personal Jesus" ends]
[menacing music playing]
[music ends]
Watch free HD Movies and TV Shows at
StreamingSites.com