-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
So we met at a party,
and it was magic.
Within a half hour,
we were driving up into this
really nice neighborhood,
and we were running down the
stairs of some stranger's backyard,
and then we were swimming
and we were in love.
What we didn't count on was that
even though the lights were off,
the owner of the home was there,
and he came out screaming at us,
and it was the greatest
night of my life.
Ready?
So my idea was, you know,
let's try and re-create that moment.
Oh, it's freezing!
It's a little colder
than I remember it.
Do you think he's coming out?
I'm sure. I'm sure
he heard us, right?
Hello? This is fun.
Yeah.
Where is he?
Maybe he's not home.
Happy anniversary anyway.
Happy anniversary.
When we were in the water
and we were waiting
and no one came out, no one was home,
and we were just floating there,
I felt sad,
and I felt like our happiness
used to be so easy
and there used to be so much of it,
and now I feel like
happiness is something
that we have to re-create.
Ah.
I'm sorry. I tried to
make a romantic moment.
I'll never take you to
a fucking pool again.
Oh, come on. Don't do that.
Okay.
This could be fun.
We're going to do a
compatibility exercise.
I want you both to play a
note at the same time, okay?
Just any note?
Yep. Knock yourself out.
Wow! You guys are
not in sync, are you?
We used to be great.
We used to be really
irreverent and...
Yeah. There was teasing.
- Yeah.
- And stuff. Like I...
I mean no offense...
But I would call you a
bitch and it was funny.
Yeah, it was hilarious.
I used to call you a bitch.
- You thought it was really funny.
- Yeah.
I just don't know how we're
going to move forward
if we keep having this
circular conversation
about me doing what I did
which I have apologized for already,
and we are here because
we are trying to move on.
I don't see why we have
to keep revisiting that
because it's the same
conversation over and over again.
Because you don't get
to decide that, Ethan.
You don't get to decide
when we move on, I do.
30, you guys having sex?
Now if you'd played
this one, Sophie...
or that one...
that's pretty, right?
But this... not so much.
Anyway, it's just an exercise.
I want to trust you again.
I want to forgive you.
I want all of those things.
I want us and I want us to work.
I don't know why you feel
like I don't want that.
Because we don't agree on
how we're going to get there.
Where are you?
Okay.
I have an idea.
This is a great place.
I think it will be very helpful.
It's absolutely beautiful.
It's about an hour and
a half north from here.
It's like a... like
a perfect retreat,
just the two of you.
Give you a chance to
reset the reset button.
I've sent a lot of couples there,
and they've all come back
renewed.
- What do you think?
- I mean, I'll try anything.
Sophie?
Wow!
Hello?
And then when you
pour the wine, you do this.
This is what they do in
the restaurants. Watch this. Whoop.
So it doesn't drip.
Even though I kind of...
- It kind of dripped.
- I don't think you did it right.
Cheers!
To me and my cooking.
There's a guest house on the
property which is pretty cool.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I don't even know if
we're supposed to use it
or if someone else is renting it.
Oh, God. What's happening?
Come here. Come here.
What's happening?
Whoa!
Yeah, yeah.
You've got to hold it.
Hold it in, hold it in.
There you go.
- Geez.
- Wow, still got it.
Get the light going.
- Sweetie.
- Sorry, sorry.
Give me kiss.
Aw! You're so cute
without your glasses.
You shouldn't wear these.
I like you without them.
Do you like me without the glasses?
Should I wear them?
Get over here!
You found me.
I found you.
Hey.
Hey there.
Hey, you know, you were right.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
Do tell.
We need to try more new things,
like weekends away
in places like this.
- You think so?
- Mmm-hmm.
It makes me excited about us again.
Do you feel it?
- I do.
- Yeah.
I love you.
And here it comes.
- Aw.
- Oh!
- Close!
- The bounce. It's okay.
- Okay, wait. Your turn.
- Okay.
- Oh, under.
- Under. Okay.
Under and in.
Oh, shit!
Oh, you got it. Oh, my God!
Of course I got it.
- Ready?
- Mmm-hmm.
This is your grape.
Hi.
Come here, come here.
What?
Come here.
That was awesome!
I knew you could do it.
Do you want to sleep here tonight?
Can we?
Sure. We can do whatever we want.
Okay. Yep.
Let me just get some clothes.
I don't want to sleep in my jeans.
- Okay.
- You want anything?
I'm good.
I love you, hon.
I'll be right here.
Okay.
Ha-ha! You're asleep.
Very funny.
You did it. You got your joke.
Ethan.
Stop it.
Stop it. I laughed. It's over now.
Where'd you go? Where'd you go?
How did you get up here so fast?
Did you find a secret passageway?
Yeah, secret underground passage.
- Wow!
- Mmm-hmm.
So mysterious.
No, seriously.
How did you get here so fast?
You beat me.
What?
How did you get here from
the guest house before me?
You mean, before dinner?
I was just walking outside
and I just walked over.
No, not before dinner, just now.
Why are you so sweaty?
Did you go for a run or something?
Oh, yeah.
Because... Is that the joke
that's happening now?
What?
The joke that you're
not going to remember
that we just had sex,
because that's really funny.
Wait!
We just had sex?
Okay. That's not funny.
I'm not trying to be funny.
I thought you were making a joke.
- Why are you doing this right now?
- I'm not doing anything.
I've...
Huh?
You know what, Ethan?
You just had a really nice night and
I don't know why you would ruin it.
I'm not trying to ruin our night.
I want to have a nice night.
Fine, we had sex. It was great.
You were amazing.
You're an asshole.
Good night.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Hey.
Good morning, handsome.
Oh! I'm hungover.
Well, it sounds like you
need some breakfast.
Not that we need to
get back into it. Um...
But that was a little bit of
a weird fight last night.
I know.
I don't really understand what
happened, but I feel like
maybe we just chalk it up
to like some bad pot...
Alcohol combo, put it behind us
and not let it ruin the trip.
Agreed, totally.
Cool.
That being said,
it was one of the weirder
fights we've had. Like...
Oh my God, I know.
Crazy, right?
I mean, I still don't
fully understand
whether you were so drunk and stoned
that you thought we had sex
or were you just were making
a joke and it backfired.
Honestly, I think it was just
one of those things, you know?
One of those things...
No, I'm asking you
was it that you were drunk and stoned
or was it playing a joke...
Because I'm still confused
what happened.
I think the important
thing is that, you know,
we fought, we made up, we had
a nice cuddle, beautiful day.
Sophie, what are you talking about?
We had a fight and you stormed out.
We didn't make up.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, are you okay? I'm...
Okay, Mr. Hangover.
I think it's time for some food. Huh?
Let's get something in your stomach.
You're kind of freaking me
out a little bit, Sophie.
I've got to say... Is that bacon?
Yeah.
You hate it when I eat bacon.
What?
What's going on?
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
I don't understand why
you're doing this.
No.
No, no, no, no.
No what?
This was...
There were plates... Hello?
What are you talking about plates?
Hello, hello? What are you... Ethan?
- Where'd you go?
- Where'd who go?
Ethan?
Hello?
There was bacon right
there on those plates...
What are you talking about?
Ethan, answer me.
You can't... The smell of bacon...
You can't get the smell of
bacon out in five minutes.
- There was bacon...
- What about bacon?
Right here. There was bacon here.
Why are you acting like this?
Shit. Sophie, Sophie.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Sophie, Sophie...
- What?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, just wait.
I'm spazzing out in there, I know,
but something fucking weird
like Twilight Zone
shit is going on here,
and I'm trying to get
a handle on it, okay?
Last night we had a nice dinner.
We had a blast together, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Then, we smoked some pot.
I fell asleep on the couch.
Next thing I know, you woke me up
claiming that we had
just had sex together.
Because we did!
Okay. I came here.
Nobody was here.
I fell asleep on this couch
and I woke up to you snuggling me.
What? What are you talking about?
No, I didn't.
That's crazy to me that you
would deny that, okay?
- I didn't.
- Exactly.
Crazy just like me denying
that I had slept with you.
You know what I'm saying?
We had two completely separate
experiences with each other
that neither of us remembers, and...
Hang on a second. I'm going to
go in there by myself, okay?
Why?
You just stay here
for like 30 seconds.
- Don't move.
- Ethan!
Hello?
Hey, Babe.
Can you hand me a towel?
You're in that shower.
I just handed you a towel.
Okay, you know what,
I'm not even mad any more.
Now you're just scaring me,
and I don't understand
why you're doing this.
Go, go see for yourself, Sophie.
Be careful.
Hey, where you been all morning?
Hello, Sophie.
I was just walking.
Oh, yeah.
It's really nice out, huh?
It's actually a little bright in here.
Do you mind if I close these?
Mmm-mmm.
The morning sun here is insane.
Give me a hug.
Sorry. I'm a little sweaty.
That's okay.
Come on.
Sophie.
Soph?
Fuck this.
You're kidding me!
What the fuck?
Sophie?
Oh my God! Hey, are you okay?
You're in there. It's you.
You're exercising.
What is happening?
I don't know.
This is so crazy.
Did that really happen?
I mean, did that, was that...
I just don't... I don't understand.
Is it another dimension, like
when you go through the door,
is it another plane
of existence or...
I don't know.
I've no clue.
I think we need to just say
some weird shit happened.
We compartmentalize it.
There was a cosmic
aberration of some sort...
- Yeah, yeah. Move on.
- And we go home.
We don't talk about this again,
and we just stop thinking about it.
Okay.
- Yeah. We could move on.
- Done.
Oh my God, I can't stop
thinking about it.
Can you?
We're just going to have to just...
I guess time, you know...
I'm not going to be able to stop
thinking about this, Ethan.
Well, what else can we do?
I mean what are we, what are
we going to do, you know?
Well, I mean, there's the...
There's the crazy thing
to do which is...
What?
Which is to, you know,
explore it further.
Explore it further?
I know you only had
a little bit of it...
Yeah. I was there for
like three seconds.
I know. And I, but I
had a whole evening...
In that house, and I have to say,
I know I sound like a
crazy person right now,
but I have to say it
was kind of magical.
- Well...
- It was...
But don't go overboard
with the whole magic
of what happened there
because I know what
you did in there, okay?
All right. That's not
what I'm talking about.
I'm not talking about
that kind of magic.
There was a rush.
It was exciting. I felt happy.
And it wasn't just that.
It wasn't just the time
in the guest house.
We had a great time
in the main house.
Yes, we did. We had a good time.
It wasn't just the weed.
I mean we were connecting,
we were talking,
we were happy, we were... Happy.
Yes.
We also had a fantastic time when
we did ecstasy at Lalapalooza,
but we're not going to do that every
day of our lives because you die...
- Right.
- Okay?
There's a question
of our safety here.
Yeah. But I didn't feel
like it was dangerous.
I didn't feel... I felt safe.
I didn't feel dangerous, either.
I felt like I was with you.
This is something that we've
been talking about in therapy...
Exploring new options,
creating a new relationship...
Not going back to the past
and re-creating old
things that happened
but starting with new things.
Yeah. Point taken.
I know that this is...
I didn't imagine this sort of...
- ...extreme.
- ...new thing.
Absolutely, but...
I imagined like horseback riding
with a little satchel
of wine, you know?
Not exploring other dimensions
in some weird version of
Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?
What if this is something
that I want to do?
You want to go back?
I want to help our relationship.
So... A little weird to say this,
but I'm struggling a
little bit with the fact
that you slept with the
other me last night.
Yeah, but I thought it was you.
I know. I'm not mad or blaming you.
I just like...
I'd be lying if I, you know,
didn't say I was a
little jealous, I guess.
All right. I understand,
but obviously I would never
knowingly cheat on you.
So it seems like it only works
if we go in one at a time.
Correct.
So I guess we'll just figure out
who wants to go in there first.
I'll be out in a minute, sweetheart.
Okay, I'm here.
That's good.
Hey, is that bacon okay?
It's been sitting out for awhile.
It's good.
Good.
Where have you been all morning?
Hanging out, you know.
Cool.
I missed you.
You missed me?
Of course.
Come sit with me.
Okay.
So...
Isn't it crazy to think that
we're actually married?
I guess so.
We are husband and wife.
- I know.
- Yeah.
I love it.
How long have you been
here, by the way?
Since we came yesterday, silly.
No, I mean, in the guest house.
Since we slept here last night.
Uh-oh. Someone's in detective mode.
Sorry. I didn't mean to be.
That's okay. I don't mind.
Have you explored the
grounds very much?
I think I have a pretty
good sense of it.
It's so pretty here, isn't it?
It is. Would you like to
go on a walk with me?
Not really right now, but you're
welcome to go on a walk.
It's your vacation, too.
Okay.
I'll see you in a little bit, Sophie.
Okay, Ethan.
Whoa!
- Fascinating.
- Tell me.
Okay. That being in there is
100% convinced that she is you.
- She is?
- Yeah.
I threw out some soft challenges.
She is unflappable.
I think when you go in there...
God, it's crazy.
Yeah, you throw out some
like very specific examples
from our past and see how he reacts.
Oh, no, no, sweetie.
I don't think we're
supposed to challenge them.
What if they disappear
or something, you know?
What if they freak out?
I'm just saying what's the harm
in letting them think
that they're us?
Yeah, I mean, I... All right.
There's no harm in it.
I just thought part
of the fun of this
was like the investigation
and trying to...
I know. Of course you thought
the fun was in the investigation.
Wait, hold on.
It's like at the magic show in Vegas
when you told me how the magician
did every single trick
and you ruined the entire show
for me and everyone around us.
Okay. You remember we
talked about the magic show
was three years ago and
we're moving past that?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Let's go inside.
We'll make up some
ground rules together.
That way neither of us
feels like, you know,
there's any kind of...
Confusion.
- Or just being on the same page.
- Okay.
While we are in the guest house
with the weird people,
no intimacy, no sex.
Yes. Absolutely agreed.
- No sex.
- Good.
What else?
Well, I would say that
would lead me to,
you know, no spying and there
has to be trust involved,
and we'll be honest with each
other about what happens
in the guest house and...
Right. It's like a...
It's like a therapy
exercise in trust almost.
- It's a trust exercise.
- Okay, great.
- That's why we're here.
- Good.
Um...
Let's see.
I guess if there's anything else...
Actually this is kind
of really important
now that I think about it.
We can have fun with this,
but if at any point either of us
becomes uncomfortable
and wants to stop,
we just cut it off, pack our bags...
Absolutely.
Absolutely. Agreed.
That's a good one,
that's a really good one.
Yeah.
Anything else?
I think that's it.
Then we are done. Those are good.
So since we're just kind of
like dipping our toes in here,
I think maybe we shouldn't
spend too much time in there
the first go-around.
Okay. How does 15 minutes sound?
Yeah, I think that's good.
Okay, but don't, you know,
stand outside waiting for me.
Wait, what?
Well, you know, I think it's
going to make me nervous
if I think you're waiting
right outside the door.
Yeah, okay. That's fair.
Oh, you mean, like right now?
- Yeah. Yeah, okay.
- Yes, sorry.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- Okay.
Enjoy yourself, but be safe.
Hey.
It's nice.
You could be honest.
I handle the criticism.
No, it's...
Okay.
I think I look a little severe.
Is that how you see me?
No.
I'm just not a very good painter.
I was trying to emulate Degas
who lights up his portrait faces
with all these wonderful colors.
Degas?
Unfortunately, it looks like
your face was lit on fire...
Which was not my intention.
I apologize.
But it yielded a
wonderful title, though.
- Uh-huh.
- I'm thinking of calling it
"Sophie My Love, the Burn Victim."
Or the ultimate tittle "Sophie
My Love, the Full-On Bitch"
because I look awfully bitchy.
- Well...
- Sorry.
Well, in all fairness,
sometimes you're a bitch.
Excuse me?
Yeah, but it's cool
because I'm an asshole
sometimes, you know?
Right.
We can say that, right?
No, I think it's good.
- Scoot over.
- Thanks.
Okay.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- To a perfect weekend together.
Hmm.
That's very nice.
Where you going?
Nowhere but here.
Why are you nervous?
I'm not nervous.
Why do you think I'm nervous?
Give me your hand.
Hmm?
What? Don't you trust me?
What the fuck?
You were spying on me.
Well, yeah. You were like
over 20 minutes in there.
Over 20... We didn't agree it
would be exactly 15 minutes,
- five minutes over?
- Yeah, but you know,
we didn't agree on like
intimate massages either.
Wait, wait. Intimate,
intimate massages?
- Are you serious?
- You were into it.
I was not into...
I was rocking your body in there.
All right. All right.
I'm sorry. I can see how that
might have made you uncomfortable,
and I apologize.
- It's a little confusing, Sorry.
- All right. It won't happen again.
- Okay.
- Understood.
- How was it in general though?
- Oh my God, it's so weird.
- It's so strange.
- It's really odd.
I mean, you were just...
You were wonderful.
You were funny and charming,
and you just kept telling
me all these great things
we should do on the property and...
Does he feel like me to you?
He is you... He's just a little...
A little what?
It's... How to describe it...
You know,
it's like you're funny, you know.
You have a great sense of humor
and everyone likes you and...
Thanks.
And that's who you are... In there,
but it's like a memory of it.
It's like I'm being reminded
of it or something,
but it's happening
right in front of me.
- Hmm.
- Does that make any sense?
You're not saying
that like it's like...
The better version when
you're in there, right?
- No, no, no, no, no.
- You're just...
Not at all. That's the crazy thing.
It is you in there, you know?
What about the physicality...
Do you notice any differences?
No. No, not really.
Yeah.
You know what, the hair.
There's something about the hair.
The hair?
Mmm-hmm. It's a little different.
It's like it's a little messier,
it's kind of beachy.
- Did you say beachy?
- Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
Come here. Let me see.
It's like, like kind of... No.
Well, well, it's like really...
I don't know. I'm not doing
it right or something.
- I don't know.
- Yeah.
Don't worry about it.
Cool.
Oh, and you know what,
you don't wear glasses.
You don't wear glasses in there
and you seem totally fine with it.
Well.
In the guest house, I'm a
surfer with perfect vision.
We'll work on this.
It's not quite... No, it's good.
We're getting there.
You've tried contacts, right?
Hey, Soph?
Hmm?
I'd like to take my session at the
guest house now if that's cool.
What time is it?
It's late, but I just can't sleep.
Oh, okay, sweetie.
Okay. I love you.
I love you.
What are you talking about? There
are like six versions of the same doll.
They're completely
unique in every way.
There are six different ladies here.
- I don't see it.
- Okay.
This one is the beautiful model
who is always talking about
how she was such a
nerd in high school,
and then oh, this one...
It definitely has two
tramp stamps underneath
that dress, for sure.
And then you've got...
This one is the coolest
girl in the world,
and she'd make the
most wonderful wife,
but no one's going to be able
to look past her chubby thighs.
Which one of these is your favorite?
Which one do you like the most?
Okay.
Ready for this?
Ooh, I dropped it.
How is that not the cutest
thing you've ever seen?
- It really is cute.
- It's so tiny.
It's adorable.
Hey.
Hi.
What you doing?
Nothing. What are you doing?
Nothing.
Have you...
Have I what?
Nothing.
Never mind.
So, what's on the agenda for today?
I was going to maybe
go explore some more
and you know, just... If that's okay.
- Of course.
- What about you?
I don't know. I thought I'd
maybe just hang out here, read.
Sounds nice. Maybe I'll
come by in a little bit
and we can spend some time.
Whatever you want.
Great.
Oh, I found your phone.
- Thanks.
- Mmm-hmm.
Come on.
Hello.
I'm up here.
Watch your head, okay?
Very cute up here.
It's a little small.
What are you doing up here?
I'm feeling very big.
I feel enormous.
Um, I'm glad you're here
because there is something
I want to talk to you about.
And it's a bit of an
elephant in the room,
and I think it's time we discuss it.
- All right.
- Okay.
- This...
- Oh, that.
...is happening.
- Oh, Well.
- Ladies first.
In that case.
- Who the fuck starts with O?
- I know.
- Who the hell do you think you are?
- It's crazy.
Goddamn anarchist.
All right. I'll just do
an X in the middle.
That's a great move.
I think I see where this is headed.
I'm not quite sure yet.
Yeah, I'm going to block you there.
- Where do you think I should go?
- How's it going to end?
What do you think I should do?
- Who's going to win?
- Oh, the suspense!
Oh, yes, and there it is.
What's your next game?
My next game is something
that is appropriate
for people over the age of six.
I think that's a thing.
Why don't you kiss me any more?
Um, I've enjoyed just hanging
out and reconnecting and...
I have, too.
I know, but I love kissing
you and I miss it.
Is there something I'm doing
that's bothering you or...
Oh my God, no, not at all.
Because I feel like we're
having a good time?
- We're having a great time.
- Yeah.
- Give me this.
- You're taking my chalk.
That's my... That's my chalk.
I know it's your chalk.
Hey.
All right. This is weird,
but I think some of
my shirts are missing.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Are you sure they're not
just hanging in the closet
and you didn't pack them
like you usually do?
No, no. Stuff that I
packed is not here.
- Well, that's weird.
- Yeah. That's weird.
What's so funny?
Oh, nothing, I guess.
Just a funny text.
Oh yeah? Who's texting you?
Um...
Wait, he's texting you?
Babe, it's nothing.
It's just a text, okay?
I'm not upset.
I just think it's weird.
They have cellphones?
What plan do they even have?
- Thanks.
- Mmm-hmm.
So nice outside today.
Can I ask you a question?
Of course.
Why did you do it?
Why did you cheat on me?
I'm sorry. That's probably...
- That's okay.
- Not something you want to...
No, that's okay.
I have been thinking about
that a bit this weekend,
and
I have no excuse.
Of course I was insecure
and of course we were
drifting apart at the time
and instead of trying to communicate
I lashed out and I made a
terrible decision, and
that's...
Right.
No, let me finish.
That's no excuse.
You had every right to abandon me,
but you didn't, and you
stuck in there with me
and you went to see that
stupid therapist that we see,
even though we didn't want to,
and you kept going,
and you kept trying,
and you met me halfway
and I was defensive and
I'm sorry about that.
And I want to say thank you
for making those efforts for us,
and I promise you I'm
going to do my best
to meet you there, okay?
I promise.
Hello.
Hey.
I didn't hear you
get up this morning.
I just came down to see if
there was anything on TV.
What, do you think I'm lying to you?
No.
No, I was... Just seemed to...
Is there anything you
want to talk about?
No.
There anything you
want to talk about?
Look, this weekend is super weird...
- That's okay, right?
- Yeah.
I mean, you know,
I think it can be confusing,
but I just...
You know it's not real, right?
I mean, I'm not that guy
out there doing sit-ups...
And I could never
be really interested
in some other version of you,
knowing that my real
Sophie is here...
- Right.
- And I just...
I want to make sure you still agree.
Yeah.
Of course.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Okay. We good?
- Yeah, we're good.
- Of course we're good.
- All right.
Thanks a lot for calling me at two in
the morning. I really appreciate it.
Like I don't have a job
to wake up for tomorrow.
Maybe next time you can't
remember where you live,
you should ask your wife.
I'm not sure what you were doing
at two in the morning anyway, but...
Hey, Bunny. It's mama.
I was just thinking about
our conversation yesterday.
I don't know.
You just didn't sound
like your usual self,
so I just wanted to
be sure you're okay...
Hey, man. The street you
grew up on was Berkman.
Hope that clears things up.
Talk to you soon.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Um...
So something really
weird just happened.
I got a bunch of voice mails
from my mom and Doug and Dave
saying I had called them
asking really weird questions,
but I didn't call them.
- That is weird.
- Yeah.
Do you think you pocket dialed them?
I don't think the pocket
dial makes as much sense
because I was talking
and asking questions.
- I would have...
- So what do you think it was?
Oh, you think that he called them.
Yeah, and to me that's
a logical conclusion.
He looks like me. He sounds like me.
He's got a cellphone.
I think he might be
impersonating me or something.
Right. I just don't think
that he would do that.
Do you think you know him that well?
Well, I mean I know him a
little better than you do.
You've never met him.
But I mean it's weird.
I can totally ask him if you want.
No, that's okay.
- It's just...
- Okay.
- It's just a weird thing.
It is weird.
I'm going to go to the store.
Do you want me to get you anything?
Uh, no. I'm good.
- Thanks.
- Well, you can come if you want.
Do you mind if I just hang out here?
- Of course not.
- Okay.
Okay.
Hey, babe.
Uh, sorry.
Great.
Hey.
Is this a bad time?
No, no.
I was, doing some sit-ups.
I need to talk to you.
What do you want to talk about?
What happened the
last time I was here.
Yeah, that was obviously
important. Yeah.
Ethan, you're so good at articulating
exactly what it is that I'm feeling
in a way that I can't even do,
and it's everything that
I've been wanting to hear,
but now I don't know what to do.
I can't get it out of my head.
Well, I'm glad I said what you
wanted to hear, you know.
Is there anything else you
wanted to see me about?
I've missed this.
Me too.
Hi.
Where are the groceries?
What?
What about the store? What happened?
- The store was closed.
- Oh.
Hey, how about I make
us a couple of mimosas?
I'm not really in the mood for
a mimosa right now, Sophie.
Aw, come on. It'll be fun.
We'll have a drink. We'll relax.
Start this day off right.
Then we can talk about
whatever is bothering you.
You know, that's really good advice.
And I should probably listen to it...
But you're not a real person.
You know you're not real.
Who the hell are you?
What the hell are you?
Are you a fucking robot?
Are you a... Like a spirit?
Because I've got to
say it's bad enough
that I'm losing my wife
to a mirror image of me
who happens to be like 20% cooler
and 20% more emotionally
evolved than me.
Now I have to sit and
look at a mirror image
of exactly who I'm losing.
So, no...
I'm having a hard time
enjoying this weekend
because this is the
weekend I lose my wife.
So, pardon me if I don't
want a fucking mimosa, okay?
It wasn't just this weekend.
How do you know?
Because as your wife,
I know these things.
Shit!
Uh-oh. I can't stop it.
I can't stop it.
Look what you did. Look what you did.
What? Souvenir?
Here comes the firehose.
I'm going to spray you down.
Are you on fire?
Why are you twirling a fire hose?
Where did you get this sweater?
What?
Where'd you get this?
I don't know. I've always had it.
- Really?
- Yeah, you just...
You don't notice my clothes, I guess.
Do you remember when you got it?
Do you want to talk about clothes?
Or would you rather have the
full Chippendales experience?
What's the full experience?
Well...
I don't think I have
enough cash on me.
You just put that away.
You don't worry about that.
Sophie?
Sophie, open the door.
Come on. It's me.
I know you're in there
with him, Sophie.
Come on. Open up!
Will you just give me...
Hold on one second.
Sophie, come on. Let me in.
Sophie.
I'm just going to keep knocking.
I'm going to keep knocking.
I know what you're doing in there.
Sophie, let me in.
Come on, Sophie. Open up.
- Where is he?
- Ethan, what are you doing?
- Where are you?
- Ethan, come on.
Ethan, stop!
I'll beat his ass. Where are you?
Where are you?
Goddamn it!
Good. He's gone.
What the hell is going on in here?
Where did he go? Look what you did!
What I did? Are you insane?
Yes, what you did.
What if he never comes back?
Sophie, come on.
Sophie, get back here.
Sophie.
He is not real, okay?
Sophie, how can you accept something
that you know is a blatant lie?
You keep saying it's
not real, it's not real,
but I'm happy.
I'm feeling that. How is that fake?
Do you hear how insane you sound?
You're not admitting that this
is just the least bit weird?
It's not weird for me any more.
So what's the endgame? Huh?
How do you see this playing out?
Are you going to write letters,
come back and visit after
we leave this weekend?
I'm not leaving.
What do you mean, you're not leaving?
Sophie, what the hell
do you mean you're...
This is... Okay, all right.
Sophie, come on.
Let's just take a breath here, okay?
I know you're feeling
something that is magical
and clearly exciting to you,
but if you think about it logically,
literally for one second...
Is this weird for you now?
Does anybody remember any
of those fun icebreaker games
that kids do at summer camp...
Spin the bottle or seven minutes
in heaven or something...
Anyhow, we just thought it was time
that the four of us sit down
and get to know each
other a little bit.
You want to get to know each other?
Hi, Sophie.
Hi.
Okay. Um...
Let's get to know each other.
Why don't you tell us the truth
of what's really going on?
The truth?
Yeah, that you basically have
been pretending to be me,
acting like I don't exist
even though you knew I
was here the whole time.
Ethan, I wasn't
pretending to be anyone.
I was just being myself.
You knew about me, right?
Did he mention me
to you at any point?
Not until this morning.
All right. Maybe all of us
were doing a little
pretending this weekend.
It's not a big deal.
I really like your shoes.
Oh, thank you.
I really like your hair
pinned back like that.
It's super cute.
I'm sorry. I still am not
buying that you are real.
Ethan, I'm sitting here,
you're looking at me sitting here.
I'm real.
You're sitting across from me, right?
I'm looking at you sitting there,
so by your logic maybe
you're not real.
That doesn't make any sense.
I'm starving.
Ethan, why don't you
clean yourself up
and we'll all have a little dinner.
There.
So, anybody interested in
going on a hike tomorrow?
I've been wanting to do that
ever since we got here.
I would love that.
All right.
Tonight though,
I'm thinking game night.
All right.
Okay, maybe you're real,
but can we admit
this isn't some normal dinner party?
Ethan, you're looking
a little uncomfortable.
Can I help you with something?
Okay, so according to you,
this is just some average weekend.
We all go home tomorrow,
and you don't need any further
explanation than that?
Sometimes these things just happen.
Yeah, that's right. They do.
I don't buy it.
All right.
One time I read this article
on cosmic occurrences.
I wish I still had it...
You would love it.
And it basically says
that aberrations happen.
You can drive yourself nuts
trying to derive meaning
from things that have no
meaning to begin with.
That's so interesting.
It is, isn't it?
It's not that interesting.
Let me think of an
little example for you,
something right up your alley.
Um...
Let's say you buy a gorilla.
Excuse me?
Let's say you buy a gorilla, Ethan.
You can't buy a gorilla.
I know that, it was for the story.
But fine, let's say you
buy an aardvark, okay?
You take that aardvark,
you put him in a dark room.
A minute later you flip that
switch, the lights come on.
Now we all know how
electricity works,
but for him it's a miracle.
Magic happened...
That previously dark
room is now illuminated
with possibilities he's
never seen before...
And what does he do?
Does he ruin it by
questioning how or why?
No. He enjoys it.
Huh.
Well, I'm not an aardvark.
And I am not a gorilla.
Don't worry about it. I got it.
Hmm.
There's a little bit left.
Should we finish it?
This is quite the situation.
You can say that again.
Has Ethan... I mean your Ethan...
Have you guys talked about anything
or has he said anything
to you at all?
Like What?
Well, Ethan... My Ethan
and I, we've discussed it.
Like he knew when I was
going to go in the house
and I knew when he
was going to and...
You shared your experiences.
Yeah, for the most part.
And you want to know if we
shared our experiences also.
Guess I'm just curious.
I can see that.
You know what I'm curious about?
Are you more concerned
with the experiences
that me and your Ethan shared
or are you more concerned
with what I know
about the experiences that
you and my Ethan shared?
Seems to me you care a lot more
about one of those
scenarios than the other.
Are you going to give that back?
I say for the sake of
the super fun evening
we're about to have,
let's keep it simple
and keep our cheery dispositions
and I'll keep
complimenting your shoes.
And you can keep pretending
that you like the way
I pin my hair back,
and we'll just have a good
time and see what happens.
On second thought, do you mind
taking care of those dishes?
You still haven't told
me where you're from.
Are we still doing this?
Are we going to compare
lists of women, too?
You know, I'm starting
to piece this all together
and see it for what it is.
You're trying to sabotage
my relationship.
Ethan, from what I understand
about your relationships,
you should be well versed
in the art of self-sabotage.
The purpose of tonight
is not to engage
in some warped
competition between us,
at least not on my end.
It wouldn't really be fair.
Yeah? Why is that?
Haven't you figured it out yet?
It's kings.
It's kings or it's aces
is what's going on.
There's something going on.
Why don't you worry
about your own cards.
I don't even know why
we're continuing right now.
I basically know every
card you're holding.
Are you saying that I have a tell?
You have big tells.
You want to know what your tell is?
I want to know what you think it is.
You have a very consistent
albeit very cute
Sophie shoulder shrug that
looks a little bit like this.
Oh! Do you do the shrug?
Uh, excuse me. Don't talk to her.
She's dead. She folded.
It's just you and me now.
You did the shoulder shrug.
You obviously have a good hand.
It's like a high pair or
maybe even three of a kind.
Fucking raise this shit, man.
You only live once.
Okay. I'll raise.
Now I know you have the confidence.
I have a shit hand.
I'm folding. Look at that.
Jesus, are you kidding me?
- What?
- You're right.
- Pair of aces.
- Ooh!
Nailed it, nailed it.
I knew you had the aces.
Dude, by the way, you're getting
very good at this game...
Almost too good.
I'm beginning to think this
is like one long Sophie con.
He clearly just let you win.
Yes, Ethan. Obviously he let me win.
Come on, guys.
This is supposed to just
be a friendly game.
You're not being very
fun to play with.
The reason he's not being fun
is because he's not even playing.
Ethan, if you want to win the game,
you've got to play some hands, okay?
That's just how it works.
All right. Fine. I'll play.
Deal me in. You and me.
Come on.
You want to play one on...
Okay. All right. That's the spirit.
Come on, buddy.
Let's get in the game.
Let's go.
Mmm-hmm.
All right.
How many cards do you want?
I'm fine with what I have.
Thank you very much.
Sticking with what you have.
All right. I'll stick
with what I have, too.
What's your move?
I'm all in.
Oh!
All in, bold move!
But you've got to be impulsive
sometimes. I really like it.
All right, so you're all in,
and now I've got to figure
out what is your tell.
You've got that restless
leg thing going on
but I think it's just nerves.
You've been chewing on
the lower lip a little bit,
but I get ulcers in there, too,
so maybe that's just what that is.
So weird lip...
Oh!
Oh, shit! Of course. There it is.
The guy who has nothing
and he knows it.
Sorry, buddy, but I've got
to call you on this one.
What you got?
Whatever.
You have nothing and I
win with an ace high.
Sorry about that, man.
It's fun playing with you, but you've
got to work on your bluffing skills.
You win.
You're an amazing liar.
Congratulations on being a shithead.
- Whoa!
- Ethan, Jesus. Calm down.
Hey, wait a minute, wait a minute.
I don't want to take
all the credit here.
You're a pretty decent
liar yourself, right?
What are you talking about?
Do you want to tell her or should I?
Is this necessary?
I think it's important that
Sophie knows what's going on.
We're all friends here, right?
Uh, would everybody just tell
me what we're talking about?
What happened?
It's nothing.
All right, look,
Ethan was a little suspicious that
something was going on between us,
so he decided to try and
figure it out for himself.
It was actually kind
of a brilliant move.
He didn't go to the grocery store.
He ended up sneaking
into the guest house,
and in a strange twist of events,
he pretended to be me,
so you actually slept
with Ethan instead of me.
I can't fucking pretend
to be you... I am me.
You... What the fuck
are you talking about?
Just shut up! Sophie, please.
That was you yesterday?
Sweetheart...
Basically, first he betrayed
you by sleeping with someone else
and then he kind of betrayed
you by sleeping with you.
Sorry, guys. I didn't want
to make like a thing here.
If you guys need some
space or something.
If you want to like take the
guest house, you'd be welcome.
I'm not going anywhere.
No, I want you to leave.
...if not, leave a detailed message
and I will return your call.
Hey. It's Ethan.
Um, I'm really just
calling to thank you
for your wonderful
recommendation this weekend.
Maybe next session you can send
us to a fucking holocaust museum.
Thank you very much.
All right, so we have to hit the
keys at the exact same time.
This is a strange exercise.
On three, okay?
One...
- All right.
- Two.
Three.
You met in Scottsdale, Arizona.
We met in Scottsdale, Arizona.
Madison, you have two sisters, right?
Yes, two sisters.
I'm the middle child,
and my dad wasn't present.
Why are you here?
You were raised in a
predominantly female household
and you had serious...
Ethan and Sophie.
Holy shit!
All right. Try it again.
I am Ethan.
I am Sophie.
What the hell is this?
That's getting good.
You're almost ready.
I never took that picture.
No, no, no, no.
No!
What the...
Shit!
Somebody help!
Help!
Help! Sophie!
Sophie, can you hear me?
Sophie, I'm stuck.
Hey.
Sophie? Sophie, I'm in here.
Sophie, I'm in here.
Sophie! I'm stuck.
- What the...
- We don't have much time.
They think I'm out picking
fruit for breakfast.
What?
Okay. A lot happened
last night after you left.
Do you know that you're Sophie?
Are you pretending?
I don't know, what's happening?
I'm not your wife.
Okay. What the fuck's going on,
and who are you?
He fell in love with her.
He's not supposed to
fall in love with her.
She's supposed to fall
out of love with you.
That's how this works.
That's how we get out.
What the hell are you
talking about? I don't...
- That's how we become you.
- You become us?
Pitting you against each other is
the best way to break you down,
and then it's your turn to stay.
What the fu... What the fuck?
Oh, my God.
Did you try to get out last night?
- Yes.
- You couldn't.
No.
That's because the closer
we get to moving on,
the closer you get
to not being able to.
Do you remember when
you first got here?
I was stuck here.
You had to come see me. Now look.
Ethan.
Ethan, it's not going to work.
I have to be the one to let you out.
Well, what? I mean,
what am I supposed to do?
I don't want to be trapped here.
- What do you...
- You're not trapped yet.
I can get you out.
Listen, only two people
can leave today.
I don't understand.
Why would you help me
if you're trying to get
yourself out of here?
Because I love him.
And I'd rather be trapped here
than see him leave with her.
So you have real feelings
like love and jealousy,
like a real person?
I am real.
We should bring a couple
extra bottles of water.
This hike can be a little strenuous.
How long is the hike?
I was just thinking I should
probably check on Ethan.
- See if he's okay.
- It's only like an hour.
Plus, I think it's good if he cools
down in the guest house, you know.
Hey, we're getting ready to head out.
You want to get changed?
Well, all my clothes are
back at the guest house,
and I agree.
I think we should give
Ethan his space.
I have an extra pair of shoes.
We're probably the same size.
Well, that's top's
really cute on you.
Do you have anything like that?
I have another one.
Come on, girls. Let's go.
They're just right in there,
the bottom drawer,
and there are some extra shoes.
Great. Thanks so much.
Sure. Do you need anything else?
Um, well, my toothpaste and
toothbrush is over there.
Do you have anything?
Sure, I'll get you something.
Just give me one minute, please.
It's important.
Did you find some clothes for her?
Yep. She'll be down in a minute.
Good.
What? Do you understand how
insane you sound right now?
Yes, I understand, but this whole
fucking weekend has been crazy.
Think about it. Everything
they knew about us...
The missing clothes and the phone
calls to my mom and my friends.
This entire weekend has been
one planned trap, Sophie.
I'm glad we have a second alone,
because I wanted to talk to you.
You do, really?
I want to talk to you, too.
What do you want to say?
You go first.
I've been thinking
a lot about things.
I don't want to leave with Ethan.
I want to leave with you.
I want to leave with you, too.
I love you, Sophie.
You're not Sophie.
Where is she?
Sophie?
Come here.
Here, come in here, come in here.
Sophie?
Look, I don't have
a lot of time, okay?
Sophie.
And I'm not going to get this right,
but I don't want you to leave.
I don't want you to leave me, Sophie.
Look, I know he is handsome
and smart and eloquent,
and he makes cool
aardvark metaphors, okay?
Sophie! You know I love you.
And I'm difficult, and I'm stubborn
and I know that I've been defensive,
and I haven't been what you needed...
Sophie!
And I take a big part of the
responsibility for why this happened.
Okay? But listen to me,
I'm your husband,
and you're my wife...
And I am not letting you go.
Sophie, unlock the door.
We're a mess, and I
love that about us,
and I don't want to be perfect.
I want to be us. So please...
Sophie, he's lying.
Just give me a chance
before he comes in here.
I love you.
Sophie, what is he telling you?
Sophie, Sophie, it's me.
Come on. Sophie...
We're leaving. Okay.
Ethan, I need you to step
out of the way, please.
Excuse me.
Ethan.
- Excuse me.
- Ethan!
You son of a bitch.
Ethan, stop!
Stop it!
Ethan, stop it!
You guys, come on.
This is ridiculous.
Sophie.
All right.
That was a stupid fight.
Sophie, come on.
Sophie!
Fine.
I'm going to fuck all you guys.
What happens if he can't catch him?
I have no idea.
Ethan!
We've got to get out of here.
We've got to go.
Leave a detailed message
and I will return your call.
Hey, it's Ethan.
I know you're dodging my calls.
I also know you know what's going on,
so we're coming over there right now.
It was a full-on grand theft covers.
I need a visual.
Look at this. Come see.
You were basically a tootsie roll,
wrapped up, rolled
over onto your side,
and you abandoned me on
the other side of the bed
and I froze my titties off all night.
Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
That's what you did to me,
your husband.
- That's horrible.
- It really is.
- What kind of a wife is that?
- I don't know. You're awful.
You owe me big time.
Why didn't you just
take the covers back?
Because you looked really cute
and I didn't want to wake you up.
Right. No, that makes sense...
I must have been pretty cute.
That was... That was pretty good,
but you're going to have to
do a little more than that.
- More?
- I need something else.
- Something else?
- Mmm-hmm.
Uh, what would you say
if I made you breakfast?
I'm not going to say anything more.
I'm just going to try
to let this happen.
- Okay.
- No sudden movements.
Be very still.
- I'm not...
- Be very still.
I don't want to...
Nothing is happening.
Don't even make eye contact.
All right, so what's on the menu?
Well, I was thinking
maybe eggs and bacon.
I'll be right there.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/32g4g
Help other users to choose the best subtitles