- Previously on Berlin Station.
- [Keyboard clacking]
I just sent you a photo.
- Who is this?
- Daniel: You tell me.
Daniel: Your friend, Claudia...
her death was no suicide.
Shaw killed her.
I said I'm sorry.
I thought she would ruin everything.
Why'd you follow me?
Why did you speak with Ingrid Hollander?
Daniel: A mutual friend died.
Tragic accident.
I don't believe in accidents.
Neither do I.
Lovely to meet you, Esther Krug.
Valerie: I've learned from a former
asset that Iosava is soliciting funds
for a new refugee foundation
right here in Berlin.
We're working on a plan
to get one of our agents
to infiltrate that foundation.
Until we can prove Iosava is a threat,
she won't authorize an audio op.
Then let me do it.
Let my people do what
you've been unable to do.
We have a 24-hour audio/video
on Iosava's apartment,
Robert: We need Faisal to nail Iosava
and to tell us what his government
is going to do about Syria and ISIL.
Hector: If we don't do something,
his people are gonna nab him!
- They'll send you home and kill you.
- It's okay, Hector.
I'm not fighting this anymore.
Are you seriously suggesting
that I chance the exfil
- of a Saudi out of Germany?
- We owe him.
Meeting at a hotel was a bad idea.
But it was something I needed to do.
I need to be myself.
I just got word that Faisal's
on a plane to Riyadh.
Get the fuck out of my face.
Hector: Beneath one secret,
there's another and another and another.
One big fucking mess
of our own creation.
You need to be careful, Daniel.
- Of what?
- Everything.
[Gasps]
I got ya.
[David Bowie's "I'm Afraid
of Americans" plays]
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Johnny's in America,
low techs at the wheel ♪
♪ I'm afraid of Americans ♪
♪ I'm afraid of the world ♪
♪ I'm afraid I can't help it ♪
♪ I'm afraid I can't ♪
♪ I'm afraid of Americans ♪
♪ I'm afraid of the world ♪
♪ I'm afraid I can't help it ♪
♪ I'm afraid I can't ♪
♪ I'm afraid of Americans ♪
♪♪
[Woman speaking French]
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app
[Metal creaking]
♪♪
[Gasps]
[Breathing heavily]
Robert: Don't tell me to relax, Steven.
Christ Almighty, relax? Look at you.
I said I took care of it.
But how? What does that even mean?
Where there's a paper trail,
there's Thomas Shaw to light it
on fire and burn us alive.
That's a little melodramatic, Robert.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
You think? 'Cause I don't.
This isn't us going down like Gerald.
You know, this is us going to
jail for running paper agents
and bilking Uncle Sam, for fuck sakes.
And by the way,
if you're looking for
a proper place to jump,
this is not it.
I got dibs on the TV Tower
when the time comes.
I took the files out last week,
and I fixed them.
I fixed them.
All the remaining agents
are marked as deceased.
Nobody's gonna find anything.
I don't know.
I don't know, I don't know.
I feel a fucking ulcer coming on.
- I'm telling you, just watch.
- Jesus, God.
Maybe I should refrain from telling you.
Houjin Lin called me last night.
How did he get your number?
Oh, I have no idea.
Said he's antsy, wants to take a walk.
Walk?
- Literally or figuratively?
- Literally.
Well, then tell Hans to buy him
a fucking treadmill.
Jesus fucking Christ, can
anything go our way these days?
[Inhales deeply]
I mean, the one thing is
Lin's on all of us,
Germans included, so there's that.
Just please tell me we're...
we're not going down next.
I don't...
You want a psychic?
They're chockablock in Kreuzberg.
♪♪
[Cup clatters]
So, did you get a chance
to look into that photograph I gave you?
Whoever that freak is,
he's of no interest to us.
There's no record of him?
Or maybe you just don't like to share?
What are you implying?
I'd hate to think you were
unwilling to cooperate
with your new American friend.
Oh. [Chuckles]
Let me be clear, Mr. Miller.
You and I, we're not friends.
Really? After the warm welcome
you've given me,
I was so convinced.
You know, the only thing I dislike
more than predictable wit
are invasions of my private time
like this.
I urge you not to make
the same mistake again.
Or what, Ms. Krug?
Best of luck finding a ghost.
[Dog barking in distance]
♪♪
- [Beeping]
- Clear... let them through.
- Clear.
- [Telephone beeps]
Yeah?
What?
How many?
Fuck.
[Elevator dings]
So, just play it unfazed.
Don't let them have the pleasure
of your panic.
- Fuck them.
- [Buzzer]
Greetings, Berlin.
I bring glad tidings from headquarters.
Hey, man. How'd the pep talk go?
You are Robert Kirsch,
Deputy Chief. Am I correct?
Very good. What's the occasion, fellas?
Uh, where is the Chief?
I'm right here.
- Excuse me.
- [Telephone rings]
Steven Frost.
Chris Bolton... Office of Security.
I'm here to get ahead of
any further station compromises.
So, you know the drill...
we'll need access to every file, folder,
and Post-it note in this facility.
This is the way you greet
colleagues then?
Well, it is today.
So, uh, just keep your troops
out of our way, we'll be fine.
Hm, a little friendly warning
would have gone a long way.
A long way towards what?
Time to cover your ass?
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
have at it.
People, please, please make way...
[Exhales]
Okay, now am I exaggerating?
If it isn't Shaw up our ass,
it's fucking headquarters.
Would you stop being such
a Goddamn head case, Robert?
- What do you want me to do?
- [Knock at door]
Well, come right in.
Excuse me.
Can I ask you a question?
What?
What the fuck is that?
Huh?
You're in my station,
and now you tap my phone.
Well, clearly we had more than
enough reason to be concerned.
Houjin Lin, the Chinese
most wanted defector,
AKA one of the biggest
liabilities we have out there,
is e-mailing you fucking photos?
Are you kidding me?
He has cabin fever.
No, he has an Internet account
that has your personal address
in his contacts.
Do you mind explaining to me
how the hell that got there?
I was planning to ask him that
question myself.
You know, the guy could probably
get fucking Wi-Fi on his chopsticks.
Let's not waste our time
marveling at Chinese ingenuity.
We'll take care of it, okay?
I hope to hell that you do.
♪♪
What?
Better Houjin Lin than our dirty secret.
Just sayin'.
[Door closes]
♪♪
[Machinery whirring]
What's this about, Bora?
Nothing.
Nothing?
I asked if you'd met with him.
Why didn't you bring this
to my attention?
I've been busy.
Aleksandre Iosava invited me
tomorrow for tea,
and I declined.
I said I had a business trip.
You came to us after
Mohammed Merah shot up
a Jewish day school.
You wanted to help
rid Islam of its bad name.
And yet, here you are
standing in front of me
lying about meeting with Iosava.
And I refused his invitation.
I am not going to the home of
even a reformed terrorist.
Yes, you are.
You will accept his invitation
and say that your trip was canceled.
You will go to his home
and bring me back
a full, detailed report.
♪♪
Jemma Moore.
- Ma'am.
- What is this?
Director Bennett will be
contacting you shortly.
All property of the Central
Intelligence Agency
must be turned over immediately.
Tell Daddy I'll call back.
[Bag unzips]
[Beep, ringing]
[Cellphone vibrates]
Riverrun past Eve and Adams.
Man: Who is this?
♪♪
[Whirring]
[Glass rattling]
Reporter: We have breaking news
on the Thomas Shaw leaks.
Reporting with the latest
information is Sally Bundock.
Sally: The newest CIA casualty being
Deputy Director Jemma Moore
here in Prague
when a second wave of revelations
pertaining to Thomas Shaw leaks broke,
exposing questionable ethics
at the highest levels of the agency.
Accused of endorsing torture
and extraordinary rendition
at the notorious ghost prisons
and black sites
that have come to
symbolize the CIA for many,
Moore's expected resignation
by day's end...
Can you call the Grand Hyatt Prague?
Find out what room Jemma Moore's in.
Sure. Why?
Because I asked.
- Good Christ, what is going on?
- No idea.
Chris: Ladies and gentlemen,
there you go.
That is why we are here.
Understand... Thomas Shaw
will stop at nothing
to rape this institution dry
from the newest recruit
to the President.
You mean "bleed it dry."
Excuse me, what's your name?
Hector DeJean.
No, Hector DeJean, I mean rape it dry.
Where's your desk?
Stuck up your ass
by the looks of it, brother.
Okay, okay, okay.
If you can't
keep your fucking mouth shut
today of all days,
then get the fuck out, okay?
[Indistinct conversation]
Sandra. Sandra.
Um...
When... when you brought the files
to the safe house the other day,
did you sign them out in the log?
So, you really did need them.
It wasn't just an excuse to see me?
[Sighs]
Is there a good answer to that question?
Yes, I signed them out.
That would be agency protocol.
But it was just your name
in the log, not mine.
Is this going where I think it's going?
Look, I... I don't want you to
feel compromised.
Good. Neither do I.
If what you're asking
is that I risk my job
so you could keep yours...
No. Sandra, just...
Just forget I said anything, okay?
♪♪
[Train rumbling]
Uh, Steven Frost
and Valerie Edwards fuer Hans Richter.
- Danke.
- [Beeping]
Steven, I thought you might
bring your new deputy,
Daniel Miller.
No, it's only his second week.
Still breaking him in.
Where's your handkerchief, Steven?
No tears for Jemma Moore?
Oh, no, don't gloat, Hans.
You might miss her when
they find a new replacement.
- [Chuckles]
- I'm sure of it.
How can we help you
on such short notice?
Oh, take your pick.
Houjin Lin, Aleksandre Iosava.
Double pain in my ass, one on each side.
Yeah, Lin is, uh... he's feeling
and he's acting cooped up,
and I think if he continues to
play the restless prisoner,
we may consider a conjugal visit.
A prostitute?
You would have to pay her a million Euro
to have sex with Houjin Lin.
[Chuckles]
We'll work on it.
What about Aleksandre Iosava?
One of our assets is meeting him.
We have full coverage from an LP van,
but we would very much like for
this to be a joint venture.
But I'm not even aware that I
let you bug the Iosava home,
- am I?
- [Sighs] Hans.
It's your country.
I don't have the means to arrest him
if and when the time comes.
Come on, do you think that
a German court will begrudge you
a warrantless wiretap urgently needed
- to stop a possible terrorist attack?
- What attack would that be?
Would you rather get ahead of it
or find out after it happens?
Business as usual, Steven,
even with Thomas Shaw
out there to expose it?
I'm sorry.
When I draw a line, I don't redraw it.
I believe you're done here.
[Door opens]
Valerie.
Week two in Berlin for Daniel Miller...
that's not what my team says.
I'd look into that if I were you.
Hello. Uh, yeah,
room service for 306, please.
Uh, wait a second.
I'll call you right back.
- Hey.
So, did you escape from the
ticker tape parade upstairs?
Breath of fresh air.
Where you headed?
Got a meet.
Someone's having a nic fit.
Maybe you should treat it,
not manage it.
- Here.
- Mnh-mnh.
Oh, sweet Jesus, don't look.
[Both giggling]
Hey.
- How are you?
- [Chuckles]
Hi.
What's so funny?
I... I think they're laughing at
you, not with you.
Oh, yeah?
Hey.
Looking for a good time, baby doll?
I hear corn-fed diplomats
are where it's at.
Easy, he's not your type.
Clare, Daniel. Daniel, Clare.
The infamous Clare. Hi.
Hey.
- You ready?
- Yep.
Ciao.
[Tires skid]
Sorry about that.
Uh, room service for 306, please.
Tomorrow evening at 1800 hours...
Hey, don't talk to me
like a Goddamn grunt.
I'm still your Deputy Director.
We will return to escort you
to the airport.
Room service.
Steak sandwich for Adams.
Wrong room.
No Adams here.
I'm sorry.
[Moaning]
[Crow caws]
Don't stop.
Don't stop, keep going.
Keep going, keep going.
Don't stop.
[Exhales]
Oh, fuck.
I'm sorry. It's been a fucked-up week.
[Sighs]
Next time, you owe me.
Let's eat.
Worst thing about the food in Saudi...
you can't wash it down
with alcohol to kill the taste.
[Engine starts]
Mmm.
It's like just I had sex or something.
- Come on.
- [Laughs]
I'm kidding.
- Have some pork and beer with me.
- I'm good, I'm good.
So, uh, were you able to
look into that thing for me?
I did.
And?
And... it's not good.
I can take it, Clare.
[Groans]
Saudis are trying Faisal for sodomy.
Okay.
So, uh, they appoint a judge yet?
Yeah.
They call him "al-Jazzar."
That's Arabic for "butcher."
[Scoffs]
Fuck.
I'm sorry, Hector.
It's okay.
See you later.
Steven.
You wanted to see me.
- [Door closes]
- Yeah.
Yeah, I just wondered
how you were settling in.
Sometimes it takes longer than a week.
I'll get there soon enough.
[Keyboard clacking]
♪♪
Haven't seen much reporting from you.
Valerie's handling Swingset.
My other agents are on ice
since Gerald was outed.
Oh, well, let me see
what I can do for you,
get you in the swing of things.
Sounds good.
I was wanting to follow up
with Joker anyway.
Uh, that's the one in network security.
Mm-hmm.
What about?
Just get to know her.
I think she took the loss of
Gerald pretty hard.
Plus, an agent in the tech field...
can't let that gather moss these days.
- I'll get to it.
- Yeah.
[Telephone beeps]
[Clears throat] Sandra?
Yes?
Uh, could you get me
Jemma Moore's mobile, please?
Of course.
[Sighs]
Jemma: Steven.
You're on speaker phone,
but we're secure.
Um, Jemma, I just... I wanted to
express my regrets
despite any disagreements
we may have had.
That's awfully thoughtful.
What? Bygones can't be bygones?
Now that I'm gone?
Tell me why you really called.
Daniel Miller.
What about him?
Well, I thought maybe you could tell me.
Did his posting here pass by your desk?
If so, with countless others.
- Why?
- Oh, well, I don't know.
I thought [sighs] you know,
is there anything
I should know about him
that wasn't on his nomination cable?
Well, I would like to look into it,
but, um, don't exactly
have access to the files.
Mm-hmm.
Well, uh, you take care, Jemma.
You too, Steven.
[Keyboard clacking]
Hector: Hey, Robert.
I just, uh, thought you should know
Faisal's on trial for sodomy in Riyadh.
In case, you know, he gets,
uh, convicted or beheaded.
It's unfortunate he decided to
play the moth
- to the flame and...
- No, no, no, what's unfortunate, Robert,
is you didn't give me a chance
to resettle him in the U.S.
- Okay.
- We could've got him a PL-120.
Hector, I understand you're upset.
Don't fucking patronize me, Robert.
What do you want me do then?
Blame you for catering to
the desires of a wayward agent?
Wayward agent?
You fucked him, didn't you?
He played that shit up to protect me,
so you and I and every other
two-faced fucking coward
in this place could keep our cover.
He's more loyal than
the rest of us combined.
Speak for yourself, Hector. I got to go.
[Engine starts]
[Tires screech]
♪♪
The United States Government
can afford a trip to Mars
but not a cleaning service?
I've been waiting for over an hour.
Work.
Unless you want me to tell
my boss why I had to leave.
Hm?
Hm.
I don't suppose there's a match
in this dump.
[Exhales]
Oh, smoker's gum.
You're welcome.
So, no more Gerald.
No, it's just you and me now.
Is this where we're supposed to
get to know each other?
This is where you're supposed to
give me useful intelligence.
You asked for the meeting, Kevin.
A.S.P... Applications,
Services, Products.
Is there anything
going on there at the moment
that I should know about?
Nils is fucking Anna.
Rebecca wants a promotion.
Lana, cut the crap.
Unless you also think it's funny
that I could expose you for
embezzling from your employer.
Am I free to go?
♪♪
I know one of your masters
lost her job today.
The Deputy Director?
Don't take it out on the rest of us
that Thomas Shaw
makes the CIA look stupid.
[Glasses clink]
Bartender: Your Wiener schnitzel.
Oh, thank you.
- Bitte schoen.
- Mmm.
Funny seeing you here.
Are you following me now?
And if I was? Do you mind if I join you?
Hey, could I get a...
Moscow mule, please?
- Of course.
- Thanks.
So, let me guess...
you're gonna buy me my dinner
if I look the other way at the station?
No, Chris, I don't eat pork,
let alone pay for it.
[Chuckles]
And if... if the hammer's
gonna fall, I'd...
I'd at least like to
see it coming, you know?
This Shaw shit's been a raw deal.
Raw deal?
Wasn't it Thomas Jefferson
that said something about
needing a rebellion every now and then?
That's one way to look at things.
That is the only way to look at it
if you want to get through it, pal.
I mean, plus Jemma Moore?
I mean, was that really
such a fucking loss?
Come on.
You like the old face of things.
I like the right person
getting the job, okay?
Not some politically correct appointee.
I'm just sayin'.
So, where do you put your money
on her replacement?
I'll tell you who it's not gonna be.
It's not gonna be any of pencil pushers
or, you know, the Beltway types that are
fucking straightening their ties
as we speak.
No, word from on high
is that next Deputy Director
is coming from the field.
Hm.
Somebody like Steven Frost.
[Chuckles] Jesus.
I'm afraid that's a bit
above my pay grade, Robert.
No, he fits the profile, you know?
- Long career.
- Uh-huh.
Brought us out of the Cold War,
strong ties to the China,
managed to stay friends with
Germany even after the NSA shit.
Now the Shaw leaks.
Well, sounds to me like
someone sees an opening.
Yeah, Chris.
I do.
Excuse me.
The... the young woman here
at the end of the bar...
could you buy her a nice glass
of wine from my friend here?
- Right away.
- [Cellphone beeping]
[Laughs]
[Cellphone clicks]
Oh, fuck me.
I got to go.
Hi.
[Indistinct conversation]
So, uh... Clare's back in town.
Shirley: Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Why?
'Cause you only think
with your schnitzel
- when that one is around.
- [Chuckles]
Don't worry. My schnitzel
was on the fritz.
Because of the man trouble recently?
I wouldn't call it man trouble, Shirley.
I was just doing my job.
[Clears throat] Losing control?
Okay, we can change the subject
now, please.
You take control, Hector.
You be potent.
Or the next thing to shut down
may be your heart.
Good, Max.
Go, Maximum!
With you here, it's like
having a dad around again.
[Chuckles]
It would be better he doesn't
get too attached.
In case the job takes me out of
Berlin sooner than expected.
That's one way to go about life.
Oh, don't listen to me.
I'm just having a bad day.
I know it can't be easy
coming back to Berlin.
Tell me about your day.
I lost a co-worker.
Puts me in a little hole on
a project we started together.
You'll pull it off.
I have confidence.
That makes one of us.
[Grunts]
Shit.
That's okay.
He'll get up.
Just like you when you were his age.
So, you lost a co-worker.
That's such a big deal
in the life of Daniel Miller?
No.
I guess it isn't.
♪♪
Bang.
Single shot to the head,
compliments of your friends
at the Ministry of State Security, huh?
- They are not my friends.
- That's my point.
I'm using the term ironically, Lin.
Walk with me. Step into the alley.
Let's go.
What, are you fucking thinking
of making a run for it
in your little slippers?
Walk with me.
[Chuckles]
What do you think I am?
Criminal or something?
No.
I am former Major General,
People's Liberation Army.
This is the gratitude I get
for trading secrets?
You know what? Let me remind you...
you're actually the lucky beneficiary
of German state protection,
aided and abetted by the help of
its American partners.
- Bullshit.
- You're also the same fucking individual
who oversaw nuclear testing
on his own fellow citizens.
Don't ever forget it. So, fuck the MSS.
Do you have any idea what would
happen to you if some...
I don't know... German leftist radicals
recognized you out here window shopping
in Prenzlauer Berg?
So fuck them, too.
Chop suey, my friend.
With Thomas Shaw out there,
you're a big enough risk
just sitting at home watching TV, okay?
German TV sucks.
Can you get me the Apple TV?
No Internet, remember?
What about this?
That work for you?
- Mm.
- You think that might help?
Or that?
[Sighs]
[Keys clink]
[Cat meows]
Steak sandwich for Adams?
They didn't have trout. [Exhales]
How'd you get out from under things?
If I can't lose a tail
for half the night
to shoot up from Prague,
I never should have
been Deputy Director in the first place.
I fly tomorrow.
Thought I'd make one last
contribution while I can.
I am so sorry, Jemma.
You didn't deserve to go out like this.
It was a good run.
It's my shot at the buzzer
getting that before shit hit the fan.
_
Kill list?
He isn't dead.
Not according to you he isn't.
Julian De Vos.
Your mission doesn't end
because I'm finished, Daniel.
I know.
But let's face it... Shaw's winning.
And taking you out, what if...
what if he knows you sent me?
What if he's just taunting me?
Fuck it.
Wouldn't be the first time
I've pulled myself up
by the bootstraps in this town.
That's what I'm talking about, Daniel.
But watch yourself.
Frost called asking about you.
Really? Why?
I don't know.
Just be careful, Daniel.
Goodbye.
[Cat meows]
[Door opens, closes]
- Me? Deputy Director?
- Why not?
Well, my age, my disinterest.
The false fucking modesty.
The subpoena with my name on it.
He's gonna start scratching
around the wrong files.
Or asking the wrong questions.
What... what does that mean?
Is there some other liability
I don't know about?
No. No, no.
- [Knock on door]
- Yeah?
Where are we setting up for Iosava?
Looks like the SCIF
is still under siege.
Steven: We'll do it in here.
- So, we just get through today, okay?
- [Sighs]
You come out looking like
that someone in the field
they want second-in-command
at headquarters.
Corner office is yours for the taking.
Well, you make it sound so easy.
Well, maybe it is.
♪♪
Hello, stranger.
Hey.
How was Saudi?
Mm.
Hot, barbaric.
Here?
Oh, you know, same old
circle jerk as when you left.
But you didn't bring me back on
short notice for the estrogen.
No.
Are you familiar with Aleksandre Iosava?
Georgian, potential overlap
with the Boston bombers,
supposedly reformed.
Operative word is "supposedly."
We're starting to run an op today.
- I'm in?
- Not yet.
But stand by.
I left pertinent reading at the drop.
What we can prove, what we can't.
We have a lot riding on this one.
I'll get right on it.
You seen Hector?
Yes, Mom. Why?
I just have one thing to say.
You jump back in the sack with him,
you are filing the paperwork, not me.
I'm sorry. That is so fucked up.
I believe that is called
protocol, my dear.
It's pornography, Val.
We're consenting adults.
I got to go.
- Good to see you.
- Mm.
Good to see you, too.
[Speaking German]
_
Sure can turn on the charm, can't he?
German as they come.
Wunderbar.
_
[Door closes]
I noticed you served
in the same capacity
under Steven Frost
in his last posting...
COS Vienna.
Yes, I did.
And was it a request on
either or both of you parts
that you follow him out here?
Or did it just kind of
work out that way?
I didn't follow him.
I presumed that headquarters wanted
the tight ship we ran there
and set down anchor here in Berlin.
Mm-kay.
I just couldn't help but notice.
Mm-hmm.
Is there a clerical question
I can help you out with?
Otherwise, I have work to do.
Ah.
Okay.
Well, indeed there is, Sandra.
_
[Chuckles]
♪♪
_
Easy, Bora.
You're getting ahead of yourself.
_
[Chuckles] Perhaps
a suicide vest or two.
_
Do not say yes.
Just tell them you will
think about it, Bora.
_
Whoa.
Whoa, what is he doing?
[Chuckles]
♪♪
_
He... he said yes?
He's saying yes?
_
What is that?
I don't know.
Hopefully, he lied for us,
like a good agent.
♪♪
Chief.
Can I have a word with you?
In your office, please.
Well?
[Sighs]
We're done.
What?
They found out?
Oh, holy fuck.
It's over.
Wait, you... are you fucking with me?
- You're fucking with me?
- [Laughs]
You're fucking with me?
Oh.
You're fucking with me.
- [Sighs]
- Fuck you.
[Sighs]
[Telephone rings]
[Sighs] Thank you for lying.
For protecting me.
Fake agents, Steven?
You know?
The last five of whom were alive
when I brought you the files,
then deceased when
you brought back the box?
The only problem being
they never existed in the first place.
Gemstone, Woodlawn, Mariner,
Sundial, Pitchfork.
Yeah, I know.
The list goes on and on and on.
[Sighs]
Um...
In 2008, Kelly and I were hit
hard by the subprime crisis
just like every other fool
for real estate in America.
And we had to cash in our 529 fund,
which was Laura's college tuition.
And I had to borrow money from friends
because no bank would take us.
[Sighs] And at the same time,
Robert was squeezed out of
every last penny
by his ex-wife for alimony.
So, there we were,
these two broke schmucks,
who watched Langley's budget
skyrocket after 9/11,
but our shit salaries never moved.
So...
[Sighs]
...we started running fake agents.
They existed only on paper.
And we took...
We took the payments for ourselves.
[Sighs]
And that was a... that was
a world that I lived in...
seemed like forever.
And then something extraordinary
happened.
You.
And you were real.
But no games.
First real thing in my life
[sigh] long time.
[Sighs]
You were like a sunburst
on a gray German day.
Boom!
Wow.
♪♪
And so I stopped.
[Breathes deeply]
♪♪
[Keys jingle]
How did it go?
[Exhales] Fine.
Uneventful.
Define "uneventful."
I arrived, we talked, we had
tea, and talked some more.
I left.
Bora, this is a debriefing.
It's not a dental appointment.
What did you talk about?
Politics, faith.
His wife was there.
They didn't reveal anything?
There was no sense of
hidden agendas on their part?
No.
There were no overtures
to get you to help them?
Just a nice invitation to tea?
That's it. It's, um, tradition
in Islam, you know?
Hm.
All right, Bora, thank you.
Have a good night.
♪♪
_
Good riddance to the suits, huh?
I'll drink to that.
So, come on, give me
the highlights reel.
10 years in 10 minutes.
Where did they post you after Chechnya?
- Don't ask.
- Come on, I'm asking.
Hell.
They sent me to hell.
_
[Cheers and applause]
- It's your lucky night, brother.
- No, no, no.
- Go get him.
- Ohh.
I got to take a leak.
Hi, how you doing?
Wow.
_
♪♪
[Applause]
[Shirley singing in German]
What? I have to ask if
I want another round, huh?
Does the Pope shit in the woods?
Is the bear a Catholic?
You want another one?
Yeah, sure.
Hey.
Happy birthday. Happy birthday.
Steven?
Are we having a senior moment?
[Sighs]
I might have a shot at Deputy Director.
What?
Yeah, what if?
Means no Provence, not now anyway.
Do you want it?
I don't know.
With all the shit that's going
on at the agency now, it's...
I don't know.
♪♪
[Cellphone beeping]
[Shoe clatters]
♪♪
_
[Footsteps approach]
You're home early.
Told my employee to shut up shop.
You just got a message.
[Drink pouring]
What?
You're worried you're gonna find out
some deep, dark secret about me
thanks to Thomas Shaw?
What about yours?
Y...
You don't mean Isolda, do you?
One of my beverage distributors.
♪♪
[Laughs]
[Thunder rumbles]
Perhaps I should've called you
to a safe house.
Seeing your cover's been blown.
Now, do you want me to explain
how I figured out what
you're doing here in Berlin?
Or you just believe me when I say
that I know you came here
on Jemma Moore's bidding?
Do you care to respond?
I'd rather not.
Because you can't trust me?
Is that what Jemma told you?
Well, she's gone,
and you can't do this alone.
I'll be the judge of that.
And I decide
who does what in my station.
Understood?
Besides, I want to help you
find Thomas Shaw.
Why?
'Cause he'll take us down if
we don't take him down first.
[Thunder rumbles]
♪♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app