Previously on "Grey's Anatomy."
"Currently, we control your hospital."
They have changed the codes.
We are locked out of the blood bank.
This woman needs blood! Who's O-neg?
We're airlifting him
to Snohomish Medical Center.
Aah! Aah!
Don't give him
heparin now! He'll bleed out!
Hey, Brooke.
There are moments in the O.R.
when everything goes to hell.
- Oh, God.
- I mean, I'm so happy
- that you're okay.
- And no matter how much
you've seen, how ready you are,
how much help you have,
nothing can truly prepare you.
Jenny, Jenny. This is Jenny.
She is my fiancée.
- Hi.
- She has made me a new man.
But hard to plan a wedding when,
legally, you're still married.
So, um, we were so relieved
when my lawyer received your papers.
Thank you.
You have to keep going,
or your patient will die.
It's nice to meet you.
You're nothing like I pictured.
I mean, you look so good, Brooke.
So much better, I mean.
It looks like you finally
got the help you needed.
The trouble is... in these moments,
every instinct in your body
tells you to freeze.
Are you... Is he... are you Paul Stadler?
- Yes.
- Oh, my God.
Wow. I am... I am such a huge fan.
Your research on minimally invasive
surgery procedures
was life-changing for me.
Um, Dr. Arizona Robbins.
- Pleasure, Dr. Robbins.
- Fetal surgeon.
- Yes.
- Wow.
Are you fan-girling here?
Your paper on introducing
multi-mode step index fibers
for scopes was revolutionary.
Oh, well, she should know it.
I mean, she was my student
when I wrote it.
- What?
- Though I'm not sure
how much she remembers.
She was quite the partier back then.
Well, I would love
to pick your brain later,
you know, when it's not as crazy.
- Yeah.
- Um, Wilson, I can't believe
that you studied under Paul Stadler.
Way to keep a secret.
See ya.
So... you haven't been talking about me.
I guess I should be grateful for that.
Is there, uh, someplace
quiet we can talk,
sign those papers, catch up?
Wilson?
Uh, Karev's looking for you.
Oh, no.
Oh, we can talk later. I'll find you.
Uh, aren't you Paul Stadler?
I am.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Right angle.
How are you holding up?
Well, if you you estimate
2 units every 10 minutes,
that gives us about
an hour till I'm empty.
Of course, I'd be super-dead by then.
Don't worry. We won't let that happen.
Just keep telling me how you feel.
Honestly, right now, I'm hot as hell.
Is that just me?
No. It's not just you.
Why is it so hot in here?
Uh, can you ask facilities
to crank the A.C.?
Oh, no. We can't.
They have run the thermostats up to 90.
They... They can hack
into the thermostats?
Yeah. Easily.
W-Why? Why would they do that?
Well, like the cardiac monitors
and turning the power
on and off, they just want to show you
that they have control, so they
turned up the heat, literally.
That is just dumb.
Such an obvious pun.
Oh.
Look, Jackson, I don't
know where the hell you are,
but pick up your damn phone.
Markham... M-A-R-K-H...
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Did you stab him?
There was an accident.
Did the helicopter crash?
No. There was some turbulence,
and the tube that was
pumping his blood came loose.
But we're gonna take care of him.
It looks like all of his blood.
Is that all of his blood?
We will get him more blood.
We've got this now, okay?
Okay.
- Ow!
- His left arm is tingling,
and he's seeing stars.
His head is killing him.
- When did it start?
- 5 to 10 minutes.
It seems to be getting worse.
The Heparin should have helped by now.
I think I made the wrong call.
Wait. Heparin? No. I texted.
They didn't reverse him. Oh, my God.
Damn it. We can't access
the reversal agent.
Prep him to move.
- What is it? What's wrong?
- Frankie's AVM
might be bleeding.
We've got to get him to the O.R. now.
But the medicine you gave him...
it was supposed to help.
I'm sorry. We need to go.
Hey. I'm so sorry. I texted.
It didn't go through.
- And then...
- And then what?
Nothing. It can wait. Just help him.
We're back to paper charts
and trying to chase
our own tails.
I was at Alexandria when they got hacked.
- It was a nightmare, I can tell you.
- Yeah.
Okay, temperature
will drop soon... or not.
I mean, we could
all get dizzy and dehydrated
and succumb to heatstroke,
damage our brains, kidneys,
other internal organs.
We could all die today.
Uh, would you excuse me
for a second, please?
- Yeah.
- Uh, Dr. Bello?
Could I have a moment, please?
Please?
Yeah.
Um... do you hear yourself?
I'm sorry, sir.
I haven't slept in three days.
When I'm not here,
I'm thinking about being here.
And then the minute I do fall asleep,
I dreamed I've cut open
the wrong person's chest,
- and I wake up screaming.
- Uh, DeLuca?
She is making my blood pressure go up.
Can you take her somewhere,
away from the patients,
until she calms down?
Sir, I-I don't really...
Oh, drop it, DeLuca.
We all heard the two of you
through the walls.
Now step up.
I'm sorry.
Um, yeah, I was saying that...
Can I help?
I know how bad this can be,
so if I can lend an extra hand,
I'd be happy to.
Yeah, the minute you get to Seattle Pres,
check everything off
the paper charts, okay?
Okay.
Larry Keys, post-tracheostomy
two months ago
and now has worsening
blood-tinged secretions.
Uh, pulse ox... 98.
Needs a chest x-ray, okay?
Hang in there, Mr. Keys.
Oh, God.
Yeah, it takes you back to Jordan, right?
Yeah, only hotter.
Uh, Chief? We already transferred
six patients, but we have eight
ICU patients who are
stable enough to move.
And the blood banks are still locked,
so we're waiting on emergency shipments
from other area hospitals.
Good, great. You are
handling your situation.
Avery and I are...
handling our situation.
He called you from the medevac chopper?
Avery's on a medevac chopper?
I can't tell you how much I want to
stick my head under a faucet right now.
I'd just settle for
a fresh pair of scrubs.
- You don't have hair.
- True.
Oh, Claude, I think
that some of your blood
just soaked through to my underwear.
So we are in this together now.
Yeah, well, I got some in my mouth.
We're not gonna think
about that, all right?
And we're not gonna
think about the fact that
his blood and our sweat
are creating their own little ecosystem.
Ugh. Yeah, no, I'm not gonna
think about that at all.
Mnh-mnh.
Clips, please.
Front-row seats to the surgical Olympics.
Schmitt, quiet.
Another one.
Thanks for calling me Schmitt.
Because, sometimes,
you call me "Glasses."
I wish we could change it to "Specs."
Specs sounds way cooler than Glasses.
Or look at me now. What about Blood Bank?
Blood Bank is awesome!
Blood Bank needs to pipe down!
Sponge stick.
Oh, Blood Bank needs somewhere to barf.
Somebody get him a basin.
The blood loss is making him nauseous.
Oh, no. They're so busy. I got it. Whoa.
Hey, Schmitt, sit down.
Whoa.
Oh, where's that basin?
Schmitt... Ugh.
Damn it.
Bokhee, give me a sterile towel
over the area he contaminated.
And someone get him a liter of saline.
Would it be wrong of me to
take out his spleen, too?
No, tell Maintenance,
if they can't get into
the blood bank doors, to call the police
for some sort of battering ram.
They're still locked?
Did they even try to override
the security system?
Your background is cybersecurity.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Hey, if you have any ideas,
- they're welcome.
- Yes, ma'am.
- On it.
- Dr. Cullen, NICU.
Dr. Cullen, NICU.
Should I just stay down here
and see where I can jump in?
That'd be a godsend. Anything.
- You got it.
- Thanks.
Dr. Webber. Dr. Grey needs
an assistant in O.R.-3.
She lost hers.
What do you mean she lost hers?
Her intern passed out.
Was it Glasses?
I.J. looks good.
ECMO access re-established.
I hope wed didn't
traumatize his daughter.
Oh, we absolutely did.
We look like we stepped off
the set of "Carrie."
Being doused in blood
was about the only thing from that movie
that didn't happen to me in high school.
Really? Oh, I was brainy and awkward
and four years younger
than everyone else.
But who didn't have
a rough time in high school?
Of course. The human superlative.
Varsity basketball?
Class president? Prom king?
Varsity baseball, I'll have you
know, but the rest is true.
Well, I was freshman age as a senior,
so I couldn't have been
prom queen even if I had gone.
What? Are freshmen
not supposed to be prom king?
You've got to be kidding me.
No, you don't have to follow me.
It was literally my instructions
from Dr. Webber.
Well, you're not a person
who can calm me down, so leave.
I'm not happy about this either.
Yeah? You're not hoping
that I drag you into a closet
and wrap myself around you?
I mean, if it'll help.
It won't help. It's the problem.
I defibrillated a sleeping person.
I told another one
that the world was gonna end.
And no one knows this, but the other day,
I didn't know where to empty a bedpan,
so I just set it on a cart in a hallway.
These are not the things that
a brilliant intern does.
I was top of my class.
Okay, but how is any of this my fault?
Because I haven't slept
because you penetrate me every 5 minutes.
Shh.
Look, don't put this on me, okay?
Every time I look at you, you...
you sex-pout at me.
That's just my face.
And... and this is about
my mind, so no more sex.
That's it. I am not gonna
fail here because of you.
Don't talk to any patients until
you get some rest, all right?
What are you doing here?
Hi.
Paul Stadler, Orlando Medical.
Yeah, I know who you are.
I'm sorry. Have we met before?
You know, your face
looks kind of familiar.
Dr. Karev, Dr. Shepherd said
Frankie's angio shows a bleed.
Yikes.
Don't let me keep you.
Intern, what's your name?
Helm. Like "Hellmouth"
without the "outh."
- Don't scrub.
- I need you to find Dr. Wilson
and bring her here.
- You want me to call her?
- No.
I want you to find her
and bring her here.
- And don't leave her side.
- Why?
Just do it.
What's going on?
Heat getting to you?
Yeah.
How is it I never knew you
studied under Paul Stadler?
Uh, it's a... long story.
Well, he couldn't have picked
a better time to come and visit.
He's pitching in in the O.R.
What?!
No. He can't.
He's a world-class surgeon,
and we're in a bit
of a quagmire. Why not?
Whatever he said to you, it isn't true.
You can't trust him. He lies.
He lies about everything.
Lap pads.
Dr. Grey? Heard you could use some help.
How are you? And please
tell me you have blood.
No. Sorry. But I do have 20 years
experience as a general surgeon.
Then get in here.
Whoa, she's losing everywhere.
Yeah, she burned through
all her clotting factors,
and I couldn't get any FFP
from the blood bank.
Let's get started. 3-0 silk for Dr. Grey.
Okay. There. I'm getting control.
Another tie.
Right there.
Good.
Scissor.
Whew!
Thanks for the assist.
- I almost lost her.
- I try.
I'm Meredith Grey.
What did you say your name was?
Paul Stadler.
Paul Stadler?
Honor to meet you, Dr. Grey.
All right, we need to do
a distal pancreatectomy.
Do you prefer harmonic stapler
or oversewn closure?
Well, oversew doesn't
require electricity, so...
3-0 silk, please.
I can ligate this one. I'm right here.
Well, I guess we should talk
about the elephant in the room.
Congrats on your Harper Avery.
Kelly clamp.
I didn't even make it past
the submission round.
I study fiber-optics for
minimally invasive surgeries.
I know who you are.
I'm friends with Jo Wilson.
Clamp.
Get an eye on the EEG,
tell me if there's any slowing.
Got it.
I'll prep the shunt,
and then we can embolize.
What the hell is taking Helm so long?
Hi. I'm here to replace Helm.
No, you're not. You're here to find her.
Turn around and go.
Y-you want me to find Dr. Helm?
Yes! And Dr. Wilson and bring them here.
Stat!
Is there any point
to this intern treasure hunt,
or is it just for fun?
We ligated the blood vessel in his neck.
He's back on ECMO, and he's stable.
You will be able to see him as soon as
he's settled in the ICU.
Thank you so much.
Oh, I really want to hug you, but...
- No, no. Please.
- Totally understand.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Sorry about your blouse.
Is it bad that I'm the same amount happy
that he's alive as I am
that we can shower now?
Is it bad that I'm happier
about the shower?
Clip.
So, Jo Wilson.
Has she said some things about me?
I can only imagine.
Was she drunk when she told you?
Suction and laps, please.
I think what Brooke craved
from me was stability.
I mean, the way she was raised.
Her mother abandoned her.
She lived in her car in high school.
And I thought I could
help her... save her.
And for a few years, I mean,
she was... she was great.
But it didn't last
because she's not stable,
and she wasn't able to hear that... ever.
She would get...
just awful if you tried to
mention that she needed help.
I wish...
But she vanished...
with a lot of my money.
Hey, I mean, if she's got it figured out,
then that's all that matters.
If she's happy, I'm happy, too.
Clamp.
- Finally.
- Shh.
What do you want?
I...
Dr. Karev said I had to find you
and bring you to him.
And I'm not allowed to leave you alone.
Shunt's in.
Nice work, Karev.
Somebody read that.
It's from Dr. Wilson.
"I'm safe, in Grey's gallery.
Helm is with me.
Can't come right now but will soon."
Hey.
Um, I thought you would
want to know that Ms. Knox
is doing fine,
and she's hopelessly in love
with her baby daughter.
Oh, yes, I did. I wanted to know that.
Find anyone promising?
Huh? Oh. Um, no, no.
I was just... I was killing time
while I'm in line to give blood.
Look at this hospital.
All this chaos because of the Internet,
and you trust it with your heart?
Well, it saves a lot of time.
It wastes time.
All the slapping the screen for hours.
And... and how do you know
if you have a connection
if you can't look in that woman's eyes?
Online is like dating one of those, um,
window dolls with no faces.
Mannequins.
Yeah.
A photo might be sexy,
but until you're face-to-face
to talk, listen, share your passions...
only then do you know
if there is electricity, you know?
Clear!
We have blood.
Jo's ex is here.
I know. I just operated with him.
- What? He's a psychopath.
- Yeah.
He had a lot to say about her.
Like what?
It's not true.
He takes the truth,
but he... he twists it
and changes it to fit his own story.
It's not... it's not true.
You are Jo Wilson.
I know exactly who you are.
It's okay.
Okay, loaded up the last rig.
I think we're good for now.
No. We're forgetting something.
We're not forgetting anything, Kepner.
It's like a sandstorm.
We got slammed,
it was blinding, and then,
when the dust settles,
you can't switch your brain
back to normal.
You can't shake the feeling like
something slipped through the cracks.
Wrong. Stop! Stop!
"Larry Keys, status post..."
I can't read the rest of this.
- It's your handwriting.
- No, I know.
It's all smudged.
Uh, "Chest x-ray, 14:09."
That was two hours ago.
Oh, found him, found him, found him!
Okay.
Okay, gross bleeding through his trach.
- All right.
- Let's get him up to the O.R.
and control this bleeding.
He's losing his airway.
He's not gonna make it that far.
- Let's get a crash cart.
- All right.
Okay, hang tight, Mr. Keys.
I need to remove your trach
and put in a breathing tube.
I'm gonna need an 8-0 ET tube.
I'm not gonna be able to see.
There's too much blood.
We got to control the bleeding.
Here. I can compress the vessel
right through the trach.
What's wrong?
- I still can't see.
- Okay. Hang on, hang on.
All right. Look for the light.
- You see it?
- I see it. Yeah, okay.
- I got it.
- Yep, yep. Okay.
Okay.
- All right.
Okay. All right.
Sandstorm.
I think we can call them off.
Helm hasn't let me out of her sight.
She was just following instructions.
She followed me into the bathroom.
The actual stall.
Hey. You guys can leave.
Thank you.
Look, I would have come myself,
but I was stuck in surgery.
- How's Frankie?
- He's okay.
We were able to stop the
bleeding from his AVM in time.
How do you want to handle this?
I want to be divorced.
I want to never see his face ever again.
I'm coming with you for that.
No, you are not going anywhere near him.
I should have killed him
when I had the chance.
Which is exactly why.
Alex, we've got this.
She is not going to be alone with him.
Parker?
I was told you used a defibrillator
to fry the keypad on the blood bank.
- People needed blood...
- Hey, I don't want excuses.
I want to know what else you can do.
Um, what's happening?
Did you know that
cellphones have 10 times
more bacteria than an average
public toilet seat?
- Cool story.
- Where are the scrubs, Maggie?
Oh, we don't have the code
for their machine, so...
So, I called down, and somebody
should be up any minute.
All right, we got to
get back to the hospital.
I mean, I don't have my phone.
I don't know what the hell's happening.
Well, if you want to
walk around this hospital
in your towel, you can be my guest.
So, what? We wait?
We wait.
You have the divorce papers?
Uh, if you wouldn't mind, Dr. Grey,
I'd like to have a moment alone with...
Actually, I do mind. I'm gonna stay here.
Okay then.
Let's get this done, shall we?
We've got it. It's faster this way.
I'm really happy for you, Jo.
I hope this brings you...
some real peace.
You deserve it.
We both do.
You don't deserve anything good.
You're a monster.
You did great, and it's over.
No. No, it's not. I need Robbins.
Where's Robbins?
I'm sure the feds are focusing
on common attack vectors
because that's protocol.
But if it were me, I'd do
offline forensic analysis
on our servers.
Fantastic. Yes.
Uh, now go tell them that.
Uh, what's the problem?
Let's just say that, hypothetically,
I was convicted
of hacking a federal server,
as part of my hypothetical sentence,
I'm not allowed to manipulate computers
in that manner ever again...
or advise or enable anyone else to.
I would say, hypothetically,
that wasn't on your application.
Fair. But records like that are sealed.
Hypothetically.
Did any of these
hypothetical crimes involve
literal children or sex or drugs
or children and sex and drugs?
They did not.
Or robbing old people of their last $2?
Also no.
- Or...
- Chief, do you want me to help you?
I do.
Hmm.
Write down what you want me
to tell the FBI.
Nigerian prince?
DMV.
My new license was taking too long.
And now you're an accessory
to whatever I do moving forward.
I did not want to know that.
I think you did.
What happened in there, babe?
Let's just get the hell out of here.
Hey. Dr. Stadler, where are you going?
Actually, we're on our way out.
Oh, no. No, you can't. You can't leave.
I have a problem with a new fetoscope,
and it's got me banging
my head against the wall.
And I know that there's an answer,
but I-I'm just...
It's way out of my reach.
It would be great if I could
just get some manpower,
you know, which... I need you.
10 minutes.
Fantastic. This way.
Wait here.
Hi.
We need to talk and we don't
have enough time.
Anything you have to say to me
you can say in front of Paul.
I don't need help.
I said the same thing when
I was with him, but I was lying.
I was lying to myself.
I was lying to everyone around me.
Oh, my God. He told me you were crazy,
and I thought
that's just something people say
about their exes.
In your case, he was clearly right.
You know, Jenny,
it's okay if you don't
want to talk to me.
You don't have to say a word.
Just please listen.
There was a dinner party
with his colleagues.
I talked too much to the man
sitting next to me.
Paul said that I made a fool out of him.
I laughed because it seemed so...
I laughed.
And his eyes went dark,
and that's the last thing
that I remember before
waking up the next morning
with my eye swollen shut.
I thought it would be the only time.
I'm sure that you did
the first time, too.
But he just got smarter after that.
He made sure that no one
could see the bruises.
He would apologize
and then tell me it was my fault
all in one breath,
and he was so persuasive.
He told me I was wrong so many times
that I believed I was wrong.
He told me I was crazy so many times
that I believed that
I actually was crazy.
The last time,
I woke up to him kicking me
in the back because he'd read my e-mail
and saw the name of a man
that he didn't recognize.
He kicked me so hard, he broke my ribs
and almost ruptured my kidney.
So, you're saying that,
with your technique,
I can repair a spina bifida
or cleft palate
or I mean, anything, right?
I mean, that's incredible, Dr. Stadler.
It's just...
That's incredible.
So you've said several times.
Well, you know, I do have
another question, which is...
Dr. Robbins, it's been a pleasure,
and I'd be happy to consult
with you on any future cases,
but my fiancée has been way more patient
than I'd be at this point.
I... Yeah. Thank you.
Thank you so much for your time.
If I hadn't have escaped that night...
He's coming back.
Say the word, and I will help you.
I will get you out of this right now.
You really should go.
You shouldn't be here when he comes back.
You know what?
This is my cellphone number.
You call me day or night,
and I will get you out of this.
How about we get out of here?
Please.
And you've combed through
the admin server logs
for any suspicious activity
on TCP ports 21 through 23?
Of course.
But reading them all will
take days at least.
Oh.
And what about scanning the log dumps,
uh, specifically for
unwanted guest Wi-Fi traffic?
You've been doing your homework.
Yeah, I know how to Google.
Well, we've done that, as well.
That's how we found their I.P. address.
Great!
You found the I.P. address.
That means that you can hack them back,
uh, ping them, storm the computer castle.
No. We still need to
physically locate them.
What you're suggesting would alert them,
and they'd pull up stakes.
We'd never catch them.
Um, hold on.
Are we trying to save
my patients or make arrests?
Have a seat here.
This is my laptop.
And this is my password.
No one will ever know you touched it.
How many times do you think that we were
in the same place in Boston
and didn't even know it?
Hmm.
The aquarium or Fenway Park?
Uh...
The Ugly Duckling?
The Swan Boats?
- Uh...
- No?
N-no.
Um... I was in Mallorca a lot.
Would you ever...
- No? That's...
- Wow. Uh...
All right.
Why would... why did
you become a surgeon?
I mean, what we do is really hard.
Where did you learn to work?
I guess, for a long time, I didn't.
I think, uh, I spent
a lot of my childhood
avoiding the inevitable, you know?
Pretending that I had a say in my future,
with my mom being
who she is and my grandfather.
I...
Yeah.
Wow.
Thank you.
For what?
That's the first time
all day I've felt good
about my childhood.
Yeah, well, I said thank God
we are from different families.
Oh, is that what you meant by that?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
I mean, that and, um...
And what?
Uh, you know, just that's
good... It's a good thing.
It doesn't define us.
We're not actually related, so...
we can be whatever
we want to be, I guess.
Hey. There he is.
Oh.
Oh. Here, your phone.
They got it from the medevac.
Oh, crap.
What happened?
27 missed calls from Bailey.
You don't have to stay with me.
I'm okay.
I know.
Hey.
Really happy you and Jenny
had the chance to talk.
She told me all about it.
She didn't say anything.
It was me. It was all me.
Yeah, it was always you.
Okay, walk away, Dr. Stadler.
No, no. She is a liar.
She is pathological.
I mean, w-what kind of woman
changes her name
and disappears on her husband
without a word?
Do you know what that did to me?
What that did to my reputation,
to my career?
You are... torture.
You are hell.
You walk around and you ruin lives,
and no one ever stops you.
They... they just believe you.
'Cause why? 'Cause you're pretty?
'Cause you're sweet?
Your looks will fade one day, Brooke.
Your looks will fade, and you'll
be left with the truth.
And you point fingers at
everyone else around you,
but you're the monster.
Security to the residents's
lounge on 3, stat.
You know what?
Jenny won't be needing this,
seeing as how we're actually happy.
That said...
I think I'll hang on to it.
So I know where to find you.
It's okay.
The phones are working?
No, but he doesn't know that.
Again? Oh, come on!
- No, that was me.
- Why?
I had to make sure I could.
And I could.
It worked.
Are you sure?
On!
On. Oh, oh. Is that what I think it is?
If what you think it is is
air-conditioning, then yes.
Yay!
Okay, now, did you
really hack into the DMV?
Why would you do that?
Because my old license
referred to me as female,
and the DMV where
I was living wouldn't change it,
so I did.
I'm a proud trans man, Dr. Bailey,
but I like for people to
get to know me before
they find out my private medical history.
Of course.
Thank you for your service, Dr. Parker.
I heard you wanted to talk to me?
Yes, I do.
Hey, I'm not sure if I should
have a lawyer present,
but I, uh, wanted
to tell you how sorry I am.
It was just so hot,
and I really didn't
want to throw up in you.
Why the hell would you apologize?
You're a damn hero.
I am?
You saved my life.
Of course, no one would know,
to see you creeping in here
like a sick mouse.
Stand up straight.
Hey, buddy. How you doing?
Thirsty.
- That's good, right?
- It is very good.
He came through with flying colors.
Because he's a fighter.
Dr. Alex, I know I didn't die,
but will you still marry my mom?
Frankie! He's still loopy from surgery.
Yeah, well, we see that all the time.
We'll keep a close eye on him tonight.
What's wrong?
He came back.
He's gone now, but I did
have to call security.
That son of a bitch.
He knows where to find me.
He knows where to find us.
You're safe, you hear me?
- You're not gonna be alone.
- What?
So that's just my life now?
I have to be guarded every second?
No. Because we will get
a restraining order,
and he will never set foot
in this hospital again.
God.
I wish he was dead.
Come on. Let's go home.
DeLuca.
Are you interested in helping me
out with this big contest?
I need a new Edwards,
and you've got potential.
Yeah. Really? Yes. Yes.
All right.
Oh, and, um, one of our new interns
wrote a paper on pupillary
response in comatose patients.
They were in med school,
it was a little raw,
- but I was impressed.
- Could you find them and then...
It was me!
S-sorry. Sam Bello. It was me.
Oh.
Hello, Dr. Sam Bello.
Welcome aboard Team Shepherd.
She read my paper.
Yeah. Congrats.
All is right with the world.
What's going on here?
Why does everything look normal?
- It is normal.
- You paid the ransom?
I didn't have to, and I'm not at liberty
to discuss why, so let's
just leave it at...
You're welcome. Those aren't our colors.
Go change.
Nurse Laskey to pharmacology.
Kepner.
Did I hear that you plugged a man's
tracheo-innominate fistula
with your finger?
Well, we didn't have
much of a choice, so...
I've got to tell you...
the dam could have broken today,
but thanks to work like that, it didn't.
Wow. Thank you, Dr. Webber.
Everything okay?
Uh, Bailey wants me
to oversee her big contest.
And... and I am flattered, honestly.
But, uh, at this age, I'm...
I'm not sure I can handle it.
I guess I'm just feeling
my seasons, you know?
Um, you... you know,
if you need some help, I...
Oh, well, it's not a matter of help.
I mean, someone needs to do everything.
I mean, you name it.
They have to handpick
the judges and set deadlines,
schedule presentations,
and the whole kit and caboodle.
Wait. Um...
I could do it?
- Oh, no. No.
- No?
- No, no.
- I couldn't possibly ask you.
You... you really mean it?
Yeah. Yes. Yes. Yes, sir. Yeah.
I-I won't let you down, sir.
Well, thank you.
This day.
Insane, right?
I feel like I can still
feel blood on my face.
That's just psychological, right?
I don't actually have any.
No, you're good.
Then what?
You want to get a drink?
I know I need one,
and it's on me, actually,
because I just got an extra
$20 mill I wasn't counting on.
- We work together.
- Yeah.
We work with your ex-wife.
And our parents are married
to each other.
That's a lot of complicating factors.
So if it went bad,
we couldn't just walk away.
On the other hand, it's just a drink.
Jackson...
no, it's not.
I'm not saying "no."
I'm just saying it's complicated.
Mm-hmm.
Maggie Pierce?
Clive Johnson, from the... Tinder?
Oh, oh, oh! Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. This day has
been absolutely insane.
It feels like months ago
since we scheduled dinner.
Did... did you want to take a rain check?
So, what do we do when
instinct tells us to freeze?
No, no, no.
No, you're here. You're here. Let's go.
- Okay.
- You kids have fun.
When we can't see the right answer.
In those moments,
it's usually a good idea
to trust the instinct and take pause.
Okay.
Because decisions made
in the heat of the moment...
What's happening?
Hit-and-run.
ABCs are intact, but he's
hypertensive and tachycardic.
...can ruin a whole lot of lives.
What did you do?