Subtitles machine translated from Spanish
HIDDEN KISSES
Do not leave me in front of the house. It is well on the corner of the street.
Good!
Am I well dressed?
Okay if it will be a party of geeks.
Okay, I will not go.
I was joking. It's very attractive, sir.
Do not know anyone...
It is not easy to move during the school year.
But this is a good start!
You've just arrived and already you've been invited to a party.
Have you seen a girl?
You've seen some girls!
Now I'm calm, I'm not the only delay.
I'll see you this afternoon!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
- Good night, boss. - Goodnight.
- Good evening how are you? - Fine thanks.
Good afternoon ladies and gentlemen.
Great...
Good night, boss.
Goodbye Sir.
- Guess what. - What?
What if I tell you that it is a noise complaint?
Party?
Yes, it's our turn. What will we do?
Hopefully to call again.
We will not go. Can you imagine the face of Nathan and Chloe?
I wonder what's going on at that party.
What are you doing?
I see the profile Chloé.
I have a deal with my daughter.
In case of problems, I have your password.
Now you're interested.
They are having fun...
Wait, come back.
Is Nathan?
It's a boy!
You are kissing a boy?
Hello Dad!
You're good?
Chloe's mother showed me a picture of the party,
blog of her daughter.
- What is that photo? - Which photo?
The photo where you kiss a boy.
Oh, it's just a friend.
We were drunk and wanted to be fun to attract girls.
- And it seemed funny? - Yes.
We have a pact.
I let you do anything ... out, but do not drink alcohol.
We both agreed that!
Forget that now, okay?
To prepare...
It's a nightmare!
Do not worry, I promise. There is no way to recognize you.
I need to see you this afternoon.
Why?
Only five minutes; I need to give you your scarf.
I will call you later.
¡Nathan!
Do you know?
More or less...
I know them from school.
They are beautiful!
Go see them if you want.
Not well. Let's go?
What a pity!
Surely you see the photo. Tell them it's a joke!
I do not care. Come on!
They are making fun of you. Tell them!
If you do not want to tell you, I will.
Dad!
For!
I do not understand.
- It does not bother you? - It was not a joke!
It was not a joke when I kissed that guy!
I have to go.
You're leaving now? But it is starting to be fun.
I know, but I'm exhausted.
Do not go. See you in the garden. We need to talk.
What do you want?
Look at the photo of the party!
Good Morning!
Yes, it is the new kid on the second year!
He's kissing a boy!
They Go to class! Good Morning!
Inward, everyone!
We could, for once in the year, starting in silence.
¡Nathan!
Good!
We started?
All right. Today,
We see how to graph a function.
I am sorry. It was foolish to publish that picture on my wall.
- Do you know who took it? - Nobody knows.
Who is the guy you kissed?
I bet it's Julien.
It was him?
They do not care what I'm saying?
The graphical representation of a function,
is the set of points.
Admit it, is Julien!
I do not remember.
- Come on, I will not tell anyone! - I do not remember!
Enough with Nathan!
Do not you think that was already noticed enough?
I do not understand why Julien is not supported.
I get it; if I were gay, I would have committed suicide.
I bet Luke is gay!
It's obvious!
Have you ever gone out with a girl?
You have not come out with any; coincidence!
Do not say that!
I'm not gay.
I'm going to hit you!
Stop!
I'm Not Gay! It's Lucas!
Are you crazy!
Are you crazy! Your friend Lucas ...
I saw them looking at each other in that game.
It is obvious that there is something between them!
It must be Lucas who kisses!
He's crazy!
What's going on?!
For! Sit down!
Sit down, Luke!
Who wrote this? "THE OTHER IS LUCAS"
You want to go to the infirmary?
I'm fine.
I would go, in fact.
Ahead.
I know what's going on here.
Everyone talks about that photo in school.
But nothing justifies your behavior, Lucas!
I'm being accused; It is normal to defend me.
The other individual must admit, right, Julien?
Damn, not wanting to go out with you does not make me gay.
Do you realize the words they use?
??Accused"...
"To admit"...
As if they were talking about a crime!
It's like "gay"; I remind you that it is an insult.
What are you talking about?
It is not an insult, it is a regular word.
Just we use it to tease!
Words have meanings!
They can be very violent!
But sir,
he chooses what he wants to be; You should assume it to the end.
Why do you think it is a choice?
Do you for example have chosen you like girls?
I did not choose it because it is within me.
Can I ask you a question, sir?
Yes.
Is it true that you like men?
What makes you think that?
I do not know, is defending gays.
And it has a style a bit ...
Whatever...
Go ahead, what about my style?
It means that something is missing virility.
So we go a little deeper,
and discover the other prince of English elegance ...
Oscar Wilde.
It is Nathan.
I'm waiting. There is nobody here...
I'm waiting...
Giving me a call.
Do you know what your child?
I do not like to be in place!
Did you tell?
No, I said nothing!
What is the problem?
I do not want to talk about it at work.
Stéphane, go for a drink, will you come?
- Not now, I'm tired. - As you like.
If you change your mind, you know where to find us.
Hey, Dad, I'm in front of your work.
I wonder if we could go home together.
If you get my message, call me.
I have work yet. Do not wait for me.
"I break the glass"; I broke the glass.
You must learn irregular verbs. The same to you.
Can I see you a minute?
Of course.
We'll talk about that.
- Please. - Thank you.
You know me, Tristan.
I'm not the kind of director who interferes with the lessons.
But I received calls from parents who really did not appreciate
the fact that talk about homosexuality in the classroom.
I did not speak of homosexuality.
I spoke about homophobia.
My job is to enable students to overcome their prejudices.
No, your job is to teach English. Point.
In this case, should be invited to an association
fighting homophobia, to speak at the school.
Students are asking many questions ...
Are you kidding?
Can you imagine the situation if such an association comes here?
Listen, Tristan.
I have nothing against gays,
even I have many gay friends.
Can behave as you like elsewhere,
but here you are a single master, is that clear?
Great thanks.
Why did not you tell them you had a wife?
They think I'm gay!
I was the second.
There was another name on the board.
Nathan was surrounded!
He had started a fight. What was the name?
- Framework. - Framework?
I do not think it's him!
For real? What does that mean?
Are you aware of what you're saying?
Relax, Tristan.
It's just an impression.
I'm disappointed by the fact that we can not help that boy!
It's his fault. He should have remained discreet.
What?
What about you, Catherine?
I believe that...
as I finished editing, I'll go elsewhere.
Wait, Catherine!
I know what you'll ask me. The answer is no!
I think it will be better if you talk to Nathan.
I will never do it. I repeat: No. Is that clear?
I am convinced that if you talk to him, will be good.
How stubborn you are! I'm not your wife!
If you know what you do,
you are well placed to know what is enduring.
I'm her math teacher.
I'm just well placed to talk about equations and geometry.
My skills stop there!
The other day, you told me that nothing in the world,
you would live your youth again. You remember?
Perhaps things would have been less difficult for you,
if a homosexual teacher you had said you were not alone in the world.
Do not you realize what you're asking me?
What are you scared?
What do people know you're a lesbian? And that?
Things have changed!
I am dreaming!
Do you think you're paranoid?
What we see homophobia everywhere?
What you think?
That everything is fine because there is a law for marriage?
You know what I hear in the yard, in my class,
even in the staffroom. You were there with me!
It's Nathan's fault, because he has not been discreet!
- Catherine ... - No, you listen to me!
As a teenager, school was like hell.
And I'm still in school.
Teaching math is the only thing I can do.
My family did not speak to me.
I was so alone. I resisted through this work.
Apart from close friends like you,
I do not tell anyone about my private life,
because I have 140 students watching me,
and 280 parents ready to call me to account.
Because I'm tired and I want to be quiet!
- And Nathan? - Will do like me ...
He will suffer, and then get over it.
Yes, it's me again.
I'm sick of always falling into your voicemail.
We can talk, right?
Call me please.
Hello ... We're on the wrong floor.
Down the volume...
Why you not say who the other guy?
I do not remember who it was. I was drunk.
Do not take me for a fool. He is threatening you, right?
I do not want to betray him!
Well, but meanwhile, you're assuming everything.
It's hell in school.
My father is yelling at me. All they insult me.
And I do not care. You know why?
Because I'm in love.
- What are you playing? - I tell the truth, is all.
The truth is that at your age, you do not love.
For real?
Do not you tell me you were in love with a girl
when you were a sophomore?
Is not the same.
That story with that boy, is not serious.
I am gay!
You need to accept, I am the only son you have!
It is not easy to have a son like you.
Do you think it's easy to have a homophobic bastard as a father?
"THE OTHER IS LOUIS"
I knew it was him!
It is not credible, I spent the night with my boyfriend.
Enough for now!
I swear that I'll getcha!
I said that's enough!
Another word and give them a try immediately!
Okay, lady ...
Do you have memorized all?
We need to act quickly.
Thus, the criminal police can work easily.
Alistémonos.
Patricia, can I talk to you?
- Sorry ... - You've become paranoid!
There are one or two colleagues who know so everyone knows it.
What you think?
What I look at you differently because of Nathan?
- Do not you know ... - Okay ...
No need to tell me that if my daughter kissing another girl,
He would have been in a bad situation. That's true, thank you.
It was unexpected ...
We were so complicit, and then nothing.
I do not know what I've done to not talk to me about that.
What about me?
I did not think I would put it this way ...
I thought it was open ...
No...
We get closer ...
When his mother died, it was Nathan who told me:
"Do not worry, Dad, we will overcome this."
Now, we are like strangers.
Still your son ...
Why do you always call?
I wanted to say it was not me who wrote on the board.
I know it was not you.
He was someone who wanted to bring trouble.
You did not need me to come to tell me that.
It's not because of that...
I wanted to see you, Louis.
I'm feeling alone.
I'm happy to see you.
I'm not like you.
That kiss was just a test.
I see...
Did you bring my scarf?
I would like to save it.
I'm not just me who knows about you.
Who took the photo also known.
Who are you texting?
My mother. He wants to know when I'll go home.
We Dance?
You go. I do not want to dance.
What do you want?
Come on, follow me.
I have also scared ...
Anyone here?
Let's go swimming?
No, do you, if you want.
Come on, it's good ...
It is time to train, Louis.
Perfect!
Friend!
I hurt you?
You're good?
- You want to win that event? - Definitely.
You need to work on your weaknesses, if you want to win.
You see? Everything is in the mind.
Well done. Very good.
So I said:
"Can I have the balance for Monday?".
My weekend is already ruined.
How was your day?
Nothing bad...
It's good to be a doctor ...
Come, Theo, be good.
I met Laura's mother.
- We talk about our lovers ... - Come ...
You're in love, right?
- We're still not married ... - Are you starting well ...
However, I have no hurry to become a grandmother.
She also told me about a new boy named Nathan.
- He said he was gay. - What does "gay"?
Eat your tomatoes.
- For parents ... - It should not be easy.
Have you talked to him?
No. Well, I greeted him.
Keep your distance.
Like a ring.
Ah, you did not see that coming.
- Without worries. - "Do not worry, do not worry."
I always hear that.
Keep going, that's good!
Keep going, Marco ...
What's wrong with you?
Do not touch me!
What did I do to you?
For! What's going on?
Do not touch me!
Get out for two minutes! Calm down!
You're good?
Come on!
Watch this! This is a scar!
I was attacked by a dog when he was young.
¡Basta, thrilling Nathan!
Gives you no shame? The girls locker room is over there!
Rather stay here; stare.
Come on, keep looking!
¡Nathan! ¡Nathan!
Hi. It is Nathan. Leave a message.
Nathan, called the school today, and they said they did not go to class.
I'm not going to punish, I just want to know where you are.
Please call me.
It's the police, do you hear me?
- Gentlemen. - Please.
A man escaped; She attacked him with a knife.
- His identity? - No documents.
Tango 2. Street Brodes speaks, there is a hurt.
Call the ambulance and also the criminal police.
I did run, this unfortunate.
He threw this.
Again with Marc and introduce yourself to the OPG.
- I stay with Patricia. - It's okay.
Hi. It is Nathan. Leave a message.
Nathan.
What's wrong?
Show me. Show me.
Show me.
What happened?
Tell me. Talk to me, I'm here.
Háblame, dime.
They beat me, Dad.
Calm down, I'm here now.
I'm here.
I'm here. I'm here.
It was I who took the photo.
Why did you do that?
He wanted reactions.
But I did not think I would go so far.
- Are you in love with him? - Do not!
So why did you kiss?
I did not do it. It was he who wanted.
Since coming to school, he fell in love with me.
He kept following me at that party.
The only way to get rid of it was to kiss him.
So I did.
But I'm not gay.
I do not care that guy. It's you I love.
I think.
Laura, you'll dine with us?
Stay, I'll be happy.
How's Nathan?
I did not want at all to go to school this morning.
He said if you are not going to ever return.
What are you going to do?
I do not know.
He does not want to get myself.
If you had seen what they did.
A parent who does not protect his son is not a parent.
Good Morning.
This is for me?
One year we're together. We must celebrate.
What's going on?
They're quiet today!
It nathan, what happened to you?
He fell, ma'am.
Nathan...
what happened to you?
I fell.
We are going now...
to finish working on ...
to finish working on probabilities.
No, I will not talk about probabilities.
I'll tell you about a girl ...
That girl was always at school with a horrible fear ...
and he went round and round to not see those who made fun of her,
why...
she liked girls more than boys.
And that girl may have less ashamed of herself,
if I had the good fortune to meet
someone like Nathan.
Someone as brave as him,
I dare say it's different.
It takes courage not to fool yourself ...
To support the gaze of others.
What is the courage of those who beat Nathan?
- Mrs? - Yes?
The girl of the speaker are you?
How would to calculate the probability that was me?
I do not know...
When a coin is thrown,
it might fall face, or you might fall cross.
We say that the probability of heads or tails,
is the half.
Get toss,
it's a problem.
Are not you going to lunch?
When I was your age,
I spent hours alone in the classroom.
Sometimes I feel I'm living that feeling again.
Hopefully never passes for that, Nathan.
You're the one who's right.
- Are you all right, Catherine? - I'm fine thanks.
Kiss Me.
Check it out!
¡Vamos, relaxation!
Get out of here. There's nothing to see!
What's going on with you?
The Times change.
I'm not scared ...
What if I kiss you now, in front of everyone?
- What's wrong with you? - Kiss Me...
- You're crazy, stop! - Kiss Me Now...
- For! - Come on, kiss me!
- Why are you doing this? - Kiss Me!
For!
For! There are people here!
- Are you afraid! - Leave me alone!
¡Piérdete!
If I let you, Louis.
I really leave.
What are you doing here?
¡Piérdete!
What's going on? Am I leading you?
Do not you're scaring me!
Also do not're scaring me!
The I'll face one by one!
I'm not scared!
What's going on? They are not saying anything!
Did I'm surprising?
It's because there are people around!
Are they afraid of being considered idiots?
Is that?
It is easy to hit someone in a quiet place.
But now...
In front of everyone...
Come!
Come, come!
They are idiots!
¡Nathan!
Hello...
- You are here. - Yes.
¿ "I will face one by one"?
I did not know what to say.
Let's move on.
Hi, this is Nathan. Leave a message.
Hi, I'm Louis. Call me back, please.
My parents come to lunch tomorrow.
The only time the weekend we're together,
and you are working.
I have a balance to deliver on Monday, that's all!
Oh no! Shit! It was turned off again!
I do not understand! I can not finish that sheet!
Use Computer Louis.
Are you crazy. It must be in his room.
Not here.
- You Have your password? - Do not...
Try "boxing" or "Laura".
- You know what the best? - Do not.
The name of the woman of my life!
He was not talking about you ...
Only for curiosity!
Since Nathan came, people just talked about it.
I went to forums to inform me!
That is all!
And gay porn sites? Also out of curiosity?
- I only went once! - You're lying, Louis!
We have reviewed your history.
I do not understand.
What about Laura?
I'm talking to you, Louis!
I know that these associations are allowed to interfere,
but I remind you that only depends on me,
decide not to invite or my institution.
And, as I told you,
Totally I'm against it!
Not think it is personal conviction.
You guys know that parents do not hesitate to come to that!
Listen, if Nathan has been hit,
it is also our fault for doing nothing.
It should not happen again,
under the pretext not to disturb some parents.
We are ready to launch a petition.
53 teachers working at the school,
47 said they are in favor of the coming of an association,
and they are ready to sign it.
And certainly a lot of parents sign too.
It's good, but you do not respond to parents.
What shall I say when we are accused of proselytizing?
To see the definition of proselytism
in the dictionary ...
We will avoid using that word again.
Homosexuality is not a doctrine ...
or a philosophy ...
It is not a lifestyle choice.
Put on gloves!
Do not you want to have a family?
I'm talking about a normal family!
You want to be sad all your life.
Is that so?
To live outside?
I'm lost, Dad.
"I'm lost, Dad."
You know why?!
You know?
Because in your little head, you know it's the wrong way.
It's not a fatality!
Do not let control for that shit!
This shit go!
I've tried, Dad ...
I swear I tried.
You've tried?!
Look at me when I talk to you!
Put on gloves!
Get ready!
Upload your guard!
Come on! Boxer!
You only have that? Come on! Boxer!
Come on! Get up!
You've tried?
¡Pásamelo!
Come on! Punch!
Come on! That is all?!
Come on!
You want to win that tournament?
Whatever you win!
Get up! Get up!
You'll still try again!
No more phone! No more Internet!
You agree in this, right?
You need to stay here. We must resolve this.
You need to go back to school.
I will make a certificate; You may be sick for a few days, right?
And it's not a lie, after all.
Do you think is the solution?
Would you still like it?
Do not? Then you have to stop and protect!
We have no right to let him ruin your life.
We need to show that he is wrong.
You need some time.
To realize. Some time, that's all.
I am sorry...
Do you trust me?
Yes I trust you.
I will go.
- Hello sir. - Hello Laura.
I come to see Louis.
No answer my messages, so I was worried.
It is normal, is in bed with a flu.
He has acute angina.
I can see?
You want you fall sick too?
Do not worry, your love will get well soon.
- I'll tell you spent here. - Thank my Lord. Bye.
I'm going!
You thought I forgot?
16 years!
We must celebrate it, right?
This is great!
Exceptionally!
Blows, eat the candles.
Blow!
If there is someone, I mean ...
If you want to invite some friends this weekend, I'll leave the floor.
It's okay...
Is Louis?
You need to explain to him someday.
I do not have anything more to do with that guy.
I'm not gay.
But Dad...
What? Come!
- Are you sure? - Yes I am!
This is my son Nathan ...
Hey, Nathan, I'm Serge.
I'm Marc. Nice to meet you.
I am delighted to meet you too.
Take a seat, welcome to the house.
It's a bit like our home here.
Well, what are you studying?
- I'm in second year. - For real?
I have a tip, do not stop studying.
Otherwise you risk ending up like us.
It's not that bad!
You also had your Gothic period when you were a teenager.
It's the same with me.
It was just to provoke.
All this is not true. I'm not gay.
This is silly, I know.
I know I've hurt you.
What about Laura?
It is because I love her, I understood all that.
What's going on?
It was just to provoke.
It was not true.
I am so sorry...
Let me call Laura.
Have you used your phone?
No...
¿No?
Are you sure?
I just wanted to call Laura.
Nathan...
Nathan.
And of course no Laura ...
Keep your phone back. Your computer also.
You can go see whoever you want.
But no longer worth you to lead us the word!
Have we're lying?
Are you treating us as if we were your enemies?
From now on, we're going to ignore!
¡Come, Theo!
- I do not like this. - Eat!
- Where are you going? - To bring the salad.
Will I eat alone all the time?
I have not done anything wrong.
I was forced to lie ...
It's so crazy ...
Mom, talk to me, please.
I'm going to change.
I swear I'll change.
But tell me, please ...
Mom, I can take some water?
You scared me!
- You were spying on me? - I thought you colapsarías.
I do not know if I will, this is too hard.
Do you think it's easy for me?
We need to hold on, it's just a matter of time.
- You're good? - Yes.
Follow?
Get out of here, Theo.
I want a hug.
Outside...
Stay away from your brother.
Follow!
I'll tell you a nice story.
Leave me alone! What you think?
You no longer exist for me!
What's going on?
I'm going. I will never home.
Tell me what happened!
My parents went crazy, they hate me ...
Is the photo?
You answer me, is the photo?
Are you really gay?
It's my fault?
Is it because I'm ugly?
Maybe I did not kiss well?
What should I do?
I need money, Laura.
You have to borrow some money.
- Dad! - What?
I need your help!
You do not have any idea where he might be?
I have no idea!
I need your help, concentrate.
Have you heard anything? Did you spot anything?
- I think I heard a train ... - A train?
Are you sure or think that?
- Are you sure or think that? - I'm sure!
Well, let the bridge.
And often it abandoned factory where we are.
Do you have a password?
Rubio, 16 years old.
Regular height.
I'll let you know.
Let's move on!
I am sorry!
Here we were!
Its over there! Stop!
Louis! Do not do that!
Leave me alone!
Stay away!
Louis, I just want to talk to you!
I have nothing to say!
There are people who love you.
Your brother,
your parents.
That's a lie!
Do not I exist for my parents!
As if it were crap, I hate!
Is not true...
Louis...
Look at me...
Give me your hand...
The greatest fear of my life ...
See you tomorrow, Serge. Thank you.
I'll take you home.
I can not go back with my parents.
You have to go home, Louis.
We can receive it for tonight ...
This can wait until tomorrow, right?
Here you have.
Nathan...
But I...
It's getting late. We all need rest.
I will go to see you.
Will you be okay, Louis?
I'll be fine.
If you need anything, tell me ...
I'm right next to you, right?
OK thanks.
I'm fine, I assure you.
Try to sleep...
Nathan...
I can not sleep.
Pass.
I was eight.
My grandparents used to come home.
Every time looked at me in a strange way.
I understood that I would never be like other kids.
I did not want my parents are ashamed of me.
I pushed myself.
I became paranoid.
When I went out with Laura, my parents were calm.
Then you came along.
This is a new student. His name is Nathan,
and I hope they get it very well.
It was the first time I felt something.
We continue the lesson about the author of "I Have a Dream".
I was very shy.
I did not know where to go.
I thought the shot would.
No...
What are you doing?
It's your scent!
When I saw love, together,
I had a strange feeling.
I felt a bit silly.
I thought I could have warned me, Nathan.
I do not know, go in stages. Slowly.
It's getting late, I go!
I hope I have awakened Chloé ...
Not here. He is with his father.
Good...
Stay...
- Good Morning. - Good Morning.
- You go? - Yes!
- Then I'll see you later ... - See you.
What will we do at work?
I do not know.
- I do not care. - Yes!
Hello Dad!
Good Morning.
You must have noticed ...
Do not bother yourself.
Y?
- You guys...? - Do not.
I knew that someday he would discuss it with you.
Even I made a little speech for the occasion.
Honestly, I thought it would be with a girl.
What you have told me?
I guess I would have said about my first time.
It was in school ...
We had scared too!
We took our time.
And the first time was magical, because we were in love.
It also functions as speech.
Yes I think so!
- Good Morning. - Good Morning.
- Help yourself to whatever you want, Louis. - Thank my Lord.
Stéphane call me.
- Stéphane? - Yes.
When are you going to call my parents?
It's done.
I talked to your mother. We had a chat.
It must be her. She's coming to get you.
Yes?
I am the father of Louis. Tell him I'm waiting.
Come for a minute!
No. Let my son come immediately!
Where is Louis?
Can we talk for a moment?
I do not see any utility. Where is my son?
Have you told his wife what he was doing last night?
Listen, I know what he has done,
and I am very grateful,
but now this is no longer your business, okay?
Louis told me what's going on at home.
And that?
You want to show me how to raise my child?
No...
I know what you are feeling; I was very angry too.
If Louis does not arrive in a minute, this will be bad for you.
I do not want your father has problems.
Are not you going back there?
I'm fine.
I feel strong now.
Thanks for everything, Stéphane.
I locked him in his room.
You know what he tried to do last night?
Because I'm aware of that, so I shut up.
Just to avoid any wrong thing to do.
Give me the key, I see it.
Not the right time, Corinne. Make things worse.
Are you crazy? Give me the key!
I have few queries. I'll be back in two hours.
The two we shall see, okay?
Corinne,
do you trust me?
Do you trust me, yes or no?
Hello?
No, I'm retired, but I listen.
Yes, call my name ...
Wait, I have his number on my agenda.
Hold the line, please.
Can I call you back?
¿Louis?
What?
I'll break the door!
I am sorry! I am sorry!
- Hello. - Hey, is my husband?
No, it's under review right now.
Good.
Goodbye, ma'am.
What are you doing here?
We need to talk.
- Can not this wait? - Do not.
What's going on?
Did you leave Luis alone?
I refuse you to continue mistreating.
!? Mistreating ?!
What are you saying?
I love my son like you. I just want to protect.
It is gay is because he wanted to commit suicide.
No, it is because we reject it;
because we did think it was abnormal.
I really feel guilty,
and if Nathan and his father had not been there ...
Wait...
Did that police brainwashed you?
We need change, not he, do you understand?
What are you talking about?
I do not know ...
- Corinne? - I'm leaving you.
I'm with the kids. I set it up at my parents' house.
And let things clear:
If you do something to stop me,
I will submit a complaint of abuse.
Think about your patients, your reputation.
- What's going on? - Nothing, come on.
How's your new school?
I do not know, I'll start tomorrow.
I've seen your email.
It is almost a novel you've written me.
I know, but I had to because it did not respond to texts.
You hurt me, you know?
I know...
You know, I will return to the boxing tournament.
Excellent...
You're going to be there?
I do not know...
So is it true ?, Do you think I'm beautiful?
Very beautiful.
Pity I'm not bisexual!
You are a bastard!
Are you there?
I need to go, but we will contact you later.
Wait, I wanted to tell you something.
I spoke with Corinne the phone before ...
And that?
He found an apartment; come this weekend.
I know...
Espera ... Detente ...
One second...
It is rare to have a physically handicapped father.
Diminished?
The last thing gets in the car!
What are you thinking?
I do not know if I did well to come.
Are you angry with me?
Maybe it was not the best question ...
You know,
It was not against you.
I mean...
It was not to hurt you.
I do not know what to say...
I'm not mad at you.
This is weird, right?
You love him?
It was not made for me ...
Here it is.
I missed you.
I can not believe that!
I can believe that! I think they are lovely.
What's going on?
- Where is your son? - He's coming.
- We are ready. - What will we do?
It's okay.
It is not Louis with you?
I do not know what's wrong, no longer he wants to box.
What's going on? Is there a problem?
I no longer want to box.
I thought I could beat him ...
But no...
What is the real reason?
It is you who should be there.
Who is going to box, you or your father?
If you do not want to go, nobody will bother.
You go home and over.
But no regrets.
Think quickly, because they are waiting ...
Could you help them?
Forget all that now ...
Breathe, think of your struggle.
That's.
All right? Let's move on.
Well, no blows to the head.
Have a good fight.
Arise, Louis!
End of the first round.
What have I told you?
Stay on guard!
Are you listening to me?
Come on, Louis!
Is brave.
Louis wins the second round ...
Have you seen my watch?
I've really progressed, right?
It is thanks to you ...
Are you coming to celebrate with us?
Stay, Dad ...
Are not you proud of me?
It will take longer.
Come on, we are waiting ...
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org