Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Ain't workin' out
for y'all, huh?
Mars is the god
of war, right?
- Planet, too.
- I know it's a planet.
But the clue is
"Greek god of war."
"Ares."
Greeks called him
Ares.
Same dude,
different name is all.
"Ares" fits.
Thanks.
It's all good.
See, back in
middle school and all,
I used to love them myths.
That stuff was deep.
Truly.
You're up.
Nathan:
State calls Omar Little,
Your Honor.
Faggot.
Bailiff:
Do you solemnly swear
to tell the truth,
the whole truth and nothing
but the truth, so help you God?
I surely do.
State your name
for the record.
Omar Devon Little.
Mr. Little,
how old are you?
About 29,
thereabout.
And where
do you live?
No place in
particular, ma'am.
You're homeless?
In the wind,
so to speak.
And what is
your occupation?
Occupation?
What exactly do you do
for a living, Mr. Little?
I rip and run.
You...
I robs drug dealers.
( spectators murmuring )
And exactly
how long
has this been
your occupation,
Mr. Little?
I don't know, exactly.
I venture to say maybe
about eight or nine years.
Mr. Little, how does
a man rob drug dealers
for eight or nine years
and live to tell about it?
Day at a time,
I suppose.
( theme music playing )
* When you walk
through the garden *
* You gotta
watch your back *
* Well, I beg
your pardon *
* Walk the straight
and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus
* He's gonna
save your soul *
* You gotta
keep the devil *
* Way down
in the hole *
* He's got the fire
and the fury *
* At his command
* Well, you don't
have to worry *
* If you hold onto
Jesus' hand *
* We'll all be safe
from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls
* We just gotta
keep the devil *
* Way down
in the hole... *
- ( siren wails )
- ( glass cracks )
* Down in the hole
* You gotta help me
keep the devil *
* Down in the hole.
What do we know?
On Sobotka,
very little.
He seems to live
within his means.
House in Glen Burnie,
paid-off truck,
modest savings,
credit history
is okay.
There's no flash to him,
nothing dramatic.
Doesn't sound much
like a money man to me.
Or maybe
he's hiding it.
The union is also
a little threadbare.
They paid the taxes on
Union Hall almost a year late
and that was only after
they got hit with liens.
Looking at
their books...
- You subpoenaed their books?
- You don't need to.
I.B.S. books are open
to the Justice Department
under the terms of
a federal racketeering case
that came out of New York
five years ago.
We just called Washington,
they sent us a copy
of everything
the Baltimore locals
have filed.
The books show that there's
less than 100 checkers
still paying dues
to 15-14.
And that's down from
about 300 in the '70s.
They're hurting.
So where's all this money
that Valchek is talkin' about?
The I.B.S. hired
Bruce DiBiago to lobby
Annapolis this session.
And through
individual officers
and union members,
they've paid about
70,000 to various PACs
and Democratic organizations
in the last eight months.
They show any of that
on their books?
No, we pieced that together
from the campaign finance
reports.
And that's just what was in
the names of the union officers
that we cross-referenced.
So, where's the cash
coming from?
Drugs?
So far, D.N.R.'s
on the union hall phones
don't show much.
Union business
and personal calls,
but no beepers.
And not much
in the way of cell numbers
or payphones either.
What's with those hand-to-hands,
anything connect?
We're buyin' from
a lotta white boys.
O'Donnell Heights, Greektown,
Highlandtown above the park.
But any port connections
feel random.
Well, the money
comes from somewhere.
Maybe it's what
the checkers do.
I mean, they monitor what
comes in and out of the port.
That's what they do,
that's their value.
They're bringing
the shit in?
Or they're
letting it happen.
Like that can
full of dead girls.
They kept that
outta the computer.
Daniels:
Which is why
we're gonna quietly
do some work
on that side of things.
Kima, Prez,
I want you to start
lookin' at girls.
No problem.
If they're coming
into Baltimore,
who's workin' them?
Are they club dancing,
whoring?
We need to plug
into that circuit.
As for the rest of you,
Lester is gonna stay
with the paper trail
and with the D.N.R.'s,
looking for connections
to the union money.
Herc and Carver,
you guys keep workin'
the drug corners
near the port.
Officer Russell here
and Bunk Moreland are
assigned to Homicide,
but for the time being
they'll be with us,
running the port database
through a computer,
looking for any pattern
involving contraband.
Questions?
Excuse me?
- I'm Thomas.
- Beadie.
Would you like to go
to Royal Farms,
maybe get
a cup of coffee?
Right.
Yo.
"I'm Thomas.
You want
a coffee?"
Hey, listen, I was gonna
ask her for her panties
to make some soup with,
but I was afraid
she'd take it the wrong way.
Nathan:
So you're saying you
were at the opposite end
of the parking lot when
the assailant drew his gun?
Little:
Thereabout.
And do you see the gunman
who killed Mr. Gant
anywhere in
the courtroom today?
Hey, yo,
what up, Bird?
Nathan:
For the record,
you are identifying
the defendant,
Marquis Hilton.
It's just
"Bird" to me.
And Mr. Little,
you had seen him many
times before, had you not?
Yeah, we jailed together
down the cut--
Objection, Your Honor.
May we approach?
Quite a witness,
ain't he?
Word on the street
is Omar ain't
nowhere near them rises
when the shit pop.
Street said
little cocksucker
was on the east side,
stickin' up some
Ashland Avenue niggers.
That's the word
on the street, huh?
Trouble is, String,
we ain't on the street.
We in
a court of law.
Your Honor--
Objection is noted
and preserved for the record,
Mr. Levy. Move on.
Thank you,
Your Honor.
Jurors will disregard that
last comment from the witness,
in which he explained
where he had last
encountered the defendant.
Yes or no,
Mr. Little?
Prior to the shooting,
did you know the defendant?
I mean,
I knew the man,
but wasn't like he was
no friend or nothin'.
So you would have
no trouble recognizing him
from a moderate
distance,
say 20, 25 yards,
in daylight?
Aw, naw,
no problem.
Mr. Little,
do you recognize
this particular
weapon?
Yeah, that's Bird's gun,
the 380.
- You've seen it before?
- Bird always flashin'
that thing.
So you'd actually seen it
before the day in question.
And on the day
in question?
It was in
Bird's hand.
When he shot
at Mr. Gant?
Yes, ma'am.
Bird covet them
shiny little pistols.
Objection,
Your Honor.
And the boy too triflin'
to throw it off
even after
a daytime murder.
You're a lyin'
cocksucker, man!
I'll rip your heart out
your goddamn chest.
Judge:
The defendant
will regain control
or he will be
forcibly restrained
and I will
clear the court.
The witness's last answer
is to be stricken
and disregarded
by the jury.
Niko.
Eton is
my friend.
It's good to have
friends meet, no?
Eton, huh?
That's from the Greek,
meanin' what?
No Greek.
Israeli.
Oh, yeah?
'Cause you look Greek.
I mean, no offense.
- Either way, I mean.
- ( chuckles )
You have
the chemicals?
I can get 'em,
as much as you want.
When?
I was gonna do
something this week,
but there's been
a problem though.
What problem?
My cousin, Ziggy.
He got into a beef with
these East Baltimore guys.
Drug dealer by the name
of Cheese took his car,
burned it,
now he's sayin'
he's gonna dust Zig
if he doesn't pay.
( speaking Greek )
Yeah, "malaka,"
right.
Zig fucked up
the package.
So, you bring us
the chemicals, we pay.
Then you
pay your debt.
It was $2,700,
right?
Now, this asshole
is sayin' it's double.
54, you believe that?
First he takes
the car,
and now he's jackin' us
around on the money.
You want,
we kill him.
No.
That ain't it
either, no.
Why not?
'Cause first of all,
Zig fucked it up.
He owes 27.
And second,
you kill Cheese
and we're
gonna have a fight
with his people, right?
A year down the road,
some nigger sees my cousin
comin' out
the burger shop,
puttin' gas in his car
on Central Avenue--
no questions,
puts a cap in his ass.
He's smart, eh?
Niko, smart.
Look...
we don't have the muscle
to go talk to this guy,
make things right.
I was hoping
maybe you do.
Mr. Little...
can I ask why you came
forward in this case?
I told the police
what I know.
Were you offered
anything in exchange?
Like what?
Were you arrested?
Were you going to be
charged with a crime
and by testifying,
did the police agree
to drop those charges?
Naw, man, it ain't
even about that.
How many times have
you been arrested
as an adult,
Mr. Little?
Shoot, I done
lost count.
Enough though not
to take it personal.
Possession
of a handgun,
possessing
a concealed weapon,
assault by pointing,
robbery, deadly weapon,
possession of
a handgun again,
followed by violation
of parole on weapon charges,
followed by one count
of attempted murder
and use of a handgun
in commission of a felony.
That wasn't
no attempt murder.
What was it,
Mr. Little?
I shot the boy Mike-Mike
in his hindparts, that all.
( jury chuckling )
Fixed it so he
couldn't sit right.
Why'd you shoot
Mike-Mike in his...
his hindparts,
Mr. Little?
Let's say we had
a disagreement.
A disagreement
over...?
Well, you see, Mike-Mike
thought he should keep
that cocaine
he was slinging,
and the money he was
makin' from slingin' it.
I thought otherwise.
So you rob
drug dealers.
This is what you do?
Yes, sir.
You walk the streets
of Baltimore, with a gun,
taking what you want,
when you want it,
willing to use violence
when your demands aren't met.
This is
who you are.
Why should we believe
your testimony then?
Why believe
anything you say?
That's up to y'all,
really.
You say you aren't
here testifying against
the defendant
because of any deal
you made with police.
True that.
That you are here because
you want to tell the truth
about what happened
to Mr. Gant
in that housing project
parking lot.
Yep.
When in fact you
are exactly the kind
of person who would,
if you felt
you needed to,
shoot a man down
on a housing project
parking lot,
and then lie to the police
about it, would you not?
Hey, look, I ain't never
put my gun on no citizen.
You are amoral,
are you not?
You are feeding
off the violence
and the despair
of the drug trade.
You're stealing from
those who themselves
are stealing
the lifeblood
from our city.
You are a parasite
who leeches off...
- Just like you, man.
- ...the culture of drugs--
excuse me, what...?
I got the shotgun.
You got
the briefcase.
It's all in the game,
though, right?
And with the economy
what it is,
you can really consider
coming in 10 or 20%
below asking and
still feel competitive.
Even on the Hamburg Street.
address?
Absolutely.
Woman:
I have to admit,
I like the house at 1501,
although I didn't like
the color of the whirlpool tub
in the master suite
bathroom.
- Magenta?
- Oh, that's cosmetic.
If they want
to make the sale,
they should at least
have some amount of couth
to change the color.
I know it's such
a tiny point to harp on.
Well...
Maybe you're right.
Maybe we should
just keep looking.
We shouldn't settle
for just anything.
And you think
there'll be some
new open houses
this Sunday?
I'm sorry,
what were you saying?
We think we're
gonna keep looking.
You'll take us around
again on Sunday?
Oh, definitely.
Okay then,
see you Sunday, early.
Great.
( phone ringing )
Elena:
Thank you.
I'll see you then.
You are a child,
you know that?
What do you want?
Dinner
and a movie.
C'mon, stop it.
- Why not?
- This isn't going
anywhere, Jimmy.
Dinner and a movie.
Then I'll walk you
to the door,
you shake my hand
and tell me to go
fuck myself,
like you should've
done way back when.
How 'bout I tell you to
fuck yourself here and now
and then you can save
that money for someone else?
Come on, Elena.
Come on, I signed
all your damn papers.
Gimme another shot.
Friday.
You pay
for the sitter.
So how that
D.C. game, man?
Same as it ever was.
Chocolate City.
I ain't been there
in a while.
Call it "Drama City"
nowadays.
Otherwise,
same ol' go-go,
same ol' bamas.
Same soup,
just reheated,
know what I'm sayin'?
If you need anything
to make this happen,
you gotta get it
yourself.
I can't go
through my people.
If Stringer Bell
reachin' all the way
past Baltimore
with this kinda work,
then we got a real mystery
going on, don't we?
Don't worry,
no mistakes.
Nothin' that might
come back on ya.
You sure of
your people?
My cousin up in there,
he on it.
All right.
I can't stand that
go-go shit, anyhow.
Ain't heard it
live, then.
I know a club in Oxen Hill
that would wreck y'all.
A'ight.
If I'm 'round the way.
So, how you doin'?
Nursing school,
right now.
Good, that's good.
Lester's been
pushing me, you know.
He does it kinda
without you knowin'
that he's doin' it.
Yeah, I know
what you mean.
So anyway, he said
that you would be by today
to talk about
the clubs.
About some girls,
Russian.
Or from that part
of the world.
The ones on
the circuit, yeah.
You should try this place
called "Nightshift" down
off of Holabird.
I have a friend
who works there
and she worked with a bunch
of Russian girls last year
- for about three months.
- Think she'll talk to me?
Only if I ask her.
Thank you, Detective,
nothing further.
Anything more on redirect,
Ms. Nathan?
No, Your Honor.
Let's take 10 minutes and then
run the closing arguments.
I have every intention
of beginning tomorrow
with jury instructions.
( raps )
How'd Omar do?
- You didn't see it?
- Not the cross.
That bad?
- ( thumps )
- ( rap music playing )
You have no problem.
Nick:
No?
To start, he wants you
to pay 54.
Then we talk.
He says no, you pay
just the 27.
Yeah, I saw
how you "talked."
But you will not
pay the 27.
Instead you will get
the money for the car
that burned.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Him, we don't know.
But the one
he calls boss...
him we know.
( TV tuning )
You gonna sit there
and pout?
I know you don't think
I'm going down to that club
just to look at pussy.
I know you know me
better than that.
I ain't even lookin'.
Everybody's lookin'.
Most of them
women are dykes.
Cheryl,
it's police work.
What, so that's supposed
to make me feel better?
Kima's out on the street,
doin' her detective thing?
All that hospital shit,
all that rehab,
all them promises--
- We talked about this.
- No, you talked.
I didn't get
a word in edgewise
once you made up your mind.
( TV off )
Where you goin'?
With you.
- Excuse me?
- Who knows?
I might see
a little something
I happen to like.
So all of that's
on the table?
Right now, there's money
in the transpo budget
for the grain pier.
Also, a bond issue that pays
for maintenance dredging
on the main
shipping channel.
- Ott: But not the canal?
- Nope, not the canal.
For that we're gonna have
to fight a little longer
- and dig a little deeper.
- So says Frank.
I gotta say
for my money,
we lucky if we pull
out the grain pier.
Be that as it may,
we spent the money
and took our best shot.
Hired a couple lobbyists,
made some smart contributions,
paid for a consultant's
report to argue
against some of
the environmental stuff.
It cost, but we're
startin' to see it.
So where y'all find
the cash?
I been robbin'
liquor stores, two a week.
- ( laughing )
- Seriously.
Seriously,
we got some help from
the national office on this,
and there been
some timely donations
from a few friends
here and there.
The point is,
at the very least,
we're likely
to see the grain pier
back up by next year,
which means maybe
a couple hundred
more ships a year,
at least.
- If...
- And it's a big
fuckin' if...
If that Polack
motherfucker--
Whoa, whoa!
Hey, hey, hey,
no offense.
If Krawczyk don't
fuck us by throwin' up
waterfront condominiums
first, right?
Nat's right.
The back door threat
is that Andy Kraw
or some other developer
gets enough last-minute votes
to sink the rehab money
for the grain pier.
'Cause those guys are lookin'
at that location, too.
So we need everybody
makin' phone calls,
let your legislators know
that we watching on this.
The money only goes so far.
Now, we gotta make some
noise, right?
- Make some noise!
- Frank: Okay, enough talk.
Some of you's got ships
to work in the morning.
The rest of you's
need to be drunk.
I'll drink to that.
"Help from the
national office," huh?
"Timely donations
from friends"?
Watch your ass, Frank.
- This is it?
- Uh, yeah.
Bunk:
Just picked it up from
the port administrator.
So what am I
looking at?
The Atlantic Light
on the day the can
with the women
was off-loaded.
The boxes
are containers.
This one's being off-loaded
and set on a chassis.
Here's the time--
10:31 hours.
See?
It was moved to lane "L",
stack six, row three,
by an R.T.G.
at 10:37 hours.
- "R.T.G."?
- Rubber tire gantry.
So from ship to stack
took six minutes.
That's the way it's
supposed to work, but...
A-Q-Q-Z, as in zebra,
three, nine,
six, five...
nine, four.
Check digit, seven.
Bunk:
That's the container number of
the can with the women in it.
See that?
It was never entered
by the checker.
So as far as
the computer is concerned,
it no longer exists.
Sobotka says that
that can happen
when the radio waves
get knocked down
or when a checker inputs
a bad serial number.
Russell:
It came off the Atlantic Light
at 11:26 hours.
And doesn't show up
in the computer again
until 15:12 hours.
I find it
two hours after that.
So for nearly four hours
it's out on the docks,
unaccounted for.
Sobotka says cans
get lost all the time.
When they get found,
they get put back
into the computer.
- You believe him?
- Humph.
No, not this can.
So what's the plan?
The database on this computer
has records for every ship
that berthed at Patapsco
over the last two years.
We gotta go back through
and find what other cans
might've disappeared
like that.
See if there's
a pattern.
How many ships
we talking about?
Hundreds.
It ain't like I got
a prayer of bringin' this
case in otherwise.
( music playing )
- Kima: That's what
I'm talkin' about.
- Cheryl: All right.
- What the hell
is your problem?
- Prez: Nothin'.
Yeah? You look like
you about to be sick
or somethin'.
I just can't
look at 'em.
Prez, you ain't never
been to a titty bar?
Yeah, sure.
But not with women.
You're sure you're not
gonna have a problem
for talkin' to us here?
I don't give a shit.
You friends
with Shardene,
all that matters.
'Sides, I'm from Westport,
and I told them club owners
straight-up, I was here
before them ho's got here,
and they better make sure
I'm here after they leave.
So how long ago
did they come through?
Six months back
was the last batch.
Russians, I think.
But shit all
sound the same
when you
can't understand
a damn word, right?
Who brought 'em?
Club owner pays
extra for 'em.
There was a woman--
she was like the madam,
who handled the cash.
But I ain't get
a name.
She Russian, too?
She was somethin'.
She had an accent.
So it's like, one day,
all Baltimore girls
are at the bar,
and the next, what?
- All foreign girls?
- Mm-hmm. That 'bout right.
They was makin' so much money
with them new girls
they start lettin' some
of their regular dancers go.
Not me, 'cause, I mean,
I got clientele here.
But some of the others.
Where'd the girls stay?
Where they told.
Shit, they ain't here
legally.
They don't know shit.
They ain't got no family.
The men
they got handlin' them
are always with 'em.
Right there to take
them from whatever
motel they using
to the club and back.
Right there when
they need to go get food,
or go to
the Rite Aid.
Right outside
the fuckin' motel door,
when they up there
in the motel rooms
with the johns.
Anyone try
to get away?
Shit, I seen one
of 'em get lit up
with one of
them stun guns
just for going
down the block
to get some dinner.
I mean, they barely
let them girls
go to the bathroom
by themselves.
And if they see one gettin'
too close to the johns,
that's when they move
the whole crew to another
town, you know?
Keep it so they don't
get no help.
You up after
the next song.
Push my numbers then.
I gotta go
get paid, honey.
You need anything else,
you can call me.
Help if I can.
I'll tell Shardene
you said hi.
Ooh, she must be
doin' good, huh,
to be out
for so long?
She must've landed
a rich one, right?
You her girl?
Yeah.
Hm. I wouldn't
let mine come in here
either without me.
These bitches in here,
are no joke.
( faint voices
overlapping )
( voices stop )
( crackling )
( flushing )
( printer whirring )
( yawns )
13 of 'em.
They had about
a third of that space,
hidden behind
the fake wall.
A few flashlights,
some junk food, some water.
A portable toilet
they had to share.
And not enough air.
Judge:
I'm going to schedule
sentencing
for the third
week of next month.
Anything else today?
Your Honor, my client,
having preserved
the necessary grounds
for appeal in the record,
wishes me to state
unequivocally
that regardless
of this jury's verdict,
he is the victim
of wholesale perjury
on the part of
the state's key witness.
And we ask that
an appeal bond be set
so that he can participate
fully in this investigation.
An appeal bond on a conviction
of first-degree murder?
- Mr. Levy, get
a grip on yourself.
- Your Honor--
Not only will there be
no bond pending sentencing,
but as far as
I'm concerned,
the pre-sentencing report
is a mere formality.
Mr. Hilton
has been found guilty
of killing
a state's witness
who testified
in this very courtroom.
He did so in cold blood
and for pay.
Unless the pre-sentence
report indicates that
he is, in fact,
the Messiah come again,
he will very likely be
sentenced to life, no parole,
by a Baltimore judge
who for once in his life
gets to leave his office
feeling that his job
actually matters.
Mr. Hilton, are you
the second coming
of our Savior?
Excuse me?
Are you Jesus Christ
come back to earth?
- Um...
- ( raps )
See you
at sentencing.
Was it good
for you, too?
- ( chuckling )
- Mr. Little,
this is good
to get-out-of-jail-free,
one time only,
on anything up to
aggravated assault.
- Why, thank you, ma'am.
- No, thank you.
A rare pleasure.
Now for the
ceremonial eyefuck.
Come see me down the cut,
you punk-ass snitch.
I'll shove a shiv down
your cocksuckin' throat.
You think
on it, Bird.
You think on Brandon while you
doin' that time, you heard?
I'm gonna see you, man,
I swear to God!
Bird:
Fuck that, I'll
do you like a dog!
You really see him
shoot the man?
You really asking?
But it's fucked
because the man got
to where he needed to be
and she wasn't even worth it.
Daisy wasn't nothin'
past any other bitch
anywhere, you know?
And he did
all that for her
and in the end,
it ain't amount to shit.
Fitzgerald said that
there were no second acts
in American lives.
Do you believe that?
Man, shit,
we locked up.
We best not believe
that, right?
He's sayin' that the past
is always with us.
And where we come from,
what we go through,
how we go through it,
all that shit matters.
I mean, that's what
I thought he meant.
Go ahead.
Like at the end
of the book, you know?
Boats and tides
and all.
It's like you can
change up, right?
You can say
you somebody new,
you can give yourself
a whole new story,
but what came first
is who you really are,
and what happened before
is what really happened.
And it don't matter that
some fool say he different
'cause the only thing
that can make you different
is what you really do
or what you really go through.
Like, you know, like
all them books in his library.
Now, he frontin'
with all them books,
but if we pull one
down off the shelf,
ain't none of the pages
ever been opened.
He got all them books
and he ain't read
nary one of 'em.
Gatsby, he was who he was
and he did what he did
and 'cause he wasn't ready
to get real with the story...
that shit
caught up to him.
I think, anyway.
( ball thumps )
( phone ringing )
( modem beeping )
( ball thumps )
Sorry, homie.
You done with
your trial?
All right then,
let's take 'er on out.
Tomorrow.
I'm back with you
tomorrow, Diggsy.
You got something
else to do today?
Yeah, last bit
of business.
This is
your business.
Nah, this is
retirement.
And after today,
I'm retired.
( motor rumbles )
Serge:
Talk when I say,
not before.
( music playing )
Tovarisch.
Serge,
my nigga.
- ( chuckles )
- You're losing weight.
- Shit.
- You are down
to nothing,
and in this country,
supermarkets are
cathedrals.
I worry
for you, buddy.
- How your peoples, dawg?
- Same, good.
You talk to the man about
that other thing, right?
Because I can get
behind that business
in a big way.
We will talk, later.
Now, another business.
Right, right.
This the man with
the raggedy-ass Camaro?
Wasn't mine,
it was my cousin's.
It wasn't all
that raggedy.
Sorry.
Nicky is with us.
His cousin--
- but family
cannot be helped.
- Who you tellin'?
I got motherfuckin'
nephews and in-laws
fuckin' all my shit up,
all the time.
And it ain't like I can
pop a cap in their ass
and not hear about it
Thanksgiving time.
For real, I'm livin' life
with some burdensome niggers.
So what the fuck?
You ain't paid
my boy Cheese
and Cheese ain't
payin' me, right?
I ain't talkin'
about all the money
in the world,
but it ain't like
Cheese be in a position
out on that corner
to let your cuz
exemplify shit,
you feel?
The man cut you
some slack
and soon every fuckin'-up
white boy be on his titty.
We wanna pay
what we owe.
The 27, anyway.
And we're
gonna have it,
soon enough.
Your man doubled it,
though.
He also
burned the car.
Now the Blue Book
on that Camaro was 51.
Now let me understand.
You gonna come up in here,
havin' fucked up a package,
askin' me to tell Cheese,
who you fucked it up on,
to pay you out 2,400.
He gets to keep
the Camaro.
Just how good a friend is
this motherfucker to y'all?
The Cheese ain't gonna be
happy havin' to pay me back,
so I would advise y'all
to give him some distance.
Just so he don't
come back on my cousin.
Anyway, thanks for
bein' straight on this.
Fool, if it wasn't
for Serge here,
you and your cuz both
would be cadaverous
motherfuckers.
I went through I.N.S.,
Customs, even the State
Department.
There was nothing.
It's time, Jimmy.
You did what
you could, right?
Yeah, fuck it,
let her go.
This one to the anatomy
board in the morning.
Jane Doe
on the paperwork.
Ain't right, Doc.
What the fuck
ever is?
You leave it
to Avon,
he's gonna get some years
off your sentence.
No doubt,
knowin' Avon.
It's all good, Dee.
Just show up and say
what Levy tells you to.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
- I'm asking you.
- Those hot shots...
that was Avon.
I want you home, Dee.
You asked me
to carry this.
I'm carryin' it.
This is mine,
right here, right now.
Boy, you ain't
listenin' to me.
- I am tellin' you--
- Ma!
Ma, remember we used
to live on Linden Avenue?
Remember
that house?
I was about six,
seven years old.
I was playin'
on the porch.
Them twins came by,
started pickin' on me,
messin' with me.
Remember that?
I'm bangin' on the door,
tryin' to get inside
and you standin'
right there
to open the door.
'Cept you ain't
lettin' me inside.
You told me to go back
out there and fight 'em,
whether I lose or not.
Remember?
They beat the shit
out of you.
Yeah.
Then you say to me,
"Boy, I might've brung you
into this world,
but you the one who
gonna have to live in it."
Well, Ma,
I'm still here.
Me.
You gotta let me live
like I need to live.
You tell Avon,
Stringer and Donette,
all of 'em--
to leave me be.
( man speaking on P.A. )
( ball thumps )
All right, look,
fuck y'all.
I need a drink.
Russell:
C'mon, we're almost
through 2002.
Naw.
Tomorrow is another
goddamn day, right?
Yeah.
( thumps )
They look thirsty,
a round on me.
Young Mr. Sobotka,
friend of the workin' man,
master of the game.
How many votes we get down
in Annapolis tonight, Frankie?
Been here long?
Since my hair
was brown.
I was tellin'
Chess about Benny.
- Benny with the harelip?
- That's a good one.
See Benny was working the hole
and he got hit with a shackle.
Chunk of steel clocked him good,
but he didn't tell nobody.
Not till
he came in here.
That's when Little Nose
told Benny to call
the union lawyer.
- Paul Sevel.
- Yeah.
- God rest his soul.
- So Benny calls Paul.
"Me been 'it wit
a 'ackerel," Benny says.
"A mackerel, Benny?
You working frozen foods
again?" Paul says.
"No, 'ot'amit.
A 'ackerel."
Then he slams
the phone down.
"'udder'ucker on
'is way over 'ere,
says he don't
udder'tan' me."
Little Nose says,
"Why he'd wanna do that?
Benny don't talk
no fuckin' better
in person."
( laughing )
So that's it?
Me and Cheese are straight?
Yeah, you're straight.
And that there's
$2,400 for Princess.
She was worth
more than that.
Hey, Dolo.
One for the bar, hon.
You win the lotto?
Hey, if my
old man can do it,
who the hell says I can't?
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
Nick, when I'm flush,
I'm flush.
We ain't gonna
live forever, right?
Next round's on me.
Not for me,
I'm gonna head out.
Aw, come on, Frank,
belly up.
Take a rain check.
And that one
as well, huh?
Makes 22.
All on the
Talco line.
All with
Horseface Pakusa
working the ship.
We're on it, then.
You gonna call Bunk?
Eh, Detective Moreland
is indisposed.
You with Daniels
and them?
Naw.
We just parked
the computer down there.
- We're orphaned, man.
- Orphaned?
Yeah.
Rawls is talkin' like
if I don't come home
with 14 clearances,
I can't
come home at all.
Lester too.
Where's
the love, Jimmy?
Where is
the motherfuckin' love?
Whoa, man.
Hey, hey--
Bam!
( laughing )
Yeah.
So what's up
with you, man?
Nothin'!
Nothin', huh?
I'm done, Bunk.
Bird was my last piece
of old business.
I got nothing new.
I was tryin' for
an I.D. on this one...
but I can't even
tell you why.
Just a way
to pretend I was still
a murder police, I guess.
Who gives
a fuck, right?
Oh!
Elena and I are
gonna try again.
Oh! Oh, shit.
Yeah.
I'm done fuckin'
myself up, Bunk.
I am done.
( sighs, moans )
Come on, man,
let's go home.
All right, man.
( faint music playing )
Over here, shitbird.
What the hell
happened to you?
I fell down.
How many times?
Let's walk.
- Pop, I'm--
- Walk with me, Zig.
Votes break for us,
that pier comes back
online by next spring.
More ships,
more work.
Yeah, great.
The fuck
are you about?
What?
Is that my son
lightin' hundred dollar
bills like an asshole,
in a bar full
of workin' stiffs?
What the fuck
is that?
- Ziggy: Just a smile.
- A smile?
Yep, a smile.
( sighs )
You wanna hit me again,
Pop, go ahead.
Take a shot.
Where you come by
that kinda cash?
You know you ain't
had the days.
Oh, definitely not.
It's 'cause my father's
in the union.
Fuck that.
Seniority
prevails, Zig.
It's the only way
to keep it halfway honest.
I know,
I ain't complainin'.
I wish I could
give you more.
You don't think
I want to throw
you more?
Oh, you throw plenty.
It's just,
Christ, Zig.
Maybe if I'd listened
to your mother
- 'cause she's the one
always talkin' about...
- Pop, it's cool.
...you should do
the community college
like your brother.
Pop, Pop, don't.
You wanna know
what I remember?
Do you?
I remember you,
and Uncle Jerry,
and Uncle Walt,
Pe-Pop...
all sittin' around
the kitchen table
talkin' shit about
this gang and that gang.
Who's better
with the breakbulk.
Who could turn it around
faster, who's lazy.
Always a fucking
argument, right?
Four Polacks,
six opinions.
I remember
when you's all went
down to picket them scabs
at Covington piers,
how Jackie Taylor got
run over by the police car
in the middle of that
whole goddamn mess.
I remember
when the Paceco fell
durin' that windstorm.
You remember, right?
Killed Fat Rick dead.
Yeah? What else
you remember?
Everything,
everything.
So tell me,
"Mr. Back-in-the-day,"
what the fuck are we doing
down here with the wharf rats
in the middle
of the goddamn night?
Beats the fuck
outta me.
Russell:
Every one of those
Post-Its is a can
that disappears
when it's being offloaded.
The yellow slips,
they show up again
with legitimate cargo intact
and are re-entered,
so you figure
those are honest mistakes.
But the pink and the green,
those cans never come back.
They stay out of
the computer for good.
Russell:
And the pink one, like
the can full of dead girls,
they're all from the same
shipping line-- Talco,
and on all of them,
the same checker,
this guy Thomas Pakusa--
he goes by "Horseface"--
he's the one working.
You went at him
already, right?
We grand juried
his ass,
but that motherfucker
didn't blink.
( groaning )
You wanna
hit the head?
Get yourself right,
Detective?
( groans )
Naw, I'm good.
Ahem.
The point is,
we have
a pattern here.
What they're doing
eliminates almost
all of the paper trail.
As long
as they can get a truck
past the outbound lanes
and there's a dozen ways
to do that,
the only thing
they leave behind
is a little tell-tale
in the computer.
A box comes off
the ship,
flashes for a few
moments, and blip,
then it's gone.
( heaving )
Freamon:
Our target is supposed
to be Sobotka, right?
I mean,
on paper anyway.
What you're tellin' me
is that it's better
than a fair bet
that he actually is
a target in Bunk's murders.
( heaving )
Maybe we can
fold our investigation
into yours, Lieutenant.
And put my ass
in the air
with 14 open homicides
that might never clear?
The bosses wouldn't
blame you for that.
I wouldn't shine either.
I'm trying to use what
we do with this detail
to get a major case
squad going.
I come up outta here
with all those open files,
it doesn't smell
as sweet.
- So what's the
next move on this?
- We clone the computer
and start watching
what's happening
on the docks
in real time.
( moans )
Oh-hh.
( retching,
spitting )
( groans )
Oh, shit.
Dee.
Yo, Dee.
Just wine, huh?
I'm not drinking
much anymore.
No Jameson's?
Maybe a quick fuck
of the waitress, then.
Okay, I deserve
that one, too,
even though I'm not
doing much of that
anymore either.
Anything else?
I'm sorry.
I don't know where
it still comes from.
I mean, it's been
a year, right?
You deserve
to be angry.
What's the point,
though?
How's work?
What, just so we talk
about everything in my life
that pisses you off?
Drinking, women,
the work.
Just trying to make
conversation.
Well, I retired.
Excuse me?
Yeah.
It's boats,
not bodies.
On a good day,
I catch crabs and
count seagulls.
That's not you.
It wasn't me.
It wasn't me
not to drink,
or dog around either.
A lot of things
weren't me.
I want another chance.
How about a fuck
for the road instead?
( moaning )
( laughing )
( grunting )
- How are you doing?
- Spiros: Okay.
You unload this shit,
you gotta ditch the trucks
and the trailers both.
Make it look like it was
a hijack, all right?
Niko.
If you want,
I will pay you straight,
or Eton can pay
in heroin.
Wholesale.
Turn it around,
you can make 60, 70,000.
Nicky, he's offering
like, three, four times
the value.
I'm out on this.
Nick, even if we
walk it up to White Mike,
we can make 30, 35,000.
Nicky, come on, man.
Half in cash,
half in dope.
( claps )
Nicky, I can turn that
package around no problem.
- No, Zig, I got it.
- Nicky, you don't know--
You hear me?
I said I fuckin'
got this one.
Why don't you stay at home
and watch cartoons,
let me handle this shit
for the both of us,
all right?
You fuckin' walkin'
home or what?
( sighs )
Hey, girl.
What do we do
with the day?
Me?
Oh, I gotta pick up
the boys from the sitter.
- Okay, great.
- They're gonna be
coming back here,
Michael has piano
this afternoon.
No problem, we'll do
somethin' after that.
Maybe we go by my place,
pick up some things.
I don't want
the boys to know
that you were here.
It's gonna get them
hoping,
so...
you need to leave.
Look at this
sorry shit.
Motherfuckers
not appreciate nothin'
that comes to 'em free.
I'll take it in the back.
Maybe they got some
duct tape will fix it.
- Dee, right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you can't be
in here now, man.
Yo, man, y'all
didn't get any final
calls this week, yo?
Yeah, we got some.
I didn't see
any out there.
All right, man,
give me a minute.
Let me finish up
right here real quick
and I'll go
and get one for you.
( grunting )
- Hey, yo.
- What's up?
I know you got
my motherfuckin' cigs, yo.
- You tryin' to curb me?
- Naw, man.
( instrumental music
playing )
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org