Subtitles by Razed (gab.com/razed)
Gab - Speak Freely
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
"Unknown caller"
Hello.
Faraz Kamali...
Who is this?
Hello.
-Good morning.
A beautiful day today.
The sky is clear and bright.
Where are you?
In a safe place.
Still in Tehran?
Yes.
Beautiful.
Call me in a few hours, I'll give you details on the rescue.
I have a plan.
What's that?
-I have a link to get into the secondary station.
-If it's not too late, we can try getting in from there.
I have a contact in a dissident group.
He is reliable. I made sure before I flew.
Is he with you now?
Are you with him, "Shakira"? Are you with "Sick Boy"?
What does he know about you?
He doesn't know anything. He thinks I'm opposed to the regime like him, but...
He knows someone on the inside, but that doesn't matter does it?
Can you be there in 48 hours?
Yes.
Ok.
For starters, put a tracker on the hacker's phone.
And send me everything you have on him, as well as his contact at the station.
What his name is, and what his role will be.
I have to go.
Come here, going to put it at the front.
Look, I added some features to the "Gershad" app.
The app isn't worth shit.
The regime reports lies to confuse you.
No way?
-In the end it leads you to bullshit.
Next stop:
Hell.
-Hell.
Crazy son of a bitch!
Tell me where she is.
Get up! Get up!
Tell me where she is. Tell me where she is!
Tell me where she is!
I don't know anything... I swear to God.
Come.
Are you taking him, commander?
I need to answer to you?!
Sorry, sir.
Where?
Brother...
Where are you taking me?
I swear to you I know nothing.
Lying dog!
Do you have children?
I have two little girls.
Masoud, I told you to shut up!
Israeli Air Force Base
Sir, Dr. Ben-Artzi here,
we'll be in the hospital for another half hour.
How is she?
Her vitals are fine but she's anesthetized.
I'll update you later.
No!
Tell the girls to come, not the boys. More girls will come that way!
Tell Parisa, Langar.
Dude I need to drive. I'll call you later. Bye.
I told you this app is shit.
There's no way around this checkpoint.
Good afternoon. How are you, sir?
Where are you going?
We're going to hike in the mountains. We're on break from university.
Licenses.
Yeah.
Here you go.
Why do you look like that, sister?
Arrange your head covering.
Are you pointing your finger at me?
Now you're going to get it!
Officer...
Come on, get out!
Come on!
-Officer.
You're not ashamed?
Officer, that's my step sister.
She's from abroad. She doesn't understand what it means.
What do I care that she came from abroad?
I ask forgiveness. It wasn't out of disrespect.
She learned in school that the hand sign means everything is fine.
Where is her identification?
I apologize, officer.
She came to visit her homeland and go for a hike in the mountains.
Explain to her that this sign is done abroad, not in Iran.
Absolutely.
What about the car? Is it clean?
Let's take a good look to be sure.
Is there a problem, sir?
Open up the back.
The door is stuck, but don't worry.
There's nothing there.
And what about him?
Drive carefully.
Thank you.
A month's work! A month's work gone, damn it!
Tell me, did you want to get us arrested or are you just an idiot?
Leave her alone. It happens.
-Shut the fuck up!
Why did you even bring her? Did you think we were going on a picnic?
Where are we going?
You really don't know where we're going?
To a party?
A party where? What are we going to do there?
Why did she even come with us? Where did you find her?
What is this talk?
I could've ditched you both at the checkpoint and driven off.
How do you know each other?
From the Internet.
We met on the darknet.
Darknet...?
How long have you known each other?
-A year.
And how do you know it's really her?
-I know. Trust me.
What the hell are you doing on the darknet?
I'm a hacker.
I make money from it.
I needed help from him on something. We started talking...
I'm really sorry for what happened.
It was stupid.
Let's go.
You owe me that money.
A million tomans gone from your mistake.
Get the hell out.
Out!
Over there.
On your knees.
On your knees!
You sold out to the Zionists.
You betrayed your homeland.
A traitorous dog like you
doesn't deserve to live for even one day.
Even one day!
You're leaving Iran tonight.
And will never return.
If you come back, I will visit your family myself.
Only then...
I'll have a full magazine.
Your Zionist friends are waiting for you in Istanbul.
Go hug your wife and daughters.
Because you will not see them again.
Understand? You will not see them again!
Yes.
Hey! What's up?
Shahin!
You took the merchandise and went for a walk.
Where is this place? We got a flat tire. We had to haul ass the rest of the way.
Let's smoke something and fly.
Go, I'm right behind you.
Milad, come.
Will she be following us around all night?
-What's the problem?
What's the problem? As if that stuff with the cops never happened?
Let's go in here and talk.
You're just being polite.
Yeah.
"The Eagle" is on the line.
Put him through.
Hey, cutie.
Have fun, sweetheart.
Hello.
-Hello.
Can you make me happy?
Hurry up.
You should have counted first.
Don't rush me, sweetheart.
What's your name?
Yasmine.
Who do you work for here, Yasmine?
I want to be sure you're not playing me.
Can you point them out?
I'll buy a million tomans worth if it's good.
Do you know what the penalty is for selling drugs? Do you know?!
I didn't sell anything.
You have two options.
Either you go to jail or you tell me who your dealer is.
There is no dealer.
Ok, come with me.
What did she do to you?
Nothing, she kicked me in the balls. Nothing serious.
Did she say anything?
-No.
Didn't snitch on anyone.
Why the face?
You still owe me money.
Karim, enough.
Hello.
My dear.
My love, how are you feeling?
Thank God.
Where are you?
I don't know.
In the hospital. Don't know which country.
It has to do with your job, where could it be?
The Israelis kidnapped you, my dear.
I thought so.
I'm fine. They're taking care of me.
You can relax.
Forgive me.
It's not your fault.
It is my fault.
I was supposed to fly with you, I was supposed to take care of you.
Me and my damn job.
This isn't the time for that.
I was told to tell you that you made the right decision
and that if you follow through, we'll see each other soon.
I need to go.
Be strong.
I swear I'll bring you home.
God willing.
Hello, commander.
-Faraz, how are you?
Very good. I was just about to update you.
Come to my office please and we'll talk face to face.
I'm on my way, sir.
Hello, ma'am.
Go on in, please
Thank you.
Faraz, how are you?
Good to see you.
You too. Thanks.
Come, please sit.
Thank you.
What did you want to update me on?
Information pertaining to the investigation.
Yeah?
Get something out of Tabrizi?
Not yet.
But I released him.
I heard about that.
I didn't believe it at first.
Faraz Kamali makes such a sensitive decision on his own?
There was a narrow window of opportunity.
I received information
that he is going to meet with a senior Mossad official in Istanbul tomorrow morning.
So why didn't you update me?
Would you have approved of it?
I wanted to come to you with all the information.
How do you know he won't run away?
He wouldn't leave his wife and daughters here.
Such traitors would sell out their family to escape the rope.
Family is more important than the fear of death.
I released him to see if he would make a mistake.
No matter what we tried,
he denied any connection to Mossad.
Look, you should have informed me!
I'm sorry, I messed up.
How's your wife?
She's fine, fine...
Recovering after her surgery.
She's still in France?
Yes.
When is she supposed to return?
In a few days.
Maybe your wife's situation impacted your judgement.
Certainly.
I haven't touched a cigarette in five years.
This is my tenth one today.
Nahid, my wife, forced me to quit.
Once when I went to get a cigarette out of the box,
I noticed that in place of cigarettes she had put rolled up notes.
Pictures of me, her, the kids, all of us on vacation.
She told me:
"I can handle the dangers of your work
but I don't want you dying of an illness.
Your death should have a purpose."
Why are you telling me this?
Nahid flew to France a week ago to have brain surgery.
The surgery was a success.
Last night she boarded a return flight. And I...
You have no idea what this is about, do you?
No, I'm sorry.
Is she OK?
God knows where the Israeli bastards took her.
They want you in return.
But I can not let you leave.
This is already too complicated a story,
to bury it.
But you said I need to leave.
Things have changed.
What do you want me to do now?
You have to stay.
Everything will remain as it was.
Your beautiful home, your business,
Your wife and daughters will know nothing.
But from now on, you work for me.
What are you thinking about?
You have no choice.
But I have nothing to give you.
You don't know what I want from you.
And what about your wife?
They wouldn't dare touch her.
Your name is flagged at all border stations,
and even if you somehow manage to get out,
once you set foot outside of Iran,
my first stop will be this house.
You know what I'm getting at, right?
What do you think?
That it's fun to be a fugitive? That it's pleasant and nice?
I love my homeland more than you think.
I'm willing to die for my homeland. Is that clear?
Perfectly.
Excellent.
You're an idiot. You have a great life here.
And if you do a good job, it will stay that way.
Yes,
until they put a bullet in my head.
Bring me Tamar Rabinyan.
And no one will touch you.
Tomorrow at noon,
Meeting with the chief of staff...
Milad Kahani, 25 years old, originally from Shiraz,
lived in Tehran for five years,
arrested twice during protests, in 2011 and in 2014, released after a few days,
besides that, clean criminal record.
Do we know where they are now?
In the mountains, outside Tehran.
Rave is illegal, apparently.
Stay on him for now.
Hello.
Is this Mr. Masoud Tabrizi?
Who's asking?
My name is Ellie and I'm with Turkish Airlines. I'm calling you about the flight that left this morning,
I understand you didn't make it in time, is that correct?
That's right. I apologize for not telling you in advance.
No worries, it happens. Are you getting another flight today?
Because if so, I wanted to let you know that you can get up to 50% credit on the ticket you purchased.
Really?
I did not know that.
Would you look at that.
Twenty years in the business and still learning new things every day.
Would you like to set an alternative date for today, sir?
No, thank you. I'll fly another day.
Of course.
Have a nice day sir.
Freeze!
Previews not subtitled.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org