Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Oh.
No, look over there.
- Look over there. Okay.
- All right. Look over there.
Let's take a picture.
One...
- You say "cheese," okay? One, two...
- Say "cheese."
- Cheese!
- ...three.
The four and the one.
No, that's your two.
There you go. Four, one.
Four, one. Four, one.
And then five, one.
When you're ready,
you can switch to five.
- Look what I got!
- What is that?
What, you don't know Pokémon?
Come on.
- Faster, faster.
- Smile! Oh, sorry. This is video.
- Just slide the thing.
- Slide the...
Video log 3.7.
I have reason to believe
my wife is a robot.
Can seemingly run for miles.
Wait up.
Stop. Don't!
Everybody's grounded!
Whee!
Yes! Bravo!
Video log 6.7.
I think we can,
I think we can, I think we...
Pam?
Pam.
Hey, Dad.
Hey, sweetheart.
How's it going?
Um...
Good.
What's up with the FaceTime?
Oh, I'm glad you asked.
What is wrong
with this picture?
I'm about to be in trouble,
aren't I?
Yes.
Yup.
Maybe we should
keep the trash in your room?
Huh?
Maybe the smell will remind you.
I'm sorry, Dad.
It won't happen again.
Okay. Where are you,
by the way?
- Study group.
- Ah. Whose house are you at?
Uh, one of my friends in bio.
You haven't met her yet.
Oh, Miss Popular.
When are you gonna be home?
Uh, I think we're gonna go late.
Late like 9:00-ish or...
- Late, like...
- all night, probably.
I thought we were gonna
eat dinner together.
We ate together on Monday.
Didn't know
you were counting.
Okay.
- I should get back.
- Right. Oh, one more thing.
- I want to know about the final you...
- Bye, Dad!
...took today.
Uh, yo, what am I looking at?
Exactly.
I cannot remember the name
of this thing.
Uh, it was like a kimchee,
okra, mussel stew.
Pam used to make it.
- Oh. The kimchee gumbo.
- Gumbo, gumbo.
- Yeah.
- That's it. Do you have the recipe?
- 'Cause I'm definitely forgetting something.
- Yeah, I might.
But I can definitely tell
you there's no pot in it.
Oh. This healthy and organic jar
of oregano?
How much are you smoking?
You doing every day or...
- Do you do it at work?
- Dude.
Can we not do this right now?
Please?
It's been a long day.
Uh... edamame.
I'm pretty sure
there's edamame in it.
Let me find the actual thing.
What's, uh...
What's Margot up to tonight?
She's at a study group
all night.
- Wait, all night tonight?
- Yeah, just got off the phone with her.
She's got a bio final
next week. Why?
Oh, nothing.
She's good, though?
Yeah. Why do you ask?
Making sure you guys
are both talking to each other,
both happy,
et cetera, et cetera.
Everything's fine, Peter.
Thanks for asking.
Hey. Look, Davy.
- Do you think that maybe you should just...
- Dude, everything's fine.
Hey, I got to go.
But send me that recipe. Please?
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Love you.
- Bye.
- Make sure to get all the water out.
- Are these ready?
Yeah, they're ready. Go on.
Stop. You got to drain
all the water.
Turn it off.
Let's stir it in.
We got to mix those up first.
Okay.
- You gonna try mixing it?
- Yeah.
Okay. Here.
Okay.
Good. Gentle. Do it slowly.
Do you see
how those are all done?
- Yeah.
Hey, you've reached
Margot's phone.
Leave me a message
or text me back.
Hi, sweetheart. Sorry I missed your call.
I was asleep.
Um, just checking in 'cause it looks like
you already left for school this morning.
Um... Also, what time did
you get in last night?
All right, give me a text
when you get this.
No need to call.
We both know you usually...
forget.
...map their topography
across all the tiers
in the application system,
and then in real time
and on continuous basis,
measure them end to end...
David, you with us?
Yeah. Sorry. I'm here.
Do you have the integration
report on the Bellington system?
Um...
Engineering is still
running tests,
but I should be able
to integrate by Monday.
Put some pressure on them,
all right?
Yep. Pressure.
Okay, team. Anything we forgot?
- I think that's it.
- I don't think we did.
All right. Have a good weekend.
- See you.
- Cool. Take care.
- Bye.
- All right. See ya.
Hey, you've reached
Margot's phone.
Leave me a message
or text me back.
Hey, Margot. Dad again.
Not sure if you've been
checking your messages,
but, um, I'm starting
to get a little...
Why did you leave
your laptop at home?
Okay, uh, it is 3:30,
one hour after school ended
on Friday, May 12.
Duh. Okay. It's Friday.
I know where you are. All right.
Ignore this message.
I love you. Bye.
Hello?
- Hi. Mrs. Shahinian?
- Yes?
This is David Kim,
Margot's father.
Yes. I'm in the middle of a lesson.
May I call you back afterwards?
Right.
No, this'll just take a second.
Can you put my daughter
on the phone just for a second?
I'm sorry, Mr. Kim. I'm confused
what you're calling about.
My daughter, Margot Kim, is in
a lesson with you right now.
Margot Kim canceled her classes
six months ago.
What?
Is she looking
to restart lessons?
Hold on. That... doesn't make any sense.
She loves piano.
Mr. Kim, is everything okay?
Yes. Um...
Everything's fine.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mrs. Shahinian.
Pick up, pick up,
pick up, pick up, pick up.
- Hello?
- Hi, hi. I'm David Kim.
- I'm Margot Kim's...
- Pam's husband.
- Yeah.
- Of course I remember.
- How are you doing?
- I'm good. I'm good.
Listen, the reason I'm calling
is that, um...
I haven't been able to reach
Margot for a little bit.
And I'm sure
her phone is dead,
but I was just wondering if I could
speak to Isaac and see if...
Well, it's got to be more of
a reception problem, right?
Uh... What do you mean?
You know, if they're
all in the mountains.
Sorry, what mountains?
Camping. Isaac is camping
with his friends.
Margot was definitely invited.
She was.
I'm pretty positive
she's there, too.
Did she not tell you?
Sh... She did.
I'm, um... Yeah, I'm looking
through her texts now.
She didn't mention mountains,
that's why. Yeah.
Yeah. They've been planning this for a
while. I can't imagine she just couldn't...
Do you happen to know when they left?
The reason I'm asking
is that school has her
marked as absent today.
Did they all ditch school?
I'll tell you something,
if that's what they did,
Isaac is in big trouble.
That's...
That's definitely what happened.
- Kids.
- Tell you what.
They're planning on heading back
tomorrow morning anyway.
Once they get reception,
I will let Isaac know
to have Margot give you a call.
Perfect. That is perfect.
Thank you.
- Is everything okay with you two?
- Thank you so...
- What do you mean?
- Well, I...
I just haven't spoken to you
since Pam's...
Oh. Oh. Thank you.
Everything is great.
Margot and I are great.
- Hello?
- Hey. Mr. Kim? This is Isaac. My mom told me to...
- Isaac! Yes, hi. Sorry to have you call me so early.
- It's okay.
Just wanted to say I'm sorry
I couldn't be of more help.
Yeah. Can you put my daughter
on the phone, please?
Did my mom not tell you?
What... What do you mean?
She never came.
What? What are you...
- Isaac, what do you mean?
- I mean she never came.
I even reached out to her
after school on Friday
when we were all heading out and
my car still had an extra seat.
What did she say?
She... didn't respond.
911.
What's your emergency?
Hi. I'm calling
about a possible...
I'm calling to report
a missing person.
- Okay, who is this regarding?
- Uh, my daughter.
I know I should've called sooner.
I just thought that...
- That's okay, sir.
- Yeah.
The first thing
we need to do is file a report.
After that, I'll put out a call to a detective
in the area who will be in touch with you.
- All right.
- Now, let's start with her name.
Margot Kim. M-A-R-G-O-T.
Kim. K-I-M.
- Hello?
- Hi. Is this David Kim?
Yes, this is David Kim.
I'm assuming this is...
Good morning, Mr. Kim.
My name is Rosemary Vick.
I'm the detective sergeant
assigned to your daughter's case.
Yeah. Good morning.
I've been waiting for your call.
Of course.
We're working as fast as we can.
I'm currently 35 minutes away
from your house.
But while I have you, do you feel
comfortable telling me what you know?
I just told every detail I know
to whoever I got off
the phone with an hour ago.
- I don't know what you guys are doing.
- I promise you, Mr. Kim,
we are taking this
very seriously.
And as a parent myself, I can only
imagine what you must be feeling.
But for me to help you, I do need
to know how everything unfolded,
from your eyes.
Understood...
Detective.
Okay, let's see
if I got this right.
One: after
a group study session,
Margot, with her car, didn't
return home Thursday evening.
Two: she called three times
at 11:00 p.m.
Three: she didn't attend school
on Friday.
And four: she's been skipping piano
classes for the last six months.
- Was all of that correct?
- Yes.
Okay. Mr. Kim, I am going to find
out what happened to your daughter.
But I'll need to know
a lot more about her, okay?
Yes, yes.
What do you want me to do?
I'll go talk
to neighbors. I'll...
We'll handle the ground investigation,
Mr. Kim. That's our job.
But if there's something
a parent can do,
it's shedding light for us
on who your daughter is
and the people she talks to.
Is that something
you can help us with?
Yes.
I can help with that.
Okay. It's already been 36
hours since Margot's last call,
so we've got to move
a little quickly.
We'll be taking a copy of
Margot's hard drive to Forensics.
But in the meantime...
any information
you can give me about her
or the people
around her will help.
Wait, you can't find Margot?
No, I can't. Do you mind
answering some questions for me to help?
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay, when was the last time you saw her?
Um... Tuesday.
Her locker's near me.
All right, on Thursday evening,
she attended a study group
for her biology class.
- Do you know anything about that?
- She's probably in AP Bio, right?
- Yes. She is.
- Yeah, no, I'm in regular.
What were you doing
Thursday night?
Thursday night,
I was at my dad's house.
Yeah, he picked me up
after finals that day.
All right.
Thank you, Jonah.
How does, uh...
how does this look?
Perfect. Hey, update me whenever
you learn something. Big or small.
Okay.
Where are you going?
To find out what the rest
of her Thursday looked like.
Oh. Oh.
And share that with me, too.
And what about Thursday night?
Thursday night,
I was finishing up
my final paper for English.
I don't know.
Xbox, dinner, some Netflix?
I just finished my last final,
which means I was
at Carmen's house playing pong.
Ping... Ping-pong.
What about study group?
Do you know who hosted that?
- I took bio last year, so no.
- No idea.
She and I
are on different AP paths,
so it was
kind of hard to keep tabs.
But you guys are friends.
Kind of.
What are you talking about?
You invited her
on a camping trip.
Well, yeah.
I mean, you know my mom.
Yes. So?
She was really good friends
with Margot's mom.
Okay, so?
She felt bad...
about everything
that happened to you guys.
But she has friends, right?
- Define "friends."
- Do people invite her to things?
I think people
occasionally invite her to things.
- She just never comes.
- She keeps to herself a lot.
- She's quiet.
- I did see her eat lunch alone.
On Thursday?
Every day.
David, look,
I know you don't want
to hear this from me right now,
but you got to take it easy.
I can help with everything
that you're looking through.
Are there any Facebook friends
you haven't talked to yet?
Yes. Ninety-four.
And, apparently, since nobody
was actually her friend,
I don't know who to talk to without
calling every name I read online.
What about offline?
- Yeah, that was at my place.
- That was your place?
- You hosted the study group on Thursday night for bio?
- Yeah.
So you were with Margot for
the majority of the night. Did you...
Well, the study group
only went till 9:00.
No, no.
She said it was going all night.
No, she definitely left at 9:00.
Maybe even earlier.
Did she say
where she was going?
- Not really.
- How'd she look?
Was she worried? Did she look scared?
Was she talking?
Honestly, I don't know.
We're not really that close.
Well, then why did you
invite her to study group?
I'm trying to get into Berkeley
next year.
Okay, you were...
You were in her class, though.
Did she mention anything unusual
going on lately?
- Was she acting strange?
- Uh...
You know,
she did go on Tumblr a lot.
What? What is a "tumbler"?
First, she fills up her gas.
Then exits off the 101.
And then turns onto
the 152 East.
10:02 p.m.
152 East?
That exit leads out of town.
She took it alone.
That doesn't make sense. This
does not sound like my daughter.
She's acting like
a totally different person.
Okay, hold on, hold on.
You just gave me an idea.
In the meantime,
start expanding
from only the people
she communicated with.
Look into her behavior also.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
She's been depositing her piano
cash into her checking account every week.
The hell was she doing
with all that money?
Six days ago, she made an
outgoing transaction of $2,500
to "Venmo."
The payment service?
There it is. $2,500.
Six days ago.
Does it say what it was for?
Nothing but a peace sign.
Who did she send it to?
Doesn't say.
Okay. That's weird.
That's really weird.
You don't think she's involved
with anything serious, right?
Davy.
I don't know. I got to go.
Sir, I don't
have to tell you anything.
I just want to know where you were
the night my daughter went missing.
Like I said,
I had a prior engagement.
- What are you hiding?
- I was busy.
- Nothing!
Then answer the damn question
before there's a cop
knocking on your door.
Where were you the night
my daughter went missing?
Hello?
Does the name
Rachel Jeun ring a bell?
No. Why?
- It's Margot.
- You mentioned earlier
she was acting like
a different person,
so I had our Forensics team look
through any deleted contacts
on the copy of her hard drive.
One of those contacts was
a local forger.
He said Margot picked up an ID
a few days ago,
around the same time
she withdrew all that money.
"Withdrew"?
What? Withdrew what money?
David, I also spoke
to security at Venmo
to find out more about the account
Margot sent the $2,500 to.
Yeah. Do they know
who it belonged to?
It belonged to Margot.
She...
She sent the money
to herself?
What was she doing,
running a laundering scheme?
That's what it looks like.
I'd see this a lot
in narcotics.
People who know their money
is being watched
just transfer their funds to
somewhere much less monitored.
"Less monitored." Like where?
The Internet.
She gets a fake ID,
she sends money to herself.
What does this mean?
That it's time to start
considering the possibility...
that Margot ran away.
Why would she do that?
That's what we don't know.
Why would she do that? She called me
three times in the middle of the night.
Three times she called me. Why?
We are going to figure out why.
- So what I want to look for now...
- No, no, no.
No, no, no.
I know my daughter.
She did not run away.
Ooh. This is a good angle.
Also, to all my fans, I know this
vlog is a little late, but...
Favorite concert in the last year?
Definitely Twenty One Pilots.
Well, thank you
for the compliment, Lucy.
Oh, this is a Fearless Core shirt.
Cost me, like, 40 bucks.
Um...
How... how would I be able
to see you?
Well, you know what?
You guys, you keep commenting,
but honestly if it's kind...
Hold on.
It's Uxie.
It can wipe out memories.
And it's kind of cute.
How'd you know I like Pokémon?
A lot of people, actually.
I mean,
ever since they started chang...
This one I took at a lake.
This one I took at a forest.
That...
I'm Margot.
I'm 15. Almost 16.
Student.
San Jose.
What's that like?
Trust me,
it's probably better than this.
This is it.
Best place in the world
to do nothing.
You work 25 hours
on top of school?
My dad doesn't know
I stopped going to piano.
He wouldn't get it.
Anyway, don't you guys have...
So...
today is this mega babe's birthday.
Happy Birthday.
You know,
if she were still here today,
a hundred percent,
she'd be making us all her...
Come in!
Hey, sweetheart. Um...
I... I...
forgot to say earlier...
Um...
It's, uh...
- Yeah, it's...
- Tuesday.
So, The Voice...
Um...
Elimination round.
Yeah, of course.
Still on?
Yeah. Megan's gonna get cut.
Yeah, she is.
I'll see you...
- Bye.
- ...downstairs.
I'm sorry, David.
It's another dead end.
You're sure you looked into
every one of them?
Every one. None of the YouCast
users Margot interacted with
have a connection
to her disappearance.
- Even f...
- Even fish-n-chips.
Using the information
on her account,
we traced her
to a Kirchick's Diner,
ten miles outside Pittsburgh.
I spoke to her and her manager,
who confirmed with CCTV
that she was on a shift.
Checks out.
I didn't know her.
I didn't know my daughter.
Couple years ago,
an angry neighbor
starts banging on my door.
When I asked her
what the trouble was,
she said she wanted the $25
that my son had stolen from her.
Now, I didn't know
what she was talking about.
I know my son,
and that did not sound like
the Robert I raised.
But as it turned out,
it was true.
My son had gone house-to-house in
the neighborhood for two weeks,
telling people
that he was my son
and that he was raising money
for a fictional police charity
called "Moms and Dads in Blue."
Hmm.
Point is...
you don't always know your kid.
And that is never your fault.
I have NCIC searching
for her vehicle in 16 states.
Let's both try and catch up
on some sleep tonight.
Talk in the a.m.
What'd you do after?
With your son,
once you found out?
Um, I told my neighbor that...
I had in fact
founded the charity,
and I thanked her for the money.
But I will deny it
if you ever bring that up.
Okay.
Look, I hope you know how thankful
I am that you were assigned to us.
I just wish there wasn't
a case to be assigned to.
All right.
Shutting down.
- Yeah.
- Talk soon.
This is it.
Best place in the world
to do nothing.
This is it.
You've reached Detective
Sergeant Rosemary Vick.
Leave a message.
I'll get back to you.
Vick, wake up!
I know why
she was at that intersection.
She wasn't leaving town.
She was driving to the spot she's been
visiting for the past five months.
It's 3:45 a.m.
I'm headed there now.
Hey.
Where are you?
You told me she ran away, Vick.
Are...
Are you at the lake?
You told me she ran away.
Okay, I'm heading there
right now.
Robert, honey,
just go back to sleep, okay?
Okay. I need you
to stay calm, all right?
We're gonna figure this out
together.
What are you showing me?
This is her key chain.
Oh, my God.
Did you call the cops?
I'm heading... I'm on my way!
You told me she ran away, Vick!
Good morning, Bay Area.
I'm Natalie Boyd.
A terrifying development today
as a vehicle matching that
of a missing San Jose teenager
was discovered late last night
underneath a Santa Cruz lake.
An operation is currently underway to
recover Margot Kim's Toyota Camry.
But at this moment,
we still don't know
whether the Evercreek High sophomore
is actually inside the vehicle.
Okay, doesn't look like there's
anyone at the front seat.
And now it looks like they're...
Okay,
they're checking the trunk.
Good morning. Thank you for
being here on such short notice.
I'm Detective Sergeant
Rosemary Vick,
lead investigator on this case.
I am joined by David Kim,
Margot's father.
We've provided you all
with a timeline of events,
starting with last Thursday,
May 11th,
when Margot first went missing.
That is yours to circulate.
But focusing on the events
of this morning,
the Silicon Valley
Police Department
was able to recover
Miss Kim's vehicle.
And to answer
the most pressing question,
Margot Kim was not inside.
However, our examination
of the vehicle did reveal
a small amount of blood
on the passenger-side dashboard,
blood that points
to a physical altercation,
meaning that this case is now
officially being considered
an abduction.
Good afternoon.
A search through the Santa
Cruz forest is now underway
for a local teen whose car
was found dumped in a lake.
Authorities are
asking anyone with information
to please call the hotline
or 911 immediately.
Starting at 1:00 p.m.,
we'll be assigning every
volunteer to a search team.
Each team is in charge
of a single section
of the critical
12-square-mile radius.
Because of the steep ravines
and otherwise
unsafe topography
on the west side of the lake,
we have already cleared
the following zones.
But still, there's a lot
of ground to cover.
- Margot!
It's been four
days since Margot Kim was last seen,
and so far,
nothing to show for it
except for the torturous mystery
at its center.
$2,500 in cash
was found in a manila envelope
on Margot's passenger seat.
Was it a runaway fund,
like the lead detective is
suggesting,
or was it something more?
We covered about, um,
half the search zone already,
and, um, tomorrow is a full day.
And the more people came,
the faster it went.
Um...
Can I?
So, if you have
some time tomorrow,
we would... love the help.
This is obviously not
the outcome we wanted,
but we will resume the search
the moment it is safe to
walk through the forest again.
In the meantime, however,
the investigation will not stop
until we find Margot.
I mean, listen,
I do not think it is my place
to say anything. I just...
I feel that these problems
usually start in the household.
She was...
I'm sorry.
She was my best friend.
I'm just a big believer
in community service.
Looking at all the things
that happened to Margot,
I just thought to myself,
"I think they could use
my help."
Don't lie to me.
You can't assist
in the investigation anymore.
What? What does that...
What does that mean?
It means that
we can't have someone
this close to the case
helping investigate it.
It's my fault for getting you
involved in the first place.
I did it because we had
already lost so much time.
You're cutting me off?
Every professional who should
be working on this case
is working on this case.
All I'm trying to do
is to help you find my daughter!
I know. But you can't
see things clearly.
Who's the one
who brought you to the car?
Who's the one who found the lake
and brought you to the car?
If it wasn't for me... not you...
you and I would both be thinking
that my Margot ran away,
but because of me, we...
We don't know
that she didn't run away.
She had cash in her car.
But what we do know
is that a 17-year-old boy
is in the hospital...
- He's gonna be fine.
- You broke his jaw!
- Mom?
- Robert! What...
Sweetheart, let me take care of this.
Please.
If you have a suspicion
about someone, that's fine.
But then it is the police's job
to look for proof,
not yours to act
on flakes of evidence.
Vick,
I shouldn't have done that.
From now on,
you just tell me what you need.
We need nothing from you.
I'm going back to the field.
Do not call me until I call you.
- Vick, please.
- Get some sleep, Mr. Kim.
Don't lie to me.
Don't walk away from me.
Don't walk away. Hey.
Oh, shit.
- Hey! Stop!
- Stop! Stop! Hey!
- Son of a bitch!
Shit!
- Oh, shit!
- Get off!
What'd you do to her?
Has anyone even considered the possibility
that it was an absolute stranger?
Some sick perv in the middle of
the woods sees a little girl...
Looking for
something to drink?
- Yeah.
- Coffee?
Yeah, coffee would be
awesome, thanks.
All right.
No, you know what,
you've been probably straight-chugging
caffeine the last three days.
I am going to make you
some tea.
Herbal.
Um, I got to go to my car for a minute.
I'll be right back, yeah?
Hmm.
How's the detective?
She working on any new leads?
No.
She's not.
What was your relationship
like with Margot?
What do you mean?
You guys hung out,
right?
Sure.
You know, it was, um...
You know,
we didn't hang out much, but...
You know, it was just...
When's the last time
you saw her, by the way?
Um...
You know what,
I'd have to think...
I think this needs some honey.
Who was that?
Work.
Oh, yeah. Uh...
What have they been saying
to you this whole time?
Going back to
the previous question,
when's the last time
you saw her?
Dude...
I can barely remember.
But you know what, let's...
let's get our minds off this
for a sec, huh?
I feel like we're just gonna drive
each other crazy talking about it.
Hey, is your tea okay?
You still want that coffee?
- "Last night was fun."
- What was that?
"I feel so weird
doing this."
"Don't tell your father."
"He'd kill me."
"Seriously,
he'd murder me."
And then
seven different times:
"See you tonight."
What'd you do
to my daughter?
I can explain, all right?
But you know what,
let's calm down.
- Let's grab a seat.
- What'd you do to my daughter?
Wait.
Stop!
What the...
What'd you do to her?
- Please!
- What'd you do to her?
What'd you do to her?
What were you doing with her?
Weed!
- What?
- Weed!
I was smoking her out.
When you guys all came back
from New Year's...
...she found my piece.
She wanted to try it, and...
it just kept happening.
You gave drugs to my daughter?
I promised her
I wouldn't tell.
So she would come to you
in the middle of the night
and you would give her weed
and do God knows what else?
That's it.
We'd get high and talk. I swear.
Look, I know
how wrong all this sounds,
and I know I should've
told you sooner, but...
Look, I didn't think it had
anything to do with this.
What kind of a brother are you?
You're asking me?
You come in here and accuse me of
something un-fucking-speakable,
and you're wondering
what kind of family I am?
Do you want to know why
she hated those piano lessons?
It's because
every time she would walk in,
she would see that thing and she
would think about her mother.
She told you that?
She told you that
and not me? Why?
Because you never asked.
Ever since Pam,
you stopped talking to Margot
about the only thing
that's been on her mind
the last two years.
She needed you
to talk to her...
not the other way around.
I just thought
it would fix itself.
David.
We... We got him.
His name is Randy Cartoff.
Davy?
Oh, God.
- Davy.
- Oh, God.
This is Eyewitness
News with live breaking news.
Good morning. I'm Faustine Rea.
A parent's worst nightmare
comes true this morning
for David Kim.
In a shocking and thoroughly
mind-boggling conclusion
to a story that's captivated
the Bay Area,
Margot Kim,
missing now for five days,
has just been
tragically declared dead.
Why? A taped confession.
Randy Cartoff,
released just six years ago
for felony drug possession
and sexual assault,
uploaded the confession online
before taking his own life.
We're going to show you
a segment of
the three-minute video now,
but please be warned:
the following contains
graphic descriptions
and disturbing content.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Dear girl in the green car,
I'm sorry for what I did to you.
And I'm sorry for not listening to
you when you begged me to stop.
I'm sorry for beating you
and crushing you
and tossing you with your suitcases
so no one would ever find you.
I thought this would be easy,
but it isn't.
When we arrived
at his Morgan Hill residence,
Mr. Cartoff was deceased,
seemingly by
a self-inflicted gun wound.
Sometimes these confessions
are hoaxes,
but based on his story,
we were able to return
to the lake site,
where we discovered trace DNA
matching that of Mr. Cartoff
in critical areas
of the search zone.
I've already spoken
to her father.
But at this point
in the investigation,
we are very confident...
that Miss Kim's life was taken
on her way out of town.
A private vigil
will be held for Miss Kim
in downtown San Jose this week.
It still doesn't make sense.
Where's the car that he took her in?
Where's the...
the suitcases?
Did he...
did he clean up the blood?
Vick, who is this guy?
I don't know.
I wish I had an answer.
All I know,
and all you need to know,
is that this had
nothing to do with you.
Yes, it did.
I am so sorry for everything
that happened to your daughter.
And I am so sorry for everything
that happened to you.
And if there's anything
I can do for you,
please do not hesitate to call.
- Okay.
- Make sure to get all the water out.
- Are these ready?
Go wake up Daddy.
Wake up, Daddy, wake up!
Wake up.
- Wake up.
- Okay, all right.
Margot, show Daddy
what you made in school.
That's not...
I'm Margot.
Hello?
Hi. I'm wondering
if I could speak to Hannah?
Speaking.
Hi, I'm calling in regards
to my daughter, Margot Kim.
You spoke to her online
as "mkmania."
Oh. Um...
You must have the wrong number.
I'm talent, not representation.
But I can connect you
to my agent if you'd like.
So you work as a waitress
part-time, then?
You told the detective you were
on a shift when she called.
Uh, what detective?
I don't understand.
Detective Vick.
She called you four days ago,
and you told her
- you were on a shift.
- Sir, I never got a call from the police.
What are you talking about?
Maybe I'm not being clear.
On YouCast, you've been chatting
with my daughter for months.
Your username is "fish-n-chips."
Your mother was in the hospital.
Right?
What's YouCast?
You've reached Detective
Sergeant Rosemary Vick.
Leave a message. I'll get back to you.
Vick, this is David Kim.
Something doesn't add up.
Call me back
as soon as you get this, okay?
- SVPD.
- Hi. Yes. This is an emergency.
I need to speak
to Detective Rosemary Vick.
- Can you connect me, please?
- I'm sorry, sir, that's not possible.
- Uh, what is this regarding?
- No. Um... This is David Kim.
I need to speak to Detective
Rosemary Vick. V-I...
Mr. Kim. I am so sorry
to hear about Margot.
- Thank you.
- We are all so torn up about it here.
- Yeah, thank you.
- Especially Rosemary.
I have never seen someone
so invested in a case.
- Yeah, I know.
- From the moment she volunteered to lead it,
- the way she handled the investigation...
- Wait.
...and really dealt with
the media, I mean...
- Hang on, wait, wait, wait.
- She...
- Did you say "volunteered"?
- Sorry?
Y-You said she volunteered.
No. I was led
to believe that she...
she was assigned to the case, right?
She was assigned.
No. She definitely volunteered.
Unfortunately, though, I...
I still can't patch you
through dispatch.
She's probably on her way
to Margot's vigil, though.
If you'd like, I can connect you
to her work voice mail instead.
Mr. Kim?
Actually, can you...
connect me to
the deputy sheriff, please?
Ms. Vick, as your counsel was
informed, by signing this document,
you hereby verify
the confession you provide today
pertaining to the crimes
you are accused of
after your arrest one week ago.
The DA's office
will then consider leniency
on any charges related
to the case,
including first-degree murder.
Excuse us.
We're taking you now
to San Jose, California,
where we're getting word now
that a law enforcement officer
has just been taken into custody
at the vigil for a local teen
who's been missing
since last Thursday.
Let's start with Thursday,
May 11th, when Margot Kim went missing.
What happened that night?
- I got a phone call.
- And who was calling?
My son.
Mom.
I made a big mistake.
I think I need to call 911.
What did you do
after hearing the call?
- I met him.
- Where?
Near Barbosa Lake. He was
standing on the edge of a ravine.
What did Robert
tell you when you got there?
He said,
"There's a girl down there.
I accidentally pushed a girl
down there."
I asked him why.
What did he say?
You need to understand
that my son
is not like other kids.
He's different.
He can be very...
What did he say?
Six months ago,
Robert recognized Margot
on a live blogging website.
He'd liked her
since grade school.
Knew all about her life.
Her interests.
So, what did he do?
Made up a story.
A new identity.
This one I took at a forest.
For six months,
they were friends.
You work 25 hours
on top of school?
It was just role-playing.
It was harmless.
Until the money.
She found his username
on Venmo.
She sent $2,500
to cover hospital expenses.
Expenses that didn't exist.
She was a good kid.
So he decided
to give her money back.
He had to come clean.
It was over.
Why didn't he just
give it to her at school?
Margot could've reacted
the wrong way in public.
Robert does not like
that kind of attention.
So he followed her.
He followed her.
And what was Margot doing
when your son arrived
at the lake?
Getting high in her car.
- Then what happened?
- He got in.
She screamed. She hit him.
Before he could even realize
that he was bleeding,
she was running, calling for
help, and he ran after her.
It was pitch-black.
He was not trying to hurt her.
He was trying to explain.
But she was punching him and
screaming, and he just... he reacted.
He... he pushed back.
And she fell.
Just...
just disappeared.
So, your son calls you,
asks you to help
cover up a murder...
No. No.
It was my decision.
Baby?
I don't want you calling anyone.
Mommy's gonna take care
of everything.
It was my decision.
Not his.
So, now you're
looking down a ravine.
- Did you go down?
- I tried.
But it was narrow, jagged,
impossible without SAR.
- So, how did you figure that sh...
- That she was dead?
It was narrow, jagged, and at
least 50 feet to rock bottom.
And it was dead quiet.
So you helped your son.
I dumped the car in the lake
and took charge of the investigation.
I convinced David
his daughter ran away.
Said forensics had
Margot's hard drive.
And told
the law enforcement team
we'd already cleared the zone
I knew her body was in.
But still,
it was only a matter of time
before they'd find the spot.
Which is why
I needed a confession.
It was the only thing
that would make it stop.
So you drugged up
an ex-con you knew
and fed him a script.
Was it really a suicide?
He's my son.
Do you know what prison would do
to someone like him?
He made a mistake.
For those of you just joining,
we are now following the police SUV
transporting Detective Vick
and the father of Miss Kim...
So, after your arrest,
on the way to the station,
you didn't say a word to anyone
until Mr. Kim asked you
was his daughter actually dead.
What did you tell him?
I said even if Margot
had survived the fall she took
it wouldn't have mattered.
She still would've had to live
five days without water.
And how did David respond?
He told them
to turn the car around.
Why?
He said it'd been two days.
And hold on a second.
She'd only have to live
without water for two days.
And it looks as though
they're making
a U-turn right now.
There was a storm
on Monday.
They're heading off
in the other direction.
We're currently
watching live footage
from our affiliates
in the Bay Area
of a recovery operation
for missing teen Margot Kim,
who authorities now believe
is at the bottom of
this Northern California ravine.
Presumed dead only hours ago,
the search for Margot Kim
is revitalized this evening
after a suspect in custody
has provided authorities
with Miss Kim's exact location.
The only question that remains:
is Margot still alive,
or is it already too late?
We are continuing
to monitor the ground,
as it appears that everyone
is still just waiting
for any update
on the operation below.
But hold on. Hold on.
We are just getting word now
that rescue responders
are beginning an ascent.
Again, for our viewers,
we do not know
what we're about to see here
as we get a peek around...
And there she is.
We are getting
a closer look now,
as two rescue responders are
pulling up
what appears to be Margot Kim
in a body basket
- to the top of this ravine here.
- Again, we just want to warn our viewers
that we do not know
what state she's in,
as we get a look
at Margot's father there.
But they are making their way
up to the top.
And it looks like
responders have gotten her up.
Again, no word yet
as to her status.
And there
you can see her father,
as it appears
that Search and Rescue
is now preparing
to lift Margot's body basket
onto a stretcher
they've just prepared.
Again, this is
live footage here,
as Margot Kim, who has been
missing for the last week,
is now being lifted
onto an emergency...
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Watching movies won't make you rich.
Trading can. FilthyRichFutures.com