(dramatic music)
(coughing)
(sighs)
♪ ♪
(glass shattering,
flames bursting)
♪ ♪
Rot in hell.
SINGER:
♪ Bring me a higher love ♪
♪ Bring me a higher love,
oh, Lord ♪
Lord, direct my footsteps
according to your word
and let no sin rule over me.
Thank you for protecting
my family.
You've kept us free
from tragedy and illness
and you have given us abundance
of wealth.
Everything.
As long as I have breath
in my body
and your spirit in my heart.
I am your servant
and your faithful soldier.
Amen!
- (chuckles)
- Oh!
Now, let's just see. Oh, yeah.
- Look in my eyes.
Let me see you.
SINGER:
♪ Where's that higher love ♪
Well, every superhero
needs a cape, Mama.
Oh, Rose, you hush up.
You hear your daughter?
♪ Think about it
there must be higher love ♪
♪ Down in the heart
or hidden in the stars above ♪
NORAH: Push in, camera one.
Take camera one.
All right.
Y'all are listening today.
Hold steady, camera one.
Hold steady.
Can you hear me in Hong Kong?
From Norway to LA?
Can you hear me in Australia?
The San Francisco Bay.
The Lord is calling on you now.
He's waiting on the line.
Are you ready?
(cheers and applause)
Are you ready? Are you ready?
'Cause we're running out
of time.
Everything we rehearsed
will be on the teleprompter.
- Okay.
- Eric, stick to the line.
(cheers and applause)
Go get 'em, baby.
(whispering)
I'll see you out there.
- Eric, honey?
- EUGENE: Come on, son.
THOMAS: ♪ Try to see
falling behind ♪
Look how far we've come.
25 years.
All things are possible in Him.
- In you.
- In us.
Oh, Lord.
Oh, it's nice of the Reverend
to try and upstage me
on my own network
on today of all days.
He'd be nothing without you.
Rose, I think we should get
the wings.
THOMAS: Be that higher love,
and stick around for an extra
special 25th anniversary.
Yeah, that's right!
Go on. Show Margaret your love.
And may God bless you now.
NORAH: And go.
Live from Sunshine Studios
in beautiful New Orleans.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Margaret Monreaux!
(cheering)
Wow! Hello!
(upbeat music playing)
SINGER: ♪ On the wings ♪
Can you believe that?
Unbelievable.
Hello!
(cheers and applause)
Oh, stop that! No!
I did that!
Look what they made me do!
(cheering continues)
Love you!
Thank you for those warm,
welcoming words.
There is something that I need
to say to all of you.
You and the Lord give me
the strength to do what I do,
so thank you.
(cheers and applause)
Now this mama bear has been
starving herself for a month
to squeeze into
those silly wings.
Ladies, I think it's time
we all had some fried chicken.
WOMAN: Ah, there you go!
Cock on the walk!
That cock better not mess
on my carpet.
MAN: Bite that apple, baby.
Yeah, bite it good.
Sorry, Kansas City Beef.
Your card was declined.
What? Can you... can
you run it again?
- Ginger.
- Yeah.
You better go check on your mom.
She's watching
that TV show again.
(groans)
(rooster crowing)
MARGARET: Thank you
to all my mama bears
for 25 years of support.
She has the perfect
pageant wave.
MARGARET: When we come back,
I have an exciting
announcement...
I was watching that.
What are you doing?
(laughs)
- You have to stop.
- No.
- You're obsessed.
You have a problem.
You know, many
in this country say
that people with our morals
are out of touch or even stupid.
Many of our sponsors wish that
they didn't need your business.
The time has come
to start shopping
in God's light,
so four months from today,
you'll be able to purchase
everything from books,
clothing, and groceries
online from us.
And we can assure you
that every employee,
associate, and vendor...
Mm-hmm.
Will share
your Christian values.
Did you know that some
online retailers
offer pornography
for their subscribers?
- (crowd murmuring)
- ERIC: Yeah.
Yeah, so next to the bleach
in your cart,
you got Drunk Teen Girls
and Boys Gone Wild.
They even sell a product
called Butt Butter.
For every item that you place
in your Praise Cart,
20% of it will go back
to our faith.
To charities and organizations
on the front lines
of God's great commission.
My friends,
I give you Sunny Club.
(cheers and applause)
(upbeat music)
(chanting)
Sunny Club, Sunny Club.
ALL: Sunny Club, Sunny Club.
(audience chanting)
♪ ♪
(twangy singing)
- What's the early word?
- Valuation's off the charts.
- Oh!
- (laughs)
You got a real winner
with this, Eugene.
I swear that camera loves
his face even more than I do.
(both laughing)
I'm sorry, Mama.
I know that wasn't
the planned speech.
- No.
- But I...
Subtlety is the footbridge
to integrity.
Amen.
True integrity means
you're the same in public
as you are in private.
- Mm.
- You attract bees with honey,
not Butt Butter.
Walk with me, Eric.
♪ ♪
I rue the day that Eric
married that man's sister.
They are family now.
We have to treat him as such.
MARGARET: And I do.
Oh, there's my girl!
Why didn't you tell the audience
I designed your outfit?
Confidence is silent, honey.
Insecurities, well,
they're loud.
Coming from the woman with
sparks shooting out her ass?
Baby, that's not insecurity.
That's show biz.
Mama will give you credit
on air Monday morning.
- Thank you, Daddy.
- Mm-hmm.
Don't encourage her.
She wants Sunny Club to carry
that clothing line of hers.
I know, it's her dream,
Margaret,
and I don't know why
we can't just set her up.
It isn't wise
to give children things
- just 'cause they ask for it.
- Mm-hmm.
(country waltz playing)
EUGENE: Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna have to go.
I'm hopping the jet
for D.C. tonight.
- Now?
- Yeah.
I was hoping that you and I
would have some time
together tonight.
SINGER: ♪ Preacher's son
but when his daddy... ♪
Just as soon as I get back.
♪ When they gathered 'round
and started talking ♪
♪ That's when Billy... ♪
Mm.
♪ Then he'd look into my eyes ♪
- ♪ Lord knows to my surprise ♪
- (jet engine roaring)
♪ The only one
who could ever reach me ♪
EUGENE: Ah!
♪ Was the son
of a preacher man ♪
Well, plenty more
where that came from,
because I am one rich
son of a bitch.
(woman giggles)
- ♪ Lord knows he was ♪
- ♪ Ooh yes he was ♪
(loud rumbling, woman screams)
♪ How well I remember ♪
- (engine churning)
- ♪ Taking time to make time ♪
(woman whimpering)
♪ Telling me that
he's all mine ♪
Lord have mercy on this sinner.
(metal rattling)
(woman whimpering)
(indistinct radio chatter,
women screaming)
♪ Was the son
of a preacher man ♪
(upbeat country music)
♪ ♪
(somber music)
THOMAS: Death takes the body,
God takes the soul,
and faith lets us know
that we will meet again.
♪ ♪
He was so loved.
NEWSCASTER:
Memorial services held today
for conservative icon
Eugene Monreaux.
This comes after weeks
of searches
in the Louisiana marsh failed
to recover his body.
NEWSCASTER: And right now
the nation mourns the loss
of the man admired
for both his faith
and his principles.
NEWSCASTER: Meanwhile the face
of the network,
Margaret Monreaux,
hasn't been on air in a month.
MAN: Mrs. Monreaux!
LUKE: Margaret,
did you know any of the women
on the plane with your husband?
Why would somebody
ask such a thing?
MAN: Ginger Sweet?
You've been served.
(LOLO's "Wild")
♪ ♪
SINGER: ♪ Head up
nothing gonna take me down ♪
(moans)
I'm so hot!
- (cow mooing)
- Hey, Rach.
I have to leave for a few days.
You're in charge
until I get back.
(low, angrily) Okay!
(giggles)
Oh! (cow moos)
MAN: (laughing) Oh, yeah.
SINGER: ♪ Let go ♪
♪ Ain't no wrong
get a little bit wild ♪
The worst thing
about being deceived
is knowing you weren't
worth the truth.
How long were you gonna keep
his will from me?
Margaret, I wanted you
to get back on air first.
So I could continue living
a lie?
Eugene was lying, not you.
No, we were lying
to our audience.
We were one. His lie is my lie.
When I think of all
the crap that I put up with
to carry on with our mission,
keeping this family together,
keeping the lid screwed tight
on my honey jar
while he cheated all along.
(breathing heavily)
And you knew.
And you can't say you didn't.
Come on.
Give me a break, Margaret.
(stammers)
I'm sorry I said that.
You deserved better from him.
And from me.
I knew there were
one-night stands,
but I never dreamed
there was a child.
(upbeat music)
♪ ♪
Children.
Keep reading.
♪ ♪
Son of a bitch!
(gasps loudly)
(Keenan The First'
"Mooda Chainz")
(both grunting and shouting)
(grunting)
There a Antonio Rivera here?
(grunts)
RAPPER: ♪ I been going up
Mooda Chainz ♪
♪ Money got yards,
got the range ♪
♪ Check, watch it go yard
on the shakes ♪
Who the hell's Eugene Monreaux?
Yeah, it's mostly CBD.
It's great for pain management
without all the wiggy-wag
and anxiety.
(chuckles)
(knocking at door)
Oh, I gotta call you back.
SINGER: ♪ It's been so hard
to find you ♪
♪ Now is the hour,
sweet and sour ♪
- Jason Conley?
- Yeah, sure.
You've been served.
Thank you.
Hey, do you want a beer?
- WOMAN: Okay.
- Okay, great.
Come on in.
(jazz music playing)
ERIC:
Mama, what's the emergency?
Why are you smoking?
Why are you wearing that glove?
I'm not messing up my nails
with nicotine stains.
I'm a lady who needs a smoke.
I'm not a smoker.
Come downstairs, Margaret.
(exhales sharply) Fine!
♪ ♪
(exhales)
Your father, he was a good man,
but not a faithful man.
He had three children
outside this marriage
from three different women.
- ERIC: What?
- ROSE: No.
FRANKLIN: While the majority
of Eugene's shares
will go to your mother,
he made a provision
that 5% be divided
equally between his children,
and, well, there are five
of you now.
- That's not my dad.
- Yeah, it kind of was.
Yeah.
Your daddy would have
a few drinks occasionally
and become remorseful,
and he called me and insists
the kids be included
and then later he would
reinstate the original will
- with no extramarital children.
- ROSE: Oh, my God.
It seems the drinky-poo will
was in place
at the time of the crash.
"Always together makes
a family forever."
- What a load of crap.
- What a hypocrite.
Why didn't you stop this?
I never knew about the kids!
(exhales sharply)
He did fess up about
that whore in Vegas.
I was so mad,
we slept in separate bedrooms
for six months,
and he only got handies
for six more.
- Oh, Mama!
- ERIC: Okay, Mom.
This can't be legal,
especially if he was drunk.
I've dealt with
a lot of bastards
to get where I am.
These three will be
no different.
Eric, Reverend Thomas
mustn't find out
about this, or Becky.
You want me to lie to my wife?
- I'm not Dad.
- If they find out,
it's over.
Well, who the hell
are these people?
SINGER: ♪ Somebody gotta ♪
♪ Gotta raise a little hell ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ ♪
(Dorothy's "Raise Hell")
♪ Somebody gotta,
gotta raise a little hell ♪
♪ ♪
(kid mumbles)
(elevator door dings)
- (elevator door dings)
- Which floor?
- Same.
- That's good.
- ANTONIO: Bro, do you mind?
- Sure.
- Knock yourself out, man.
- No, dude.
Don't smoke that
in front of my kid.
Of course I'm not the only one.
I'm Ginger.
Apparently I'm your sister.
(quirky music)
♪ ♪
My name is Franklin Lee,
in-house counsel,
and I'll need your letters
and your IDs.
♪ ♪
You must be Ginger,
Antonio, and, uh, Jason.
Well, who's this little cherub?
ANTONIO: This is my son, Jesus.
MARGARET: Oh, if only somebody
could bottle up the smell
of little babies.
If anybody could have,
it would have been Eugene.
Well, all right, then.
These are my children,
Rose and Eric.
Rose?
ERIC: I'm the senior VP
of operations,
at least until the dust settles,
and, uh, you know,
from my perspective,
there's no way I'm giving
a single piece
of my family company
to a hooker...
- Hm?
- ERIC: A hoodlum,
and a drug dealer.
Yo, I'm gonna knock
your teeth in, homie.
This is my humming bird cake.
I made it myself this morning
especially for y'all.
(chuckles) Back up.
I'm not a hooker.
You're not, huh?
Yeah, I pulled up Sin Wagon
on my laptop.
Nuns, milk maids, farm girls,
doing the most despicable,
disgusting things.
So you subscribe
to our premium package?
- Jason, you want some tea?
- You know what?
I'm okay.
Oh, she won't stop asking
until you say yes.
- It's what she does.
- I'd love some.
MARGARET: Rose.
It was, uh, quite a surprise
that all of you
were in Eugene's will.
One which we are prepared
to contest, by the way.
- There's a...
- MARGARET: But in fairness
and sensitivity,
we are prepared
to make an offer.
FRANKLIN: Contingent
on the results of DNA tests
and in signing
a non-disclosure agreement,
each of you
will receive $1 million.
MARGARET:
I hope you enjoy my cake,
after you provide your saliva,
of course.
I grew up dirt poor knowing
Eugene Monreaux was my father.
Y'all built this place
on the back of a secret
I kept for you.
I'm not walking away
for a million bucks.
You're valued at 2.2 billion.
And you flew us coach?
I'm gonna need to talk
this over with my brothers
and we'll get back to you.
You take all the time you need,
but for the financial wellbeing
of the company,
your discretion is required.
We wouldn't want anyone
finding this out
and nor should you.
Well, that's all for now.
Please spit.
(quirky music)
GINGER: In my line of work,
I've learned that
a desperate person
will pay anything.
(spits)
Thank you for the lovely cake,
Mrs. Monreaux.
Oh, you're welcome.
♪ ♪
Maybe we should have some sort
of relationship with them.
I mean, I don't know,
if Dad thought
- putting them in the...
- Can it, Rose.
(exhales)
THOMAS: How'd that go?
How'd what go?
You told Becky.
ERIC: She's my wife, Mom.
Yeah.
THOMAS:
We have bigger fish to fry.
The network is falling apart.
The business of the network
is none of your concern,
Preacher.
You are the talent.
Well, thank you, Franklin,
for acknowledging that.
So here's the plan.
You need to get back on air.
People watch Sunshine
for two reasons: you and me.
Without you, I suffer.
No one should be made to suffer.
So you make Eric the CEO.
I will serve in official
advisory capacity
just as Eugene wanted,
and you go back to doing
what you do best:
recipes and advice.
(soft dramatic music)
Eric, should we grab that lunch?
♪ ♪
(door closes)
(jazzy music playing)
Margaret really hooked us up.
Yeah.
LUKE: Place has been energized
with fresh faces
since the patriarch passed.
Excuse me?
Luke Taylor, Daily Edge.
Reporter?
Well, my mother prefers
investigative journalist.
Rolls off the tongue nice,
right?
You mind if I ask what business
you had today
at Monreaux Unlimited?
BELLMAN: Sir, I'm gonna have
to ask you to leave.
No press allowed.
♪ ♪
You should call me.
(upbeat music playing)
(food sizzling)
GINGER: Dude, they're loaded.
What are you talking about?
I could train full time
and have child care for Jesus.
Man, Eugene knew about you
and he let you struggle.
Look, all I know
is one minute I'm broke,
sweating my ass off in Queens,
and the next minute
some white lady
is offering me
a very delicious piece of cake
and a million bucks.
I'm good with both those things.
And I bet this is
the first time in your life
that you've got real power.
Not strength or muscle,
but power.
- Don't you see that?
- Listen.
I'm taking the money.
Antonio,
I'm asking you to fight.
When was the last time people
like us came out on top?
People like what?
♪ ♪
Is that what you're
gonna teach your son?
♪ ♪
What about those DNA tests?
Positive, except Jason's sample
was contaminated.
He's retaking his.
I am so proud of you.
(upbeat music)
♪ ♪
NORAH: Live from
the Sunshine Studios
in beautiful New Orleans,
ladies and gentlemen,
once again, Margaret Monreaux.
(cheers and applause)
♪ ♪
MARGARET: Thank you.
Thank you all so much
for that warm welcome home.
One month ago,
I lost my beloved husband
and best friend.
I miss him greatly,
and truthfully,
I didn't know if I could go on.
(somber music)
Then I thought of one
of Eugene's favorite verses.
"Be watchful.
"Stand firm in your faith.
Act like men. Be strong."
(machine beeping)
Because of Eugene,
because of your faith
in our mission,
I'm back here today...
Because we have work to do
in our great country.
People like us, people of faith,
we are under constant attack,
and now more than ever,
I realize we must all stay
close to our families
and keep them safe.
That's what Eugene
would have wanted,
both at home
and right here with the family
we have in this room.
Always together makes
a family forever.
And family is the most
valuable thing in the world.
(cheers and applause)
And that's why
we're not walking away
for a million bucks.
FRANKLIN: All of the other kids
have refused our offer.
MARGARET: It's Ginger. (groans)
FRANKLIN: Can you blame them
for wanting
a proper seat at the table?
MARGARET: You sound like
you're on her side.
I'm on my side, Margaret.
I love you
but I got a lot to lose
- if this company goes belly up.
- I know that.
I got the place in Pebble Beach.
You got the loft in SoHo.
Now, you know I like
my real estate, Margaret.
- I said I know.
- (dogs barking)
Just saying,
taking a moment to look at it
from her side, okay?
That will keep us from being
helpless in the negotiation.
The only time a Monreaux girl
is helpless
is when her nails are drying.
If Ginger wants a proper seat
at the table,
- let's give her one.
- (horse brays)
I think a ladies luncheon
would be of great benefit
to Miss Sweet.
Oh, Madge, darling,
- you just look wonderful.
- Oh.
Did you get the chocolate
éclairs that I sent you?
They were Eugene's favorite.
Oh, dear. Who is that?
(sweeping orchestral music)
MARGARET: An acquaintance.
Excuse me.
Of course.
♪ ♪
Margaret, darling.
Thank you for the invitation.
You should feel stupid
right now,
'cause I certainly don't.
Why, you wore my color.
(Rose chuckles)
♪ ♪
Where did you get that outfit
on such short notice?
- A friend sent it overnight.
- I love it.
GINGER: Well, I love
what you're wearing.
- You make that, too?
- ROSE: Uh-huh.
I have a whole line planned,
but somehow I'm not gaining
any traction on it.
Excuse me.
Good afternoon, ladies,
and welcome to
our annual ladies luncheon.
This year our focus is
on the city's mentoring program
for girls,
or as we prefer to call them,
businesswomen of the future.
It's been a sad time
at the network,
so although I previously
agreed to speak today,
I hope you'll understand
and forgive me
if I do not, but in my place,
I'd like to introduce a woman
with a successful company
that she built
from the ground up.
The lovely lady
in that charming hoop skirt,
Miss Ginger Sweet.
(applause)
Come on up here, Ginger!
(upbeat country music)
♪ ♪
Let's welcome Ginger.
Why don't you start by telling
these young ladies
what you do for a living,
sweetie.
Inspire them.
I know how proud you are
of what you do.
(soft music)
♪ ♪
Well, it seems that Miss Sweet
has a bit of stage fright.
We've all been there.
Why don't we bring up
our next speaker
and, uh, we'll get this
all sorted out?
(chuckles)
Come on over here, sweetie.
There's no place for you
in civil society.
I'm offering you
two million now,
which we feel is quite generous,
considering you represent
no more than ten minutes
of my husband's pleasure.
♪ ♪
You take the money and go home.
Nothing makes me happier
than cooking for my boy.
- Thanks for coming over.
- Aw. Wow.
Mm-hmm.
No, no, no. None for me.
Becky and I are off sugar.
It's 100% pure unfiltered maple.
It's good for you.
It's full of magnesium
and zinc and...
All right, all right.
(chuckles)
Why am I here?
Well, I've thought about it
and I've prayed on it,
and I don't think you're ready
to take your father's place
in the company.
Now, the world is watching
and we need
to take things very slowly
for a beat.
Slow? No, why slow?
The company needs to take action
to preserve its future now.
Son, this may not feel like
a loving statement but...
You lack polish.
(soft dramatic music)
♪ ♪
Maple syrup is still sugar,
Mama.
♪ ♪
You can dress it up
all you like.
It's still gonna kill you.
Dad told the Reverend
he wanted me to take over.
Why are you denying me?
What, doesn't Dad get
a say in any of this,
or have you already
forgotten him?
(door opening)
♪ ♪
Come on in, Franklin.
Mom's serving up sugar.
♪ ♪
(door closes)
Rumors starting to fly
about our hotel guests.
Might be best to keep them
out of public view.
We'll bring them out
to the camp.
Let everybody simmer down
for a bit.
It's time to replace Eugene.
♪ ♪
For the sake of the family.
Earl. (dog tag jingling)
(dog whining)
This is for you, baby.
- (TV playing indistinctly)
- Eric!
NEWSCASTER: For more
on this developing story,
we take you live
to the company's headquarters
- at downtown New Orleans...
- ERIC: You all right?
NEWSCASTER: Where a news
conference is happening now.
I would like
to assure our audience
and our shareholders
that we are far
from a rudderless ship.
Monreaux Unlimited
will remain in the family
in trusted, responsible hands.
Effective immediately,
the new CEO
for Monreaux Unlimited
will be Margaret Monreaux.
MARGARET: Thank you.
- (camera shutters clicking)
- Thank you all so much.
Your mom's a bitch.
MARGARET: I take this
responsibility seriously.
- Two million?
- Wow.
- Well done.
- I'm not taking it.
Why?
I can see a loss
when it's coming.
- (knocking at door)
- We're worth more.
All of us are worth more.
They're trying to erase us.
If I'm gonna be erased,
it's gonna cost her.
Good morning.
Mrs. Monreaux
has invited you all
to stay at her hunting camp.
So she can shoot us?
ANTONIO: Yo, yo, look.
You can stay here if you want,
but I'm going.
Me, too. I'm not worth more.
(dramatic music)
(car engine revving)
♪ ♪
(car door opens, closes)
ERIC: I can't believe
my own mother
would take a job
from right underneath me!
- I went to Wharton!
- You about flunked out.
ERIC: You think the Reverend's
gonna be reassured
with you at the helm?
You watch that tongue,
young man.
I created the network,
I have the most-watched
lifestyle show on TV,
and I am your mother.
I will not tolerate disrespect.
- (helicopter whirring)
- ROSE: Hey, Eric.
Our sister and brothers
are here.
They're staying with us.
You have lost your damn mind!
- (slap smacks)
- Oh.
♪ ♪
(exhales sharply)
(upbeat music)
(door squeaking)
MARGARET: Welcome to the camp.
Make yourselves at home.
Take your shoes off.
Oh, these are my Tuesday socks,
and it's Friday. Are you sure?
You got a point. (laughs)
I'll take my hat off, then.
Antonio, I got you a babysitter.
Pick a room upstairs. Any room.
Any room? Ah, thank you.
Hey, let me show you around.
- Okay.
- Come on, okay.
So, this is our, like, main...
About lunch.
What I did was wrong.
We're both strong-willed women
working through our emotions,
and I'd like it
if we could start over.
You really think I'm stupid,
don't you?
No, definitely not, Ginger.
I've learned never
to underestimate
Eugene's progeny.
Pick a room, Ginger.
I'm cooking you all
a traditional Cajun dinner
tonight.
I know you probably have some
hard feelings towards Dad...
But I think if you'd known him,
you would have liked him.
- I don't know about that.
- Hmm.
He was, like, the only person
who believed
in what I'm trying to do.
You mind if I smoke some weed?
Just calms the nerves.
What do you have
to be nervous about?
(scoffs)
I'm kidding. (laughs)
This entire situation would
turn anybody into a pot head.
SINGER: ♪ Never change, yeah,
just always the same ♪
♪ Whatever ya need ♪
Oh.
SINGER: ♪ And all you gotta do
is call ♪
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I can't believe I did that.
I'd like to clear the air
and apologize to you three
for how I've conducted myself
After much prayer
and reflection,
I've decided to give each
of you 1%
of the company.
It is what Eugene wanted.
All I ask is that you sign NDAs
protecting the reputation
of the company
and our interests in it.
1% comes out to 6 million.
Wow.
- Thank you.
- No.
Uh, Ginger, you do realize
that she's being really,
really nice to us right now?
MARGARET: Thank you, Antonio.
JASON: Personally, I wanna say
I will take your offer
and go home
and none of you
have to see me ever,
ever again. I totally promise.
GINGER:
Given there are five of us
including Eric and Rose,
I think 5% is a better number.
$30 million?
And biblically speaking,
the number five symbolizes
God's grace,
goodness,
and favor toward humans.
It's mentioned 318 times
in scripture.
The ten commandments contain
two sets of five commandments.
The first five commandments
are related to our treatment
and relationship with God,
and the last five commandments
concern our relationship
with others,
like me, Antonio,
Jason, Eric, and Rose.
What do you think, Rose?
(soft dramatic music)
Is $30 million enough
to ghost this joint
and start your own
fashion house?
Yep.
♪ ♪
You are a goddess.
Just a complete
and total goddess.
I wish I was more like you.
You're more like me
than you know.
I see you.
I see a girl who spent
her whole life
making sure her mom was okay
before she even thought
to have a thought for herself.
Tell me about your mom, Ginger.
Can you just keep telling me
how awesome I am?
No prob.
(knocking at door)
(door opens)
Despite what you may think,
your father cared deeply
about you.
You didn't know it,
but he followed your business.
He didn't like it,
but he couldn't help
but see a bit of himself in you.
He wrote this letter recently.
(clears throat)
Said he wasn't getting
any younger.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
EUGENE: Dear Ginger,
I want you to know that
I've thought of you every day.
I'm proud of who you are
because you're not afraid
to be who you are.
I've always loved you.
I wish I'd been
the father you deserved.
(upbeat music)
ERIC: Come on, church!
Put your hands together!
Hands together for the Lord!
♪ Trying just to hold on ♪
♪ While the ground
keeps shaking ♪
♪ But I'm never gonna question
who I place my faith in ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ No, no, no 'cause He rose ♪
(cheering)
(laughs)
♪ Yeah He rose ♪
♪ ♪
I love when he sings.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
ERIC: ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ 'Cause he rose ♪ - Whoo!
Hands together for the Lord.
He's alive forever.
For Tuesday's cooking segment,
how about deep fried ham cheese
basil sandwiches?
The spirit comes into a man's
heart when he is in need,
and the Spirit says,
"Lay it all unto me."
Brother Eric,
unburden your heart.
Thank you, Reverend.
Um, yeah, my heart is, uh...
My heart's heavy
and full of grief
for myself and my family,
uh, for I fear
that we've lost our way.
Speak the truth, all right?
- God's listening.
- Unburden your heart, brother.
ERIC: So my father, Eugene,
um, the man that...
That you all knew and loved...
- Oh!
- Unbeknownst to us,
- he had three...
- (grunts)
Matthew 26:15 asks,
"What are you willing to give me
if I deliver Him over to you?"
Now, there are a lot
of businesses out there
who take far more than they give
when it comes to deliveries.
They say vote with your dollar.
Well, I say pray
with your dollar.
Reverend, can I have a word?
I give you Sunny Club.
Hello, everybody.
Now, Sunny Club
is an online fellowship...
I see what you're doing.
You will lose. You hear me?
You put Eric in charge
or the world hears the truth.
You were preaching
inside a double-wide
when I found you. I created you.
- You don't scare me.
- Well, maybe I should.
Can you hear me in Hong Kong?
From Norway to LA?
- Can you hear me in Australia?
- (chuckles)
The San Francisco Bay?
You'll be lucky
if they can hear you
in Luling, Louisiana after this.
You're out of your depth, CEO.
You get rid of me,
you lose all your precious
Sunny Club customers.
Who'll be left
to buy your toilet paper
and your greeting cards?
You might even have
to sell Butt Butter.
MARGARET: Simply sign up...
Excuse me. I have a show to do.
Praise Cart and behold...
- Norah!
- They're coming soon.
THOMAS:
Today's sermon is Luke 8:17.
"For nothing is hidden that
will not become evident
when come to light." Eric?
(dramatic music)
♪ ♪
(crowd murmuring)
(clears throat)
We all have secrets.
Don't we?
(cell phone ringing)
- Hi.
- TINA: Hey, baby doll.
Rachel and I were just thinking
about how much we missed you.
- Hi.
- How's it going down there?
Well, you're not going
to believe it,
but I am staying at their house
in the country.
Of course you are.
- (sighs) I bet it's huge.
- Hey, I wanna talk to her.
Honey, when are you gonna
come back, huh?
Tina, give it.
Let me talk to her.
TINA: All right, Rachel
wants to say something to you.
RACHEL: Hey, did you
not get my text?
Yeah, I just... I haven't
had time to...
Big Sally poached
Sheila and Kitty.
I have been
at the mall recruiting
for, like, four straight days.
Hmm? Yeah, I'm listening.
Okay, let's just talk
about it later.
Obviously, you're busy there.
- GINGER: I'm sorry, Rach.
- Mm.
Yeah. You're fine.
GINGER: It's just...
Don't tell Mom...
But...
I'm starting to like
these people.
Eugene wrote me a letter.
(soft dramatic music)
♪ ♪
(door opens)
GINGER: I have a question
about my father.
Hello, honey.
I didn't see you there.
I'm a lefty.
My mom told me that
I got that from Eugene.
Is that true?
Is everything all right,
sweetie?
A right-handed person
wrote this.
♪ ♪
Eugene didn't feel this way
about me, did he?
Did you fake this?
What kind of person does that?
(exhales sharply) I...
Uh, I don't know what to say.
I don't want your money.
Or your disgusting family.
You know, maybe someday
you'll be as good
as you think you are,
and just so you know,
Eugene spent more than
ten minutes with my mother.
They were together for a year.
♪ ♪
(zipper zipping)
(dramatic country music)
Jason and I are taking the deal.
Fine. Take their money.
Make sure you get it
while they still have it.
Don't mess this up for me.
♪ ♪
I am struggling, Lord.
I am struggling to understand
your will for me.
Show me the way.
I will follow.
(baby cooing)
♪ ♪
I'm so sorry.
He... he got away from me.
♪ ♪
Um, Miss Monreaux, I, uh...
I just wanted to say thanks.
For everything.
You're gonna change
my little boy's life.
♪ ♪
Have you thought
about education?
You... you have
to get on that right now.
There are some amazing schools
in New Orleans.
You should discuss it
with his mother.
She's not really in the picture.
Oh.
ANTONIO: Miss Monreaux,
I wanted you to know that
Ginger's been talking
to the press.
♪ ♪
LUKE: Did you get my message?
GINGER: Are they ready for me?
Yes, full house,
but we got a problem.
What's the issue?
I gave you the exclusive.
We had a deal.
Yeah, but my boss just made
a different one.
Ginger, don't go!
MARGARET: Ladies and gentlemen,
I thank you for coming together
on such short notice.
In the past few days,
it has become abundantly clear
that I cannot do this job alone.
Congratulations, CEO.
(exhales)
Now with the passing of Eugene,
we lost our CEO,
I lost my husband,
and Rose and Eric lost
their father.
But we have gained as well.
Unbeknownst to us,
Eugene had fathered
three other children.
(crowd murmuring)
And they're here with us today.
God, he sees all,
and he forgives all.
- Eugene. (chuckles)
- (mutters)
We all know that
he had his demons.
We all do, and so I forgive him.
And Reverend Thomas,
he forgives him.
Oh, now that's
true Christianity.
Judge not lest ye be judged.
That's what the Reverend
told me,
and he got us through this.
Thank you, Paul.
God decides who comes
into your life,
but your heart must decide
who stays,
so with the Lord's guidance,
I welcome Antonio Rivera,
Jason Conley,
and Ginger Sweet to ours.
(country music)
Hey, Jason, where...
Where you going?
He's a camera-shy cutie.
Ginger, get on up here.
I know you're not shy.
(camera shutter clicks)
Did you really think you'd have
the upper hand
with the press in my town?
♪ ♪
What in Heaven's name is that?
That's my mother.
♪ ♪
(suspenseful music)
(gasping)
Is this Hell?
No, Louisiana.
♪ ♪
(upbeat country music)
SINGER: ♪ Gold coin ♪
♪ Stacks on stacks ♪
♪ Make 'em write that check ♪
♪ I want hard cash ♪
♪ Greenback ♪
(sings indistinctly)
♪ Oh, that's a fact ♪
♪ I got the right class ♪
♪ Yo, what's her weight ♪
♪ Rubies, rubies, yin and yang ♪
♪ Pounds on pounds
in Swiss banks ♪
♪ That's the language
that I speak ♪
♪ Now I lay me down to sleep ♪
♪ Amen ♪
Subtitles Diego Moraes(oakislandtk)
www.opensubtitles.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org