Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Corner of Wiltern and Wetherly.
Tumbler messed up.
Said the Porsche would be
at the corner of Wiltern and Wetherly.
- Right there.
- You're bullshittin' me, right?
- 9024 Wiltern?
- What? That?
I gotta get my tool.
- Kip!
- He ain't bullshittin'.
Kip! Man, that's not a tool.
That's a damn brick.
Kip, man, we gonna use a brick, man,
we might as well call prison
and make reservations. Aw, come on.
- Oh...
- Get the number.
42850.
Hurry up, man.
Man, let's go!
Let's get the hell outta here.
OK, Billy Badass. You got us in here, now
tell me how the hell we gonna get out.
Oh, no, I know you ain't gonna do
what I think you're gonna do.
Oh, man!
Come on!
- This ain't The Dukes of Hazzard.
- Come on!
Aaaaaagh!
Yo, so check out my new move.
I call it "the stranger."
What I do is, I sit on my hand for, like,
15, 20 minutes, until it goes numb.
No feeling at all.
And then... I rub one out.
"The stranger," huh?
It's like a little boy's nursery school
I've come upon here.
Where are they?
Hey!
- Leave those people alone, man.
- Oh, my God. Sweetie, you're so talented.
- Stolen car. Stolen car.
- I know. I know.
Hey, I love ya.
Man, we going to jail, man!
Come on!
...hands behind your back.
You have the right to remain silent.
Hey, watch it!
We have a silver Porsche,
estimated speed 80 miles per hour,
- heading west on Wilshire Boulevard.
- Yeah.
This is Air One.
We have a visual of the suspect,
southbound on Vincent Thomas Bridge.
- Something wrong, Tumbler?
- Yeah, I'm missing Jerry Springer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
That's right, that's
right, that's right!
- Ha-ha! What's up, old man?
- She'll go zero to 60 in 5.2 seconds.
Believe me, I can vouch for that.
Ground units, be advised, suspects last
seen entering south side of warehouse.
13 down, 37 to go.
- What the hell is that?
- What is that, man?
Now you've gone and done it, Raines.
Tumbler! Get the board
and get the lights!
- I got it!
- This is bullshit!
- It's not comin' off!
- Keys! Get the keys!
- I got 'em, I got 'em!
- Come on, everybody, let's go! Hurry up!
- I got it!
- Let's go!
Toby. get it!
Let's go, boys!
Come on, come on, come on!
I got the light! I got the light!
Go, 90. go!
Let's go!
Shit!
VIN number on that? Got it.
What do we got?
All gone. We didn't get a single one of 'em,
and we are talkin' about professionals.
No visible damage to locking mechanisms,
steering columns or ignitions,
and, as you can see,
these are not Honda Civics.
This is one of three brand-new Mercedes -
a car they say is unstealable.
Yeah, unless you get
the laser-cut transponder key
sent directly to the US dealer
from Hamburg.
They got somebody
working on the inside.
Let's find out which dealership sold 'em,
serviced 'em, et cetera, et cetera.
Yeah, I'll get on it.
- Mr. Drycoff?
- Yeah?
Let's impound these
cars for one month.
I don't give a damn
if they belong to Torn Cruise.
Control.
Vision.
Determination.
These are the three
fundamental components
of the new-generation
race-car driver.
Speed is a by-product. Goin' fast.
But remember - the car is you.
You are the car.
OK? Let's ride!
Billy, you just shaved one second
off your lap time!
Tommy, I don't know what that was,
but it wasn't driving.
Go get 'em!
Well, well, well.
What do you pay your pit crews with?
Oreos and Gummi Bears?
I folded, Atley. You know that.
What are you doing here?
- Is there some place we can talk?
- About what?
About your brother
and the deep shit he's in.
Frank. Would you watch the kids
for a minute?
- Tell me about Kip.
- He took a job and he fumbled it.
Now he's jammed up.
He's jammed up bad.
- What kind of job?
- A boost. A big boost.
A boost.
What's Kip doin' on a boost?
Oh, you're shittin' me, man. Kip's become
quite the little crew runner since you left.
- You don't talk to your ma?
- She neglected to mention it.
Listen, I need somethin'.
I need something cold to drink.
I thought we were goin'
someplace to talk.
- Who was the job for?
- A new guy named Raymond Calitri.
They call him the Carpenter. He's runnin'
all the dark ponies down there now.
He's a full-on devil-came-down-
to-Long-Beach trip.
He's bad.
He's real bad.
And this Calitri
is the one who's after my brother?
Like stains on a mattress.
And you should know I work for him.
There weren't a lot of opportunities
for retired car thieves on the gimp.
He put me to work.
But I gotta tell you, Memphis, this guy,
he scares the shit out of even me.
What are you doing, man?
Stop!
Atley Jackson.
Right.
- They have Kip.
- Take me there.
Raymond Calitri, Memphis Raines.
I try to learn your ways,
understand your obsessions.
But this baseball,
it's so bleedin' boring. Isn't?
Where's my brother?
Memphis Raines.
Your legend precedes you.
Atley tells me you're the best.
After you left, auto theft
in the South Bay area went down 47%.
Where's my brother?
I'm proud of these. Straddle chair
from the Arts and Crafts period.
Mahogany table with cloud-lift pattern,
black walnut wine table.
Metal's cold, ugly.
Wood's warm, clean.
Provided by nature.
To see a piece of furniture take shape,
it's like watching a child grow.
I asked you a question.
They threw us out England,
threw us out of France, but here we are.
Flourishing, really,
except for the minor inconvenience of
despising everything about your country.
On this list, you'll find 50 cars.
Five-zero.
I need all 50 delivered
to Long Beach Harbor, pier 14,
by 8am four days from now.
I'm paying $200,000.
I'm not interested.
I'm just here for my brother.
Your Kip came to me.
He had street cred.
The brother of the notorious
Memphis Raines.
So two weeks ago I hired him
and advanced him $10,000.
Atley told me. If it's about the advance,
I can understand your anger.
A debt has to be settled.
Ten grand, from me to you.
- I wish it was that easy.
- I don't see the complication.
I have four days to deliver 50 cars,
and I have no cars.
- Well, that's another problem.
- It is another problem, isn't it?
It's about me delivering 50 top-end cars
because I said I would,
because if I don't, my South American
friend goes somewhere else from now on.
And that's not good.
It's a humiliation.
Because I'm the arsehole
who said I could deliver.
Am I an arsehole?
Do I look like an arsehole?
Yeah.
- I need that paper satisfying.
- I'm retired.
Now, where the hell is my brother?
I made this as well.
My first one.
It takes 80,000 pounds of pressure
to crush a car.
Kip?
- Who's that?
- Memphis.
- Oh, shit.
- You OK?
- Shut it off!
- Turn it off!
You've got 30 seconds
to consider your options.
Shut it off!
One. You kill me, they kill you,
your brother dies anyway.
Two. You lie, you accept the job,
you take your brother, you run.
I hunt you down, I kill you,
I kill your brother
and I kill your mother
for the aggravation you've caused me.
Three. You accept the deal, you steal
some cars, you make some money
and you be a big brother.
- Memphis!
- 8am, Friday morning.
The cars are on the boat,
or your brother's in the coffin.
Get me out of here!
Somebody get me out of here!
Listen, you really
don't have to make me anything.
Oh, hey, you come down here,
you save my ass. It's the least I can do.
Hey, I heard you were, uh, pumping gas
some place up north, or something, right?
- Yeah, working with kids.
- Oh, yeah.
First place.
I remember this.
Oh, yeah. That was a...
that was a long time ago.
- What did you put in it?
- I don't know.
It's good.
- Does Mom know about any of this?
- No, she doesn't, and...
I don't think she should.
You know, she works really hard, and...
She doesn't need to know
about any of this stuff.
Look, you know,
I got everything under control.
Kitchen's on fire.
Uh... Man!
Hey, Memphis.
It's good to see you.
Haul the cartons over there!
- Hey, Fuzzy.
- Aw, shit. What are you doing here?
- I told you I don't know anything.
- Yeah, but you're a liar.
- You're gonna get me fired, man.
- Fired? That's not good.
- You're on parole, right?
- Fuzzy. Hey.
Nobody wants to get you fired.
We just need this information, is all.
Two weeks ago, a call came in
for a lot of top-end cars.
- And who made that call?
- I don't have a clue.
- OK, we should go talk to your boss.
- Shh!
The delivery date.
I know the delivery date.
- And when is that?
- Thursday, Friday, end of the week.
Well, you get me a name
within 48 hours, or we'll be back.
- Good to see you, buddy.
- Thank you.
- I'm looking for Helen Raines.
- Helen, some guy is here for you.
What guy?
What's he look like?
Like a firecracker.
Like your son.
- You look so good.
- Thank you, Mom.
- I got a spring bouquet.
- What are you doing here?
Well, Atley Jackson came to see me.
He told me something about Kip.
Can I help you with one of these?
Tell Castlebeck he's not gonna believe
who just walked into the Quality Cafe.
I can't say I'm surprised.
All his life he looked up to you,
tried to be you.
Guess now he is.
So why is this happening?
I send you guys money.
He met some people, and he changed.
He lost that... that sweetness.
You know?
OK.
Tell me.
How deep in is he?
Deep.
Can you get him out?
It means doing things.
Things I told you
I'd never do again.
Do what it takes, Randall.
- When did you get into town, Raines?
- Last night.
- Last night? What for?
- I thought I'd catch a Lakers game.
Heard we got Shaquille.
You guys wanna go?
- Guess not.
- Randall, Randall, Randall. Come here.
I get this call from this uniform,
you know. Axton.
Very nice man.
Remembers everything.
This man calls me up, says,
"Guess who's back in town."
I say, "Who?"
He says, "Randall Raines."
I say, "Randall Raines the car thief?"
He says, "Yeah."
I say, "impossible."
He says, "No, he's back."
I say, "No, he's not." He says, "Yes, I will
bet you $200 I just saw Randall Raines."
- You guys said a lot. Look, Detective...
- No, whoa, whoa.
What's really, really
ironic about this -
two nights ago, we snare these 13
fresh stolens waiting for export, right?
And at the time I'm thinking,
"This feels like Randall Raines."
Now, it didn't have
your panache, your ﬂash,
but it just felt like Randall Raines.
And now here you are.
Look, I don't know what you boys are
looking for, but I just got back. OK?
It was a family emergency.
Now, that's the truth.
"Family emergency." Yeah, I got
a family emergency, too, Randall.
I gotta go tell my woman
that I just lost $200 on a stupid deal.
- Mm, she's mean.
- What?
She can be mean.
It's not so...
Come here.
Come here, Randall.
And take those glasses off, Randall,
please. Do me a favor.
Six years ago you make
a real smart move, you know.
You retire from a life that's gonna get
you busted or killed, or maybe even both.
And I'm thinkin' that not putting
you away when I had a chance
is like this big bug up the ass of this
real impressive career that I've had.
Oh, yeah, well, without disappointment,
you can't appreciate victory.
- Eleanor tell you that?
- Well, now, that's hittin' below the belt.
Yeah, all right, let me tell you
about "below the belt," Randall.
I tell you what - from here on out,
if you walk across the street
outside of a crosswalk,
if you roll through a stop sign,
if you use an aerosol can
in a manner other than directed...
I mean, I don't care. You make one slip,
and I will put you away for good.
- OK.
- By the time you get out, asshole,
there won't even be cars.
We'll all be cruisin' around in,
you know, little spaceships.
That's gonna suck.
Who's Eleanor?
It's a damn car.
And don't ever talk about my wife.
Excuse me.
Do you know where Otto is?
He's in the back, in the paint shop.
Is that you?
It's about time you came to see me.
- I missed you.
- Good to see you!
- You look great.
- It's good to see you.
- You remember my Junie?
- Hey, Junie. How are you?
- We're doing good, thank you.
- Good. Good.
- You look happy.
- Well, I am happy. I really am.
- So what happened here?
- What do you mean?
Well, it's nice. But the chop shop,
the stripped cars, my education...
What happened?
Hey.
Old age happened. That's what happened.
Got tired of killin' 'em.
You know, I woke up
one morning and thought:
"I'm no longer a destroyer.
I am a means of resurrection."
Now we restore, we revive. Come here.
Remember when we used to do this?
- What?
- You know. Come here. OK.
The Ferrari 365 GTB/4 Daytona.
Le Mans 1971.
- Quad cam.
- That's a V-12.
V-12! Right, right, right, right!
Here it peaks... at 5500 RPM!
What do you know about
Raymond Calitri?
- Who?
- Raymond Calitri.
Uh, excuse us, sweetness.
I'll be right back.
- We can talk right here.
- No, no, no, no. It's all right.
Raymond Calitri.
He's a jackal tearing at the soft belly
of our... of our fair town.
And he's an asshole to boot,
so be careful.
I heard about Kip.
- Are you considering a comeback tour?
- Do you think it can be done?
Don't do this to me, OK? Please.
Please. Not now.
Oh, man.
- How many cars?
- 50.
- How many days?
- Three.
How many in your crew?
One, but I came here hoping
to negotiate for a second.
No way. It can't be done. I mean, you need
time to prep, time to shop. You know that.
It has to be.
They're gonna kill him.
Man.
It was a mistake to come here.
You have a great life now.
I don't wanna upset that.
Uh, wait a minute.
Whoa. Hold on.
Look around you.
These days I'm all
about second chances.
So let's make a few phone calls
and we'll go from there, OK?
OK.
Don't look at me.
Look at the people next to you!
Turn the wheel!
Pull over!
Pull it the hell over!
- Asshole!
- Learn how to drive!
Don't touch nothin'. Just...
No!
You can't negotiate turns,
you can't signal properly,
you can't maintain speed, you can't
parallel park. Hell, you can't drive, honey.
Shit, I can't swim.
I know I can't.
So you know what I do?
I stay my black ass out the pool!
All right, now, just...
Just... Can you...
Hello?
Memphis!
Hey, how are you?
Sure, sure. When?
OK.
All right, man.
Thanks a lot.
Donny.
Just take it around the block
a couple of times, OK? All right.
Hello, I'm calling for Frankie Fish.
Frank's dead, man.
Yeah, he got scragged.
I'm sorry.
Uh, yeah, I'm looking
for Henry Santoro.
He went down to Florida
with that asshole Frankie Fish.
You see him,
you tell him I want my money.
I didn't mess with your money.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm looking for Dan and Mikey.
Both of 'em up to Chino,
doin' a nickel apiece.
No, I'm not so sure
I wanna tell you who this is.
Yeah, try it, asshole.
You sound, uh, very busy right now.
You sound very, very busy.
Whoo.
- There's only two names left.
- Yeah? I wanna see who you got.
Sphinx...
Those two? No way.
- There's no one else.
- Are you sure?
- You tell him.
- Listen, why should I be...
You were the one
who answered the phone, right?
Fine!
But how's a guy who can't speak
gonna take a phone call?
You've got a call!
Sphinx, is that you?
Press a button if it's you.
- Sway, you set up this brake job?
- Yeah.
He warped all four rotors. He must've been
riding those brakes like an old lady.
- That's nice.
- Sounds like the left bank's running lean.
The service department's over there.
- Can I talk to you?
- Talk to me? Yeah, sure. Talk.
- Well, thing of it is, I came back because...
- Do you know what time it is?
It's 5:30.
I came back because...
- I gotta go. I'm late for work.
- Here.
- You're at work.
- I got two jobs.
I have discovered that you have to
work twice as hard when it's honest.
- Hey, Sway, can I get another shot?
- Yeah.
- You're still looking amazing.
- While you look like a bible salesman.
You're healed.
- Can we improvise a little bit?
- Sure. What do you have in mind?
Do you wanna get a little crazy?
There's a Cutlass 4-4-2 in the back.
We can strip down and shine the hood.
What do you say?
- Uh, that's not what I had in mind.
- No?
It's about my brother.
- Kip's in trouble.
- In trouble?
- He took a boost, and he blew it.
- Shit.
- And you got some Italians?
- Five or six.
- Right.
- It's 50 ladies in 24 hours, $200,000.
Well, I've cleaned up.
I understand. I hate to even
come here and ask you...
- Sway, can I get that drink now, please?
- Yes.
And I had to ask a few of the others,
too, and I feel bad about it, but...
But you had no choice.
You had to come here. Yeah.
Pretty much.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
I'd love to help Kip,
but I'm not into the life anymore.
- Well, that's a good thing.
- Yeah.
- I'm glad to see you're doing well.
- Sorry I can't help you.
- I'd like to pay for your drink.
- That's fine.
How about that drink?
Yeah, how about that drink?
Raines! Memphis Raines, huh?
- Do I know you?
- Well, you should know me,
considering all the business you done
screwed up for me in the past, baby.
- Johnny B.
- That's me.
What can I do for you?
Well, I'm gonna tell you
what you can do for me, baby.
Get out of Long Beach tonight.
I'll be gone in three days.
I'm just here on some family business.
Word on the street says Raymond Calitri
hired you and your brother for a top order.
- A order should've went to me.
- That's not the way it went down, Johnny.
Hey! Get away from my car, asshole!
You got somethin' to say
before I kill you, fool?
Sphinx.
Otto send you?
Oh, Dad.
Probably both be working
at the dealership if he hadn't died.
Just like normal people.
Shit.
What's the matter with you?
Man, six years does
a lot of different things to people.
You know, I don't
know where you went,
but, you know, you're in there,
you're talkin' about bein' normal.
I mean, you were always the one
who was goin' after the easy money.
I didn't do it for the money.
I did it for the cars.
Gleaming in marina blue...
sunflower yellow... Marlboro red.
Begging to be plucked.
And I'd do it.
I'd boost her...
and just blast to Palm Springs,
instantly feeling
better about being me.
And then, the next day, it seems
like, I'm getting shot at,
my friends are dying,
people are going to jail.
I didn't like what I'd become.
Yeah, and then you left,
and then I didn't have
a brother anymore.
And now you wanna give me advice,
and I don't even know you.
And, you know, I got my own family now.
I got my own friends.
And, you know, you can say what you want
about them, but they're loyal.
Well, when you hit the wall,
the same thing is gonna happen.
You and your family
are either gonna get shot
or get a five-year jolt at Corcoran.
Those Mercedes we impounded,
need those newfangled laser-cut keys?
Each one's from Dressner Foreign Motors,
downtown Newport,
where all the employees are clean
except for him.
James Lakewood, served a nickel
at Folsom for auto insurance fraud.
Well, gosh, I bet he just neglected
to mention that
to the people
at Dressner Foreign Motors, huh?
It gets better. Young James there
places orders for lost keys
to Mercedes home office in Germany.
The list.
Ah, the list.
I guess we gotta start beatin' the bushes
and try to find out where they... Whoa.
- 1967 Shelby GT 500.
- I know. I know.
You got Eleanor here?
Otto, there's somebody
here to see you.
Oh! The puppy's a big dog now.
- How you doin'?
- Hey, there, Kip. What is this up...
What's that up under there?
Hey, Otto. How you doin'?
It's a long time.
Good to see you.
What are you doin' here, Kip?
Well, actually...
We came to talk about some things.
- About what?
- Well, you know.
It seems like you guys need a little help,
and we thought that we should participate.
But I just promised Morn
I was getting you out of this.
Listen... No, no, we're talking
about a lot of money here.
- And if you guys think you're gonna be...
- What? Money?
...gettin' into our Kool-Aid...
Is that why you think I'm doing this?
You inconsiderate little punk!
- If you wanna participate, tell Morn...
- You think three washed-up car thieves...
...why her little pumpkin's gonna get hurt!
- ...are gonna steal 50 cars in two days?
Hey. Hey.-
This is why I do not
do business with family.
I think you should consider this.
Oh, come on, now, Otto, please. No,
his criminal career has come to an end.
Well, his life will come to an end
unless we pull this off.
And how can we do it without him?
It can't be done, and you know it.
- You guys have any skills at all?
- Please.
Yeah, we have skills. Urn, Mirror Man
here, he's an electronics expert.
You know, he's got some gadgets that
you old farts probably never heard of.
You know, uh, Tumbler over here, he can
pretty much drive anything with wheels,
and, you know,
some things without wheels.
And, uh, Toby, he's a computer genius.
He does fascinating things with computers.
What exactly can you do
with a computer, Toby?
I can hack into the DMV mainframe,
I can change VIN numbers,
I can change addresses, registrations.
I can do a lot of really tricky stuff, OK?
All right, all right,
we do this, we do it my way.
I run this show.
You take your orders from me.
If you have any problems with that,
you can leave now.
No, that's fine.
Who is Gilligan here,
and what does he do?
Gilligan is actually Freb. Freb can order
pizzas like nobody's business.
- What?
- It's true.
Hey, People gotta eat, right?
This is outrageous.
I want my lawyer.
- I'm not saying a word till I get a lawyer.
- All right, James, that's an option.
- And, frankly, a reasonable one.
- So you call your lawyer, James.
You tell him you've been arrested
on suspicion of grand theft auto.
- We indict you.
- He'll bail you out.
- And we move on to trial.
- OK, OK.
Kid came to me, said
he'd pay $500 a key.
So I put the order forms through, and
he picked 'em up a couple days later.
- What's the kid's name?
- We kept it anonymous.
He was a well-built kid.
Uh, looks like a boxer.
- What do you want me to do?
- When he comes back, you call us.
- What says he comes back?
- A hunch.
To make the Friday 8am deadline,
you're gonna have to go old-school.
A one-night boost.
Put all your nuts in one basket. OK?
- One night?
- Yes.
What, are you crazy?
One night?
What, do you have, like,
a better plan or something?
Yeah, you spread it out.
You play shadow games and shit.
We're on a truncated timetable.
Otto, I'm sorry. Can you just listen
to me for one second?
We heard you, Kip.
Shadow games.
But what you have to understand
is that if you play shadow games,
by the second night,
the heat is onto you.
With a one-night boost, by the time
the first car is reported stolen,
your ship's set sail.
It's a surprise attack.
This is a complicated list, fellas.
it really is. OK?
There are 25 that aren't a problem,
but these exotics are tough to find.
And the new Mercedes,
they require laser-cut keys. OK?
- Yeah, I got that covered.
- You have that covered?
What'd I just say?
Yeah, I got it covered.
All right, all right.
Well, then, let's get to work.
Toby, hack into
the insurance database
and find as many cars as you can.
Yes! I got addresses on Hilary,
Natalie and Tracy.
Donny, check the DMV
for the remaining cars on the list.
I'm sorry, miss, but you've missed
five questions. That's failing.
No!
No! Why? You're supposed to go
faster when somebody tailgates you!
Ah. Hello again.
Here's your list of the 20 car owners'
names and addresses that you requested.
- Thank you.
- That's $100, please.
$100?
Well, $5 a car, 20 cars.
Would you like a calculator?
It used to be $2 a car.
Thanks a lot.
My name's Roger, sir.
May I be of some help?
- That's funny. My name's Roger.
- Two Rogers don't make a right.
- Roger, I have a problem.
- Yes?
I've been in LA three months now.
I have money, I have taste.
But I'm not on anybody's A list,
and Saturday night is the loneliest
night of the week for me.
Well, a Ferrari would
certainly change that.
Perhaps. But, you know...
This is the one. Yes, yes, yes.
I saw three of these parked outside
the local Starbucks this morning,
which tells me only one thing - there's too
many self-indulgent wieners in this city
with too much bloody money!
Now, if I was driving
a 1967 275 GTB four-cam...
You would not be
a self-indulgent wiener, sir.
- You'd be a connoisseur.
- Precisely.
Champagne would fall
from the heavens.
Doors would open.
Velvet ropes would part.
I don't have one here.
However, I do have one in the warehouse.
Superb. What else do you have
in the warehouse?
Mm. All right. Uh-huh.
That was Mr. Lakewood
from the dealership.
He says that boxer-looking punk
is gonna pick up the keys
to three new Mercedes today.
Same make and model as the ones
we already got impounded.
Now we talkin'.
The El Spirito de Graciela
sails Friday, 8am sharp.
We'll target all the cars
within 45 minutes of here.
By the time their alarm-tracking systems
are activated,
the cars will already be
in these containers.
Fellas, this is Sway.
No questions. I'm here for Kip.
- All right.
It's me. He's here.
- In the red Chevy Nova?
- Uh, that's affirmative, sir.
What's goin' on, bro?
All right, as soon as he leaves,
you call me with the owners' addresses.
- All right?
- I'll get those forms right over, sir.
Damn boss. Always on my case.
- I got three here?
- Mm-hm.
Thank you.
Huh.
Randall Raines, Donny Astricky.
Otto Halliwell.
- Should I set up some tails?
- Uh-uh.
They're too smart for that.
They'll just dump the cars.
No, we'll get them with the Mercedes.
Let's set up, uh, three surveillance
teams at those addresses.
Now, you go ahead
and you make your move, man...
and I will be waiting for you.
Why do you call 'em girls' names?
That's a good question.
It's code. You say Jane,
you say Shirley, Lucy, Edna,
and nobody listening on the waves
is the wiser.
Got 'em.
All right, we've got the addresses
on all 50 ladies. Let's scout 'em.
- There she is.
- Nice.
Damn, it's cold up here.
They keep these Ferraris refrigerated?
Man, you know black people don't like
cold weather. We're a tropical people, man.
When this is over, I'm gonna smoke
a joint, watch two hours of Roots,
and I'm gonna kick your ass.
Hello, and welcome
to "TV Car Trivia."
First question -
who was the driver of a '73 Firebird?
- Uh, Otto.
- Jim Rockford, Rockford Files.
Give me Columbo.
- A Peugeot convertible.
- What color?
Gray.
- How you know that?
- 'Cause I love that show.
Well, I got three words for
all y'all - get a life.
Oh, this is some
kiddie shit, Sphinx.
- What's on Magnum PI's license plate?
- Robin1.
Wait, wasn't Robin that
fagoty guy who hung with him?
No, that was Higgins.
That was Higgins.
Hey, ten points for
our fearless leader.
Sway, how about giving us the honor
of the Bill Bixby trifecta?
He drove a Corvette
in "The Magician,"
a Ford pickup truck
in "The Incredible Hulk,"
and in "The Courtship of Eddie's Father,"
he walked.
- Bingo.
- My man.
Al, tell me somethin'.
Nothin' doin' here, sir.
Nobody's showing.
COPY-
A minivan approaching. And it seems
a little late for soccer practice.
Heads up.
I think we got some activity right here.
Oh, that is... Looks like it's Kip Raines.
And we got a Randall Raines.
If they take this, we
will take them down.
He's pulling something out of his pocket.
You see that?
It's a camera. Looks like
he's just doing some homework.
All right, let's leave him be. I don't
wanna burn this. They will be back.
Huh.
You know what?
Let's go over to Otto's in the morning.
Kick over some rocks,
see what's underneath there.
We saved the best for last -
the '67 Shelby Mustang GT 500.
- The GT 500?
- Yeah, yeah.
There she is.
Yep.
There's Eleanor.
- Eleanor is Memphis's unicorn.
- What's a unicorn?
A fabled creature? You know, the horse
with the horn? Impossible to capture?
The one car no matter how many times you
try to boost, something always happens.
We're gonna get through this
this time, right? It's gonna be smooth.
- What's he doing?
- It's gonna be easy.
He's talking to her, man.
Trying to get reacquainted.
You know, they had a rough history. She
almost got him killed a couple of times.
- He flipped one on the Harbor Freeway.
- He went off the Long Beach Pier once.
A smooth, easy ride.
We're just gonna glide.
Big night tomorrow, guys.
Let's go home.
- Did you get the picture?
- Yeah.
See you tomorrow night, Eleanor,
with your fine ass.
Yeah, we're almost home.
You wanna get something to eat?
I'd like to get a chocolate malt.
- Hey, man!
- Get out of the car!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
- Why are people shooting at us?
- 'Cause I blew up their car.
Over here!
"Beast"?
OK, OK.
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
Aah!
on!
Oh, you think it's a game?
Johnny B! Cops, man.
I ain't got nothin'
but time, baby.
Oh, man, we're gonna
be here all night, man.
Look! Cop car! Uh-huh!
Long as I'm in here, you're just gonna
sit out there. Aren't ya? A'ight?
Hey, listen, this is the plan.
This is what we're gonna do.
There's a big rig over there.
Uh, mister, is that your truck
out there, the Big Rig Wrecker?
- The Big Rig Wrecker's mine...
- That's cool.
What do I gotta do? How do I learn?
What do I do? Where do I go?
- Well, you gotta go to truck-driving school.
- Truck dri... I know, man, I know.
But I mean, like, um...
You boys ready to play
a little pin-the-tail-on-the-donkey?
Can I get you a jelly doughnut
or something, man?
- No, I'm just gonna go ahead and go.
- 'Cause I'm gonna have the waffle...
Maybe next time, though.
I'm gonna smoke you!
Damn!
What the hell's going on?
Want some of this?
Yeah.
- You guys got permits for these weapons?
- Oh, man.
So you think I can
only get pizzas, huh?
- Boosted it myself.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. How'd you get it?
Actually, the keys were in it.
Well, that kind of
defies the point then, don't it?
You stole a car that wasn't on the list.
You stole a car that wasn't on the list!
Why didn't you just go to the police
station in a red clown suit
and let everybody know
what we're doin' here?
- What have we got?
- I don't know.
- Shit! Fellas.
- What?
- Give me that. Let me see that.
- Check this out. Check this out!
- What?
- Look.
- This looks like heroin.
- What?
Where did you get this car?
In front of some poker parlor
in Chinatown.
Ever consider why a car in a neighborhood
like that would have its keys left in it?
Maybe because nobody
in that neighborhood
would be stupid enough
to try to rip this car off.
- Get this shit out of here. Take it back.
- No, no, no, we can't take it back.
- Get it out of here!
- Will everybody relax for a second?
Shut up!
Take it back!
I'm comin' after this shit.
Give me that. Give me that.
Now! Now!
- Look what you...
- Man, I will knock the shit out of you.
- Shut up.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Who is it?
- Detective Castlebeck.
Oh, Christ!
Goddammit.
- Hey. Hello, Otto.
- Detective. Good to see ya.
- Long time.
- Yeah. You're looking good.
Thank you.
So, Randall, what do we got here?
We got a multigenerational
gathering of players?
- Is that what we got here?
- Yeah, right.
Here's Donny.
- How you been, D?
- I'm just happy to see you, brother.
Yeah.
I got to tell you, Randall,
seeing you here, Otto, Donny...
makes me feel almost nostalgic.
Kind of like a big reunion.
You should stick around, 'cause later we're
gonna make s'mores and sing "Kumbaya."
- What is this?
- What, this?
- This.
- They call this a Cadillac.
- What's wrong with it, Otto?
- Needs restoration.
- What?
- Brightening.
- Otto. You got a '39 Ford right there.
- Well, that's a pretty car, isn't it?
- Isn't that a nice car?
- Right here you got a '53 Fiat Vignale.
Now these are beautiful cars, Otto.
And here we got a '83 Cadillac Eldorado?
Yeah.
I mean, who the hell pays
to brighten up a Cadillac Eldorado?
I think it holds a certain...
sentimental value, you know?
N-nothing more.
Run me down a tag.
License 329 HRO.
That is, Harold, Randall, Otto.
Burgundy Cadillac.
No faith in our newfound
goodness, Detective, huh?
Task force runs on statistics
and numbers, Otto. You know that.
- Randall, this Kip?
- That's my brother. He's all grown up.
One Baker Eleven,
Pacific Division.
Three two niner
Harold Randall Otto -
no wants, no warrants at this time.
DMV not on file.
- Copy that. Thank you.
- See, I know what you're doing.
I know.
You're thinking there's no want,
but that I stripped its guts
and crated her up, right?
- Is that what you did, Randall?
- No, I didn't do it.
You know, forget it.
You're trying to hurt my feelings? Fine!
You know what? Go ahead.
Do it. Let her rip.
- Go ahead. Rev it up.
- All right, goddammit, I will.
Sell it to you cheap.
Yeah, '83, first year they put
the auto-ride control on these boys.
Oh, I don't know. You probably know
more about cars at this point than I do.
Ha! What, you slippin'
on me, Randall?
No, it's just your knowledge
overwhelms me.
It's got a real nice-sounding engine,
right, Otto?
4.1-liter.
- Digital fuel injection?
- You got it.
- Let's see what she got.
- You the man.
Give it some more.
- Yeah, that's it!
- Go! Go!
- Let's go!
- Come on.
Baby, don't be so mean!
- Yeah, that's it!
- OK, yeah. That was good.
Yeah, you break it,
you buy it, my friend.
Yeah,
she got some power goin' on.
All right.
I'll catch you later, then.
- It's on for tonight.
- How do you know?
They got the call signs
of all the units working tonight.
What were you gonna do with this?
- I was gonna bonk it.
- What? Bonk?
For the next 24 hours, all your decision-
making privileges have been removed!
- You got it?
- Got it.
Yeah, that's cool, man.
Obviously, they're on to us.
He's sniff in' real close.
If anything tonight
appears out of place,
I want you to cut bait,
get out of there and walk away.
And get rid of this goddamn car!
- What's up, Kip?
- Toby, what are you doin'?
You think you're comin' with us,
but you're not.
What are you talkin' about, man?
I'm part of the team. I get to go.
No, no, wake up.
You're gonna end up in jail
or in the morgue or some shit.
Don't be stupid.
What am I supposed to do?
Did you see a box
of rubber gloves here, man?
Gloves? Man, you don't need gloves.
This is the new age. Check this out.
- What is this?
- Let me see that big claw you call a hand.
That's not doughnut jelly,
so don't eat it.
Your new fingerprints.
Elvis is back.
- Boy got skills, right?
- Yeah, you do.
Look like a little ghetto Smurf.
I am a bad man.
Thanks. Thanks for doin' this.
Keep it real.
Think slow.
We should get through it just fine.
"Low Rider," Donny.
Donny? "Low Rider."
OK, let's ride.
Oh, shit!
Give me the damn torch.
Ha-ha! What?
I tell you, I'm the man.
Now, where does this go?
Find a way to get in here.
Get this...
I tell you, I'm running this shit!
You do that again, I will kick...
Cool, man. You don't have
to take it so damn personal.
Ah! Everything is perfect.
Hello, ladies.
Always was a sucker for a redhead.
Let's go. Come on.
Move, move. Go, go!
Work your magic, baby. I know
you know Ferraris. Work your magic.
Girl got skills.
Whoo!
You all right?
- You think we're gonna make it?
- I don't know. It's too early to tell.
Diana, Tricia, Nadine
and Rose are on their way.
Good goin', guys.
Al, tell me something.
Unit Two.
Sorry, sir, nothin' yet.
Son of a bitch. I know you're not
parking right in front of me.
Oh, no, I can't see a damn thing.
All right, we gotta move.
- You ever feel bad about any of this?
- Hell, no.
I'm Robin Hood, man. I rob from
the rich and give to the needy.
Damn!
- Donny!
- I got you. I got you
- You mean the poor.
- Cutters.
Cutters.
No, like I said, the needy.
'Cause, brother, we need this car.
- What's up, Doc?
- You're new, aren't you?
- Yeah, how can you tell?
- Now, listen, son.
- You take real good care of this car...
- All right.
...and I'll take care of you.
Tell you what. Save it. You get another
one of these suits, all right?
- God bless you, son.
- You need a fashion counselor.
All right, babe. I ain't here
for the door. I'm here for the car.
- Get your big ass out.
- Hm?
Out! What the hell you lookin' at?
- Damn, man, that was easy as pie.
- I'm a veteran, son.
Get out of the car, bitch,
or I'll blow your brains out!
- You gotta be shittin' me.
- I will shoot you, dammit!
Damn!
You lazy, half-ass bully!
Any asshole can pull
a gun on somebody!
You don't know the first thing
about stealing a car. Boy, I...
You need a role model!
Stacy.
Shannon.
Laura.
Lindsay.
Rachel.
Hey. Check this out.
JJ, he's back, but he's smart.
He watches his ass.
Just hold our positions.
- If he rolls, you follow him out.
- Copy that.
What's he doing?
What are you doing?
We might as well roll down
our windows and wave.
- JJ, you tail him, all right?
- Copy that.
Let's go.
- Good luck.
- Piece of cake.
Unit One, this is Unit Two.
Astricky has landed.
If they roll,
we take 'em down.
Last night that van was parked
four houses down. Now it's only two.
- We got company.
- Shit.
He's at the car.
Bird, come back.
Stand by, Unit One.
What?
- Where are you?
- Where do you think I am?
I'm at the casino, picking up
the pit boss's lady. What do you want?
The ladies are dirty.
Walk away.
- The ladies are dirty.
- What?
I want everybody to get back
to the garage now.
Oh, so she's having
the baby right now?
- I guess I better get to the hospital, then.
- He's having a baby.
- Something's got him spooked.
- My wife is having a baby.
Gotta get... I'm just nervous. This
ain't even my car. I'm way over here.
He's heading away from the vehicle.
I see you.
Pull in over there.
Uh, this is Unit Two.
I lost them.
All right, it's time
to talk to Fuzzy again.
Check this out.
Laser-encoded keys
that send a message
to a receiver inside the car.
You wanna tell me what you're
doin' with these?
Yeah, these are from last week.
These are from the other boost.
- Give me this back.
- Who is it?
- Where did they come from?
- It's the keys! The keys! The keys!
- Give me them!
- Take it easy!
Now, give me this!
- What happened?
- Where'd you get these from?
- What's the problem?
- The Mercedes are dirty!
There are surveillance vans all over them.
Where'd they come from?
My guy in Southland. The same guy I used
last time. Same guy I used before.
- Before when?
- When we took the other cars.
- Other Mercedes.
- Oh, Christ.
Castlebeck.
He got to one of the guys
at the dealership and he turned him.
- That's what happened.
- Eight hours left.
So, what? We're gonna
stand around and have a meeting?
What's going on?
Memphis...
Maybe it's time for us to start thinking
about how to get these kids out of town...
- Oh, man, you know what? No! That's...
- What are you talking about?
If there's no Mercedes,
there's no point in boosting any
other cars. You hear me? That's it.
47 is not 50, Memphis.
You know that's what he'll say.
Yeah.
Hey, Memphis, you know, we still have
the Mercedes keys from the last boost.
Hey! Those cars are
at the police impound.
OK? The police impound. You want us
to go there and start stealin' cars?
- Yeah.
- What?
- Yeah, let's do it.
- You're crazy.
- We're gonna get hectic. Let's go.
- No, Memphis, no. Don't do this!
Hey, Sphinx,
I don't look suspicious, do I, man?
Otto, man, I think that
your dog ate the keys!
Wait. He usually goes
for license plates.
- You sure? What?
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
- The dog ate the keys?
- Yes.
- How are you gonna get them out?
- Not funny.
- Wait! Wait! Wait!
- Don't even think about it, Sphinx.
It's all right.
Say, Toby.
- See if you can get some Alpo and Ex-Lax.
- Oh, Lord.
- No way, man!
- Bad dog!
Let's get back to work.
- Hey! Open the door!
- Oh, Jesus.
- Hurry up. Hurry up.
- End it, rock star. Get in.
Jesus Christ!
Now what, man? What else?
Fuzzy, you never called me.
So now we gotta stay down here
till you tell me everything you know.
I told you everything I know. I know that,
because I said, "This is everything I know."
Detective Drycoff,
does it seem like the suspect
is violating his parole right now?
Why, yes, Detective Castlebeck.
if by violating his parole
you mean failing to cooperate
with a law enforcement officer.
A little trick I learned
in the car-thief retirement home.
Could you hold this?
No, no, no, I'm not failing
to cooperate. It's just that...
Yeah, OK, OK. Word has it that Kip Raines
took the job, and he screwed up.
He screwed up pretty bad.
And who put out the
order for the job?
It's Raymond Calitri's order.
Nice.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Yes!
We have six hours left.
Has the dog done its business yet?
Toby and Freb
are walking him right now.
He's not gonna do it.
It's not gonna happen, man.
Come on, dog.
What's wrong, Hemi? Poop, dog.
- It had to be a girl car.
- Girl car?
What kind of a girl
drives a Hemi 'Cuda?
I'll show you.
Lipstick?
Matches the car.
What's next? Blush? Mascara?
Next time I'll pull out
the leather and high heels
and pink underwear for you.
- Leather, high heels and pink underwear.
- Pink underwear.
Pink underwear works.
Raymond Vincent Calitri did five years
in South London for manslaughter.
- He immigrated in '98.
- Look at this.
Loansharking, extortion, fencing.
Ha-ha. His front's a salvage yard.
Gonna have to wait it out.
- So, you seeing anybody?
- No.
No, I had a girl once.
She was great.
Hm. So...
If she was so great,
Why'd you leave her?
I did ask you to come with me.
No, you asked me
to be a different person.
I didn't want to see people get hurt.
I just wanted you to slow down.
Well, I couldn't.
- 'Cause I wasn't ready.
- You're straight now.
Yeah, I am.
'Cause it wasn't the same without you.
- Excuse me, gentlemen.
- Hey, asshole. I was reading that.
- Watch your mouth, kid.
- What's goin' on?
This is a homicide file
from a homicide investigation.
It took us three months to get
a magistrate to give us a wiretap on him.
No other division, including GRAB,
can go near his person, residence
or place of business, all right?
You got it? Let me tell you guys
something, all right?
Raymond Calitri is going down
for murder one, boneheads.
Who gives a shit about
grand theft auto? Really?
Man, I can't watch this.
Come on, come on, come on.
Get it on. Get it over with.
What do you think is more exciting,
having sex or stealing cars?
Having sex or boosting cars?
Um...
Ooh!
Well... um...
Well...
How about having sex
while boosting cars?
God, that's a good line.
Ooh...
Doesn't work on a lot
of girls, though.
I just blurted it out.
I'm s...
But you haven't
answered the question.
Well, you see, the problem is,
how do you get over the shifter?
- Oh. Oh, right. 'Cause the...
- 'Cause it gets in the way.
Because you wouldn't want to disrupt
the synchromesh, right?
Or... the throttle linkage.
The clutch master cylinder.
- Or the overhead camshaft.
- I can't do this.
Wait, wait, wait. Just...
Straight in-line six.
Triple Weber carburetors bolted
to each other's body structures.
- What?
- Well, it's time to work.
Good brakes.
Good brakes, too.
- There's nothing happening.
- Maybe he's got indigestion.
Well, dude,
give him some more Ex-Lax.
- He already ate two.
- Hey, little man.
Oh, man.
I thought I told you this is our turf.
What, you want to make a move?
We don't want anything
to do with your turf.
Something wrong with
where we live, dog?
No, no, it's cool for you.
I mean, it's just not for us.
So now you think you're better than us?
Maybe we should cut you up, dog?
- Dude, the keys.
- Right. Excuse me a second, guys.
Oh, man!
- Oh, I'm gonna throw up, dog!
- Man, that's disgusting.
What kind of pervert gets
their jollies off playing with dog shit?
Look, man, I got 'em!
Look! All three, man!
- You guys are sick!
- I got 'em!
Wake up, man.
Check this out.
Every time I drive my Volvo
in Beverly Hills, they tow the shit.
- We ain't got any Volvos here.
- There is a Volvo here. I know it.
- They told me...
- Just wait a minute. Wait, wait.
What I'm tryin' to tell you is,
there ain't no Volvos here.
Then get in your book, do something.
Find my damn Volvo!
Sphinx. Sway.
It's got to be somewhere in there.
Check it out, man.
Wait, wait. It's not. Nothing here.
There's nothing here. Look.
- So, look, there's another one back here...
- No! No!
No, no. Hey, hey, hey, tell you what.
Look at this.
Look, I'm sorry.
I don't even need to be out here.
Hey...
I got a midget pagin' me right now.
I gotta get outta here. Time is money.
This is the worst
damn day of my life!
"Detective Castlebeck.
Glass shards from the warehouse
were from a black-light bulb
available at any local hardware store."
All right, what the hell
is a black-light bulb
doin' in a warehouse in Long Beach?
Come with me.
- See this glass right here?
- Let me guess. Black-light?
Black-light. You take that
wall, I'll take this wall.
- Remember the '70s?
- Too young, thank God.
Black-lights were
all the rage back then.
You know, they had this ink,
these Magic Markers.
Only show up under black-light.
So if you got a whole lot of information
that you don't want anybody to have...
- Like a shopping list of cars?
- There you go.
Whoa!
Yes! Yes!
Here is our list.
That's a big list.
- We can't handle all these cars.
- Maybe we don't have to.
I tell you what, let's concentrate
on the rarest ones,
and let's just hope for some luck.
Let's get somebody
on these right here.
You and I will take this one right here.
'67 Shelby Mustang.
- Can't be but a few of these in town.
- Yeah.
But how do you know
he hasn't already stolen it?
Oh, if I know our boy, I believe
he'll leave this one till last.
- Why?
- He's afraid of it.
Yo, guys.
It's me. Man.
Oh, man.
What are you doing?
I wanna roll with you
guys on a boost.
Later. Come on.
Go, 90, 90-
- What's the matter with you? Come on!
- Hey! Call security!
- I'm coming.
- Someone's stealing the car!
- Go! Go! Go! What are you doing?
- Jesus, bro. I ought to leave your ass.
You know that?
What's the matter with you?
Hey, Sphinx, check this out.
Homeboy got "Snake"
on the license plate.
Well, Snake gonna have to slither his ass
all the way to the bus stop in the morning.
Police officers.
We need to check the lot for a car.
Go ahead.
Check this out, man.
Here's some low-ridin' music.
It's a little bit different than that
cracker shit you used to be playin'.
Check this out.
Ah, you like that.
You feelin' it?
Are you feelin' it?
I know you're feelin' it.
Oh! Snake!
Get this thing off me!
Snake!Snake!Snake!
Get this thing off me, man!
It's a snake!
It's trying to kill me, man!
Get this thing off me!
Man, they always want to kill
a brother, man! This is wrong!
What the hell are you doing?
Get the snake!
- Use the brakes!
- I am!
Aaargh!
This snake is crawlin' up my ass, man!
The snake is up my ass!
This snake gonna swallow
my shit whole, man!
God, I love that car.
All right, two ladies home safe.
He's tucking in Vanessa,
and Bernadine just took me for a ride.
- What's the count?
- 48.
Yes!
Yeah, but Mirror and Sphinx
had some unexpected visitors.
- Castlebeck?
- I think so.
- Everything cool?
- Yeah, yeah, they're fine.
They're on their way back to Otto's.
Donny and Freb are already there.
- What about Kip and Tumbler?
- No word yet.
Lost in suburbia.
Hell, where are we?
What do you mean?
You don't know where you're goin'?
Which way is out?
I don't know where I am.
- Everything looks the same to me.
- You don't know where you're going?
- That is a cop.
- No, it's not, that's a rent-a-cop.
- Slow down, slow down.
- He's pulling a U-turn.
Oh, man, we're in big trouble.
In pursuit of stolen Cadillac
SUV, traveling west on Murray Drive.
- Roadblock, Kip.
- Dude, look out for the roadblock!
- Shit!
- Go, go!
Go!
Oh, man!
- Son of a bitch!
- Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
- I need some help, man.
- What's the matter? What?
- He's been shot! Oh, shit! Shit!
- Don't touch me!
Dude, go to the hospital, man!
- People ask questions in hospitals, Kip.
- Go to the hospital!
- Use your head. We're in a stolen car!
- Oh, man!
- Oh, man! Don't move, man.
- Now this does not look good.
- It's gonna be all right, man.
- Relax.
- Oh, man!
- What happened?
We ran into a security patrol, man.
He hid in the van.
We didn't know he was there.
We gotta get you to a doctor.
Private. I know just where to go.
- Let's get him to a car.
- No! Ow!
Lie in the back.
Lie down in the back.
Tumbler, you and Kip
take the last van back to Otto's.
- What are you doin'?
- I'm goin' with him.
- If something should go wrong...
- Let's go!
I'll take care of him, man.
Let's finish this.
- What's up?
- What's the story with that Humvee?
- Gone.
- Cadillac?
Same. Where we goin'?
The only '67 Shelby in the area
is registered at a place called
the International Towers in Long Beach.
Let's go to Long Beach.
I know we got a history, Eleanor,
and that that history
has not been great,
but I promise,
you take care of me,
I'll take care of you.
Shit.
The easy way or the hard way, Raines?
Easy way or the hard way?
Hey!
I think he's choosin' the hard way.
All right.
One Baker Eleven.
In pursuit of '67 Ford Mustang, gray.
- That sign said "do not enter."
- Yeah. You noticed, huh?
- Jeez.
- Keep your pants on.
Suspect now traveling
east on Fourth Street.
Correction.
Make that north on Main.
- Move!
- Back up! Get the...
Get outta there!
Oh, you wanna get crazy with me?
Come on, boy!
Aaaaaah!
One Baker Eleven. Unit Three involved
in a TA at St. Vincent's and Seventh.
All units, pursuit has
entered flood control near 710 Freeway.
- Where's that air unit?
- Requesting air unit same location.
Air One.
We're opening pursuit.
Suspect traveling southbound
at 9O miles an hour.
- Stay with him, Air One!
- I'm all over him.
- Suspect has increased speed to 120.
- Maintain visual, Air One.
- 140 miles an hour.
- Do not lose him!
This is an A-Star, sir,
not an Apache.
150. 160.
He's gone.
- God!
- Man, this guy can drive!
- What? What?
- It's probably mostly the car.
Hey, what time is it?
7:30.
I think I'm gonna have to
get you out of town or something.
Your brother's the best boost
in the world,
but I don't know
if he's gonna make this one.
I'm not like my brother, you know?
I just don't abandon my friends.
Oh, man, I ought to
smack you silly, boy.
You think your brother ran away?
Is that what you think?
You better get your story straight.
Well, go on then.
Straighten it out.
Your mother told him to go.
She knew if Memphis stayed,
you were gonna walk his line.
You were gonna join his crew.
And she told him to pick up and go.
And he did, thinking
it was best for you.
He left all of us... for you.
Guess it wasn't that big a deal
for him, though, really.
Wasn't that big a sacrifice, leaving
everything he'd ever known behind.
And six years later, ain't life grand?
You became a car boost anyway.
How about that?
I sedated him. He's sleeping.
He's gonna be just fine.
It's just a scratch, Eleanor.
It can be fixed.
No, no, no, don't.
Don't do this to me.
Don't start with me.
Don't. No, don't do... No, no, start!
Start, start.
Come on. Come on. Shit.
I need you, Eleanor.
I need you now. Now.
Yes!
All units, be advised, suspect vehicle
headed south on Henry Ford Boulevard.
We should hit him at Ocean Avenue,
at the end of this bridge.
- There he is. There he is!
- Yeah.
I got you, Raines!
I got you,boy!
Whoa! Shit! Shit!
One Baker Eleven, suspect heading
westbound. Head east to intercept.
One Baker Eleven, maintain your course.
Suspect heading in your direction.
- Hey, what are you doing!
- Hang on.
Take it up!
One Baker Eleven, he's at the end
of the pier turning toward you.
Christ! Hang on!
Hang on to it!
Whoa! Shit!
- Hey!
- Move!
Is he OK?
- How ya doin'? Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- Are you OK? Just sit back. You all right?
- I think so.
Are you sure?
'Cause you just went through a wall.
Long Beach Tower, this is
LAPD Air One in pursuit of suspect.
Requesting permission
to cross airfield.
Negative, Air One. Incoming
aircraft on approach. Hold your position.
I repeat, do not enter
airport airspace.
- Ready to go.
- Yeah, Lieutenant.
We're done. Wait up!
He's got a broken leg.
There he is. There he is!
Get out of the car, man!
Raines!
- Where's Memphis?
- I don't know, man.
He's not back yet.
What do you mean he's not back yet?
It's eight o'clock.
- Atley.
- Time's up, Atley.
I've got 49 cars.
That's one less than required.
- Bring the kid and we'll settle this.
- What kid is that?
Oh, you know, the Cincinnati Kid. Billy
the Kid. Which kid do you think I mean?
Oh, gee, I don't know.
I think that maybe you mean Kip Raines.
Well, gee, I think you're right.
Yeah, well, you know, it's a funny thing.
The little son of a bitch evaded me.
- Find him, Atley.
- Well, what if I can't find him?
Then big brother takes the fall for
the slip-up. Doesn't matter much to me.
One Raines is as good as another.
It never rains but it pours.
Son of a... Well, you know,
I think you can thank your big brother.
I think he just took your place
under the guillotine.
Sorry, mate.
We're all done here.
- No, we're not done. This is number 50.
- You're late.
So sod off. You got a problem with that,
take it up with Calitri.
- You're late.
- Wait, wait.
You're gonna argue with me
over 12 minutes?
I just stole 50 cars for you
in one night, all right?
I'm a little tired, I'm a little wired, and
I think I deserve a little appreciation.
I said 50 cars, not 49 and a half.
49 and a half?
She's not so bad, man.
She's got, what, you know, a lit...
some paint and...
You know, some fiberglass.
Yes, indeedy.
You know, and the book on her
is 60, 70. Call it 80.
So you take 80, all right?
You subtract it from 200.
All right? And we make a deal.
You take 80 from 200 and we call it even.
Done.
All right. Good.
And this thing with my brother is over.
It's over.
It's done. It's finished.
Done. Finished.
Nobody insults me.
Nobody puts a gun to me head.
Kill him. Shred the car.
All right.
Where's Raymond Calitri's place?
Exeter Salvage and Steel.
It's on the water. Why? Are we goin'?
Because, you know, Homicide specifically
ordered us not to interfere.
To hell with Homicide.
- Unicorn.
- What?
Nothing.
So, where would you like it, sir?
In the head, or in the chest?
- The chest.
- My pleasure.
Hey, wait a minute, fellas. Hold it.
Big change of plan here.
- That's far enough, Atley.
- What are you doing? No, no, no!
I said stop there, Atley.
No, no. Calitri just sent me
up here to ask you a question.
Shit!
All right? Everything's gonna
be all right. We got it covered.
Get my brother out of here.
Hey.
You made a mistake picking a kid
to do your dirty work.
Made an even bigger mistake
picking my kid brother.
And now you just made the biggest
mistake tryin' to kill me.
- No. Be careful with that.
- This?
- Just put it down.
- That's right. You got a thing about wood.
Just put it down.
No.
- No! No!
- I'm-I'm...
- No!
- Oh, no.
Go!
Psst.
I'm good.
God! Jesus!
God!
- Who are you?
- I'm a police officer.
- Hey, you don't wanna do that now.
- Yeah, I do.
Listen to me. You walk out of here
with me, you got some options.
You kill me... now,
you think about this...
I'm a police officer,
your life will be over.
No, you've got that the wrong way round.
If I kill you your life's over.
Not all bad, though.
Funeral will be on the telly.
Everybody out there pressed
and dressed. Guard of honor.
Twenty-one-gun salute and the Stars
and Stripes draped all over your coffin.
It'll be the greatest
day of your life.
Here I am smack-dab in the middle
of a moral dilemma, Randall.
You've torn this town to shreds
with that little escapade of yours,
you and your Eleanor.
But I understand
what brought you back here.
A brother's love is a brother's love.
You saved my life, didn't you?
- So what am I gonna do?
- It's your call, Detective.
Get outta here, Randall.
I'll clean this up.
Go, Randall, before
I change my mind. Go.
Oh, there's a container ship
at pier 14.
You might wanna check it out.
Oh!
Can a good-lookin', hard-workin'
chef get a beer around here?
Come on, Tumbler. You ain't doin'
nothin'. Hand me a beer, baby.
All right. Memphis?
Guys? Food!
- Thank you, sir.
- Damn.
Ow. Ow.
Poor Toby, man.
Sure looks like he's in a lot of pain.
Hey, if that's pain,
you can shoot me anytime.
Sexy, sassy.
If his unpleasant wounding has in
some way enlightened the rest of you
as to the grim finish below
the glossy veneer of criminal life,
and inspired you to change your ways,
then his injuries carry with it
an inherent nobility
and a supreme glory.
We should all be so fortunate.
You say, "Poor Toby."
I say, "Poor us."
- He spoke.
- Yeah.
Hey, man, I thought
you were from Long Beach.
Memphis. Hey.
- I have something for you.
- What is this?
Open it.
Keys. Keys are good.
What do I do with them?
Hey, everybody.
Everybody, inside here. Let's go.
Everybody, come on.
Let's go!
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's my great pleasure...
to present...
- Oh, man!
- Your very own Eleanor.
- What? What? It's Eleanor!
- Look at his face.
All yours.
It's a heap, but give me a couple of weeks
and it'll look like a streamlined butterfly.
- You didn't...?
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
I parted the chopper out for that.
I'm blown away.
You bought me a car.
Well, yeah, you know,
it's just a token of my appreciation
for everything, you know.
That's the way it should be.
That's right.
Yeah.
Why don't you get in there
and go for a ride?
I know what you did.
- And thank you.
- I'll see you later, man.
All right.
Yes!
- You wanna go for a ride?
- Hell, yes.
Oh, don't do this to me.
Whoo!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org