Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Naughty thought.
How about we don't wait
12 minutes
for our next kiss?
We would never see
the end of the movie.
Oh.
Mm.
It's better if we stick
to the schedule.
Sure.
Didn't hear you come
in last night.
So I'm guessing
it went well at Carly's.
The end of the movie
was very predictable.
Not the question
I was asking,
but, you still
managed to answer it.
Carly touches me
when we kiss.
You don't like her
touching you?
- Oh, I... I do.
- Oh.
But I prefer to touch only
one thing at a time.
Have you told her
you prefer
to touch only one thing
at a time?
In those exact words?
Oh!
Whatever it is,
I'm definitely in.
My first lead surgery!
- Oh!
Shaun!
That is awesome!
I am going to
rock it!
Oh, hells to the yeah
you are!
Oh!
*THE GOOD Doctor*
Season 03  Episode 05
Episode Title: "First Case, Second Base"
Sync corrections by srjanapala
How you doing?
I'm good.
Thank you for helping me
with the sea lions.
I'll never say no
to a caper.
But I'd like to keep my mother's
death between the two of us.
I just...
I can't deal with
people's platitudes
right now.
Okay, but that kinda suggests
you're not good.
This is textbook denial.
It's only going to inhibit
your grief process.
Denial is the first step
in the grief process,
so I'd say I'm right on track.
But thank you
for your platitudes.
This is Curtis.
He decided to fix his chimney
without a safety harness.
He has open bilateral
tib-fib fractures.
They wanted $1,200
for a two-hour job.
And I can still do
a Hurricane Grind.
It's a skateboard move
that builds off a 180 Ollie.
I got great balance.
Pupils are slow to react.
Unfortunately, balance is less
great after a few cocktails.
Not me.
Clean and sober six years,
three months,
and... and 24 days.
Get him on IV antibiotics
and to OR Level One.
And run a BAC.
I'm Dr. Shaun Murphy.
Your surgeon.
Esophageal cancer
is a serious condition.
However,
you don't have any remote
or metastatic disease
and responded well
to chemoradiation,
so a resection of the esophagus
should render you
cancer-free.
You look awfully young.
I always say, the younger they are,
the smarter they must be.
Oh, oh, yes.
We will pull the stomach up
and attach it to the remains
of your esophagus, keeping your
GI system connected,
so you will not need
a permanent feeding tube.
My oncologist told me all this,
but I refused to believe it...
that it was all gonna be okay...
until I heard it
from my surgeon.
Oh!
I'm sorry, it's just...
I've been through a divorce
and a career change...
and I finally bought
my own cafe...
three days before
I got my diagnosis.
And I thought it was a sign
I was making a mistake.
But it was just the opposite.
I wasn't done.
Oh, I'm sorry...
I have to inform you
of the risks of this procedure.
There is a 7% chance
of heart and lung problems,
a 12% chance of infection,
a 0.5% of death, among others.
Bring it, Dr. Murphy.
Shaun got very lucky.
Landed the world's most genial
patient for his first case.
- Nice.
- Of you.
You picked that patient for him...
I heard it was Park's chart
before you stepped in.
Shaun's weakness is
patient management.
You shouldn't be coddling him.
We challenge him too much,
we lose him.
Murphy?
He perseveres.
He's annoyingly resilient.
I agree that some failures
don't seem to faze him at all.
But it's his lifelong dream.
So, yes,
I think we could lose him.
I'll tough-love his ass next week.
Okay, Curtis, we're good to go.
Curtis, my God.
Are you okay?
I'm thinking I should've gone
with the contractor.
His thinking was impaired.
He had a blood
alcohol level of .09.
Your test must be wrong.
You were quite inebriated
when you came in.
That's impossible.
Curtis doesn't drink.
We'll make a note of it
in his chart.
We've got to get him
to the O.R.
You play softball?
Uh, my junior year in high school,
I had an ERA of 2.95.
My wife's got an arm.
I can't believe
you're my wife.
Till death do us part.
Yeah.
Oh, you found Wally.
You have a name for it?
Yeah,
he's my Walther PPK .32;
he and I go way back.
Is it loaded?
I mean, is this a problem?
'Cause I... I just...
I keep it in my bedside table,
in my gun safe...
combination 7-3-5-9.
I'm not gonna
remember that.
I don't want
to remember that.
If we're gonna live
together,
we're gonna need
to make some... compromises.
You nervous?
How badly
are you freaking out?
I'm not badly freaking out.
I've assisted in six
esophageal resections,
all of which were
free of complications.
So you're overdue
for a blow-up.
Sorry.
I'm just a bit annoyed
'cause I had my hand
on this case first,
and now I'm third out of four,
at best.
But I'm happy for you.
Really.
I'm happy for me,
too.
She has extensive
scar tissue.
And it's plastered her stomach
to her anterior abdominal wall.
I told her she wouldn't need
a permanent feeding tube.
But she will.
We've got to tell a budding chef
she'll never eat again.
How will she react?
Don't know.
Badly.
But the specifics...
You should tell her.
She's your patient,
it's your job.
I'm bad
at patient communication.
If I make her
very unhappy,
she may not want me
to do the surgery.
If you're not willing
to take that risk,
then you should hand
the case over to Park.
No. I don't want to hand
the case over to Dr. Park.
Park will tell Beth.
And, Shaun,
it's still your surgery.
Drill.
Do you see his heart rhythm?
Rate controlled A-fib.
Wasn't on his record.
Ask his wife about it post-op.
Probably a symptom
of binge drinking.
Which he'll lie to us about and
she'll tell us she believes.
She's in denial?
You had surgery as a child.
As a baby,
I don't even remember it.
There's considerable
scar tissue...
more than we'd typically
expect to find.
Which has affected
our surgical plan.
How?
Dr. Murphy will field that question.
No, Dr. Lim s-said...
Proceed, Dr. Murphy.
Somebody please tell me.
We can't move your stomach up,
so you will need a feeding tube.
For the rest of your life.
The good news is that
this surgery is simpler,
so your recovery time will be
shorter by three to five days.
Hey.
Do any of you
own a gun?
Is there someone you'd like
"taken care of"?
- Ah.
- I still have my service pistol.
I have a Sig P365.
Do any of you have,
or have you ever had,
issues about it
with your significant others?
After our son was born,
my wife suddenly hated
having a firearm in the house.
And one night,
I came home late to a...
PowerPoint presentation.
90 minutes of horrifying
statistics.
Now it's in a locker
at my gun range.
Lotta set up but I like that.
I had a boyfriend who felt very weird
about me having a gun.
He wasn't big on logic,
so I took the emotional approach.
Told him
it's not for the firepower,
it's for the confidence it gives me
as a woman when I carry it.
I lived with a guy
who had a gun.
Had to use the nuclear option.
It goes
or he goes.
It worked...
they both went.
Well, that's just
wonderful.
I heard your news.
It's pretty exciting.
I jumped seven times.
How's the anxiety level?
Why do people
keep asking me that?
Everyone has doubts, Shaun.
I'm excited.
You can be excited.
And nervous.
Usually they go together.
Speaking of, uh,
I'm sorry if I was a bit
too assertive last night.
Lea said
it must be tricky for you.
So now Lea is also privy
to the intimacies of our intimacy?
- Great.
- Yes.
Oh.
Lea said to tell you
that I prefer to touch
only thing at a time.
Located upper esophageal sphincter.
You have a good tumor margin...
resecting above or below?
- Below.
- Mm-hmm.
Shaun gave the news
to his patient after all.
Shaun did
what I expected.
He upset her,
but the news is upsetting.
She'll deal with it,
he'll learn how to...
She wants him off the case.
- Shaun...
- No...
Shaun, I will find you
another case.
This is my case.
I prepared for this case.
I don't want another case.
Dr. Murphy...
You're learning, Shaun.
That's what you do
at a teaching hospital.
I'm learning, too.
Going from attending
to Chief of Surgery
is... a big deal.
Every day, every decision,
every mistake...
I learn something.
So do you.
No, I don't.
I have
a developmental disorder.
- Come with me.
- I'm waiting for my bus.
You can take a later one.
I'm sure
I mentioned I was Chief?
Hi, Beth.
I'm sorry for
what you're going through.
And Dr. Murphy's phrasing was
unfortunate.
But there's been no deceit
or negligence.
He's an excellent surgeon
who has my full confidence
in the O.R.
And if you don't trust him,
you don't trust me.
So, I would recommend
you have your surgery
at a different hospital.
I can make arrangements.
However, if you reconsider,
we can proceed as scheduled
first thing
tomorrow morning.
If you don't want people to know
your mother died,
stop acting like someone
whose mother died.
I'm gonna move on to the second
stage of grief... anger.
I'm not acting depressed.
No, you're acting bitchy.
But you're not a bitch,
so that looks weird on you,
and people are gonna
know something's up.
So, do you want me
happier or sadder?
Let me know, because I'm really
looking for your approval.
Bitchy...
You really think this guy's
still on the wagon?
Just because he's a drunk
doesn't mean he's not sick.
But all you can see is an addict
married to an enabler,
so all roads
lead to rum.
C'mon, that was cute.
No IV wall motion abnormalities.
No valvular disease
or dysfunction.
Ruling out any structural cause
for the arrhythmia.
You win.
Congratulations.
- H-Hey!
- Hey.
How was your day?
Good, good.
Pensive.
I was thinking
about your gun
- and why you need it...
- Oh, Aaron,
- I... I don't...
- No, no, no.
I was an idiot and a guy,
I get it.
You walking alone
in a garage late at night,
you walking alone on the street
late at night...
Or getting into my own car,
or even my own house.
Exactly.
That's why I got you
a surprise.
- Yeah?
- Right outside the back door.
We have exactly 10 seconds
to punch in the code
before S.E.A.I. Team Six arrives.
7-3-5-9.
Every door, every window,
every vent over 36 inches.
This is your security fob.
Works in all 48 contiguous
states and Canada.
You have no idea how much extra
comfort this is gonna give me.
Actually, I was hoping
it would be
your primary source of comfort.
You were thinking that
this would mean
- I would give up my gun?
- That's exactly what I was thinking.
Well, the first rule of security
systems is redundancy.
By that logic, we should get
a tank for the garage.
Aaron, it shouldn't matter
why I want a gun...
whether it's because it makes me
feel more secure,
or it was a memento
of my dad's
or just because
it's fun to shoot.
All that matters is
I'm a grown-up,
and I'm responsible,
and I want it.
You're ruining Shaun.
Maybe you got him over the hump
of patient management,
but what about
surgical management?
Taking charge of the O.R.,
keeping lines of communication open,
everyone cooperating.
You're throwing him
into the deep end,
and that's unfair to him.
Unless you plan to scrub in
as a lifeguard.
He'll be fine.
You handpicked
his surgical team?
You're ruining him.
The tests prove his arrhythmia
is associated
with excessive
ethanol consumption.
But there's no
permanent damage
and his rhythm will
return to normal
in the absence of
any further drinking.
We met
when we were 15.
I was first clarinet,
he was second.
We were at a band festival
in Anaheim when he found out
his parents died
in a plane crash.
We grieved together
and fell in love.
Then he started drinking.
It wasn't until I threatened to leave
that he finally woke up.
The day he received
his two-year recovery chip
was the day we got married.
The day he vowed to me,
and a church full
of our family and friends,
that he would never drink again.
Our marriage is built on
his sobriety.
I believe him.
Teal,
we ran the BAC three times,
and the results were consistent.
I believe in my husband.
I have to.
His BP is dropping.
Temp is normal.
Check for causes of shock.
Upper GI bleed...
need stat hematocrits
and transfuse blood.
Surgery's the easy-peasy part.
You wanted this,
enjoy it.
I can't.
If I get distracted,
if I get upset...
If you do,
Andrews has your back.
If Dr. Andrews has to take over,
then I have failed.
I have failed, and I have
endangered a patient's life,
and if I'm no good
at the easy-peasy part,
then what part
am I good at?
What do we do
when we get all nutty like this?
Blow out the candles.
How many do you need?
Three.
Hey. I was looking for you.
Big day, huh?
How are your nerves holding up?
I'm not nervous.
Of course you're nervous.
Everybody's nervous.
It just means that
you care.
Being nervous
means
I feel inadequate
and unprepared,
and if I am
either of those things,
it doesn't matter
whether I care or not.
You are more than adequate,
and you're very prepared.
You remind me of a...
a young surgeon I knew once.
The day he got his first lead,
he was thrilled,
but he was a mess, trying to
remember a million things,
imagining a million things
that could go wrong.
But then he remembered
the birth process,
how moms are asked
to pick a focal point,
- let everything filter through that.
- Hmm.
So, he chose the color orange
to focus on.
This is the cap
that he focused on,
and he got through it
with flying colors.
Maybe it'll help.
Why do you have
the young surgeon's cap?
I was being coy.
The young surgeon
was me.
Konnichiwa.
That's Japanese for hello.
I have surgery in 42 minutes.
Which is why I'm here,
to wish you luck.
I don't need luck.
Everyone needs luck.
That was a good luck kiss.
How can a kiss give you...
So was that.
I am feeling
a bit lucky.
You know the thing
that Lea told you to tell me?
Yes.
That was actually great advice.
It's important
that we tell each other
exactly what we like
and what we don't.
I also don't like pickles,
sirens, anything wool...
I was thinking
more in the romantic area.
And right now, we are not going
to touch lips anymore.
Because there's something else
I want you to touch.
So, what do you think?
You don't have any lumps.
Win-win.
Lab and imaging tests
rule out Crohn's,
gastroenteritis, C-diff colitis,
and even H pylori.
Leaving bleeding ulcers.
Caused by alcohol abuse.
He needs to be
on a proton pump inhibitor
and octreotide to prevent
any further blood loss.
No.
He loves you.
That's why
he hasn't been honest.
Doesn't make it right,
but it's that same love
that kept you together
through everything.
And it'll get you through this,
too.
He's telling the truth.
We'll run more tests.
Your faith in your husband
is impressive.
But it may have just
killed him.
Ten blade, please.
Located lower end of
esophageal lesion.
Linear cutting stapler.
Resecting the esophagus
from the stomach...
I'm now
at the upper end of the lesion.
Hemoclips.
Dr. Murphy?
No.
No...
What's the matter?
No, no, no...
Shaun, what are you seeing?
Can't... can't do this!
What... what can't you do?
- No!
- Don't... No.
No! No! No! No!
- Dr. Murphy!
- No!!
Dr. Murphy!!
Go, go!
Page Dr. Lim.
Keep her stable.
No. No. No.
Yur...
No.
- Yur...
- What happened?
- No, no, no.
- He lost it, walked out mid-procedure.
Yuri... Yu...
- Yuri kucho saiken.
- Shaun?
Yur... Yuri... Yur...
Okay, Park,
take over the surgery.
Y... No!
Dr. Park.
Y...
- No.
- He obviously can't.
I don't think he lost it.
He was in complete charge
of that room.
I don't think
this is a meltdown.
He said he can't do it.
He said, "Can't do it."
Maybe he meant we can't do it.
I think he's seeing something...
We have a patient open
on the table.
Shaun, you have to tell us
what you're seeing.
It's okay, Shaun.
Breathe.
That's it. Now slowly.
What are you thinking?
When...
Okay. When I examined
the upper portion...
When I examined
the upper portion,
there was
a much larger area
of tumor-free esophagus
than anticipated...
That's correct, but not nearly
enough to reach the stomach.
But there is enough to accept
a jejunum free flap,
using a portion
of the small intestine
to replace the resected esophagus.
We don't do jejunum
free flaps.
They do in Japan.
I've been studying
their technique...
Yuri kucho saiken.
They have had great success.
It would mean Beth
wouldn't need a feeding tube.
But...
it is v-very complex.
It's too complex for you
to lead.
So you'll lose your case.
Yes...
I haven't done a transposition
graft like that before.
Think you can walk us
through it?
Yes.
I'll scrub in.
Stomach...
is perfect.
Check the duodenum.
The only way Teal
will accept the treatment
is if we give her
no room for denial.
Did you really believe
what you said?
That their love is enough
to get them through this?
Such BS,
the belief that love is enough.
Even worse, it's corollary
that a lack of love
is the real problem.
If only they had someone
in their life
who had enough faith in them,
had enough love for them,
they could've pulled through.
It's wrong and it's mean.
What's that?
Flush the area.
There's our bleed.
But it's not coming
from an ulcer...
It's coming from a tumor.
It's obstructing
his digestive tract.
I'm paging Melendez
to the O.R.
- Okay.
- Actually, I'm...
I'm gonna need
an extra shot.
Rough day?
Had to... help out in the E.R.
with an eight-year-old boy
who was accidentally
shot by his sister.
He'll survive,
but with brain damage.
That's horrible.
Yes, it is.
And quite coincidental.
Like so many
other coincidences.
You know how many kids are shot
every day in this country?
19.
You know you're three times
more likely to be shot
if you have access
to guns than if you don't?
Here's another fact...
one in four women are victims
of violence at the hands
of their intimate partner.
No, no, no.
I'm not afraid of you.
This isn't about you.
Did something happen?
'Cause if it did,
I want to know about it.
You figure something horrible
must have happened to drive me
to such an irrational,
fear-driven choice?
I'm sorry. Hi.
The ends of the harvested
jejunum have been matched
for caliber size
for the attachment sites.
You should begin
proximal attachment
at the neck incision,
using layer-to-layer technique
on the esophagus
and microvascular anastomosis
of the vessels.
You wanted to know
when Dr. Semler
was heading to O.R. #3.
Dr. Park, scrub out and join Semler.
I-if it's all right,
I'd rather stay here.
You're needed
where you're needed.
Tumor is free.
Bag it, tag it,
and get it to Path.
Do you smell that?
Smells like a distillery.
But we know he couldn't
have touched a drop
for at least 24 hours.
Final stitch is yours.
It's completely symbolic,
but symbols can be powerful.
Easy-peasy.
You had something called
Auto-Brewery Syndrome.
The tumor we found was blocking
your intestinal tract.
So carbs weren't being digested,
they were being
trapped and fermented.
Your stomach was actually
creating its own alcohol.
You were drunk,
but not from drinking.
With the removal of the tumor...
which was benign...
you're all good.
And the arrhythmia's gone, too.
I never doubted you.
Her faith in you
saved your life.
Thank you.
I was so pissed
when Lim kicked me out...
until I found Semler had
an appendectomy waiting for me.
Got my first lead after all.
I'm happy for you.
Really.
I'm happy for me, too.
You earned it.
And you'll get your chance
again soon, Shaun.
So that's it?
All's well that ends well?
Your surgeon walked out
on his case.
That's your takeaway?
That he failed?
A chef can eat.
Well, as a diagnostician,
he did something wonderful,
but as a surgeon?
Yes, he failed.
We don't work alone,
Marcus.
Every time
we have a good outcome,
it's because everyone in the room
did something right.
Shaun came up with the idea,
Park got it out of him,
I approved the surgery,
and you?
The only reason
Shaun is working here
is because
you believed in him.
Yay, team.
Are you still having
a gun fight?
Oh, yeah.
Second day of my marriage
and we are at an impasse.
Tried the logical approach,
I tried the emotional approach,
no compromise.
Only thing left is the nuclear option,
which really sucks.
The thought of having a gun
in my house makes me sick...
Has Debbie let you touch
her breast?
What?
Has Debbie let you
touch her breast?
Yeah.
Then you shouldn't worry
about anything else.
I was wrong...
this time.
But 99.9% of cases,
I would be right.
If... if someone acts like an addict,
lies like an addict,
smells like an addict,
then they are an addict.
And just because
we stumbled across
the one ridiculously
fluky exception,
that isn't going to change
my attitude moving forward.
I respect you, Claire.
Might even go as far
as to say I like you.
And I know
you're angry right now.
At your mother.
The world.
Yourself.
Eventually,
that'll go away.
Or... at least some of it will.
But until then,
giving up on that 0.1%
means giving up on
something else.
Hope.
Hope...
killed my mother.
We need to talk.
About the 800-pound gun
in the room.
I'm working
on my compromise skills.
Okay.
Looks like your first
lead surgery went well.
I didn't have
a first lead surgery.
Yes.
It went very well.
Can I check
your other breast?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org