Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Today is not Saturday.
Why did you make me pancakes?
They are fresh start pancakes.
Like the first day
of school every year
when you get to wear
a brand-new outfit.
Well, not everyone
wore a new outfit.
But the rule in this house
is that when you start
a new life event,
you get pancakes.
I don't want a fresh start.
I want to stay in surgery.
I know.
And I am really proud of you
for handling it all so...
Doctors, please give me
one more minute.
We have an associate pastor
at the church,
but Clarence
likes to write the sermons.
- Sorry.
- Please.
Although this is important too.
The surgery consists
of two steps.
First we fuse the spine
to stabilize it,
and then we remove the tumor.
Because the cancer has spread
to your lymph nodes,
you'll still have
to follow up with chemo.
Clarence, are you in pain?
Quite a bit actually,
but I'm fine.
Well,
since what's causing your pain
is the tumor pushing
against your spine,
the spinal fusion will ease
pressure on your nerves
and should eliminate your pain.
Please, I, uh...
I need this pain.
Can't you just do the second
part and remove the tumor?
If we don't fuse the spine,
it'll make removing the tumor
a lot more difficult.
More difficult,
but it can be done?
It can.
But I recommend against it.
Especially since
there's no reason not to.
I did something
unforgivable.
This pain is my punishment.
Can I ask what you did
that was so bad?
I killed someone.
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
My sister and I were
coming home from climbing
Mt. Whitney.
We're doing the State 50 climbs.
The numbness started
during the climb?
First my hands,
and then my feet.
You have a headache?
Yeah.
High altitude causes headaches.
Dehydration compounds it.
From now on just climb
slower and drink more.
Tell them about the other thing.
Before leaving for the mountain,
I had this
weird sensation like...
Dread.
I couldn't shake it.
Well, when people describe a sense of
impending doom, it's usually anxiety.
No, it was like a premonition,
that I was going to die.
I'm sure it was...
Dr. Park will run a brain scan,
and we'll do some lab work.
Shaun.
Hello, Dr. Lever.
Carly is fine.
Welcome to pathology.
It is going to be great
working with you.
What do you think?
I know it's a lot to take in.
It's kind of like your first
time at Disneyland, right?
I've never been to Disneyland.
Let me give you a tour.
Cytopathology, forensics,
genomics, microbiology.
We get to identify organisms,
interpret cell morphology,
sequence genes.
Is that a D300e
pathogen antibacterial
bioprinter?
It's new.
You're working on
antibiotic resistance
in emerging microorganisms?
It's "we" now, Shaun.
Yes, we are.
Do you want to play with it?
Very much.
Go ahead.
It's kind of your job now.
We are the detectives.
Surgeons are just the beat cops.
Our best bet is to try
to separate the tumor
from his cord,
and then resect it.
Okay, this is insane.
You know how
he "killed" a person?
He was counseling a parishioner
who committed suicide.
That must have been traumatic.
Traumatic, yes.
Murder, no.
Hey, I know it's stupid,
but he has autonomy.
I didn't stay stupid.
I said "insane."
You want to override his
wishes because he's religious?
Something like 90% of
Americans believe in God.
I'm one of them.
Are we all mentally impaired?
Should you ignore us all
if you don't like our choices?
Only those getting divine
messages from their tumors.
He's not crazy.
Okay, you're right.
He is just stupid.
But don't we have a duty to educate him?
You're gonna talk him
out of his religion? No.
You told him the surgery
was more dangerous this way.
I don't think he appreciated
how much more dangerous.
Good idea.
He thinks he'll go to hell if
he dies before he's forgiven.
Make sure he knows
it can happen on the table.
An MRI for anxiety?
It does fly in the face of reducing
unnecessary medical tests.
When I was a resident,
I had a patient come through the ER.
Female.
35 years old.
Slight cough.
Slightly hypothyroid.
Normal vitals.
I labeled her a whiner
because she kept insisting,
"I'm gonna die."
I sent her home.
And she died?
No. She kept
coming back.
Over and over again.
We do this test,
we prove there's nothing wrong with her,
we send her home reassured.
Damn.
The MRI showed
a high grade meningioma.
An advanced tumor that grows in the
tissue layers that cover the brain.
Its features are consistent
with it being malignant.
These tumors
tend to be aggressive
and impossible to fully resect.
Um, so what...
What can you do?
Palliative care,
symptom control
with medications.
You're risking spinal damage,
paralysis, death.
If that's what God chooses,
then that is his will.
If you have cancer because
he wants you to have cancer,
why are you here?
Getting treatment?
I'm here because
I believe in science.
I am who I am
because I believe in God.
So do you think all people who
are sick are being punished?
I mean, we have an eight-year-old
down the hall with bone cancer.
You want to go tell her
God hates her?
I'm sure that girl is not
suffering as a punishment.
She's suffering so others
may have a chance
to show her mercy,
to show her compassion,
so she can inspire.
I don't know His plan, but I know
it's not as simple as you would...
No.
No, it's not simple.
Except for your pain.
His name was Michael.
His wife found his body.
You had no idea.
I knew he was depressed.
But you thought
he was getting better.
I didn't take his call.
Because I was having a drink.
It'd been a long day
dealing with the renovations,
and I was having a damn drink.
Hey, Shaun.
Hey, Carly.
I started Sadie Barnes
on anti-seizure medication,
need you to run
a peak phenytoin level.
The couriers must be happy
that the surgeons
are doing their own
specimen deliveries.
How you doing down here?
Carly says pathologists
are the detectives,
surgeons are just the beat cops.
Shaun, are you happy here?
When did you give the patient
her loading dose?
One hour ago.
Hmm.
Shaun, if you're happy,
that's great.
But if you're not,
you have to tell Han
how you feel.
You need to show him you care
and that you believe
in yourself.
Do you need this done STAT?
No.
She's asymptomatic.
It's just for seizure prevention.
Good.
Carly says that in pathology
you can take a break
whenever you want.
I want to take a break now.
I'm going for a walk.
He shouldn't be in pathology.
He's a good surgical resident.
You're right.
Then you'll move him back? No.
You're wrong about that part.
He should be in pathology.
But he was a good surgical resident.
Then why...
Because he'll never
be a good surgeon.
How do you think
he'll do in three years
when no one's looking
over his shoulder?
When he's looking over
someone else's shoulder?
Supervising new residents,
leading grand rounds,
advocating for
vulnerable patients.
Do you see him doing any of
that without a safety net?
We can help him get there.
Just because he wants
to be a surgeon,
just because you want
him to be a surgeon,
doesn't mean he gets to have
that dream come true.
Has it occurred to you
that maybe
we know Shaun
better than you do?
Has it occurred to you that
that might be your problem?
That your view of him might be
distorted because you like him?
Has it occurred to you that maybe
he's better off in pathology?
That maybe he'll even like it?
Do you care?
I thought you might.
We need better ventral exposure.
Drill off more of the
pedicle and vertebral body.
Ligate the exiting nerve root.
We'll take it with the tumor
for a wider margin.
I can't see it.
The tumor's causing the spinal
cord to be bowed up to us.
We need more exposure to get
around and in front of it.
The vertebrae is
too fragmented and displaced.
We can't get a complete
resection without stabilization.
He's tanking.
Probably spinal shock from tension
on the cord. We need to abort.
All right, on three.
One, two, three.
You fixed me!
No, no.
What happened to my pain?
Stop!
We didn't fix you.
There was a complication.
We injected anesthetic.
It'll wear off.
We had to stop the surgery
before we could
remove the tumor.
You went into shock.
We lost your heart rate
and blood pressure.
We warned it would be a trickier
surgery without the fusion.
Nothing has changed.
The anesthetic will wear off,
the pain will come back,
but worse.
When can you try again?
Try again?
We failed.
There is no reason
to think we will succeed
next time unless
we do the fusion...
But you know what the issues are,
you learned... Why haven't you?
Do think God wants you to die?
Please.
Try again.
Cyanide poisoning.
The cause of death
on the Atlin case.
You know how I found it?
I smelled it.
Almonds.
Dr. Park's patient.
I flagged her eosinophil count.
It doesn't match up
with the diagnosis
of advanced meningioma
listed on the requisition.
Great. Nice work.
I'm going to talk
to Dr. Lim about it.
Whoa there, Shaun.
Hold up.
You don't need to do that.
The attendings are on the lookout
for the flags. They'll run with it.
I want to run with it.
You've been on the receiving
end. You know how it works.
How it works
is I see something abnormal
and then I discuss it
with the team,
and we plan how we'll fix it.
We run with it.
Shaun, once a test is done,
we move on to the next one.
I'd like to take a walk.
Are you going to walk to Dr. Lim
and discuss this case, Shaun?
That's not what we do here.
We investigate, report,
and then we move on.
Are you gonna be able
to do that,
move on?
I don't know.
But I will try very hard.
Next time.
Dr. Browne.
Is this about a patient?
No.
Come in.
I've heard a lot about you.
I'm aware you stood up
to a supervisor.
Is that what's happening now?
Um, I put together
a list of cases
which Dr. Murphy
contributed to.
Uniquely.
You're a loyal friend.
I've specified the ideas he had,
ideas that no one else
around here could have...
Do you think I hate him?
No.
But I think
you might be biased against
him because of his condition.
So he doesn't have communication issues?
I'm wrong about that?
No. But he...
If he had the flu,
I would tell him to stay
home until he got better.
He has autism...
I could tell him to stay home
until he gets better.
Instead I found a place
for him to help us,
to save lives.
And you should know I have rather
mixed feelings about loyalty.
All righty.
There you go.
Hello.
Aaron.
It's good to see you.
Yeah.
The feeling is mutual.
Can I have one of those?
The chocolate chip muffin?
Yes, please.
Special occasion?
Yes.
Yeah?
As of today, I am no longer
injecting toxins into my body.
Except, of course,
with chocolate chips.
Oh, you're done with chemo?
Wow. That's amazing.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I was thinking of going out
tonight and celebrating
what may be very good news.
If you're free, my treat.
I...
I'm sorry, Aaron.
I have, uh, another commitment.
Oh. Um, tomorrow then?
This week is really crazy.
You know what? I am not doing
chemo every night next week,
so I am free every single
night, so...
Aaron, I'm seeing someone.
I'm sorry.
Nothing to be sorry about.
It was good to see you.
Keep an extra close
eye on blood pressure and heart rate.
I have extra
fluid, vasopressors,
and inotropes ready.
Why no God?
You follow in the tradition
that you're handed.
My family wasn't religious.
We never went to church.
I was there every Sunday.
8:00 a.m.
for Catholic mass.
My parents eventually got tired of
all the rules and turned Lutheran.
They found that dull
and went back to Catholic.
That's my tradition.
What do you think
it'll be like when you die?
Probably like it was before I was born.
A whole lot of nothing.
We're there.
Where we were when everything
went wrong last time.
We need to remove the tumor
without putting any pressure
on his cord at all,
or he'll be back in spinal shock.
And we need more tumor release
from the vertebral body.
Extend your osteotomies
proximal and distal.
Good.
I think I got a free plane...
Retract it from the cord
a little more.
I got it.
Now, when you remove it
careful not to morselize it.
Can you hold that up?
Dr. Reznick,
give me a measurement.
Max length is 4.5.
Get a pre-op scan up.
That says the tumor's
eight centimeters.
How does a tumor shrink
from eight centimeters
to 4.5 without radiation
in two weeks?
It doesn't.
Why the page, Shaun?
And why are you in radiology?
We rely on flags.
You have to count on
the ordering physician
seeing it while you move on
to something else.
Okay. And?
I don't agree with
Sadie Barnes' diagnosis,
and I think her tumor
should be biopsied.
Shaun, I...
Dr. Han wanted me away from patients.
Patients are not allowed
in the viewing room.
So I'm not doing anything wrong.
Two radiologists said
it was a malignant meningioma
in the insular region
and encasing the MCA vessels.
That's exactly where it is.
And her clinical picture
matches perfectly.
Arm and leg numbness.
The tumor attachment to the
dura is slightly anomalous.
And the insular region
is slightly atypical, too.
What differential diagnoses
are you proposing?
I need to speak to the patient.
Should I ask
Dr. Han for permission?
Shaun, I...
...will bring your concern about
the scan to the head of radiology.
But approaching Dr. Han?
Don't do that.
Now, I already talked to him
about your reassignment.
I don't know if it'll make
any difference...
If I were Claire, would you
let me approach Dr. Han
about something
that concerned me?
Yes.
I probably would.
Hmm.
Is that because Claire doesn't make
mistakes when she's communicating?
Yes.
Then do you think Dr. Han made the right
decision by sending me to pathology?
No.
The lymph nodes
have shrunk, too.
This is a PET scan
from two weeks ago.
Enlarged and cancerous.
Today...
...they've all regressed.
Spontaneous regression
has been reported
in melanomas,
renal cell carcinomas,
neuroblastomas, and some
types of blood cancers.
In a sarcoma
that's metastasized?
No. But if it happened
in those others, why not?
Because none of them make sense.
When I read about
disappearing cancer,
I always think some doctor missed
something, forgot something,
screwed up something.
The theory is that
the body somehow triggers
an immune response
against the cancer.
Something somehow lights a fuse.
The theory says the fuse
is lit by an infection.
His lab work proves
he hasn't had one.
At this point, the most
credible explanation is...
Are you gonna use the "M" word?
You seriously can't say it?
Only when referencing
the 1980 U.S. hockey team.
Keep testing.
Anything you can think of.
Molecular markers,
T-cells, PD-L1.
We'll need permission
from the patient.
Which raises another issue,
what are we gonna
do next, medically?
He was supposed to
start chemo next week.
No, it'll wipe out
his immune system,
which may be what's
actually killing his cancer.
If we don't know
what's making him better,
we don't know what
to stop, what to start.
So we do nothing?
Just trust God to fix him?
We trust whatever is currently
fixing him to keep fixing him.
If he took a Tylenol
yesterday at 8:00,
he takes a Tylenol
today at 8:00.
Monitor him. Closely.
Scans constantly.
Hmm.
Hello, Dr. Glassman.
Hi.
Thank you for coming.
He has been doing this
for two hours.
Shaun.
What are you up to?
Alphabetizing our canned goods
and checking
all the expiration dates.
Well, somebody's got to do it.
Is something wrong?
No.
Okay.
Okay. I think
Dr. Lim's patient's
diagnosis is wrong,
but I can't prove it
without information,
and I'm not allowed
to talk to patients.
Shaun.
I want to run with things.
I want to fix people.
Can you help me become
a surgical resident again?
No. I can't, Shaun.
I'm not president...
Yes.
I'm not the president of
the hospital anymore, Shaun.
And even...
Even if I was, it's irrelevant.
You have to stand up
for yourself.
And you know what?
If you can't,
then the new Head of Surgery,
the Chief, he's right.
Now, I can go
tell him he's wrong.
It won't do any good.
Or you can go show him.
I'm doing research
concerning Sadie Barnes.
She's asleep.
Perfect. I'm not allowed
to speak with her.
I'm looking for her sister Jess.
I haven't seen her.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
Can you explain why, instead of
remaining in pathology as directed,
you were in a patient's room,
going through her purse?
I didn't speak to her.
She was asleep.
Dr. Murphy,
any reticence I had
about removing you from
surgery just vanished.
You shouldn't be in
contact with patients.
Or their families.
Or anything they own.
Do you understand, or am I
gonna be forced to fire you?
Sadie's social media says that
she finances her climbing travel
by working as
a freelance food critic.
She reviewed a Japanese
restaurant that used to have
a Restaurant Grading System Score of
"A," but then it dropped to a "C,"
which corresponds to very
bad food safety practices.
Bad sushi can lead to worms,
but it usually doesn't
because stomach acid almost
always kills fish parasites.
But not if someone
is taking an acid blocker,
which 60 million Americans are.
I saw a bottle in her purse.
Sadie could have sparganosis
with an encapsulated worm that
is mimicking a meningioma.
That's a good idea.
Excellent.
I'll tell the patient.
I will tell the patient.
I'll tell her
we're doing a biopsy
to confirm
the initial diagnosis.
But we're...
It will tell us
if the initial diagnosis
is correct.
Your theory is a real long shot.
It would be irresponsible
to get her hopes up.
Hmm.
The surgery went well.
We were able to extract the
entire tumor without complication.
Thank you.
When can we start chemo?
There are a few follow-up
tests we want to run first.
And we want to retake
your history.
Make sure we have a proper list
of all medications
you've been taking.
You want to take his history
after the surgery?
What's going on?
What are you not telling us?
What went wrong?
Nothing.
The fact is, the surgery went
better than we'd hoped.
Your cancer seems to be
going away on its own.
We'll run our tests.
We're confident that there
is a medical explanation.
Oh, Clarence.
Hi.
Hi, Aaron.
Um, what I...
What I told you earlier,
that I'm seeing someone...
I'm not.
I mean, I-I-I had one date,
but it wasn't, you know... Okay.
We're... We're just...
We're not a good match.
That's what
I wanted to tell you.
That's not true, you know.
You know, that's not true.
You like me. A lot.
And I like you
even more than that.
So what is this?
You know, I'd really
rather not get into it.
You came to my house...
To tell you what I told you,
which I just told you.
Okay, you came here to be honest,
and you're only
gonna be honest halfway?
You're not timid.
No.
Okay. Then what?
The last time I was here,
we were headed upstairs...
Yes, we were.
You fell.
Yes, I did.
I tried to help you,
and you pushed me away.
I was embarrassed.
You were sick.
You needed help.
And I'm not sick anymore.
Maybe.
And I want to go and celebrate.
With you.
Specifically with you.
'Cause we have fun.
You... You make...
You make me laugh.
You make me feel good.
I like being with you.
Sounds horrible.
But bad things are gonna happen.
Aaron, I-it can't just be
about having fun together.
One of us is gonna get sick,
one of us is gonna need
to be taken care of...
Wait, wait, wait.
I just want to go out
and have a nice dinner with you.
Not to run away to Reno,
find a priest in an Elvis suit.
What are we gonna do, Aaron?
Just drive to a hill with
a view and neck till prom?
And then I'm gonna come home
and hope you call?
Yeah, uh, you know,
I just came to apologize.
I'm sorry.
And I'm really glad...
I'm... I'm glad
you're finished with chemo.
And...
You're gonna...
You're gonna beat this thing.
Your immunoglobulins are normal.
Everything is normal.
We can't find
a scientific explanation.
Our prayers...
It's a miracle.
Miracle or not,
it seems we're
on the same page now.
There is no reason not to do the
spinal fusion to eliminate your pain.
Do more tests.
Clarence.
There are no more tests.
T-T-There must be.
There must be an explanation.
Redo your tests.
Find new tests.
"Let all bitterness and wrath
"and anger and clamor and
slander be put away from you."
Ephesians 4:31.
I didn't take you
for a believer.
I'm not, anymore.
I'm not sure you are either.
God speaks directly to Noah,
Moses, Job, and Solomon.
And now apparently
he has singled out
Pastor Clarence of San Jose
to join the ranks
of the prophets.
I'm sorry, but unless
there is a burning bush,
it is narcissistic
to think that God
has made you
his personal project.
God speaks to every one of us.
You just have to listen.
You are not listening.
People get cancer all the time.
Often that results in pain.
Those things are not unique.
What is unique
is having an aggressive
metastatic cancer
start to disappear without
any rational explanation.
The issue isn't God.
You have to forgive yourself.
What I did...
Cannot be undone.
But your pain can.
Clarence.
Your pain...
Your pain does no one any good.
Okay.
Osteotome and mallet.
You lied when you said you never
went to church. What happened?
I didn't want to have this
conversation is what happened.
I'm not judging.
My brother took
a year off school to travel
and came back a non-believer.
So ask him.
Was it freeing,
or did you feel empty?
Hand me the
first polyaxial pedicle screw.
It was like losing a loved one.
The moment of truth.
Follow me.
Our initial diagnosis was wrong.
You don't have a meningioma.
You have a worm in your brain.
And while that sounds fairly gross,
it is completely curable.
So, the sense of doom, it was...
It was wrong?
It saved your life.
As did Dr. Murphy.
This is the pathologist
who noticed
an abnormality
in one of your tests.
That led us to this discovery.
Can I give you a hug, too, Dr. Murphy?
No.
You and your sister
will be free to conquer
whichever of the remaining
50 peaks you choose
as soon as my team
surgically removes the worm.
Thank you.
Oh! Of course.
There are not a lot of doctors
who would have made the leap
that you made today, Shaun.
Good work.
Yes, it was excellent work.
Most people
would say "thank you,"
but technically that's not
an incorrect response.
Hmm.
Have a good evening.
You've earned it.
I don't want to go on walks.
I don't want to move on
from cases
after the tests are done.
I do not want to be
a pathologist.
Dr. Han, you need to make me
a surgical resident again.
I appreciate
you telling me that.
I was wondering whether you had it
in you to advocate for yourself.
But the truth is, Shaun,
what you did today,
it proved I'm right.
Your skills are tremendous.
Your weaknesses,
equally significant.
You could be
a great pathologist.
Just think of all
the Sadies out there,
waiting for you to save them.
Dr. Browne,
Dr. Reznick.
The surgery went well.
Your spine is stable.
I'm scared.
There may still be some residual
pain as you heal, but...
No, I...
I keep wondering,
what if I disobeyed God?
You have to have faith.
But you lost yours.
I didn't have a miracle to
help me through the dark times.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org