(SITAR MUSIC PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
YOGA INSTRUCTOR: Move from
Bhujangasana into Adho Mukha Svanasana.
And hold that.
Do you like this? Mmm...
I'm not sure.
I like that you like it.
(ALARM CHIMES) Time for work!
(SIGHS)
Guess we'll finish Vinyasa
flow... (RECORDING TURNS OFF)
next time I come over.
You shouldn't come over anymore.
You should move in.
Things are different now.
You lived here before.
What's different?
Everything is different.
Then, we were roomies,
pals, buddies,
and now we're... a real thing.
A better thing, for sure,
but also more complicated.
We're the same people in the
same place doing the same things.
It's bigger than that, Shaun.
I hope it is. I...
Living together means more commitment,
more trust.
And I don't think
we're quite there yet.
You don't trust me?
No, I do. It's just...
I need a bit more.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(WHISPERING) Copernicus1543.
It's my banking password.
(EXPLOSIONS)
(BOTH SCREAM) Yes! I got you!
No! Bow to your queen.
No, bitch! No! Yes!
(BOTH LAUGH)
Argh! Where did you find the
10,000 hours that you put into that?
Phew! I like filling my evenings
with numbing mindlessness. Mmm.
(CELLPHONE CHIMES) Oh.
Ugh!
Morgan needs me to
go in ASAP. (TYPING)
You figure she
shouldn't page you?
She can handle it on her own
because she used to
be a surgical resident?
Be the bigger person.
It's an ingrown hair.
Mmm.
Definitely an ingrown hair.
Unfortunately, the ingrown hair
caused an abscess
that needs to be lanced.
By a surgeon.
Please give this man
the VIP treatment.
I have another case to attend to,
but don't worry.
I'll be checking in.
Such a nice lady.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
So, how shall we proceed?
I'm going with "drain the
abscess and dress the wound."
Set it up.
Maybe we should do a biopsy?
Well,
it could be a cutaneous pili migrans
or have a deep sinus tract
or a creeping eruption
caused by a parasitic disease.
Give him the VIP treatment.
Abdominal pain can be
scary when you're pregnant.
But I wouldn't worry. You
have two rambunctious boys.
I know. It's like a cage
match in here. (CHUCKLES)
Shaun,
where's your first-year resident?
I have two first-year residents,
but I don't want to teach them.
They're very distracting.
You have a dizygotic,
dichorionic,
diamniotic pregnancy.
It just means your
twins are fraternal
and in separate amniotic sacs.
First-years aren't
distractions. They're godsends.
She has edema.
Not surprising for someone
who's 26 weeks pregnant.
They'll do anything you want.
Scut work, follow-ups,
coffee runs...
I don't like coffee. ...laundry,
apple runs.
I already did that.
(MACHINE BEEPING, HUMMING)
What was her BP? Normal.
(MACHINE BEEPS) BP's no
longer normal. She's hypertensive.
What does that mean, Dr. Murray?
Is your vision blurred?
A bit. I'm tired.
Sounds like preeclampsia.
If we don't get your
BP down ASAP,
you could lose your pregnancy.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
We need to start you on
anti-hypertensive meds,
but your edema makes
it difficult to place an IV,
so we need to
run a central line.
(APPLE CRUNCHES)
(MUFFLED) Dr. Jackson?
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
(WINCES)
Mind if I give a hand,
Dr. Murphy?
Hmm.
Is there anyone
you want us to call?
Uh,
my boyfriend decided his obligations ended
at offering to pay
for an abortion.
Soft man in a hard world.
(CHUCKLES LIGHTLY)
(RAPID BEEPING)
Fetal heart rate's dropping.
But only one of them.
Did you have another birth?
No. Any pregnancy?
Miscarriage,
abortion, stillbirth?
I had an abortion when I was 15.
It's not preeclampsia.
One fetus is Rh-positive,
and the mother is Rh-negative,
and her body is
perceiving him as a threat
and attacking him
with antibodies.
Antibodies she could only have
if she had an earlier pregnancy.
My body is trying to
kill one of my babies?
Yes.
Waiting on Billy's
biopsy results?
To confirm an ingrown hair?
You grew up in a Hasidic family,
right?
How are they handling
you being a doctor?
(INHALES DEEPLY)
I haven't spoken to them in
four years, except one sister.
I chose not to live
by their rules. I...
I knew the consequences.
My dad was a real estate agent,
obsessed with two
completely unrelated things,
teeth and taxes.
Thought I'd spend the rest
of my life selling condos.
Now I'm a surfin' surgeon,
but I still floss
three times a day
and pay my installments
four times a year.
So, what's my dental floss?
Fire and brimstone.
Mmm.
Actually,
that is from the New Testament.
I don't even know
what brimstone is.
I meant you fear disaster.
Your people's history
is kind of filled with it.
Billy has cancer.
How are your first-years doing?
Jordan talks too much,
and Olivia talks too little.
And Olivia does not know
where the jugular vein is.
You see her resume?
Her grades and USMLE
scores were nearly perfect.
So,
if it's not a lack of knowledge,
what do you think it is?
I think Olivia has the potential
to be an exemplary doctor
if you push her,
give her a little extra attention.
Isn't that unfair to Jordan?
Was it unfair to the applicant
who didn't get your position
because Dr. Glassman thought
that you needed some extra attention?
Olivia just doesn't like being
in the spotlight. That's all.
Olivia's resume didn't say
anything about not liking the spotlight.
Exactly.
Don't trust resumes.
SHAUN: Locate jugular vein.
Insert needle.
Get a venous blush.
Remove syringe,
leaving needle in,
then thread... Thread
wire into needle.
Remove needle.
Scalpel to skin,
while being aware of a persistent
left-sided superior vena cava placement,
present in 4% of those with
congenital heart disease.
Remove wire.
Suture in line to skin.
And done.
I guess you were nervous before.
Didn't you have
first-case jitters?
No.
(PAGER CHIMES)
The sick twin has gone
into severe distress.
You have amelanotic melanoma.
Skin cancer.
DR. REZNICK: But
there's good news.
We should be able
to remove all of it.
We can do it today.
Sorry. Car trouble.
Hi, Dr. Park. Just telling
Billy about his cancer.
I got a great mechanic for you.
If you tell her Billy sent you,
she'll give you a
friends-and-family.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
Thanks for that.
You have an amazing attitude.
You know,
my wife used to tease me about that.
She died three years ago.
I'm sorry.
(SIGHS)
You know,
on our second date, I got a flat.
Now,
I think she thought I was gonna curse,
(CHUCKLES) but
all I could say was,
"Good timing. Costco's
got a sale on tires."
(CHUCKLES)
(SNIFFS) It's Addy's Auto,
Los Gatos and Gateway.
(SIGHS)
(MONITOR BEEPING,
ULTRASOUND PULSING)
We are through the uterine wall.
Dr. Jackson,
what's our next step?
Advance through the trocar
15 millimeters beyond the tip
until the opening
of the distal basket
can be confirmed by ultrasound.
Exactly.
What would you like me to advance,
Dr. Jackson?
Oh. Yes. Right.
OLIVIA: Obviously, you would be advancing
the double basket rocket catheter, not this.
Sorry.
Not your fault.
If a junior resident
is ill-prepared,
that's on the senior resident.
How is it fair that I get blamed
for a first-year's mistake,
and how can I help that person
without being unfair
to the other one?
And how fair was the preferential
treatment that you gave me?
And how fair was it to
the other first-year resident,
who didn't get placed
because you helped me?
And how fair was... Whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Put the list down.
Only four questions at
a time. That's my limit.
What kind of mistake?
Even though I went over
the procedure with Olivia,
she still gave
Dr. Andrews the pusher rod
when he needed
the rocket catheter,
and he said it was my fault.
It was your fault.
You got to help
her a little more.
That is not fair to Jordan.
What does fairness
have to do with it?
It's not about equality.
It's about figuring out
what each person needs
and then teaching
them how to get it.
How do I know what they need?
(SIGHS) Well,
you've taught them medicine, right?
So, uh,
maybe it's something else.
Maybe it's an emotional issue.
Well, then I definitely can't
give them what they need.
You can ask them.
About their emotions?
Yeah, ask them how they feel.
I don't care how they feel.
That's the beauty of it.
You don't have to care.
You just have to ask
them how they really feel.
Then they start talking.
(LAUGHS) And some
people love to talk.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(MONITOR BEEPING)
CLAIRE: Oh. (SCOFFS) Mmm.
Have you been working out?
DR. PARK: I could
only find mediums.
(LAUGHS)
You know how many sets
of large scrubs I had to hide?
Thirty-one.
DR. PARK: Injecting dye.
(WHEEZING)
(RAPID BEEPING)
BP's dropping.
Diffuse skin flushing.
He's in anaphylactic shock.
He's allergic to the
dye. Ten cc epinephrine.
BP barely measurable. We
should intubate. Initiate CPR.
You should cannulate
his femoral vein
to give pressers and volume.
Let's intubate and cannulate.
His jugular's distended.
Maybe he has cardiac tamponade
from a pericardial effusion.
He might need
open-heart surgery.
ENRIQUE: Worst-case scenario
worked out for you the first time.
Really think lightning's
gonna strike twice?
Maybe not, but I'm still not gonna
stand on a hill in a thunderstorm.
Let's call Lim.
Prep the patient
for a pericardiotomy.
Two for two.
(SITAR MUSIC
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Okay, you can't do yoga at work.
I do it at home.
What's the difference?
Work behavior is not the
same as home behavior.
Ooh. So you're
saying context matters.
Of course.
Same way that two
roommates living together
is different from a
couple living together.
Same people, same place,
different context.
Once our feelings change,
everything changes.
I still feel the same
way when I'm with you.
Happy.
Kenzie's BP and
edema have improved.
The fetus's echo shows
improved heart function.
Catheter's working.
How do you feel?
Okay.
How do you really feel?
Um...
Really okay?
You want to know why
I'm so nervous all the time?
Uh...
I don't know. (CHUCKLES)
I've always been
very terrified of firsts.
First day of school,
camp, church,
all the new faces watching me,
just waiting for me to screw up.
(SCOFFS)
First day of fifth grade,
when Mrs. Deloitte asked
me what 6 times 9 was,
I told the whole
class it was 45.
Yeah,
I can still hear them laughing at me.
And two nights ago,
I dreamt I was standing
in front of Mrs.
Deloitte's class again.
Couldn't wait to wake up.
But when I did,
I realized that if I got
the answer wrong today,
no one will laugh,
but someone may die.
The kids laughed at me, too.
Even though I knew
6 times 9 was 54.
(CHUCKLES)
One of the amniotic
sacs ruptured.
The strong twin's.
It's metastasized to his liver.
So, what do we do?
Laparoscopic
radiofrequency ablation.
Short recovery time, but a
significant chance his cancer returns.
Care to rebut?
I think we should consider
a hepatic lobectomy
and lymph node dissection.
Remove the affected
area of the liver,
all the surrounding tissue,
and every swollen node we find.
And that's the
aggressive approach.
Longer recovery time,
high risk of complications,
and, uh,
admittedly,
the best shot at beating the cancer.
By "complications,"
you mean a barely functioning liver,
a persistent threat of fatal bleeds,
and chronic pain.
As surgeons, you can gut him,
but as his primary doctor,
I have to find the balance
between longevity
and quality of life.
CLAIRE: Last week,
you were trying to perform surgery
from the gallery,
and now you hate surgeons.
Pick a side.
ASHER: A piecemeal approach
is not going to work with Billy.
Every time we try
to solve a problem,
we discover another one.
You may have left
your religion in Brooklyn,
but you keep looking for
meaning in random events.
The dice have no memory.
ASHER: I'm not looking for
meaning. I'm looking for patterns.
Maybe he's got some
underlying condition.
I agree with Asher.
The dice have no memory,
but they can be loaded.
So... safe and
seriously compromised
or aggressive and possibly dead?
Your case, Dr. Browne.
Your call.
How you feeling?
You sacrificed a lot.
Your hands, your career.
And you're taking it
out on me and Claire
and the whole
surgical profession.
I get it. It hurts.
You're pathetic.
You're worried about me
because I'll never be a surgeon?
Boo-hoo.
You're worried about me
because I took pleasure
in screwing with you and Claire?
That's who I am.
The question is, who are you?
You don't show up late
with lame-ass excuses,
and when you get dissed,
you diss back, so...
How are you feeling?
Forget I asked.
He's lost most of
his amniotic fluid.
Won't last very long in utero.
In helping the weak,
we hurt the strong.
C-section?
If we do a C-section
to save the strong baby,
there's a 90% chance
the weak baby will die.
But if we do an amnioinfusion
to save the weak baby,
there's an 85% chance
that strong baby will die.
It's the better option.
5% to decide which baby lives?
Kenzie's body has
already made that choice.
If there's a strong
baby and a weak baby,
it's pretty clear
which one we save.
Survival of the fittest.
Sorry. It's just...
That's not really what we're about,
is it,
as a civilization?
Aren't the strong morally
obligated to help the weak?
And if they don't,
isn't everybody ultimately worse off?
Neither baby has to die.
Delayed interval delivery.
We induce labor,
deliver the strong twin,
then stop the labor to
keep the weak twin in utero
until his lungs mature.
The chances of stopping
labor are very slim.
That's true. There's about a 70%
chance that both babies would die.
Which makes it the
worst possible choice.
We need to ask Kenzie.
No, we don't.
Once she hears there's the
slightest chance of saving both babies,
she won't listen
to any alternatives.
Statistically,
it's a terrible option.
But it is an option.
No. No,
you can't seriously be asking me this.
I know that this is something no
mother should ever have to decide.
There are no good options here,
but there is one that'll most
likely make you the mother
of a healthy baby boy.
Okay.
Prep for an amnioinfusion...
Have you named them?
Dr. Allen.
Braydon and...
Landon.
(CRYING) No. No,
I can't do this.
You have to save both of them.
CLAIRE: We're at the tumor.
Unipolar ablation probe?
Pretty cool to think
that we diagnosed Billy
with metastatic
melanoma on Tuesday
and send him home on a Thursday.
Well, let's wait till Friday
to congratulate ourselves.
Current at 480 hertz, please.
Wait.
We got a leak. Bile
duct. (RAPID BEEPING)
Suction, suture,
linear stapler, stat.
(DOOR OPENS)
I believe she made
the right choice.
She made a choice
any mother would make
because the alternative
is unthinkable.
Isn't that exactly what
made it the right choice?
She has to live with it.
The safe choice is not
always the best choice.
If it were,
I'd be on an army base in Germany,
married to 1st Lieutenant
Dwayne Buckman.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Dr. Andrews,
you wanted to see me?
Yes,
Dr. Jackson. Please come in.
"Dr. Jackson."
I cannot say those two
words without grinning!
I know. (BOTH LAUGH)
So?
Uh, just checking in with you,
Livy.
(SIGHS)
Like you do with
all your first-years?
You wanted hands off.
You're getting hands off.
But I can still say
hi to my niece.
(LAUGHS)
It looks like you're
settling in pretty well.
No,
the way you spoke up yesterday...
I mean, that's a tough case,
tough crowd,
but you held your own.
I'm getting there.
Dr. Murphy's been
very supportive.
Murphy? Yeah,
I'm glad to hear it.
I'm sure he sees your potential.
But if you need anything,
you... Mmm.
...ask anyone but me.
Very hands off.
Hmm.
Shaun, this is not an argument
I ever thought I'd have
to have with a boyfriend,
whether moving
in together matters.
It so obviously does.
It so obviously
changes everything.
But
one of the reasons
I'm in this relationship
(SIGHS) is because of that.
You are different.
And when I think about us,
say, a year from now,
I can't imagine us
not living together.
So, if it's inevitable...
Shaun,
I am moving in with you.
Does that mean
you think we have enough
commitment and trust?
Honestly...
I'm not sure.
So,
you want to do it just
because it's inevitable?
Mmm. That makes
it sound terrible.
But that is kind of how I feel,
so, yeah.
You're moving back in!
(SIGHS) (CHUCKLES)
(PAGER CHIMES)
My girlfriend is
moving in with me.
We need additional venous
access to start the oxytocin.
I'll insert a 16-gauge IV.
How do you feel?
Good.
Insert a 16-gauge IV.
(SOFTLY) Okay.
All right.
There's gonna be a pinch.
Very good.
Once we start that drip,
at least one baby will be born.
I understand.
Okay.
Where are you going?
Kenzie's only two
centimeters dilated,
and even though
I'm not a surgeon,
I have other
important things to do.
You were wrong.
First-years aren't godsends.
They're a lot of work.
But I fixed Olivia.
Wonderful. Now fix Jordan.
She's the one you
have a problem with.
No. I... I don't.
Well, technically,
she has a problem with you...
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
...and anyone in authority.
You need to rein her in.
Okay, how do I do that?
How'd you fix Olivia?
(BUTTON CLICKS)
DR. REZNICK: No new paint,
no new parts.
No way you took this to a shop.
So,
there is something up with you.
Something personal.
Something you don't care
about. (CAR UNLOCKS)
That goes without saying.
Except,
it's messing with my games.
I just wanna humiliate you
without feeling like
I'm punching a kitten.
I was finalizing my divorce.
I thought you were already...
Not until yesterday.
And we didn't wanna deal with
a formal custody
arrangement for Kellan,
but now that he's 18,
it's official.
I know it's been over for years,
but when it's really over,
it hurts.
And I'm pissed at
myself for being hurt,
and, uh,
now I'm pissed at myself
for admitting that to the
coldest person I know.
(SIGHS)
My place has two
masters with en suites,
and it's rent-controlled,
so it's still probably
cheaper than your motel.
But staying with
me will cost you.
Kitty gotta punch back.
Thanks. But I'm good.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(KENZIE MOANING)
DR. GROMSKI: She's at 10 centimeters.
SHAUN: Prepare packed red
blood cells for possible transfusion.
Prepare forceps,
clamps, and scissors.
(MONITOR BEEPING,
ULTRASOUND PULSING) (KENZIE CRIES)
How do you feel? Really feel?
I feel fine.
Why do you have a
problem with authority?
(KENZIE MOANS) Seriously?
I have a problem with you
not acting like an authority.
You're not doing the
one thing any junior needs
from their supervisor.
If I'm screwing up... (WHIMPERS)
Not now. Not gonna screw up now.
(GROANS)
I need to know you're
at least watching.
I need to know you
got my ass covered.
(BREATHING HEAVILY, MOANING)
The leak in your bile duct
has caused an infection
that could lead to peritonitis.
We've got you on multiple
aggressive antibiotics,
but this infection
acts very quickly,
sometimes in a matter of hours.
Well, I feel fine.
Dopey, but fine.
Billy,
do you understand
what I just told you?
I might die tonight.
I get it.
What...
How do you do it?
I've...
(CHUCKLES) had worse days.
(SIGHS)
The day after Linda died...
I went to buy a gun.
Never used one before,
but I figured,
"How hard could it be
"to put it in my mouth
and pull the trigger?"
On my way to the store,
I saw a car parked
on the side of the road
with a flat.
Couple of kids who...
(CHUCKLES) clearly didn't know
what the heck they were doing.
And for some reason,
I pulled over and
changed their tire.
As I was leaving,
I told them, "Good timing.
"Costco's got a sale on tires."
That's when I
heard Linda's laugh.
"Hey, dummy.
"If you kill yourself,
"who's gonna
change the next tire?"
That's what saved my life.
Just wanting to help people.
Makes life worthwhile.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(MOANS)
(MONITOR BEEPING,
ULTRASOUND PULSING)
Brady. (CHUCKLES)
His lungs are also
underdeveloped.
SHAUN: He needs to
be placed on a ventilator.
Let's get him to the NICU.
SHAUN: Starting
magnesium sulfate.
That's to stop your labor.
I also need to ligate
the umbilical cord
and return it to your uterus.
Okay,
I have to focus on the patient
and I have to focus on Jordan
and I also have to focus on you.
I don't know how to do that.
Clamp.
Don't worry about me.
I appreciate you noticing I needed help,
but I'll be fine.
I didn't.
Dr. Andrews?
Your uncle.
Absorbable sutures.
He told you?
Not that part. I googled that.
I couldn't trust your resume.
How do you feel?
I feel
like my uncle doesn't
think I can hack it.
I feel... sick.
(GROANS) (RAPID BEEPING)
She's having
another contraction.
Adding terbutaline and
calcium channel blockers.
Am I gonna lose Landy?
Am I gonna lose both of them?
I don't know.
(MOANING) (MONITOR
BEEPING STEADILY)
She's still in labor?
BP's 95 over 60.
Kenzie,
we need to do a C-section.
No, no. If he comes out,
he'll die.
If he doesn't, you both will.
No. 69 over 40.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RAPID BEEPING)
We're doing a C-section.
No! Let's prep and drape her.
No. I can't.
I can't lose Landy.
No!
We need to restrain her.
Landy's going to be just fine.
Landy is not... Shh!
Kenzie,
just listen to my voice, okay?
Just focus.
(GROANING) What's
your favorite board game?
(MOANS) No! No!
SHAUN: Okay, restraints, please.
(MOANING)
Look at me. Don't look at them.
Board game.
(SNIFFLES) Uh... Mmm-hmm?
Scrabble. A classic. Nice!
Eight years from now,
Landy hits a triple word score
with the word "breathe."
Try it. Breathe.
(BREATHING DEEPLY) Good.
What's Brady doing?
Uh... He's...
He's mad that his
brother just schooled him.
(CHUCKLES) Of course he is.
(CHUCKLES)
(RAPID BEEPS)
(BEEPING SLOWS)
100 over 65.
Contractions are stopping.
Words with "X" and "Z."
Only way you're gonna beat them.
I better brush up.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Delayed interval twin delivery?
That's awesome. I can't teach.
Did you ask the
first-years how they feel?
Yes. Unhappy.
Okay, that's great.
Not that they're unhappy,
but that you asked them,
they confided in you,
and you learned something.
I learned that Olivia needed help,
so I helped her,
and now she feels sick
because I helped her.
Morgan says Jordan needs help,
but Jordan says she
doesn't need help,
but Jordan's mad
because I didn't help her.
Okay, that sounds tricky.
That was my point.
(SIGHS)
You know what?
You'll figure it out.
And even if you don't this time,
that's okay.
You'll learn something.
And you know what?
You're a wonderful teacher.
I've been learning from you
since the first day we met.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
DR. PARK: How's he doing?
Well,
either he wakes
or he lapses into a coma
and slowly fades away.
Beautiful day.
(GASPS)
(VALERIE BROUSSARD'S
"HOLD ON TO ME" PLAYING)
** You've been
walking alone for so long
(BILLY MOANS)
(GROGGILY) You call
Addy about your car?
(CHUCKLES) Not yet.
Been a little busy.
(SIGHS)
Helpers aren't so
good at asking for help.
Kinda glad I did, though.
** This time,
I know you'll be all right
** 'Cause I'm
standing at your side
** Whoa
** 'Cause when you feel
like you've been falling
Congratulations.
You helped save a life today.
Despite the bickering.
Opposing points
of view are great,
as long as you actually
listen to the other point of view.
You're carrying baggage
that is affecting your decisions.
And you saw that because
you're good at reading people.
Other people.
Figure out what you're carrying.
** There is a light at
the end of this long ride
** Whoa
** This time,
I know you'll be all right
** 'Cause I'm
standing at your side
** Whoa
** 'Cause when you feel
like you've been falling
** Hold on to me
** And when the river
sweeps you right off your feet
** Hold on to me
** Oh
It's a list of all the things
you did right on this case.
You can hack it.
It's a list of all the things
you did wrong on this case.
I'm covering your ass.
** Hold on to me
** Hold on to me, now
** Take you to higher ground
** Hold on to me **
HARRY (ON TV): But don't be
late if you don't want no bloody nose.
BILLIE: Would you do me a favor,
Harry? (KNOCK ON DOOR)
HARRY: What?
BILLIE: Drop dead.
(TV SHUTS OFF)
Great to see you've started
your own clothing line,
the official gear of
those who've given up.
By "en suite,"
I meant there's a trash can in your closet.
Hey. Want a ride?
Murphy told you.
You never knew
your Great-aunt Winn.
She moved in with
us when I was eight.
Your grandparents
weren't getting along,
lot of fighting.
But whenever it got really bad,
Auntie Winn would take your
mom and me into the kitchen,
make cupcakes,
something out of papier-mache,
or teach us a card game.
I've always wanted to be
that kind of person for you.
You have been.
But now I need to know
that you think I can do this.
Accepting your help...
(SIGHS)
makes me feel like garbage.
Livy, I'm sorry. I...
I know. I...
I love you, too.
But I have to make this work.
Feels like home.
Again.
It feels like home again
to me, too.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe things are the same.
No.
You were right.
It's not the same.
It's better.
(CLOSING THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org