OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
'And it's Divorce Referendum in the
lead, followed by Glory Be To God.
'Glory Be To God creeps
ahead of Divorce Referendum.'
Come on, Divorce Referendum! Come on!
'Divorce Referendum
is way in front.
'Divorce Referendum is
speeding towards victory.'
- Yes, yes!
- 'Oh, no!'
'Disaster for Divorce Referendum
'as he turns
in the opposite direction
'and simply runs off the course.'
Oh, flip!
You flipping, flipping flipper!
Oh, it's the knacker's yard
for you, pal!
(Door bangs )
(Man on radio ) 'So what role
do you see the Church assuming?'
Hello, Ted.
What are you listening to?
Oh, it's just a programme about
the Church and God and so on.
Oh, right. Right.
Where's Father Jack, Dougal?
- Where's Father Jack?
- Yes.
Father Jack, where is he?
He's in his... Oh.
- Erm...
- You've lost him again, right?
I have, Ted, yeah.
You took him out for a walk
and you lost him...again.
That must've been
what happened all right.
So what have you got to say
for yourself?
Well, like I said the last time,
it won't happen again.
Dougal, are you not going
to go and look for him?
Ted, he'll come back.
What's the worst that can happen?
He could have an accident
and be killed.
Oh.
Er, wait a second, Ted.
Is that not Jack there?
(Snoring)
Ah, Dougal. You didn't even
get him out the door, did you?
I thought the wheelchair felt
a bit lighter today all right.
Come on, help me get him up.
(Groaning)
(Jack muttering)
- Dougal, take off his gloves.
- Right so, Ted.
- Ted.
- Hmm?
Ted, they're not gloves.
God, they're very hairy hands
altogether, aren't they?
- What's wrong?
- I don't know.
Do you remember the time
his head went septic?
Yes. I mean, I didn't think
a whole head could go septic.
I mean, a whole head, you know?
But that's Jack for you.
I'd better look in the book.
Right.
Hold his hand up there, Dougal.
Well, he got up to stage four
after drinking that brake fluid.
I think this could be a stage six.
- Hello to the lot of yous.
- Hello, Mrs Doyle.
Ah, would you look at him there
with his hairy hands?
Yes, and we're going
to have to call Dr Sinnot.
He's good. I had to go myself
a couple of weeks ago.
Really? I didn't know you were ill.
What was the trouble?
A bit of a woman's problem.
I was having a bit of trouble...
I'd better ring him
before it's too late!
(Phone buzzes )
- So it's the hairy hands.
- Yes.
- A stage six?
- It looks like it, yeah.
I'll get ready upstairs.
Ted, why is Jack
so scared of doctors?
They remind him of illness
and his own mortality.
He hated visiting the sick.
Oh, God, he hates the sick.
And the poor as well.
- The poor really got on his nerves.
- And the needy.
(Sighing) Them as well.
What was it he used to say?
He had a term for them.
- A shower of bastards.
- That was it.
When we bring the doctor in,
just behave normal.
Just pretend he's a normal visitor.
We don't want Jack
to suspect anything.
Doctor? Ready?
All right, in you go. Remember...
completely normal.
So it's off to St Clabbert's
again, Doctor?
Yes.
It's more for your sake than for his.
That hair thing
can be very contagious.
- How long will they have him?
- Hard to say.
Could be for a while.
Actually, you should be prepared.
It might be better for
his own sake if he doesn't come back.
Great! I mean, oh, no.
We'll just have
to grin and bear it, I suppose.
I'll try and break it to him gently.
Thanks, Doctor.
Yes! Wahey!
Father Jack?
Do you remember that great time
you had at St Clabbert's?
Remember the fun you had with
those nuns fussing about you?
Dr Sinnot thinks another spell
there would do a world of good.
Ok, it might mean giving up
the odd glass of sherry or two,
but that's all for your own good.
You'll have a fantastic time,
it'll be one big laugh with
all those nuns fussing all the...
Father? Father?
Where's he gone?
(Motor chugging)
God, Ted, how did the sergeant
catch Father Jack at all?
Well, Dougal...
He's an elderly priest driving
a Flymo around a small island.
How hard could it be?
Anyway, he's up there
in St Clabbert's now.
It's weird the way
you get used to something.
Seems like only yesterday he was
here drinking his head off.
Dougal, it was yesterday.
Yeah, but that's why I said
it SEEMED like yesterday.
Right, because it WAS yesterday.
Yeah. What time are Father Rory
and Father k en coming on Wednesday?
About six.
Six o'clock?
- Yes.
- Right. Good, good.
Actually, it's just as well
Jack's not here.
He can get very irritable
around strangers.
Jack was very bad around strangers.
And people he knew.
Yes, very bad around strangers
and people he knew.
- Anyway, night, Dougal.
- Night, Ted.
(Ted) Aw, damn!
(Whistling)
No, Dougal, it's not morning.
I forgot to wind the clock.
Oh, right. Sorry about that, Ted.
Hello there, Father...
Father... Who are you?
Who are you?
Father Ted Crilly.
Very pleased to meet you.
Oh. What's this?
Oh, I see. It's from the Bishop.
You're taking Father Jack's place.
This is a surprise.
Has Mrs Doyle shown you around?
Well, anyway,
welcome to Craggy Island.
The meals are at 11,
one, half-two, three,
five, seven and nine.
And if you ever want a snack,
you can ask Mrs Doyle.
No, er... No, actually,
that's actually mine.
Well, you go ahead there
and have it anyway.
Dougal, this is Father Fintan Stack.
He'll be staying with us now.
Oh, right, yeah.
This is the brains of the operation.
Ah, no, that'd be Ted.
I wanna listen to some music.
Oh, go ahead, there.
I wasn't asking for permission.
( # Jungle music)
( # Muffled thumping music)
So, erm... What do you think
of Father Stack?
Well, erm...
It says in his note that they never
found a suitable parish for him.
- He's not a very nice man, is he?
- I've never met anyone like him.
Who would he be like?
Hitler or one of those mad fellows?
Oh, worse than Hitler.
You wouldn't find Hitler playing
jungle music at three in the morning.
God, he almost makes Jack
seem normal.
You know, he nearly does.
(Howling)
Right, carry on.
I was going to say
you'd almost miss Father Jack.
He had his funny little ways.
But whenever he'd hit you,
he'd never do it out of spite.
He'd only do it because...
he thought it was funny or whatever.
I suppose when you think about it
now, it was funny.
Remember that time he gave you
a big kick up the b-o-t-t-y?
And do you remember
when you were bending over him,
and he held your nose so tight
that you had to open your mouth
and then he dropped
a big spider in it?
No, that wasn't funny, Dougal.
It was funny when
he kicked you up the arse.
It wasn't funny when he put
the spider in my mouth.
- It was, Ted.
- No, it wasn't, Dougal!
- Ah, Ted.
- Dougal!
Anyway, he's gone now.
It's funny how you miss
someone's little ways.
(Sighing)
(Screaming)
( # Muffled jungle continues )
God, I've had enough.
It sounds like someone drilling
holes in a wall or something.
- I'll have a word.
- Careful.
Come on, I think he's out.
- What's up, Ted?
- Ted's gone mad.
- Lead on, MacTed!
- Shh.
- Right, the coast is clear.
- Father Jack's not here?
No, he has the hair thing again.
He's in Jurassic Park.
Oh, right. St Clabbert's.
Father Walton's up there, I hear.
- Sherry all right?
- Lovely.
Did you know Father Coogan
at all, Ted?
Hmm... Oh, yes. Father Tom Coogan.
Wasn't he in Africa?
He was, with Father Shortall
and that load.
Then he was back in Wicklow.
I think Windy Shepherd Henderson
was his priest there.
Windy Shepherd Henderson
that was in Tralee?
No, a different
Windy Shepherd Henderson.
- There's four of them.
- At least.
One of them was with
Father Daley in Chicago.
Wasn't he the first man on the
scene when Malcom X was assassinated?
No, that was Father Burke.
Father Daley had the lump on
his head in the shape of Connaught.
Like Father Caroline - he lost
the use of his ears in an accident.
- He's deaf?
- No, just lost the use of his ears.
He used to be able to wiggle them.
Remember Father O'Reilly?
He's in Clare.
They moved him after he owned up
to that OJ Simpson thing.
Father Bigley from Ardee
did his wedding, I think.
- Father Bigley? Is he not dead?
- No, he just looked dead.
Ted, did you say
Father Larry Duff was coming?
God, I'd better give him a call.
I hope he can make it.
Larry is tremendous fun.
(Mobile phone )
Ahh!
No, he must have it turned off.
God, I wonder where Dougal is?
Come on, Ted.
Shall we watch the sports video?
Oh, yes. Come on, Ted.
Ah, here's the lads.
And away they go!
Ah, look at your man at the back!
I remember this.
(All cheering)
(All) Look at Mrs Doyle!
- She looks great on the telly!
- She's wearing the hat for a bet!
(Ted) I'd say so.
Oh, here's Buckin' Bronco!
Or Hopalong Cassidy.
- Here's the champ.
- Fair play. Fair play to him.
(Cheering)
What are we watching?
We're looking at the sports day.
Lots of young fellows
running around in shorts.
That's the kind of thing
you like looking at.
And I bet you like that, too.
You're probably imagining
what they'd look like without shorts.
You're sitting there, imagining that,
with a big smile on your face.
You dirty fecker.
If you're trying to embarrass us,
you're not succeeding.
Yes, I am.
Well, I have to say,
I think that you're a very rude man.
If you ever say that to me again,
I'll put your head through the wall.
(Crashing)
- Dougal, where did you go to?
- Ted! How are you?
- Dougal, what the...?
- Yes? What, Ted?
- What?
- Have you been drinking?
- I have, Ted.
I been drinking like a mad eejit.
No, no, wait.
No, I haven't.
Dougal, I'm ashamed of you.
Ted, Ted, Ted.
Come here, Teddy, Teddy, Ted.
You're my best friend.
God, I love being a priest.
We're all going to heaven,
lads, wahey!
Perhaps I should explain.
Your friend and I were enjoying
a bottle of whisky I found upstairs.
Well, that is the last straw.
I'm driving. I'm driving home,
I'm perfectly capable.
By the way,
I got the keys of your car
and I drove it into a big wall.
If you don't like it, tough.
I had my fun
and that's all that matters.
- Ted, I can see up your trousers.
- Right. That's it.
I thought giving alcohol
to Dougal was the last straw,
but it was the second last straw,
because this is definitely the last
bit of straw in...the thing.
There is no more straw left!
- Ted, it's a little late.
- Yes, I think we should go.
- No, you don't have to go.
- I think we should.
Woooo!
Bye, girls!
Pair of wankers.
Oh! Come on, Dougal, we've had enough
of Father Stack for one evening.
To the pub, Ted!
( # Jungle music)
- Hey, Ted, what's going on?
- We're going to kidnap Jack.
kidnapping, wow!
What will we get for him?
- Shut up, Dougal. You ready?
- I'm with you, Ted.
Right so, let's go, then.
(Doorbell)
Hello?
- This is a bit mad, Ted.
- Shh!
Why don't we ask the nuns
to give him back?
Dr Sinnot said
moving him might be dangerous.
Anyway, I got a second opinion.
- Who from?
- Mrs Doyle.
Ted, I'm not sure if this
is a good idea. I mean, kidnapping!
It's not kidnapping, it's bringing
him back to where he belongs.
It's like Lassie Come Home,
with Father Jack as Lassie.
- Who are we, then?
- I don't konw. The other people.
You're Roddy McDowell
and I'm Liz Taylor.
Fine. I just wanted to get that
straight in me head.
- Right, let's go.
- Right.
- Come on, Dougal.
- (Shouting) Right behind you!
Shut up! k eep it quiet.
Look around
and see if there's a light switch.
(All shouting)
(Silence )
- (Nun ) What's all that noise?!
- Quick, Dougal, here.
(Nun ) Calm down, all of you!
Some people
are trying to get some sleep!
Arse! Feck! Oh!
Dougal, that's not Father Jack.
- Hello, Father Walton.
- Feck off!
- Will he not do, Ted?
- No. I don't think so, no.
A stage 12.
I never thought I'd see one.
Ah, Ted, can we not keep him?
No. Come on, let's get Father Jack.
- You got the torch, Dougal?
- Yes.
- Arse!
- Feck!
- Drink!
- Girls!
- Feck!
- Drink!
- Arse!
- Girls!
(Posh voice )
I really shouldn't be here.
- Drink!
Drink! Feck! Arse! Girls!
(Jack) Drink! Drink!
Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink!
- All right, Father, all right.
- Drink! Drink!
Drink!
Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink!
- Drink! Drink!
- Try upstairs, Father.
(Jack whimpering)
- Jumping on my picture again?
- You got a problem with that?
- None. Enjoy yourself.
- What was all that noise?
That's Father Jack,
the fellow you replaced.
Tell him to get lost. I'm here now.
You might like the pleasure
of telling him yourself.
And what happened to his whisky.
(Shattering glass, screaming)
He'll fill you in.
I'm supposed to be scared?
Drink!
- Listen to that, Dougal.
- I don't hear anything.
That's what I mean.
The sound of silence.
No, I still don't hear anything.
I'm sorry I didn't disinfect
Jack's chair like you told me.
It's my fault
that lad got the hair thing.
Don't worry. I'm sure he's fine
up in Jurassic Park.
Best place for him.
k eep him out of trouble.
Anyway, how are we getting on
in there, Father?
It's a great invention, isn't it?
And no more St Clabbert's.
(Muffled) Drink! Drink! Drink!
Anyway, time for bed.
Come on, Dougal.
(Muffled) Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink!
Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink!
Drink!
(Man on loudhailer)
'Fathers, please. Calm down.
'Someone step in there, please.
That really is not on.
'You're ruining it.
'Sister, if you could just
step in there.'
Break it up, break it up, Fathers.
Break it up.
Put that down.
(Men ) Drink! Arse! Drink!
Feck! Girls! Drink! Arse!
(Nun ) Good night, Fathers!
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN