Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I'm pregnant.
Good.
That's real good.
There it goes.
Whoo! Whoo!
Yes. Timing's still off 'bout two degrees.
Looked fine to me. What you think?
I think we won.
That's fine right there. Now, come on.
Come on, now. Come on.
Now that's a fast car you fellas got.
And it's mighty fine of you
to let us boys race with y'all.
Whoo!
Get your hands out there, come on.
Come on, Garnet, come on.
Get ready to dance with old Virgil.
Come on.
Damn, Richard. Slow down.
- All right now.
- Where you going?
What you think? Do you like it?
Like what?
This spot. Right here.
This field?
Yeah.
This field not a half a mile from my house
I've been knowing all my life?
Yeah, yeah.
Yes. I like it.
I'm gonna put the kitchen back.
Right back here.
Richard, stop this!
I don't know what you're saying.
I bought it.
This whole acre.
I'm gonna build you a house.
Right here.
Our house.
Mildred?
Yes?
Would you marry me?
Garnet, come.
He said he'd bought the whole acre for me.
And then he asked me to marry him.
- No he didn't!
- Yes.
- Right out in the field?
- Uh-huh.
Oh, Lord, that man might be crazy.
Well, when you gonna do it?
He didn't say.
Soon, though.
Before the baby comes.
He gonna take my sister from me?
No.
We'll be right down the road.
Everything looks fine.
- Thank you, Miss Lola. We'll see you soon.
- We'll be here.
Hey, now.
- Hey, Momma.
- They're out back.
- How we doing?
- Hmm.
Get that board and get up under there.
See if you can get that collector loose.
So I'm gonna take Mildred
up to D.C. to get married.
So, you sure about that?
Yeah.
And you need a witness?
No.
I'm gonna ask her dad
to come up there with us.
Rich is gonna take Mildred
up to D.C. to get married.
String Bean?
Don't make no damn sense.
Now, you'd be fine living in the house.
No wife, just fine.
You don't need no wife.
Well, now, she gonna be your girl.
Why people wanna get married?
Don't make no sense, man.
You think they'll see us today?
Yeah. I called up there.
Seem like a long drive to me.
Thanks for coming, Jake.
Daddy, what's the city like?
It's fine.
Marriage is an institution
of the highest importance.
And it's made honorable
by faithful couples
who are committed to each other for life.
Do you have the ring?
By the power vested in me
by the District of Columbia,
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
I may not forgive him.
Come on, now.
You lucky if I forgive you.
No reason to go all the way up there
for this and not take us.
We took Daddy.
Like that means a thing.
Richard said there would be less
red tape in Washington. That's all.
You can stop looking at it,
String Bean, you know it's purdy.
I'm turning in.
What you think 'bout
a bedroom in the back?
I'll like it however you make it.
I'll be in there soon.
Mmm-hmm.
I thought something like this.
Hey, Momma.
Sheriff's Deputy came by looking for you.
What did he want?
Wanted to find you.
Hmm.
Did you tell him where I was?
I didn't have nothing to tell him.
Like me raising a barn, but, you know...
Thinking the kind of fuel in that car,
that was different.
- That car was great.
- Applesauce good.
But, you know...
What you like, Rich, Ford or Chevy?
Eh, don't make much difference.
But which one faster?
That depend on who built it.
That's what I said.
How much money you win with that car?
Boy, why you're asking
him about his money?
He doesn't have to answer me.
How many races you won, Rich?
Oh.
Uh...
A lot.
You need my hand, you need
my hand, too? Count on this one.
I didn't think he was gonna stop.
I wanna know, you know?
Ask that question...
In here!
What you doing in that bed, boy?
- Richard?
- What're you doing in bed with that woman?
I'm his wife.
That's no good here.
Get your pants on, boy.
You get out of that bed.
Get out of that bed!
All right.
Come on.
She goes in there.
It's all right.
- Come on!
- It's okay.
It's okay.
Richard Loving?
Yeah.
You made bail.
Bean?
Richard?
Go on down.
- What about her?
- Just you.
What do you mean? Wait, wait. Wait!
Don't pull me again.
- Come on now.
- That's not right.
Bean.
Richard?
- It ain't right now!
- Come on!
It ain't right!
Sign at the bottom.
What about my wife?
You'll have to talk to the Judge
about that on Monday.
Monday?
That's good.
Okay. Just rest. Just rest.
Richard!
- Richard!
- Yeah?
Bring me that fresh water
and take this one out.
Okay.
Bear down.
- Here, Mom.
- Leave that down.
Good. Good.
Wait. Wait.
What you gonna do?
How did they know to come get us?
Somebody talked.
Hey!
We told you to come back
on Monday and talk to the Judge.
I ain't gonna let her
stay there till Monday.
- It's not right.
- Talk to the Judge.
You're not allowed to bail her out.
- I'll get a lawyer.
- You can.
Hey, boy.
Come on.
Sit down.
You back here trying to bail her out?
You know they aren't gonna
let her out to you?
You best send some of
her people up here to get her,
because they won't let her out to you.
- But, she's pregnant.
- Shut your mouth about that.
I'll throw your ass back in there
for that. You know better.
It's just not...
What's that?
You do know better, don't you?
Nah, maybe you don't.
Your daddy worked for a nigger, didn't he?
Running timber?
I'm sorry for you.
No, I really am.
All you over there in Central Point
don't know up from down.
All mixed up.
Part Cherokee,
Rappahannock,
part niggra, part white.
Blood don't know what it wants to be.
You just got born in
the wrong place, is all.
I see you got to thinking it was fine.
You might think people
around here wouldn't care.
Hell, maybe they wouldn't,
if your dumb country ass
hadn't gone off
and married her, but not me.
You hear me?
That's God's law.
He made a sparrow a sparrow
and a robin a robin.
They're different for a reason.
No.
You go on now.
Get on home.
Send some of her people
up here on Monday to get her.
I see you trying to bail her out
again, I'll arrest you.
I should put you in with her tonight.
Your daddy posted your bail.
It's all right, Bean.
It's all right.
Where's Richard?
He moved his things out.
Said they'd arrest y'all again,
if they catch him here with you.
Now, come on. Come on here.
Come on.
Bean?
Hey. It's okay.
Oh, I got you.
You okay?
They hurt you?
No.
I'm just scared.
They said I couldn't see you.
I know.
What are we gonna do?
I got a lawyer.
They say he's the best in the county.
He gonna get it all straightened out.
- I don't know.
- It's fine.
All we gotta do is just keep
to ourselves for a while.
And this will blow over.
Yeah?
I better go.
Better go.
We'll walk over there in a minute.
But I met with the Judge this morning,
and I worked out a deal
I think is pretty fair.
Judge Bazile is a friend.
But he is not a fan
of your particular situation.
If you all plead guilty,
the Judge is willing
to suspend any prison time.
Hmm.
We'll do it.
Now, in exchange for suspending
the jail time, you and your wife,
unless you decide to
dissolve the marriage,
will be forced to leave the state.
Leave the state?
What does that mean?
It's exactly what it sounds like.
You two are not allowed to be
in the state at the same time,
and certainly, aren't allowed
to be here together.
For how long? How long will that last?
Twenty-five years.
That can't be right.
Look, you got a year
in state penitentiary,
which, I remind you, could have been
up to five years at the maximum,
you got a year in prison on one hand,
and leaving the state on the other.
That's an easy choice.
Try not to talk unless he directly
asks you a question, which he won't.
Just like we talked about,
he'll ask what you plead,
you say guilty, and this will be
over quick enough.
"...the said Richard Perry Loving,
"being a white person,
and the said Mildred Dolores Jeter,
"being a colored person,
did unlawfully and feloniously,
"go out of the state of Virginia,
for the purpose of being married
"in the District of Columbia,
on June 2nd, 1958,
"and afterwards returned to,
"and resided in the County of Caroline,
"State of Virginia,
cohabitating as man and wife,
"against the peace and dignity
of the Commonwealth."
How do you plead?
Guilty.
The court does accept the plea of guilty,
and fixed the punishment
of both accused at one year in jail.
The court does suspend said sentence
for the period of 25 years,
upon the provision that both the accused
leave Caroline County
and the State of Virginia at once.
And do not return together
at the same time
to said county and state
for a period of 25 years.
Do either of you have anything to say?
No, sir.
You are released from custody.
Settle your court costs with clerk.
Thank you, Your Honor.
It's 36 dollars
and 29 cents apiece.
That's a number in Washington
for Nancy's brother Alex.
His wife Laura's there most days.
If you need to get us, just call.
Okay.
Daddy?
You okay?
You knew what you
was doing taking her up there!
You had no right for that!
Bean?
How you all doing?
We're fine.
Thank you for taking us.
We've got plenty of room.
- You remember Richard?
- Yes.
Thank you.
No. Glad to have you.
Come on in. Let me show you the house.
Yeah, they live, like, what,
two blocks over there, right?
I know them.
Okay.
I'll be back by dinner.
If the vehicle goes aloft
at too step an angle,
its velocity is cut by 800 feet a second.
Working more directly
against gravity than planned.
Reaching over 23,000 miles an hour,
it carries to nearly 80,000 miles.
Thirty times as far as ever before...
Another moon shot is...
What can I do?
Nothing.
Bean.
It's just...
I always thought your mother
would be the woman to deliver the baby.
Damn it.
Okay.
Hey, Momma.
Put some wood in the stove.
Thank you for doing this.
All right.
All right, String Bean, it's on you now.
- Yes, it is.
- Drink this.
Rich!
Her water broke.
Okay. Take a breath. Take a breath.
Breathe.
Okay. Bear down.
Bear down hard.
Thank you, Momma.
You never should have married that girl.
Well, I thought you liked her.
I like a lot of people.
That doesn't mean you should have
gone and done what you did.
You knew better.
Sidney.
Hi, Sidney.
Call the lawyer.
Tell that woman to come out here.
She ain't here.
She left.
Boy, I will split your
head into white meat,
and go arrest every soul in that house.
I won't ask you again.
No.
You are in luck.
The Judge is in today.
You'll go straight there.
For violation of your parole,
you are ordered to post a $200 bond,
and appear before this court...
In the next...
Yes, Frank?
We ask for leniency.
I incorrectly told the Lovings
it was fine for them to return home
for the birth of their child.
It... It was my mistake.
Your Honor, I think...
Fine.
Thank you.
Don't come back here again.
You do and you go to prison.
This doesn't happen a second time.
Sidney, Donald, come on down.
Hey!
Okay.
Come on in.
You go.
Hi, pretty girl.
Your cousin, Gerald and Davis, are fine,
and Sue and Terry send their love.
They just had a little girl, too.
- Really?
- Their second.
Hmm.
Sidney, don't jump in the house.
They're big.
Yes.
I hate it for them.
It's like they're caged.
Not even any grass for them to run in.
And Daddy?
He's fine. Stays up in that
chair more than in the field.
I told Momma if he don't start
getting some work done,
Mr. Banks liable to find
someone else for it.
Clay said he'd have to stay
with me until after the party.
- Good. How are you doing?
- Where is that piece?
How was your sister?
- I need one piece.
- She's fine.
- I almost have it.
- Yeah? You wanna show me?
The long awaited march
for jobs and freedom
on Washington D.C., has started
and it's about half of the
100, 000 estimated crowd
headed off down Constitution Avenue
toward the Lincoln Memorial
which is where we're seated now.
It is here that the climax of the march...
You boys stop that wrestling.
Come and help Miss Laura
with her groceries.
...coming in around the plaza
surrounding Lincoln Memorial.
They say over 100,000 people are there.
...is standing by along the parade
route at 17th and Constitution.
Can you imagine?
Might as well be half way
around the world.
What?
Nothing.
You know what you need to do?
What?
You need to write Bobby Kennedy.
I'm serious.
I mean, that's what they up there for.
All this talk of civil rights.
You need to get you some civil rights.
...engaged in demonstrations before.
In the background, you can hear
some of the young people shouting.
"Freedom, freedom now."
Mmm.
- They in bed?
- Mmm-hmm.
I'm sorry I missed them.
They ask for me?
Peggy did,
but she went down fine.
Will you get Saturday off?
I hope so.
Sidney, get up
and strip those sheets for me.
My turn, my turn, my turn! My turn.
Don, make sure your sister gets a turn.
My turn, my turn, my turn.
Byrd residence.
Hello, I'm calling to speak
to Mildred Loving.
This is she.
Hello, Mrs. Loving,
my name is Bernard Cohen,
I'm the lawyer that was referred
to you by the ACLU.
Are you familiar?
I'm sorry. No.
You wrote a letter to Attorney
General Kennedy, is that right?
Yes.
He was not able to help you
with your particular case,
and sent your letter
to the American Civil Liberties Union.
The ACLU contacted me,
I'm a lawyer in Virginia,
and we would like to
help you with your case.
I see.
- Momma! Momma!
- Don, baby, hush.
Would it be possible for you
and your husband to meet with me?
I would have to check with my husband.
Okay. I'm based in Alexandria,
but I have an office in D.C.
If that is a concern.
Well, as I said in my letter,
we really can't afford a lawyer.
No, ma'am.
The ACLU will take care of any fees.
Mrs. Loving? Are you there?
- Yes, we'll see you.
- Wonderful.
I'll have my secretary
call you back to set up a time.
Nice speaking with you, Mrs. Loving.
Come here, baby.
I got a call from a lawyer today.
- A lawyer?
- Mmm-hmm.
From the American Civil Liberties Union.
Robert Kennedy told him to call us.
Go help your sister brush her teeth.
They wanna help with our case.
Well, we can't afford a lawyer.
He said they wouldn't charge us.
I'm gonna go see him on Thursday.
His name is Cohen.
Hello.
I'm Bernard Cohen. I'm in from Richmond.
I talked to Jim about using
his office for a few hours.
Yes, Mr. Cohen, do you know it?
- Down the hall?
- Yes.
My clients are Mr. and Mrs. Loving.
Could you send them down when they arrive?
Certainly.
Come in.
- Mrs. Loving.
- Hello.
Please, have a seat.
Bernard Cohen. It's a pleasure.
Thank you for coming in today.
So, as we discussed on the phone,
the ACLU would like to take on your case.
I was actually a charter member
of the ACLU in Virginia,
which is why they assigned me to you.
The bottom line is,
we wanna get you all some relief.
That's very generous. Thank you.
Now, the first step is to appeal
the sentence in Caroline County.
That will be our fastest
route to Federal Court.
- The problem is...
- Federal Court?
Yes, the goal is to try to get
the Federal Court to hear the case...
Excuse me, I don't understand...
Federal Court.
I see it as the best route...
Can't you just go and
speak to Judge Bazile?
I mean, we ain't hurting anybody.
- I don't think that...
- Well, just talk to him.
Just talk to him.
Just tell him if he lets
us back in the state,
we won't bother anybody.
Look, I do not think that this case
will be resolved in Judge Bazile's court,
or probably any other court
in the state of Virginia.
I believe this is a court battle that could
go all the way to the Supreme Court.
We're listening.
Our problem is that in order
to appeal the judgment of conviction,
we would have needed to
do so within 60 days.
Now, given that it's been five
years since that conviction,
we have to find a way
to get it back into the courts.
- Are you following?
- Mmm-hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
Now, I've given this some thought,
and I have a somewhat unorthodox
idea on how to do this.
My suggestion would be for the two
of you to return to Caroline County,
get re-arrested, and then we will
have an avenue for our appeal.
You want us to get arrested again?
Yes. It's an idea.
I, of course, will be
there to bail you out.
We aren't gonna do that.
Right...
I can see how that was a mistake.
I understand.
Look, I need to do some more
thinking on this first issue, but,
bottom line is we are gonna
get you all some help.
We appreciate you.
We really do.
Yeah.
If it gets us home, we'll take their help.
Well, you get what you pay for.
Get off the street!
Lee, give him a hand!
You gotta pull that concrete. Yeah.
Pull more.
- Whoo-hoo!
- I got it!
Hey!
Look out!
Donald!
Momma!
- Mildred!
- Up here!
What's going on?
Donald got hit by a car today.
What?
He's fine.
Just scraped and bruised is all.
Hey.
You okay?
I wanna move 'em back to the country.
I don't care what they do to us.
I won't raise my family here.
All right. Y'all get loaded up now.
Come on.
Thank you, Al.
Thank you, Don.
Thank you, Miss Laura.
Hmm.
You just go on.
I'll see you tonight.
- You all be good.
- Okay, Daddy.
Hey.
Daddy!
My cousin has a house he might rent out.
But I thought Jim's brother
said it was fine here.
I don't trust them. Too many people.
Where is it?
King and Queen County.
Just a farmhouse up there.
I figure it gets you out the county,
but keeps you close.
You'll be on your own out there.
It don't have no phone or nothing,
but no one's gonna find you
unless they know to look.
I can get word to you when you need it.
How much you think he'd want for it?
Ah, he'll be fair.
Hey, look.
Peggy!
Hey.
I'll try and get home before dark.
Mmm-hmm.
We'll be fine.
"We haven't heard anything from you
for so long we had given up hope."
Martha, call Chet Antieau's office at
Georgetown Law and try to set a meeting.
Yes, Mr. Cohen.
Come in.
I'd never seen anything like it, you know.
Excuse me.
No matter how many times I get down south,
there's always something that surprises me.
Oh, yes. Please bring him back.
This is good timing.
I want you to meet
a former student of mine.
He called about a case
you may find interesting.
Yeah, sure. What's it about?
Well, we only spoke briefly
on the phone, but, in essence...
Ah...
Hello, Professor, thanks for seeing me.
My pleasure.
You've come at a good time, Bernie.
This is Phil Hirschkop.
He's a brilliant civil rights lawyer.
Nice to meet you.
So...
What's the problem?
Well, I'm a bit stumped.
The ACLU referred me to this case
concerning an interracial couple
that was married in D.C.
They were arrested for
living together in Virginia,
and the judge suspended their sentence
under order that they
leave the state for 25 years.
I filed a motion to vacate the
judgment with Judge Bazile,
the original trial judge
in Caroline County,
but he's stonewalling me.
Of course, the ACLU sees this,
and I agree, as a potential contender
to repeal the anti-miscegenation
laws nationwide.
I just need to get the
ball rolling, as it were.
It's a very delicate
situation because by appealing,
you open up the possibility of
sending them both to prison.
I think regardless, file the 1983
motion explaining your complaint.
It'll force Bazile's hand and get you
in front of a federal three-judge panel.
All right.
Look, I got to catch a plane
to New York tonight,
but I'll work up a draft
and I'll find you on Monday?
Great. That's just great. Thank you.
Yeah. And, Bernie,
if you don't mind me asking,
how much experience do you have
with constitutional law?
Some.
Very little.
You realize this case could alter
the constitution of the United States?
I do.
I'll call you on Monday.
One, two, three!
I'm a good dog!
I can never get mine to rise.
It's not you. It's the humidity.
Just thick.
Come look, Meme. Come look.
- Peggy.
- She's fine.
What you want from your Meme?
Lilly won't share her tea.
She must be upset.
Well, she wants to sit with us out here.
Momma, get Peggy inside!
Bean!
Hey. What is it?
Well, I got a message for you.
What?
Well, that lawyer called.
Said he wanna meet with y'all.
Sidney! Donald!
Raymond, why you
driving so fast like that?
What you mean? I always drive like that.
- What?
- Richard.
- What is it?
- It's okay.
"Almighty God created
the races white, black,
"yellow, Malay, and red, and he
placed them on separate continents.
"And but for the interference
with his arrangement
"there would be no cause
for such marriages.
"The fact that he separated the races
"shows that he did not intend
for the races to mix."
I know it sounds strange,
but this is really wonderful.
By issuing this ruling, Judge Bazile
has really given us a road map
right to the Supreme Court.
I'm sorry, I'm confused.
He ruled against us again.
That's right, but now we're allowed
to appeal that ruling to the state.
From there, if the state rules against you,
we'll have a chance at the Supreme Court.
That sounds wonderful.
I have one little piece of housekeeping.
LIFE magazine contacted us about
sending a photographer out to you all.
Keeping the possibility of
the Supreme Court in mind,
I think it's a fair idea that we
raise the profile of your case,
but I, of course, want to make sure
that you are all comfortable with that.
It'll be fine.
Hello!
Grey Villet, LIFE magazine. Pleasure.
What you got there, a small block?
Yeah. Yeah.
What's the trouble?
Carburetors.
Oh.
Then you're a better mechanic than me.
If you rejet them,
it goes faster, though, right?
I'm sure you already know that.
Is your wife inside?
Uh-huh.
Oh. Hello.
Grey Villet. LIFE magazine.
May I?
Of course. Come in.
Oh. Something smells good in there.
So, I can't go back without
a photo. No photo, no job.
And this is LIFE magazine and
the pigeon guy isn't around.
- Pigeon guy?
That's right.
Looking up at this office
building and it hits me.
Right. I go 55 stories up
and I talk some office girls
into letting me look out the window.
Before they could do anything,
I throw open the window,
sit on the ledge and dangle my feet out.
They start screaming,
but I got this great shot
of my feet flying over
42nd and 5th Avenue.
Yeah. So what happened?
Security threw me out head first.
But, LIFE magazine hired me the next day.
That's a story, all right.
Yeah, that's a story, all right.
You go to the Virginia
State Court next, right?
Yes.
You nervous?
I suppose.
Hmm.
The lawyers told us not to expect much.
You think you'll lose?
Well, yes.
But I think it's all right.
We may lose the small battles,
but win the big war.
- ...coleslaw.
- Yeah.
And here's the surprise.
Some of my new homemade pickles.
That certainly is a wonderful surprise.
Look at that, Barney, Aunt Bee's brought
us some of her homemade pickles.
I see. Sure is wonderful.
You really shouldn't have, Aunt Bee.
That's right, Aunt Bee.
You go to way yonder too
much trouble to please us.
It's no trouble at all.
There's plenty. I made eight quarts.
Eight quarts?
Aunt Bee made eight quarts. Eight quarts.
You can have some every day.
Well, I had an awful big breakfast.
I just stuffed myself something fierce.
Have some pickles.
Here you are.
And here you are.
Mr. Loving. Mr. Loving.
They just wanna ask you a few questions.
Uh... All right.
Mrs. Loving, you rolling?
Mrs. Loving, the Virginia Supreme Court
just ruled against you.
How do you feel about
what happened here today?
Well, I feel hopeful.
I'm hopeful.
And where will you go now?
Well, I guess we'll go back to Washington.
You'll go back to Washington?
Mr. Loving, do you have anything to say
about what went on in the court today?
No. I don't have anything to say.
Okay. Thank you, folks, very much.
Did you get that?
- I think so.
- Okay, cut, Tommy.
Mr. and Mrs. Loving?
We wanted you to know that, with all
this travel back and forth from Virginia,
you have my number
and if anybody arrests you,
you have them get in touch with us.
We're not gonna let you spend
one minute longer in jail
than it takes us to get down
there to get you out, okay?
Okay.
Good luck to you.
You did a good job today.
Well, I sure appreciate
what y'all are doing.
Okay.
Well, we'll see you soon.
Bye.
Thank you, gentlemen.
You know they aren't
going back to Washington.
And there's no guarantee we can
get them out if they get arrested again.
Mmm-hmm.
Sidney!
I want you to go next
door to the neighbor.
You gonna ask him to use the telephone
and you gonna call Raymond
and ask him to bring his gun, okay?
Go. Go on now.
Run through the woods. Go on.
Everything okay?
It's fine.
Richard?
Go on inside.
That truck may have
just been going fishing.
Could be.
You ever hear from anyone
at your work about it?
Not to my face.
Well, I'll tell you this, Rich,
nobody gonna tell you what you can't do.
You're all set.
Thank you.
Who we gonna call, Momma?
I don't want you calling anybody.
How did that go?
Doctor said she'll be fine.
Just put her on aspirin.
Who was that?
Telephone man.
Richard had him install a phone.
Momma, you feel okay?
Yes.
- You got some tea I can drink?
- Mmm-hmm.
All right.
Testing, testing. Testing.
What do you think you would do if you...
If you lose the case?
Well...
If we lose, then we would have
to go back to Washington.
And how does that make you feel
having to go back to Washington?
Mildred?
Come here.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
I don't want those people here.
I'm done with all these cameras!
Well, I think it's important.
These people want to help us, Richard.
Well, actually, although I'm sure
the publicity isn't very pleasant,
if it works out for you, it will work out
for a lot of other people, too.
Yes.
I hope so.
It's the principle.
It's the law. I don't think it's right.
And if... If we do win,
we will be helping a lot of people.
Mmm-hmm.
And I knew... I know we have some enemies,
but we have some friends, too.
So it really don't make a difference
about my enemies.
Push in hard on that one.
You go straight down the way, okay?
I got it. I got it. Don't worry about it.
- Hey. Good ride.
- All right.
Make sure you get it
into second as quick as you can.
- You got it.
- All right.
Car looks good.
Yeah, it's running all right.
You see him driving today.
It was like he was sitting
in the back seat.
Oh, man. I miss you, Rich.
Hell, I can say it.
Hey, Percy, don't you miss Rich?
Yeah.
I miss you too, Virgil.
Man. So, what's all this you got going?
- All what?
- What you got.
You just went made it hard now.
No, no. You think I'm crazy,
but you know what hard is now, don't you?
Yeah.
Richard, you are white.
Now, you may think you're like
a black man, but you're white.
You hang around all these black folks,
but when you go to work,
you're still white.
But not now.
Now you know what it feels
like now, don't you?
You're black now, ain't you?
- You're a damn fool.
- All right, come on now.
No, he needs to hear it.
Look, every nigga in here
wish they were you, Rich,
and you ain't got sense enough for it.
You got a fix. I ain't got no fix.
So yours is easy.
All you gotta do is divorce her.
Divorce her?
All you gotta do.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Really.
- I'm gonna divorce her.
- That it.
That's all you gotta do, right?
That's all you gotta do.
Apologize now, Virgil.
Come to bed, Richard.
We've been
talking to lawyers for
near 10 years now.
Let's go to bed.
I can take care of you.
I know that.
I know.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's very good.
Well, I have some really terrific news.
The Supreme Court has agreed
to hear our case.
Now, of course, the state
of Virginia will mount their defense,
but we are feeling very good
about our chances here.
You've got the full weight
of the ACLU behind this.
- It's a miracle.
- Hmm.
What's their defense?
I'm sorry?
Virginia.
How are they gonna defend
what they done to us?
I guess we won't know until the hearing,
but it's likely that they'll use
a defense similar to something
they've used before.
What's that?
It's your kids.
Our kids?
The state of Virginia
will argue that it is unfair
to bring children
of mixed race into the world.
They believe the children are bastards.
Now, as the defendants in this trial,
you are allowed to come
and hear the arguments.
No. We don't need to do that.
It's a tremendous honor to sit with
the Supreme Court. Very few people...
No.
That's fine.
Excuse me.
Mildred?
I wouldn't go without him.
You know, Richard, it's, of course,
up to you not to attend but,
you should know, the Supreme Court
only hears one out of every 400 cases.
It's historic.
Thank you, Mr. Cohen.
Well. Is there anything
you'd like me to say to them?
And by "them" I mean the Supreme
Court justices of the United States?
Yeah.
You can tell the judge...
Tell the judge I love my wife.
You okay to park? Thanks, Martha.
Number 395.
Richard Perry Loving et al, Appellants,
v. Virginia.
Mr. Hirschkop.
Mr. Chief Justice, Associate Justices,
may it please the court?
You have before you today
what we consider the most odious
of the segregation laws
and the slavery laws,
and our view of this law,
and we hope to clearly show,
is that this is a slavery law.
We ask that the Court consider
the full spectrum of these laws
and not just the criminality,
because it's more than criminality
that's at point here.
It's the right to inherit land,
the legitimacy of children,
and many, many rights.
Mr. Cohen.
Mr. Chief Justice,
may it please the court?
What is the danger to the state
of Virginia of interracial marriage?
What is the state of danger
to the people of interracial marriage?
Marriage
is a fundamental right.
Hello?
- Mrs. Loving?
- Yes.
It's Bernard Cohen.
Oh, hello, Mr. Cohen.
I'm calling with great news.
- Just wanted to let you know.
- What's that?
Yes, I'm here.
That's wonderful news.
Yes, I understand.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Cohen.
Mr. Loving? Mr. Loving?
Mr. Loving, how does it feel
to have the Supreme Court...
Have you heard from the Attorney General?
Mrs. Loving, what does
this mean to your family?
Do you plan to return to Virginia?
Have you talked to the Attorney General?
Several Southern states have
already announced this ruling...
Take that to your daddy.
Oh.
- Wanna help me?
- Mmm-hmm.
You wanna brush the wall?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org