Previously on "Deception"...
You've been helping the FBI
solve crimes.
I want you to...
help me commit one.
What are you willing to do
to save your brother?
Anything.
Cameron, you helped to steal
a diamond worth millions.
You're in a lot of trouble.
I made a lot of mistakes.
But I didn't do that.
So you think Mystery Woman
has gone to great lengths
to recreate this exact moment.
My guess is
whatever she's up to,
the answer's in this photo.
Here's the thing about a city.
It's like an audience...
a fragile family of strangers
held together by a simple,
unspoken agreement.
We all have a role to play,
from the paramedics who save us
to the bartender
who listens to our worries,
to lovers...
Good evening.
Who remind us
what that felt like.
We trust everyone
to play their part.
And when someone breaks
that trust...
Have a good night, Jerry.
Well, that role
falls to someone
who protects and serves.
They help make things right.
And I look through them streets
and find you.
Tommy, Tommy, Tommy.
Where you been at, huh?
Been trying to get ahold of you.
So where you been at, man?!
Mission at the park?
Just... Just...
Just let me out, man.
I'll keep quiet, I promise.
That's not what
I'm trying to hear.
I wanna hear, man!
No!
Aah!
Freeze!
Get on the ground!
Ugh!
Officer...
you all right?
That was one hell of a fall.
You hit your head pretty good.
That's not
a suggestion, you know?
Who are you?
I work here?
You been drinking, Officer?
Th-That's not mine.
A man was killed here tonight!
I saw it!
Okay, well,
I had the caution sign out,
so don't sue me.
I saw it.
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
Cameron, you can't be here.
Deakins revoked your access,
remember?
Can you believe that?
They also took away
my observer badge
and gave me this crappy
visitor one instead.
It's temporary.
I have to give this back?
What are you doing here?
I don't know, just thought
I could smooth things over,
get the team re-instated.
What's with these new cases,
by the way?
They're not cases.
They're crackpot reports.
And thanks to you,
Deakins has us clearing them
until your little diamond heist
blows over.
Oh, she's blaming you
for what I did?
That's not fair.
You worked with
an international criminal
behind our backs.
She doesn't trust you.
Now, would you please go, before
I get in any more trouble?
Okay.
Oh, w-what you're saying is
if we clear these cases,
we get you out of the Deakins
doghouse, we can get back to work?
Oh, I'll be out of the doghouse, but there
is no way that you are coming back...
Okay, cool, because look.
Crown Heights, Brooklyn...
yeah.
A cop witnesses a murder
in a bodega.
He passes out, he wakes up,
and the evidence
has all vanished.
That screams deception,
am I right?
Cameron...
go home.
Okay, going home.
Yo, the rat is here!
Yeah, ya punk!
The hell's this?
Welcome back.
You didn't save me any eggs?
Me and Dina had eggs,
but we're a team.
We do things together.
Well,
not things-things.
It's not my fault Cameron
only asked me to help.
He got kidnapped
by you-know-who.
He... Gunter, do you
remember the last time
Cameron did a show
without all three of us?
Maybe he did it to protect you.
I don't know.
What was I supposed to do?
I don't know, say something,
tell us, be cool?
Not likely.
Seen the way he dresses?
Like a break-dancing
lawn jockey.
Working on the big mystery...
why is Cameron's
great-grandfather
in a photo with those rich guys,
and why is the Mystery Woman
obsessed with recreating?
Dina?
Yes?
Those men were ruthless...
into dark deeds
like our Mystery Woman.
Cameron's great-grandfather
was a magician,
not Voldemort.
He was probably
performing for them.
Well, Alistair Black
was not a performer.
He was a builder.
But he didn't just build tricks.
I heard he made hidden passages,
secret chambers
for his mistresses and victims.
Victims?
Like "Special Victims Unit"
victims?
Gunter?
Do you think that Alistair
was making secret things
for those men?
Yes, Dina, I do.
Question is...
what and where?
I'm gonna find out both.
Alone!
Excuse me, Officer.
That's not a crosswalk, pal.
Oh, yeah.
No, sorry.
Just, uh...
you don't know who I am?
No, who are you?
Oh.
Well, uh, name's Cameron.
I'm, uh, FBI...
official observer, technically.
What's that, like
a junior detective or something?
I was wondering
if you wanted to talk to us
about this bodega murder case
that you filed with us.
What's there to talk about?
You guys didn't believe me.
I believe you.
I mean, I don't think that
what you saw is impossible.
And even if it was,
impossible's my middle name.
Yeah.
People like that line.
So, this kid shoots the clerk
right in front of you.
Before you can do anything,
everything goes black.
That right?
Yeah, someone knocks me out.
I come to,
the dead clerk's gone.
There's another clerk there
calling me crazy.
No mess, no body, no nothing.
I was standing here.
The perp was here,
and the clerk was shot
right here.
No one was shot,
Mrs. Laurie.
You ain't gotta...
Thanks.
Take it easy.
That camera got me coming in,
and that camera's busted.
There's no clear view
from the door,
and the place is spotless.
Whoever did this was good.
All right, so,
clerk's standing here
and he got shot, right?
So his blood would spatter...
right here.
You said this happened what,
three days ago?
Yeah.
All these packing dates
are exactly the same,
and fresh.
What kind of
cost-conscious bodega
switches out an entire deli case
at the same time?
And what are the odds
somebody bought 'em all?
I'm starting to get the feeling
someone bought it,
all right.
And they restocked
this entire case
in order to finish cleaning.
"End and clean" in magic
refers to the final move
where you ditch
the evidence of the trick.
What?
I mean, uh, in crime fighting.
It's a new FBI terminology,
which, uh, we use to...
you know,
I'm just gonna demonstrate.
May I? Thanks.
Ace of Spades, eh?
You gotta pay for those now.
You know that, right?
Yeah, sure.
Now, it looks to you
like I just tore that up, right?
But in fact, what I did was I...
replaced it.
Now you're doing card tricks?
Yeah, it's a...
you know, forget it.
The real question is,
what happened
to the deli products
that this stuff replaced?
Maybe they're in the trash.
Stop!
Stop! FBI!
Stop the truck!
Maslin!
I saw the clerk
throw a bag in here.
Don't touch that.
Found it.
Exhibit A...
blood-covered cold cuts.
You were right, Officer Maslin.
There was a murder.
We got a case.
What is that?
American.
It could be cheddar.
Also evidence!
Which is why
I wrote "evidence" on it.
Cameron, how is it we are
up to our necks with crackpots,
and yet you are the most
annoying thing about this job?
I don't know,
guess you're lucky.
So, I happened by the bodega
where this alleged murder
took place.
Looks like this cop, Maslin,
he's not making it up.
You found this cheese digging
through a garbage truck?
Sure, but the blood on it
will match the victim,
I guarantee it.
This is a real case.
You can trust me.
We need more than a gut feeling,
like a body to match this blood
which came from a trash can,
so it could've come
from anywhere.
W...
Plus, this is PD's case,
not the Bureau's.
All right.
Look, you guys
are in trouble because of me.
I just...
just wanted to help.
I'll stop.
Sorry.
But if you get the chance,
this cop, Maslin,
he's a good guy.
I believe him.
All right.
I'll see what we can find out.
Thanks.
What's that?
Alistair Black's ledger
of all the tricks he ever built.
If he made one
for one of the men in the photo,
it should be here.
We should check the plans
for project number 617.
Alistair built it for Houdini...
took 12 years.
And how long have you been here?
20 minutes.
What could've taken
12 years to build?
Trust!
Trust takes
a long time to build.
Okay, okay.
Can you take your messy little
investigation elsewhere, please?
What's the occasion?
I am having a companion
over for dinner.
A date! With who?
The first domesticated man
I've ever dated.
Sounds like Mike.
I promised him
a home-cooked meal.
And I don't have
a working oven in my place...
Because you can't cook, so you
got him takeout from Trubiano's.
A harmless deception, Jordan.
Now, both of you, go.
Please?
That's deceit, but in a fun way.
You should be taking notes.
And I'm headed down to
Alistair's deep storage room...
alone!
617.
6...
Mm.
One...
Seven.
What are you hiding, Alistair?
Let me out of here!
Jordan?
What the hell?
What is this?
Aah!
Hey.
Just wanted to let you know
I've been reassigned,
but you got some actual
special agents on your case now,
so that's good for you.
Come here, come here.
That's my captain.
I told you,
she doesn't believe me.
Check this out.
I've been looking
at mug shots for hours,
cross-references those
with narcotic files,
and I got him.
Who?
The perp from the bodega...
Alex Boyd.
He was busted three months ago
for dealing in Prospect Park.
This makes sense.
He mentioned a park
before he shot the clerk.
Maybe that's his territory.
I... Okay, look, look.
Cameron, I know it's thin,
but it's all we got to go on.
We gotta get down there.
I just told you,
I'm not on the case anymore.
Cameron, we gotta find this guy.
We gotta shake him down,
see who he works for.
Look, Maslin, I can't go.
I can't do this alone.
This is my shot to prove
that I still got it
and I ain't crazy.
All right.
Okay, but there's a right way
to do this and a wrong way.
I need to call my team.
No answer from Officer Maslin.
What do you have?
A body was found
in Rockaway Inlet...
matches the description
of the victim Maslin described.
Kid's name
was Tommy Ramos,
new to the neighborhood
and the job,
which explains why Maslin
had never seen him before.
And his DNA matches
the blood Cameron found.
Cameron?
Cameron found the evidence
that led to the body.
I discouraged him, but...
It's Cameron.
I get it.
He just wanted to redeem himself,
prove he can still help us.
Nothing makes me angrier
than corrupt cops...
even our magician.
Elevate to a full investigation.
I'll alert the PD brass.
And tell Mr. Black I'd like
to speak to him ASAP.
Got a book for ya.
Didn't order a book.
Somebody sent you one.
I'm starting
to sense a theme here.
Lots of rumors about you.
Word is you're a snitch
for the feds.
Well, that's not true.
Rumors are dangerous in here.
I have access
to anything you need.
Shiv, blades, mace.
Why do you want to help me?
I know what it feels like
to be scared.
And 'cause a man's gotta eat.
$40.
$20 now, $20 on delivery.
I'll get you a list.
Oh, give me some of those
nature magazines before you go.
We've been here awhile,
and there's still
no sign of Boyd.
Yeah, you're right.
This guy's not gonna show.
Hey, are you...
are you Cameron Black?
What are you
hanging around here for?
Do you guys need some drugs?
I'm kind of busy
right now, so...
Dude, I-I-I've seen
all your specials, man.
You're, like, the greatest
magician of all time.
Thanks.
Magician?
Are you working on
a new illusion,
like, right now or something?
Cameron Black, the Magician.
I thought I recognized you.
You don't work for the FBI!
No, look...
FBI? Whoa.
I gotta, uh...
Maslin,
I-I work with the FBI.
I mean,
not technically right now.
Hey, Cameron, what's going on?
Hey. Is this the
cop we're helping?
Who's this guy now?
Look, he's part of my team.
Your team?
What, your magic team
or your FBI team?!
Well, both.
This is a big joke to you,
isn't it?
No.
No, Maslin, I'm helping you.
No, you're not.
You're playing me.
I used to be a real detective.
Now look at me.
I gotta go to work.
Damn, you're on fire today.
Dina, Gunter, that guy...
literally everyone hates you.
So, what do we do now?
We go talk to him.
Who's that?
It's the killer.
Jordan? Jordan?
This Alex guy's
a popular drug dealer.
Yeah.
So, Maslin's plan was to wait
till he ran out of drugs
and then follow him
to his supplier.
But given the fact
this guy's a murderer,
that could get us...
killed.
Jordan!
Please tell me you didn't just
buy drugs off him.
Are you crazy?
Of course not.
I stole drugs from him.
I think I saw a narc over there.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, over there, at the light.
What are you talking about?!
Aw, man, I think he left.
I think he left.
Oh, we're good, we're good.
We're good.
All he had on him...
probably $1,000 worth of Molly,
I'm guessing.
Watch out.
He should be leaving
to resupply in three, two...
All right, come on. Let's follow him.
Wait, Jordan.
Feel like it is my duty
to be the adult in the park
and ask the question,
what would an FBI agent do?
He'd call his partner...
call Kay.
Cameron.
Kay, it's me.
I'm with Jordan.
We're in Prospect Park.
It's him?
Put him on speaker.
Just won about
a gram's worth of Molly.
Or is it ecstasy?
I don't know the difference.
They're the same thing.
All right.
Well, it's not as much as you'd
think it would be. Anyway...
Mr. Black,
you're on speakerphone.
Oh. Hi.
Great.
Uh, first of all,
good to hear ya on the phone.
It's been awhile. Hey,
Cameron, what's going on?
I... Okay.
So, Maslin and I found
the bodega killer.
His name's Alex Boyd.
He's a drug dealer
in Prospect Park.
Right now, he's on the move.
He's headed south
towards Parkside.
But don't worry, we are
absolutely not following him.
Yes, you are.
Follow him now.
I... Sorry,
you kind of cracked up there.
It sounded like you said,
"Follow him."
Keep your distance
and do not engage.
Agent Daniels will meet you.
Yeah, she totally hung up on me.
Come on.
This smells amazing.
Are you sure you're not Italian?
Oh, aren't we all,
just a little?
Um, would you like some bread?
Sure.
It's garlic bread, yeah.
Mmm.
My boys would love this.
I mean, they're just stuck
eating my same three recipes,
heavy rotation all the time.
And they would love this place,
especially my little guy, Jamie.
Loves magic.
Maybe you should
bring them by some time.
That'd be nice.
You hear that?
Uh, yeah, it's just
the building settling in,
old plumbing.
This old place makes all sorts
of weird noises at night.
The only person who really
knew how to maintain it
was Jonathan.
Uh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have brought him up.
Oh, it's okay.
It's never easy
when something ends.
Even though life goes on,
I believe a little part
of everyone stays with us.
Makes us who are, going forward.
Mm-hmm.
You sure it's just the plumbing?
Bloody hell.
What you search for,
you will never find.
Give up, or discover
my horrible gift for you.
Oh!
See the truth.
And run.
I ain't got it.
What do you mean,
you ain't got it?
Something happened.
I think I got pick-pocketed.
Yeah, well, you lose the product,
you pay for the product.
You hear me?
I haven't got time for this!
Get me my money.
What's up?
Freeze, FBI!
Aah!
Hey, great entrance!
How long you been up there?
The drug dealer
lawyered up fast,
just like the clerk...
both afraid to talk.
But we need the man in the car.
I'm guessing he's in charge.
You found a body.
We'll take over
and find out who did it.
What is it, Captain?
Why didn't the NYPD investigate?
There's something you should
know about Officer Maslin.
Besides being an alcoholic,
he was once investigated
for racketeering
when he was
a narcotics detective.
Internal couldn't prove it,
but if I were a betting woman,
I'd say Maslin
is involved somehow.
Look, I'm sorry I lied to you.
But the FBI's all over this.
We got Boyd.
I can ID his boss.
We got a ton of drugs.
I don't know
what the etiquette is
of disposing of those, but...
Hey, thanks, Cameron.
I'm sorry I bailed in the park.
I shouldn't have left you there
without backup.
You're a good cop, man.
And you're
a pretty good magician.
I checked you out
on the computer.
Pretty good?
Come on, name two magicians...
Hey, Maslin!...currently
living that are still...
Hey, look who it is! Hey.
So...
giving to the boxing league
this year, Mazzy?
Yeah, sure.
All right, good man.
Who's your friend?
Cameron Black...
Magician Cameron Black.
All right.
Detective Leo Baker...
He's one of the good ones.
Don't let this get around, Leo,
but, uh,
Cam's also with the FBI.
FBI?
Oh, that's very interesting.
All right.
Well, I'll see you around,
Mr. Black.
Take care, pal!
You, too!
Detective Leo Baker, narcotics,
decorated five times.
Arrested both Alex Boyd
and Tommy Ramos in the past,
but released both
with only warnings.
In exchange for letting them go,
they start working for him.
Pushing drugs
seized from Baker's busts
back onto the street.
There's no way
that Baker's working alone.
In my humble opinion.
You think Cameron's right?
I'm not sure.
But I do know we can't trust
anybody in that precinct
till we get in
and see for ourselves.
You and Alvarez run point.
Well-done, Cam.
Did you hear that?
She just called me Cam.
That is my first official "Cam."
I have had some "Camerons"
before, but...
Baker's operation's going down.
We are back!
We are not back, Cameron.
Y-You heard Deakins,
I mean...
At the auction house,
you went behind my back and
you helped the Mystery Woman.
You kept me in the dark,
and you almost...
It was really bad.
Whoa, wait.
Y-You're saying this...
this whole thing
wasn't about Deakins?
You don't trust me?
No.
I don't trust you.
Hey, where you been?
What's...
What's going on?
You don't want to know.
Did you find Alistair's trick?
617, you know, uh,
the mystery of the picture
and all that?
No.
But I found a message direct
from Alistair Black himself.
Direct from Hell.
Hey, dude, you're...
you're actually scaring me.
Whatever
the Mystery Woman wants,
he's protecting it
from beyond the grave!
Okay, uh, Gunter, I...
I had some pills in my jacket.
You didn't... You didn't
take them, did you?
Dude, I found straps
on his workbench...
straps to hold a man down.
Now, if Cameron finds them,
he's gonna try
and figure this all out.
He's gonna get himself killed.
Now, listen.
I forgive you
for keeping your secret,
but you've gotta help me
keep mine.
Look, but this could help us figure
out the Mystery Woman's plan...
why...
why she framed Jonathan.
No, we have to tell Cameron!
It won't lead to anything good.
Listen, you were right.
Alistair wasn't Voldemort.
He was worse, much worse.
The rumors?
They're real.
Okay, what do you mean, real?
Dark deeds, mate!
Dark deeds.
If you're looking for
"Chicken Soup for the Soul,"
it's checked out...
all 92 copies.
Oh, that's a shame.
Could've read it twice
while I was waiting for you.
Not my only client, my boy.
I gotta admit,
couldn't figure out what
you plan on building with this.
Sure you don't wanna go with
the coffee-creamer flamethrower?
It's my specialty.
I design my own tricks.
Thanks.
It's your money.
You pay well, kid.
But someone else paid even more.
Tell whoever
put a price on my head...
It's not gonna be that easy.
Captain Clark,
this precinct is officially
under FBI investigation.
You can't be serious.
What for?
We have reason to believe
some of your officers
are involved
in criminal activities.
Well, that's vague.
You're raiding my precinct,
and you're not telling me why?
With all due respect, Captain,
that's all we can say
at this time.
Let's go.
Clear!
Oh, looks like
we got us a party here.
We need to look into your bags.
By all means.
Pardon the dirty socks.
Guys do fluff and fold,
by any chance?
Maybe after you finish
your little goose chase,
you'd like to, uh,
come down to the gym with us
for a few rounds, Agent.
Nah.
I'm more of an MMA guy.
Thanks.
Nothing on Baker, and the evidence-locker
inventory squares up with the records.
My guess is they skimmed the
drugs before the got logged in.
Well, everything seems clean.
Not completely.
Officer Maslin,
we need a word with you.
We found the drugs in your desk.
They're not mine,
I'm telling you!
What about
the racketeering charges?
I didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't do anything wrong then,
I didn't do anything wrong now!
I'm being set up.
I mean, you see that, don't you?
I see a cop
who is in a lot of trouble,
who has struggled
with addiction.
Hey,
I-I used to be
on the other side
of that glass, you know.
I was a respected detective.
Two different rooms.
It's two different rooms...
it's just two different worlds.
In there, you're trusted.
In here, nobody believes you.
You know
what landed me in this room?
People.
They're always fake to me.
Yeah, I was a drunk.
I was never a criminal.
And I got sober.
But still,
they see what they wanna see.
I was a good cop.
This doesn't feel
like Maslin to me.
I think Baker's setting him up.
Maybe,
but Cameron's ID isn't enough
and Baker's squeaky clean.
Too clean.
The only narcotics in his desk
was a prescription for oxy
he had filled out after
shoulder surgery last month,
and it all checked out.
What is it?
Who boxes
right after shoulder surgery?
The gloves.
What if
they're moving out the drugs
inside the boxing gloves?
Oh, we gotta go back.
Uh, we just conducted
a high-profile raid on them
and got nothing.
We can't go back.
The FBI's not going to
do anything to help Maslin.
If that is the case,
his life is ruined.
Maslin's gonna take the fall
for Baker.
But if we can devise a deception
to get into the precinct,
we can get this guy.
Sorry, man, no dice.
Not again.
Maslin's a good guy.
All right, sure,
he made some mistakes.
But doesn't he deserve
a second chance?
Sounds remarkably like
you're talking about yourself.
He's always
talking about himself.
I'm talking about all of us.
This is our chance
to prove to the FBI
they need the deception group.
Look, I... I know
my judgement's been
a little...
questionable lately.
But Maslin's being framed
just like Johnny was,
and we can do something about it
if we work as a team.
Dude, even if we were on board,
there's someone else
you'd have to convince first.
He's right.
You can't do this without Kay.
Without her, you're on your own.
Freeze, dirtbag.
You're gonna die screaming.
Breaking into
a police detective's car...
not the sharpest knife
in the drawer, are you?
Okay.
You know...
caught your show in Vegas
a few years back.
So we're not taking any chances.
Detective Baker
will be here soon.
He's got some questions for you.
He's gonna want
to take his time.
What the hell were you thinking?
That I'd get away with it?
This is so far beyond!
You're screwed, Cameron,
and I can't get you
out of it this time.
Oh, Kay, you gotta do something.
I'm already persona non grata
with the DA after the warrant.
You're stuck here.
Can you give us a sec?
Seriously?
Oscar-worthy,
can I just say?
I-I genuinely thought I was
gonna spend the night in jail.
You still may.
The night is young, so move.
This plan of yours...
this is genius.
So much better than
the deception I was thinking of.
Mine did have a helicopter.
But if this FBI thing
doesn't work out,
you'll make
one heck of an illusionist.
You're clear this way.
Watch out.
Baker's men are on high alert.
Okay.
Cameron, darling?
Follow my instructions,
and don't you dare
go off-script.
I say
we go semi-gloss.
Semi-gloss a ceiling?
You're dumber than
an Eskimo in Speedos, son!
Fellas, what's this all about?
He's got it.
W-We're here
to paint the east wing.
Nobody told me about
any work order.
Well, well.
I told him,
phone ahead and confirm.
But does he listen?
Yeah, I went to art school,
not secretarial school!
Take it up with Janice
in the office, all right?
All right, all right, all right.
Go ahead, do what you gotta do.
Nicely done, boys.
System's a go.
Now, be careful out there, okay?
The locker room
is on the second floor, Cameron,
56 feet from the stairwell
on the left.
Got it.
Deception's a go.
Not quite as romantic,
but, uh, will you consider this
our second date?
Um, Mike, I...
I really need
to confess something.
The dinner was Trubiano's.
I just...
I really wanted to impress you.
Next time,
don't worry about that.
You impress me every day.
Very sweet, you two.
Now, where the hell
are we going?
I'm sorry.
Um, you're nearly there.
It's the second right.
Okay, Baker's locker
is number 22.
We're in business, guys.
Found the drugs.
Whoa, there's a whole lot.
Okay, Cameron?
You
need to get out of there, now.
Aah!
Somebody sound the alarm!
Some kind of break room.
Talk to me, Dina.
It's like a maze in here.
I... I said left!
Left, and then right!
Where are you now?
I'm somewhere near
the holding cells.
I'm seriously lost, Dina.
Go right!
There's two rights!
Second right.
Dina, I'm sending you
the pictures now.
Congrats.
You picked the exact wrong room
to hide in...
soundproof, no cameras,
no recording devices.
Nobody to see what happens next.
Why don't you hand me
that phone?
All right, so,
guess we're done here.
We're far from done.
Well, you just destroyed
all the evidence.
I mean, what evidence, right?
I didn't see anything,
so you can just let me go.
You're an escaped prisoner
loose in the precinct.
You stole my weapon,
locked us in this room.
There was a struggle.
I shot you
in self-defense.
All right, well,
that's one option.
But Maslin's on to you, man.
He's gonna talk.
Yeah, well,
I'll take care of Maslin.
But you're right.
I should've killed him
that night in the bodega.
Damn loyalty to a brother
in blue got the best of me.
Oh, right, so you just
ruined his life instead.
That's your version
of integrity?
I always felt sorry
for the lush.
And he repays me
by nosing around
where he doesn't belong?
Also known as, doing his job.
Or digging his grave,
just like you.
Any last words?
Bravo.
Come again?
Well, I just gotta
hand it to you.
The trick was impressive.
Convincing Maslin that he never
saw what he saw?
It's not bad.
But a master of deception
like you should know...
sometimes what you see
on the outside...
Isn't really what's happening
on the inside.
We chose this room on purpose...
a place you feel safe
that nobody was watching.
So you think
you turned on the light,
but in fact,
you powered up a projector.
And this is just the image
of an empty room.
And that was the screen
you projected it on.
Detective...
you're under arrest.
And now we're done.
All right,
all right, knock it off.
I just wanna thank you guys
for helping me
bring down Baker and his men,
and for helping me
get my gold shield back...
and helping me get my life back.
To Detective Maslin!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Salud.
Hi.
Sorry we're late.
It's okay.
Come here,
I want you to meet the boys.
Boys?
Hmm?
I want you
to meet my friend Dina.
This is Jamie and Diego.
Hi.
My boys.
So, I think I've officially
run out of ways to apologize.
So I just...
Are we good, you and I?
I mean, or just close to...
I mean, a little good?
I wasn't completely honest
with you, either.
I was mad, but I was also...
Seeing you almost suffocate
in that vault,
it really scared me.
I'm not so good at being scared.
But you're scary all the time.
This was different.
Guys?
I have something I wanna say.
Look.
An illusionist's
only as good as his team...
his whole team.
We're a family,
and I'm sorry that I divided us.
So from now on, no more secrets.
I promise.
What?
What is it?
Mike and I
are officially dating.
I still have $1,000 worth of
illegal drugs hidden on my body.
Fine.
I found a secret death trap
in the archive of illusions.
And your great grandfather
has threatened to kill anybody
who goes looking for whatever
the Mystery Woman's looking for.
Happy?
Sorry, mate.
Johnny?
Cam, someone's been murdered,
and everyone here
thinks I did it.