Previously on "Deception"...
What are you willing to do
to save your brother?
Anything.
Hundreds of jewels
in the Rockefeller Collection
are being auctioned off
tomorrow.
One is key to something
far more important.
Next up for bidding,
the Lynx Diamond.
It all connects. The diamond is
just another piece of the puzzle.
♪ ♪
Deakins: You helped to steal
a diamond worth millions.
I made a lot of mistakes.
But I didn't do that.
♪ ♪
[ Chatter ]
[ Scanner beeping ]
♪ ♪
[ Scanner beeps, hums ]
Whoa, relax, Marcus.
Forgot I had my keys.
♪ ♪
[ Scanner beeping ]
[ Sighs ]
Thank you.
[ Scanner beeps ]
♪ ♪
Running a bit late again today?
Sorry, James.
Traffic.
Congratulations,
you've given the most cliched
and uninspired excuse
of all time.
I said I was sorry.
Want me to apologize
for the excuse, too?
[ Whispers ]
Get to work.
♪ ♪
James, I need access
to the server room.
Can I use your pass code again?
[ Keypad beeps ]
We're still on for lunch, right?
Depends.
Are you gonna make me
apologize again?
I'm sorry.
I just... I can't have it
look like I'm playing favorites.
I'm already over it.
[ Sighs deeply ]
It doesn't seem like you are.
Morning, Teddy.
Mr. Collins.
Actually,
I need something from in here.
[ Chuckles ]
The lab?
Even I don't have access
to that room.
He does.
Anne, what are you doing?
Enter the code right now.
I'm not letting you in there.
James: Anne, wh...
[ Gunshot ]
How 'bout now?
♪ ♪
[ Keypad beeping ]
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
♪ ♪
Jordan: This woman
killed her boss?
Kay: Almost. The bullet
just missed a major artery,
but he's gonna be okay.
Cameron: A splash of skim,
extra shot, and some foam.
Thank you.
Is that...?
Sprinkle of cinnamon? Yeah.
You know me so well.
I'm a good observer.
So, Kay, what did she steal?
It's classified.
We won't tell anyone.
Oh, well, in that case...
Can we guess?
Was it nuclear?
Weapon?
A nuclear weapon?!
I haven't been briefed yet,
so I don't know.
Probably not nuclear, though.
♪ ♪
You're disappointed.
Well, I always wanted
to mess around
with one of those
and get my head under the hood.
So, why bring the
Deception Group in on this one?
The building is one of
the most secure in the world.
Impossible to get a weapon
of any kind in there.
Yet, somehow, Anne Rojas managed
to shoot her supervisor.
Sorry, go back. Did you, uh,
you say, "Impossible?"
You know
you don't own that word.
Well...
He did try to trademark it.
Still pending.
[ Door opens, closes ]
Dina: Good morning!
How is everyone?
Why are you in such a good mood?
[ Door opens, closes ] I'm not.
Just said, "Good morning."
Good morning.
Oh, hey, Dina.
Hello.
Kay: You're up to speed,
Mike?
Yeah, Deakins filled me in
on the case.
Cameron: All right,
feels like we should just
get to this building
and see how "impossible"
the security is to penetrate.
All right, Cam.
You ride with me.
♪ ♪
Guys, why don't you
go work on something nuclear?
I don't think they noticed.
Well, you could've waited
more than five seconds
before following me in.
Well, I thought maybe
if I came in right away,
it would look so suspicious,
it wouldn't look suspicious.
Oh, like,
reverse suspicion psychology.
Exactly. Yeah, no,
it's not a thing.
♪ ♪
Last night
was pretty incredible.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was.
And look, we're not gonna have
to sneak around much longer.
I just want Jonathan
to hear it from me.
I don't want him hearing it
from this lot.
I'm sorry
I brought so much baggage.
It's okay.
We all got baggage.
Why wasn't there a surveillance
video outside the lab?
The entire lab's
a sensitive area.
No cameras, cellphones,
or surveillance.
People aren't supposed to see
the stuff the lab's working on.
What do you mean
by "stuff?"
Don't answer that.
Did you find Anna's gun?
No.
Don't know how that gun got in
or where it went.
People know you can't
slip through our systems.
The Stream Wave 4 body scanner,
it's state of the art.
If you have a piece of metal
larger than a paper clip,
we're gonna see it.
What if it's smaller?
Than a paper clip?
No, you can't kill someone
with a paper clip.
♪ ♪
This is Anne's gun.
Every piece in here
is smaller than a paper clip.
It would've got through
the scanner undetected.
Anne would've smuggled one in
every morning,
piece by piece.
She built a homemade gun.
That must've taken forever.
Eight months, to be exact.
She was "Loading Up."
Refers to when a magician
pulls off a trick
thanks to extreme preparation.
Like, uh, planting a
playing card months in advance,
then waiting
for the perfect moment.
Is that why I keep on finding
random cards in my pocket?
No, that's for
a different thing.
Really?
No.
The question is, what kind of person
could pull something like this off?
♪ ♪
A spy.
What do you mean?
Like, a spy, spy?
[ Cellphone rings ]
Sleeper.
An ex-pat freelancer.
Alvarez.
She must've had
everybody fooled.
She was probably here naked...
No backup.
You know a lot about spies.
On our way.
Anne's supervisor,
James Collins,
just woke up at the hospital.
Let's go talk to him.
No, you're not cleared.
We need to question him
about the item Anne stole.
Alone.
Hey, hey.
I'm good with secrets.
Not these secrets.
♪ ♪
[ Telephone rings in distance ]
Doctors say one inch lower
and I'm not alive right now.
Kay: We have evidence
to suggest
that Anne was planning this
for months.
Were there any warning signs?
D-Did she get in the lab?
Yes.
[ Sighs ]
What was in there?
You can tell us.
We both have compartmental
security clearance.
It's a miniature
electro-scrambler.
[ Sighs ] The NSA has been
developing it for years.
It's designed
to disrupt computer networks
and take down any security
protocols within 200 yards.
[ Sighs ]
I'm such an idiot!
Everything she said to me
was a lie.
Were you and Anne
romantically involved?
Uh, no.
It's against company policy.
Well, you do look like someone
who was left at the altar.
You don't want to lie to us.
♪ ♪
[ Chuckles ]
We started dating
a few months ago.
[ Chuckles ]
She's way out of my league.
And she asked me out.
Such an idiot!
Of course it wasn't real.
[ Sighs ]
God, I even gave her a drawer
at my apartment.
A drawer?
♪ ♪
Cameron:
Okay, it's a gym bag.
Kay: That was in the drawer
Anne Rojas had
at James Collins' apartment.
I think there's something
hidden in there.
Do you mind if I have a look,
mate? Thanks.
Jordan: The straps
are different sizes.
Maybe a millimeter off.
Oh, check it out...
A sports bra.
What?
Something hidden in it?
No, I was gonna make a joke,
but the mood's all wrong.
I found something.
Oh, it's a secret compartment.
Looks like you might be right,
Kay. It's pretty spy-ish.
The question is,
who is she spying for?
Jordan:
Oh, wow, too cool.
To the naked eye, this just
looks like a regular pattern.
But magnified...
Cameron:
That's a blueprint.
This is a map of downtown.
♪ ♪
Yeah, with a line drawn
from Chambers Street subway
to the Nimitz Building.
The blueprint must be
the Nimitz building.
Interesting.
The Nimitz building houses
a global connection of networks.
When you send an email,
passes through that building.
When Gunter searches
for porn... We get it.
Okay, so,
this building is the backbone
of all communications
in the city.
Why draw a line from the subway?
It's 200 yards.
The range of the device
Anne stole.
What device?
What'd she steal, Kay?
I can't talk about it.
But if she uses it
near the Nimitz building...
Let me guess.
Wipes out half
of New York's communications.
I'll call Deakins. We can get a
tactical team there in 30 minutes.
Do it.
We could be there in 10.
[ Siren wails ]
[ Chatter ]
Still unable to tell me
what this device is?
All you need to know is if
Anne activates the device here,
it'll be really bad.
♪ ♪
You sure about that?
The janitor at my 9:00 has just
been avoiding the trash.
30-year-old teenager
just walked by
pretending to play
his video game.
Homeless woman...
She's got a fresh manicure.
Woman in the red jacket
over here,
she's having a very nice, long
conversation on her cellphone,
but... you getting
any reception down here?
Well, fancy mom, cheap stroller.
And last but not least, we have
a very dashing gentleman
in a black overcoat over here
who's been staring at us
this entire time.
I think we just walked into
a deception.
We did.
Man in the black coat
watching us, he's CIA.
How'd you know that?
♪ ♪
[ Sighs ]
He's my ex.
Oh.
Should we wave?
Definitely not.
So, we just walked into
a CIA stakeout.
Doesn't change our plan.
Anne Rojas is still
our top priority.
Oh, ex-boyfriend's walking over.
He is?
Yeah, be cool.
I'm cool. I have some
questions for him.
No, you don't.
Kay.
Isaac.
Let me guess.
Anne Rojas.
Classic crossover jurisdiction.
Mm-hmm.
Well, my team's
already in place.
I can see that.
We'll back you up.
Cameron,
why don't you wait upstairs?
Plenty of agents down here.
You're benching me again?
♪ ♪
All right.
Oh!
Sorry. Sorry.
Kay, she's coming toward you.
There she is.
Woman in the purple coat.
On my mark.
Move in. Now! Go!
Agent Hockley: On the ground!
Don't move!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
♪ ♪
She's got a gun!
[ Grunts ]
♪ ♪
Help me.
Does she have the device?
No.
♪ ♪
No, just a deck of cards.
She was reaching for this.
♪ ♪
Sorry. Sorry.
Uh, thanks.
Who the hell's this guy?
He's with me.
He's with you.
I'm with her.
He's not with me, with me.
We just... We just work together.
He's a consultant.
That's good that you clarified that.
Cameron Black.
Observer.
Magician.
Isaac Walker.
♪ ♪
It's been too long, Kay.
[ Buzzer ]
Hey.
Any progress?
I just hit a roadblock.
There's this entire page
that they, uh...
♪ ♪
What is it?
Bad news?
No.
No...
Um, it's just, um...
Well, I-I mean...
Just say it, Dina.
[ Sighs ]
[ Clears throat ]
Mike and I, we've decided...
[ Coin clatters ]
♪ ♪
He's a lucky guy.
Are you gonna let me finish?
[ Sighs ]
I know the ending.
♪ ♪
Can I... Can I help?
No, I'm all good.
Thanks for the update.
♪ ♪
Wait.
Maybe you can help.
I need to figure out
what the FBI's hiding from me.
What do you mean?
There's an entire page
that they redacted
from the Mystery Woman's file.
Why?
We're all on the same team.
Well, that's what I thought.
Do you want me
to ask Mike about it?
[ Inhales sharply ]
No.
No, I-I don't want you to
ask your new boyfriend about it.
I just, um...
[ Clears throat ]
I thought maybe
you could borrow his ID
for a couple minutes
and download the original file.
Johnny...
I can't do that.
You're not
just a tiny bit curious
to see what's on this page?
Please.
I'm just trying to get home.
♪ ♪
Cameron: So, when were you
gonna tell me?
Tell you what?
That you dated a super spy.
I wasn't hiding it from you.
I've replayed
eight conversations
we've had about exes in my head.
And it could've come up easily
in any one of them.
What else
are you not telling me?
A lot.
Fair enough.
Isaac: So, how you been, Kay?
You seeing anyone?
That was fast.
She's single.
I've been busy.
Work.
What about you?
Also single.
Really? You?
I'm gonna hang back.
Let you guys talk.
♪ ♪
Just got off the phone
with Langley.
FBI and CIA have
equal jurisdiction on this,
but they want this contained.
Cameron, you're off this case.
Oh, it's all good.
I can handle it.
CIA thinks otherwise.
Sorry, Cam.
Why don't you wait in my office?
It's nothing personal.
It's starting to feel personal.
♪ ♪
[ Knock on door ]
Hey.
Is now a bad time?
It's never a bad time
to see you.
[ Both chuckle ]
Hey, aren't we violating
FBI policy or something?
Probably.
How did it go with Jonathan?
As I expected it would be.
Sorry.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
Something else on your mind?
Um...
so, a page from Jonathan's file
on the Mystery Woman
has been redacted.
And he was just wondering
why the FBI would want
to withhold information
from him.
Files are made classified
for a lot of reasons.
To protect informants
or sometimes it's a bigger case
that can't be exposed.
Tell Jonathan I'm sorry,
but we can't share
classified files.
Are you still coming over?
I sent the boys
to their grandma's house.
Oh.
Well, then, yes.
I'll be there.
[ Chuckles ]
Great.
Isaac:
Where's the device, Anne?
It's close, but I still need it.
Why didn't you have it on you
at the train station?
What are you planning?
♪ ♪
I'm gathering information.
On what?
♪ ♪
Redbird.
What's Redbird?
♪ ♪
Can you excuse us, Kay?
No.
What's Redbird?
♪ ♪
You don't have clearance
for this conversation.
If you prefer, we can
transfer her to a CIA facility.
We have equal jurisdiction here.
And I can't continue
this line of questioning
with you present, Kay.
Let me find out
what she's up to, okay?
So many secrets, Isaac.
[ Sighs ]
I will give you
five minutes with her.
But Anne Rojas stays with us.
♪ ♪
[ Door closes ]
So, Kay's ex is CIA?
Cameron:
He's a super spy.
Didn't know
she dated James Bond.
Can't tell if you're impressed
or threatened.
I'm not threatened.
I just... I don't know.
It's weird to think of Kay
in a relationship.
But he seems cool.
Even if he did throw me out of
the interrogation room earlier.
Apparently,
this Anne Rojas character
has some sensitive information.
How'd you catch her? Found
a map and the blueprints
of the building
she was targeting.
Sloppy.
No, it was very well-hidden.
She's got some serious skills,
but what's weird is
she didn't have the device
on her at the subway.
You sure that was her target?
Well, why else
would she be there?
What's bothering me
is she spent months
meticulously planning
this thing and then...
Only to get easily caught.
Maybe that was her plan.
She wanted us to catch her.
♪ ♪
Don't let her out of your sight.
Agent: Yes, sir.
How's Redbird?
Kay.
Let me guess.
Code word.
Mission?
Energy drink?
How am I supposed to do my job
without all of the relevant information?
Job is done.
We caught her before
she could activate the device.
End of story.
Let us take it from here. The
device is still out there.
Who is she, Isaac?
Can't talk about it.
It must be tiring.
What?
Endless secrets.
Always shutting everybody out.
[ Sighs ]
You haven't changed
since we were together.
Kay, it's part of my job...
Hey, how was it with, uh...
Sorry,
am I interrupting something?
Feels like
I'm interrupting something.
Actually, we were...
What is it, Cameron?
I don't think the Nimitz
building was Anne's real target.
Why was she
at the subway station?
This is just a theory right now,
but I-I think she wanted us
to catch her.
Why would she want us to bring
her here to FBI headquarters?
♪ ♪
[ Coughing ]
Hey, are you okay?
♪ ♪
[ Grunts ]
[ Coughs ]
♪ ♪
[ Coughing ]
[ Device humming ]
[ Alarm blares ]
[ Electricity crackles ]
We have a Code Red.
Security accounts are breached.
[ Alarms blaring ]
♪ ♪
Security's down.
We need this door open now.
♪ ♪
What the hell?
He's alive.
Where did she go?
♪ ♪
She's escaping.
We have to get to the ground floor
before she exits the building.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What if I was right and this
was her plan to get caught?
Why would she want to do that?
Elevators are down,
along with security.
Let's take the stairs.
I don't know, but she obviously
stole the device to use it
in this building.
So, the... the question is, why?
What else is in this building?
Uh, EPA, Department of Labor,
Health and Human Services...
23rd floor.
What's on the 23rd floor?
♪ ♪
How did I not know there was
a CIA black ops location
in my building?
They don't put up signs.
[ Shouting, gunshots ]
[ Gunshot ]
Damn it!
♪ ♪
[ Gunshots ]
When Anne activated
the scrambler,
every computer
and network device was disabled.
If she wanted to
steal information from the CIA,
she'd have to come here.
These are actual CIA files?
Yeah, going back decades.
Any idea which one she's after?
Check the Redbird file.
What's Redbird?
It's gone.
She can't get out
of the building.
Everybody's searching for her.
Guys, wasn't Anne wearing
a purple coat?
Yeah.
Anne?
If you can hear me, do not move.
Careful, Kay.
♪ ♪
It's not Anne.
Haley. Agent Haley Riggs.
Her badge is missing.
Whoa, that's Woman in the Red
Coat from the subway station.
Anne switched coats with her.
Signal's still scrambled.
We can't radio the lobby.
♪ ♪
Her real name is Anais Gomez.
She's Venezuelan intelligence.
Russian trained.
Five years ago, the CIA
had an operation in Venezuela.
Rendition of
a rogue intelligence officer.
Her mission was to grab them
and move them
to one of our black sites.
The operation was called
"Redbird?"
Anais was part of
the intelligence officer's
security detail.
Things went sideways.
She escaped with
the intelligence officer,
but the rest of her agents
all died.
Her whole team was wiped out
by the CIA.
So, she's a spy.
One of the best.
An assassin.
Highly trained.
Expert marksman.
What does she want
with the file?
It has information
about the operation.
Identities of
the CIA agents involved.
Informants.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
Excuse me.
[ Cellphone clicks ]
Yeah?
You know he's not telling us
everything about Redbird.
I'm surprised
he's giving us this much.
Was it like this
when you two were dating?
I mean, it can't be much
by way of work talk
when you're off
to kill bad guys.
Isaac isn't a spy.
He's a field agent,
but he did have
his share of secrets.
Definitely put a strain
on our relationship.
How serious was it with you two?
♪ ♪
[ Sighs ]
What happened?
Uh...
Alex...
Alexandra.
She was part of
the Venezuelan operation.
She retired last year
to work here in the city.
♪ ♪
Anne got to her first?
She killed her.
♪ ♪
Sniper bullet.
This was always
about revenge for her.
That's why
Anne stole the Redbird file.
It's her kill list.
Who else was on that list?
♪ ♪
I'm gonna need your jacket.
What?
Isaac?
What's going on?
Kay: I'm FBI.
We think someone wants you dead.
It's Anais Gomez.
Venezuela?
She already got to Alexandra.
She was shot
with a sniper rifle.
We believe
you're the next target.
So, uh, take off your jacket.
Why?
It's the only way you're getting
out of this tunnel alive.
♪ ♪
Okay, Cameron,
stick to the plan.
And don't give Anne a good shot.
♪ ♪
Cameron, we're sweeping
the rooftops for Anne,
but we're gonna need a second
to find her.
We need you to stall
while we search.
Look for cover and run
as fast as you can, okay?
♪ ♪
Kay, I'm running out of trees.
You'll be fine.
♪ ♪
[ Gunshot ]
Cameron!
♪ ♪
Gunter: Absolutely brilliant!
This dame's a crack shot!
If this wall wasn't here,
your brains would be
all over your trousers!
She's aiming somewhere worse.
Jordan:
Still on task here.
Here's the janitor
with his ray gun.
It's called lidar protractor.
Sounds a bit rude, doesn't it?
[ Protractor beeps, buzzes ]
♪ ♪
Do we have a location?
We do now.
Hotel Lavender.
On the roof.
Mike, it's the Hotel Lavender.
Mike: We're pulling up there now.
Anne Rojas,
you're under arrest. Again.
Got her.
♪ ♪
That's easy.
Isaac: Hey.
Thanks for all your help.
You know, when Kay first told me
about your Deception Group,
I was, uh, skeptical.
[ Chuckles ]
Now I want my own
magic consultant.
All right, well, as long
as it's not David Blaine.
Hate that guy.
Kidding.
[ Telephone rings ]
So, uh, want to grab a bite
at Bamonte's?
Like old times?
Thought maybe we could catch up.
You know,
like regular people do.
Yeah, no.
I don't... I don't think
that's a good idea.
♪ ♪
Right, right.
No, I understand.
Well, I'll... I'll call you.
If something
comes up with the case.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
[ Sighs ] Hungry?
I'm starving.
Isaac just asked you to dinner?
There's a little
too much history there, Cameron.
Well, why don't you leave
the history in the past
and, uh, eat a pizza?
Because it's not that simple.
It's dinner, Kay.
I feel like Isaac has some stuff
he wants to say to you.
And I think you have some stuff
to say to him, too.
Tell me I'm wrong.
♪ ♪
You're not.
Like I said,
I'm a good observer.
♪ ♪
Isaac.
So, you told Kay
to go on the date?
Cameron: Yeah.
So, what's the problem?
She went on the date.
Yeah, I'm struggling
to connect the dots
that lead back
to you calling me.
Yeah, so am I.
Do you not want Kay
to get back together
with her super-spy ex?
I just want her to be happy.
Does she seem happy?
Yeah. So, everything's good.
If she's happy, I'm happy.
You don't sound happy.
I'm not.
Oh.
There it is.
Took longer than I expected.
What?
You've developed
feelings for Kay.
That explains
why you're jealous.
Jealous?
Come on, I'm not jealous.
I'm never jealous.
David Blaine.
♪ ♪
Holy crap.
I'm jealous.
Thanks for coming.
Hey, I'm sorry to talk shop,
but are Redbird questions
still off limits?
[ Inhales sharply ]
Depends on the question.
Anne and her team
were protecting
an intelligence agent...
Redbird's target.
Whatever happened to him?
We received credible intel
that he was killed
not long after the op.
♪ ♪
So, Anne lost her entire team
for nothing.
♪ ♪
You feeling sorry for her?
No, but I work with a team
that I care very much about.
I get what she lost that day.
♪ ♪
Hospital just called.
James Collins disappeared
from his room.
Wait, what?
Her supervisor?
He got shot.
Why would he...
Oh, my God.
I even gave her a drawer
at my apartment.
Kay: That was in the drawer Anne Rojas
had at James Collins' apartment.
The blueprint must be
the Nimitz building.
Oh, my God,
he's working with Anne.
Why do you say that?
He's the reason
her entire plan worked.
He led us to the duffel,
which led us to Anne.
Anne almost killed him.
Yeah, but she didn't.
From two feet away.
A-An expert marksman.
She had me cold
from 400 yards out.
If she wanted him dead,
he'd be dead.
So, if James
is working with Anne...
He's gonna finish
what she started.
Killing everyone
on the Redbird mission.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
You gotta go save the world?
[ Ringing stops ]
A CIA agent
turning off his phone?
I don't believe it.
For one night.
Hmm.
♪ ♪
[ Cellphone clicks ]
I haven't done that
since I was a deputy.
Since...
We were together.
Felt good.
When we were together?
When I turned off my phone.
Oh.
[ Both laugh ]
♪ ♪
Isaac: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
They closed Tiki Town?
Kay:
Last year.
It's where we had
our first date.
I remember.
My God,
you were acting so weird.
I asked you
what you did for a living
and you said,
"Global-ish stuff."
Hey, you cover was bad, too.
"Legal processing."
Yeah, and by the way, you didn't
need to hide your job.
You weren't a secret agent.
I wasn't going to tell you mine
if you didn't tell me yours.
And I don't think you would have
if I hadn't guessed it.
Well, I'm surprised
I got a second date.
[ Chuckles ]
Hey, you remember
the last time we were there?
♪ ♪
Why would you bring that up?
I think about it a lot.
Me, too.
♪ ♪
I still can't believe
you did it at Tiki Town.
It's not the most romantic spot.
I said yes, didn't I?
♪ ♪
The CIA's systems
are back online.
They gave us a copy of the file.
Turns out Redbird wasn't the
name of the Venezuelan mission.
It was the code name
of the team leader.
That must be their main target.
Does it reveal his identity?
No.
Just height, hair color,
and the name of his fiancée
at the time.
His fiancée?
It was the secrets.
It was all of the lies.
I know that was
part of your job, Isaac,
but when I saw
our future together,
it's just...
It's just not
what I wanted my life to be.
♪ ♪
Kay, I have to
tell you something
about the Venezuelan mission.
Redbird?
♪ ♪
I led the assassination team
that killed Anne's colleagues.
You were there?
On a kill mission?
But you were a f...
You were a field agent.
I've never been a field agent.
But when we were together, y...
♪ ♪
That's why you shut me out.
I was trying to protect you.
Wait,
if you were on that mission,
then your name is in that file.
No, because I was
the team leader,
only my code name
is in the file.
Your code name?
♪ ♪
I'm Redbird.
You've reached
Agent Kay Daniels.
I can't make it to the phone...
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Damn it.
Kay's not answering, either,
and the restaurant line is dead.
Why didn't Isaac tell us
he was Redbird?
Why didn't Kay tell us
they were engaged?
And why did they put her name
in the case file?!
Standard protocol.
The CIA lists
significant relations
just in case things go badly.
If James thinks
that Isaac was Kay's fiancée,
he's gonna kill 'em both.
Come on, Mike.
Put your foot down, man.
[ Tires screech ]
Oh, come on, you've got to be...
[ Horns honking ]
Oh, you got to be...
There has to faster route.
Are you using Waze?
It's a half a mile,
but with traffic...
Cameron, you are not
going out there without backup!
Back me up!
Cameron! Ca-Cameron!
♪ ♪
You gonna say anything?
What's the point?
You probably have
the perfect answer planned
for every question.
No.
Not right now.
Please.
Ask me anything.
♪ ♪
Was it real?
What?
Our relationship.
Was it ever real?
♪ ♪
I have never stopped.
Yes, it was real.
[ Sighs ]
That's why
I asked you to dinner...
Don't.
I think...
W...
Let me finish, please.
♪ ♪
You said earlier
that it must be tiring.
A lifetime of secrets.
Sacrificing everything
and everyone important to me.
Even losing you.
You're right.
I'm tired, Kay.
♪ ♪
[ Sighs ] Kay.
Kay, come on.
Sorry about tonight.
♪ ♪
Cameron:
Kay! Stop! Stop!
You're making a mistake!
What are you doing?
Don't do this.
Don't... Don't leave me
for some guy you just met.
Kay, we were engaged
just three years ago.
This... This is wrong.
This is impossible.
I mean, come on, look at him.
Then look at me.
How is this even a choice?
We had it all.
Don't throw it away
'cause this...
We were in love.
We still are.
Kay, I love...
[ Gunshot ]
Oh!
[ Gunshots ]
Cameron! Got him. Suspect down.
[ Groans ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Tah!
[ Stammering ]
Can't say, "Dah."
Ugh.
Still can't say it.
[ Police radio chatter ]
[ Door opens ]
How's Cameron?
Stupid. Bruised.
He's lucky James didn't
go for a head shot.
He was, uh, very convincing.
He is a master of deception.
Right.
Oh, he was just saying whatever
he had to to protect you.
I don't think I was the one
he was trying to protect.
[ Inhales sharply ]
Listen,
I'm sorry about all this.
If I'd have told you sooner...
No.
No one's fault.
Plus, neither of us
had our phones on.
[ Cellphone rings ]
♪ I see our footprints in the sand ♪
So much for that, huh?
Time to go save the world.
♪ I feel hairs raise
on the back of my hand ♪
[ Ringing continues ]
♪ Take me northbound ♪
[ Cellphone clicks ]
Yeah.
♪ Back to home ♪
♪ Where I know ♪
♪ You feel like you're alone ♪
Isaac.
♪ And you feel like
something's wrong ♪
♪ I feel like... ♪
Nothing?
There wasn't anything useful
on the redacted page?
Just phone numbers.
Names of inspecting agents.
Judges that signed warrants.
Nothing gets us closer
to Mystery Woman.
So, the FBI
wasn't hiding anything.
It's not a dead end.
It's just...
I have to go.
Thanks, Dina.
♪ ♪
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Can I help you with something?
Keep walking.
♪ ♪
♪ The concrete skyline
comes along ♪
♪ I hold your picture,
and now I'm gone ♪
♪ Take me northbound,
back to home ♪
♪ Where I know ♪
You are gonna
feel that tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
You'll see.
♪ And you feel like
something's wrong ♪
♪ And I feel like I won't know ♪
[ Sighs ]
That was really stupid, Cameron.
Yeah, well, worked, didn't it?
[ Groans ]
Just so we're clear,
the confessions of love
were strictly professional.
Don't worry.
Jonathan already told me.
Not your type.
Did he?
Mm-hmm.
Ah.
[ Both chuckle ]
♪ You feel like you're alone ♪
How was it with Isaac?
We ate.
We laughed.
And then we said goodbye.
♪ I won't know ♪
Isaac just felt like
moving backward.
I'd rather focus on the future.
♪ So, keep me in mind ♪
[ Door opens, closes ]
♪ ♪
Mike.
What's wrong?
I just talked to Deakins.
I've been suspended
pending an investigation.
♪ Keep me in mind ♪
So, you've been spying on me?
Guard: Watch yourself, Black.
That is what I've been doing.
That's not all
you've been doing, though.
How'd it go?
Stealing files from the FBI.
Find everything you need?
I thought maybe you could
borrow his ID card
for a couple minutes,
download the original file.
Don't worry.
I'm just here to make sure
you stay out of trouble.
♪ ♪
Suspended why?
My ID card got stolen.
Cameron: Who could've stolen
your ID?
I don't know.
It's missing.
Someone used it to break into
the evidence lockup.
♪ ♪
[ Computer beeping ]
Well, what did they take?
Evidence box 9187.
What's in the box?
Lynx Diamond.
No.
I don't understand.
Why?
She wants you alive.
For now.
♪ ♪
Dina: Oh, sorry.
It's her.
The Mystery Woman.
If she stole the diamond...
Then, the puzzle's complete.
She won.
♪ ♪