We've seen fragments before,
enough to confirm that
he kept journals, but
nothing like this. Are they just
fantasies that sustain
him? Or are they a record
of nine more murders?
The police say they have a confession,
that you made a number of admissions.
I... I don't remember any of that.
- I understand he's conscious.
- Yes,
but there is an issue.
It seems Mr Spector
suffered some memory loss.
Are we supposed to be
taking this seriously?
I think we have to.
- Do you know who that is?
- No.
You will be held on remand in hospital
until arrangements can be made
to transfer you to a
secure psychiatric clinic.
If she told the truth
in the first place, about
Spector's whereabouts,
then perhaps Rose Stagg would
not have been put through
the ordeal that she has.
Drink it all up.
Good girl.
Why are you so kind to me?
If I've done the things
that the police say I've done
then I'm a monster.
It's my job.
He's just the sort of
person who would feign
amnesia if he felt that there was
something to be gained from it,
even for the sheer delight of
duping people, particularly experts.
Someone like me, for example.
I found a murder that looks promising.
Law student, Susan Harper.
The only problem is, there
is someone doing time for it.
I'll pray for you.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Rise and shine.
Time to get up.
Stella, for star.
Five more minutes, Daddy, please.
There are no scratches or nail marks
on the soft parts of the victim's face,
no bruising or
lacerations to the mouth or nose
to suggest they were
held closed by a hand.
The original case file
suggests that David Alvarez
suffocated her using a pillow.
There was no saliva,
blood or tissue cells
on any of the pillows, were there?
They could have been washed.
Yes, they could.
Do we have the toxicology report?
Page five, Ma'am.
When was the report done?
Susan Harper's body was
found cool to the touch
on a Monday morning.
Toxicology was 24 hours
later, during autopsy.
Tests 24 hours after
that on the Wednesday.
Based on these figures,
I'd say the victim took
cocaine within hours,
minutes, even, from death.
Do we have anything at all to put
Paul Spector or Peter
Baldwin in London in 2002?
Nothing as yet, Ma'am.
Was there a plastic
bag found at the scene?
No mention that I've seen.
Well, Spector is due to be moved today,
which means the next
part of his assessment
is about to begin.
We have to keep believing
that it will go to trial...
... and when it does,
we have to put together
as strong an evidential case
to the PPS as we possibly can.
We have to be ready.
The truth of a confession is immaterial.
What is of crucial importance is
how the confession was obtained,
not whether or not it's true.
The court must exclude the confession
if it finds it was
obtained by oppression
or under circumstances likely
to render it unreliable.
I've read the transcripts.
- I didn't see any signs of oppression.
- I'm not so sure.
The circumstances are certainly unusual.
Why is a Superintendent doing the
job of a Constable or Sergeant,
interviewing a suspect?
Surely, when you get to
her level, you supervise,
manage and direct the
officers, not do their job?
It was at his request,
- "Just you, Stella, no-one else."
- That's my point.
She didn't really use any
standard interview techniques.
She didn't offer psychological excuses
or minimise the seriousness
of Spector's crimes.
She didn't praise or flatter.
She even used leading questions
that elicited one-word answers.
Almost not like a
police interview at all,
more like an intimate conversation.
She didn't need to establish a rapport,
because their relationship
had already been established
on the phone.
While they were still hunting him,
it's claimed Spector and Gibson
had private conversations.
She gave him her personal phone number.
They even suggest he
was in her hotel room.
Why would he do something so risky
just to leave an entry in her diary?
It speaks of a kind of obsession.
Stella?
Yes.
How nice to hear your voice again.
Is that you, Peter?
Yes.
Why are you calling me?
Because I'm looking up at the sky.
Stella.
Shining star.
It's a beautiful night.
Made me think of you.
Do we have that diary, that entry?
It hasn't been disclosed so far.
Get it.
So...
- ... she seduced a confession from him?
- Maybe.
If you can support
what you're suggesting
with case law, legal principals,
I might include it in the brief.
These are all of the books
from Spector's lock-up, Ma'am.
Ma'am,
there's something you should see.
The wife of the man the police
claim is The Belfast Strangler
was involved in a bizarre
incident earlier this morning,
captured on video by a
passer-by as it unfolded.
Images that some viewers
may find disturbing.
Oh, my God, that's a car.
- Hey, hey!
- Michael, be careful!
Hey, hey!
Oh, my God.
The car being engulfed
by the incoming tide
belongs to Sally-Ann Spector, 32.
The windows are raised,
the doors are locked.
Inside are her two children.
- Oh, my God!
- The girl, aged eight,
can be heard calling for help.
- Help us, please, help!
- The lock.
- Hey, hey!
- I can't wake up Liam!
Please, get it open!
Michael!
Mummy!
At last, it seems the doors are unlocked
and the two children are lifted
clear and carried to safety.
In the background, Sally-Ann Spector
can be seen walking unsteadily
away from the car through the shallows.
Over here.
Are you all right?
She's so cold.
A moment later, the car
is almost washed away.
Somebody help that woman!
The family was airlifted
by police helicopter
to the Belfast General Hospital,
where Paul Spector is being
treated for gunshot wounds
he sustained in Police cust...
How were we to know
she was that desperate?
It's what women do
with their anger, Jim.
They harm themselves
or extensions of
themselves, their children.
What frame of mind must she have been in
to think that they were
all better off dead?
Instead of caring for her,
supporting her, all we could do
was drag her through the courts and
threaten her with prison.
It wasn't just down to me.
The DPP was of a similar mind.
Yeah.
Well, now you can add attempted murder
to her list of charges.
All I ever wanted to do
was keep those children
safe, Stella, that's all!
Healy.
Right,
thanks for letting me know.
Spector's wife and children
have been taken to the General.
- Why?
- It's been on the news.
See if you can find it on your phone.
Point of care testing found
benzos in the girl's urine.
We haven't managed a
sample from the other two.
The son, Liam, is GCS. 12, 13.
With stimulation, he's rousable.
Check the summary care record.
I see she's on the blues.
Severe anxiety and insomnia.
Five milligrams TDS,
titrating to a maximum of ten,
review after two weeks.
So the mother fed the
kids the anxiolytics
and then drove them to the sea.
Looks like it.
She's unresponsive,
not saying anything.
Pupils are mid-sized and reactive.
- How's his blood glucose?
- Normal.
He might need Flumazenil.
Let's put him into paediatric
ICU to keep an eye on him.
Right now, she's
conscious but not talking.
I don't think she's fit
for psych evaluation yet.
We're moving the boy up to the kids ICU.
The girl is awake, she seems OK.
Have you seen the newsreel footage?
No.
It looks like a deliberate attempt
to kill herself and her children.
A cry for help?
Maybe.
- Can I say hello?
- Sure.
Hello, Olivia.
Do you remember me?
How are you feeling?
The bullet fragments in Mr
Spector's body contained no iron,
so he had the MRI scan this morning.
There's an absence of evidence
for established infarct...
... but a suggestion here
of a loss of grey white
matter differentiation.
Now that may be in keeping
with ischaemic insult
in the frontal temporal lobe region,
but I can't say it
explains the memory loss.
I'll pass the results on to Dr Larson
and he can include
them in his assessment.
Do we know what happened
to his wife and children?
- How are they?
- No serious injury, I think,
but I'm awaiting a call
from the ED Consultant.
- Has Mr Spector been informed?
- Not yet.
I'm going to wait for
further information.
I think we have to make a
holding statement of some sort.
Definitely.
Everyone will have seen it by now.
Let's...
confirm that an incident happened,
identify the individuals involved.
Oh, there's nothing else,
no speculation about motivation.
The press will do that for us.
Yeah.
Will you handle this, please, Matt?
I'll sit down with DCI
Eastwood and work something out.
Sound a warning to the press.
And, Matt...
Show a human face.
Paul, the police claim your
fingerprints are on a
pair of decorating shears.
They say the shears, the scissors,
tested positive for Joe
Brawley's DNA, a blood sample.
They were retrieved from the water...
here.
I know where that is,
I go running there sometimes.
Is it possible you
came across the scissors
while you were running,
considered them dangerous,
picked them up and
threw them into the
water, out of harm's way?
I don't remember any scissors.
The one real eye witness is
his sister, Annie Brawley.
After the attack and
before you were arrested
you went to see her in hospital.
I did? Why?
She was grieving the
death of her brother.
You were employed by
the Alice Monroe Fund
to offer her support, counselling.
- What happened?
- Nothing.
You talked.
She said you were helpful.
Hold on. I'm, er,
sorry, I'm very confused here.
This is someone the
police say that I attacked?
Yes.
Well, why didn't she recognise me?
I don't know.
Why would I go and visit
someone that I'd attacked?
What if she recognised me,
what if she started screaming?
It doesn't make sense.
You do have alibis
for all of the murders.
They have been provided by an individual
called Katie Benedetto.
She claims she had a sexual
relationship with you.
I don't know her. What age is she?
She's just turned 16.
She says she was 14 when
you first slept together.
That's not possible.
A child? That's not possible.
There are doubts about her
credibility as a witness.
The real issue, Mr
Spector, is the confession.
I think you should hear a little
of the recording that was made.
It might jog your memory.
Tell me about the first time.
What was it like?
It made me sick.
The smell disgusted me.
The first was the worst
and hardest to get over,
but a switch had been flicked,
a line crossed.
Something was done that
couldn't be undone.
Something that separates
you from the common herd.
I was ill for four days after.
You're in a state of
existential shock...
... but then you find
yourself unchallenged
by divine and secular power.
OK.
So why not do it again...
... but better?
Tell me, do you speak to them?
To the women that you torture and kill?
No.
Do they die slowly?
Yes.
Loosening and tightening your
grip around their throat?
Keeping them suspended
between life and death?
Yes.
Binding them first?
How long do you torture them?
- Stop it. Please, stop it.
- Do you inflict sexual acts...
That can't be me talking.
How would I forget something
like that? That can't be me.
There are other recordings, Mr Spector.
These are video recordings.
The prosecution suggest that...
they were found on your phone.
That you made them.
- That's Rose.
- Yes.
You want to be noticed.
You want to be paid attention to,
make your mark?
Fine. Hurt me,
do whatever you want to me.
Do your worst.
Nothing you can do
will ever take away how
much I love my husband,
how much I love my children.
Nothing you can do
can make me devalue my life in any way.
I will celebrate life.
I love and I am loved
and nothing that you...
Why the fuck are you watching this?
You sick shit.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Nurse!
Paul, Paul, stop that. Can
you step outside, please?
Paul, that's enough,
Paul, focus on your breathing,
focus on your breath.
Come on, that's enough.
Just in and out.
Slow breathing, you're OK, Paul.
In and out, big, deep breath.
Yeah that's good, that's it, you're OK.
Jesus, what have we got ourselves into?
- You having doubts?
- No.
- You sure?
- Yes.
Because if you are, you
can pack up your briefcase
- and sell houses instead.
- I'm not.
Are you Sean Healy?
Yes.
Will you give this to Paul for me?
Katie?
Please, just give this to Paul.
Katie, you're in breach
of your bail conditions.
You're in serious trouble.
We can't take that letter from you.
Katie, stop!
Katie!
I can confirm that there
has been a serious incident
involving the wife and the two children
of the defendant, Paul Spector.
All three are currently being treated
in the Belfast General Hospital.
Their injuries are not life-threatening.
In light of the torrent of publicity
since Paul Spector was
arrested and charged,
the Police Service Northern Ireland
feel bound to urge the
media to exercise restraint
and caution in reporting
the details of this case.
Yep.
We've had a request to
disclose your dream diary.
Sean Healy wants his
own handwriting expert
to examine the entry Spector made.
He's in hospital,
he's incapacitated...
... and yet he's still
infecting the lives
of every person he
comes into contact with.
Everyone who fucking crosses his path.
He's a contagion.
Shall I just let them see that page?
They'll just come back
asking for the rest.
No.
Clear it with the PPS.
And if they agree, send all of it.
I can't believe that
she would harm Livvy.
I just don't think she could do that.
I can picture Sally,
nursing her.
Just...
Just so blissfully happy.
She'd never hurt her.
Where are you in that picture?
Where I always am.
On the outside, looking in.
When I was unconscious,
I was...
I... I could see myself.
In this room. I was able to
see myself from above,
lying in the bed,
with all the tubes and monitors.
Have you ever experienced
anything like that before?
Being outside of your body like that?
When I was young, yes.
When things got really bad, I
used to be able to split myself.
If I was lucky,
a part of me would just drift away.
To another place, a...
better place.
Have you thought any more
about what death means to you?
What I think can only disappoint you.
That doesn't matter.
I think that,
just as I didn't
exist before I was born...
... I simply won't exist after I die.
I can't agree.
Do you believe
that you did the
things they say you did?
Do you?
If I did, then I wasn't arrested...
... I was rescued.
I need you to go to London.
My boss at the Met, a
man called Chris George,
Chief Superintendent.
I just spoke to him.
He's agreed to sign the
authorisations you will need
to access the Susan Harper files.
He's agreed to reopen the case?
He's agreed to let us look at the files.
There's a flight leaving Belfast City
in just over an hour.
Will your arm be all right?
Yeah.
Take Ferrington.
These notes cover wound care
and list the medications you're on.
You've had four days of
broad intravenous antibiotics,
but I must remind you, because
of the loss of your spleen,
you will be on lifelong
prophylactic antibiotics.
Is there any chance I could see my son
before I go?
Which one is he?
Just there.
Do you remember him?
Do you think he looks like me?
A little bit, maybe.
Paul.
I can walk.
Hospital policy.
Sit in the chair.
Thank you for everything.
Detective Superintendent Gibson.
I'm here to see Dr Larson.
He's been expecting you.
Please sign in.
Thank you.
Have I seen you somewhere before?
You tell me.
This is Foyle One,
where Mr Spector will be housed.
Doors are kept locked,
all areas are monitored by CCTV.
Staff have lockers here
for personal belongings.
You can leave your mobile
phone, any keys here.
What level of supervision
have you set for Spector?
We have agreed to level
two care for Mr Spector:
continual presence of nursing staff,
but privacy granted for bathing.
All patients in Foyle One
are allocated a primary nurse.
- Male?
- Male.
How many beds are on this ward?
12 in all.
All the patients we have
on the ward at present have
access to their rooms at all times,
except when they're being cleaned.
Some patients have keys
to lock their bedroom doors,
but staff carry override keys.
This way, please.
Most of the patients are on
pharmacological therapy.
We'll assess the need for a
drug strategy for Mr Spector.
Care and treatment is provided
by a multidisciplinary team,
but I will do the legal assessments.
Yeah, Mr Spector is here now.
- There's coffee here, please help yourself.
- Thank you.
I'm going to greet him.
Mr Spector,
I'm August Larson,
the lead clinician here.
Follow me, please.
Nurse Ritchie will orientate you.
I will be along to talk
to you in a little while.
Follow me, Paul.
There's some toiletries for you there.
And that's your information
on ward routines,
policies and procedures.
Are you hungry?
I haven't been eating much.
I'd like some water.
I'll get you some.
Do you have time to talk?
Yes.
Have a seat, please.
Actually I...
- I have some things I want to show you.
- Hmm?
And you're certain these are his work?
Yes.
Is this his poem?
I think so.
"Dark voices tonight...
... foreign ladies
talking to dangerous men.
Their eyes are lunar divisions.
They lie on dead sheets.
A drunken midnight approach.
Her smile is a crooked lamplight.
Red lips parting...
... soft vowels begging...
feeding the night."
Some clean clothes for you.
Is this his, too?
"I don't believe in love.
At least, I believe in love, but not
in happiness.
The only love that lasts
is unhappy love."
Again, I think it must be him.
I haven't found either
on an internet search.
There are some things in
there that are new to me.
He writes at one point about
the battle, as he perceives it,
between "good Paul" and "bad Paul".
He describes
standing back, being a
spectator of his own actions,
that there's an observing
self and a participating self.
There is a dazzling
array of perversions.
I mean, beyond the sadism and the
overwhelming fetishism
with female underwear.
He was a voyeur,
a transvestite...
into autoeroticism and necrophilia.
There's also signs of
pygmalionism, his obsession
with mannequins and dolls.
I've sometimes wondered if he
breathed air
into his dying victims
to prolong their lives...
... so that they could see clearly
that he was going to kill them.
When young children are abused,
they experience fear and anxiety.
They then attempt to
contain those feelings
by acting out sadistically.
If a person is able to do to others
what he fears may be done to him,
he may no longer be afraid.
You assume he was abused?
He was in Gortnacull, I think?
Doctor, I understand that
for you he's a patient,
an abused child,
someone who deserves understanding and
compassion, even.
But to me, he's a...
He's a sexual predator,
and it's my job to protect
the potential victims
from the threat that he poses.
Viewed from a psychodynamic perspective,
even the most apparently insane violence
has meaning in the mind of
the person who commits it.
I have to try to understand that meaning
and learn from it
in the attempt to
prevent further violence.
Yeah.
Just...
don't underestimate the threat...
... the danger that
Paul Spector represents.
I won't.
Do you have an idea
about Mr Spector's pre-morbid IQ?
He was tested as a child
and scored in the very
superior intelligence band.
Thank you.
It's been a pleasure talking to you.
Psychiatry needs feedback from patients.
It's realised in interpersonal contacts,
so trust is essential.
It is not my place to judge him
for what he may or may not have done,
but I will try to get to
the truth of the matter
for the courts and for you.
He is going to prison.
Let me show you out.
All right, boys.
Out you come.
You should try to eat
some fruit at least.
Rose Stagg is waiting for you, Ma'am.
- Oh, right.
- She's in the interview room.
What's... What's happening
with the Benedetto girl?
She's in custody, due
in court again tomorrow.
- Will you sit in with us, Gail?
- Yes, Ma'am.
What's the next thing that you remember?
Darkness.
And movement,
being thrown around.
I think he must have drugged
me when he gave me water.
It took me a while to work
out what was happening...
that I was in the car,
in the boot of a car.
It was terrifying.
I was thrown around horribly,
particularly towards the end.
I felt like a rag doll.
Every bump made me cry out.
Then the car stopped,
the engine was turned off.
The driver's door opened...
... and then silence.
I waited and waited...
but nothing happened.
I realised I'd been left there alone.
There were some old
water bottles in the boot
so at first I could drink.
But then there was none left.
I tried to pull the brake lights out
to let in more air,
but I couldn't shift them.
I felt so weak.
There was no air.
I became obsessed
with the sound of my own breathing.
I'd fall asleep, but
I'd have no idea for how long.
At first I thought I could tell
whether it was day or night
from the smell of the air,
but then the air got staler and staler.
I lost all track of time.
I tried to think about the kids,
but I couldn't focus.
I felt my brain was shutting down.
The last thing I remember
was thinking that I should burrow,
that I should dig down
into the earth to hide,
to feel safe and warm.
Like an animal,
digging...
I don't remember anything after that.
Thank you.
Can I talk to you...
alone?
Without the tape?
This is DC Gail McNally
suspending the interview at 10.43pm.
I haven't been...
I haven't been completely
honest with you.
I led you to believe
that after that one
time he strangled me,
that it ended.
But it didn't.
I suspected as much.
It wasn't that simple.
We went to some dark places.
The first time it happened,
I was giving him...
I was...
using my mouth on him.
He squeezed his legs around my neck.
I couldn't breathe. I was...
Take your time.
Er...
He squeezed really tight.
I thought I was going to pass out but
he released me.
He treated it a bit like a game,
at first.
I'd already begun to
think he didn't have
much enthusiasm for
ordinary intercourse...
... but then things got more serious.
He asked me to play dead.
And then there was the
time that I told you about.
I think he revived me, mouth to mouth.
There were times when he
wanted to use a plastic bag
on me,
on himself.
He said that we all
try to live in the light,
that we all try to build walls around us
to block out the darkness,
the danger that's out there,
but it can't be done,
it's a lie,
that in reality there
are dark gods out there
and that men could become gods on earth
through a certain kind of sex.
And women?
I think so.
I'm sorry.
I can't really explain it.
Why did you walk away?
It felt to me
that everything that was happening
was about pleasing him.
That it wasn't about me at all.
I left him and I went back to Tom.
And what about Spector?
He went to London,
I think.
Did you and Spector ever do drugs?
- I think I told you that we drank a lot.
- Hm.
Cocaine?
No,
not with me, but maybe he did back then.
My life with Tom couldn't
be more different.
Things have been difficult
since the birth of Cody.
Actually, since my first Caesarean.
And how are they now?
It's strange.
When he talks to me now, I...
don't really listen to
the words that he's saying,
just to the tone of his voice.
From that I can work out
whether he likes me or not,
whether he's emotionally close to me.
Right now, he's angry...
... and I don't think
he likes me very much.
Rose,
there's something I need to tell you.
I think that...
I'm the reason that
Paul Spector came after you.
How?
I think I...
I think I revealed your
identity as my informant
when I used his name, Peter.
The name that you gave me when
I spoke to him on the phone.
Using that name,
together with the E-Fit
that we had created,
I think led him straight to you.
I was
trying to convey that...
... well, that we were on to him.
I was trying to scare
him to stop the attacks.
And it worked to the
extent that he ran, but...
but when we didn't do anything,
when we didn't pounce...
he came after you.
I hadn't realised
your relationship was
so meaningful to him.
He said I was the only one.
That I was the only girl.
I believe it.
I'm glad I'm not the only
one to have made mistakes.
Thank you.
Go fuck that!
Jesus fucking Christ!
I'm Mark Bailey.
Who are you?
I'm told I'm the Belfast Strangler.
Are you?
Maybe.
Right now, I don't remember.
Wasn't well. Better now.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org