Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Who is it? Answer me, Samantha.
Don't you imagine it?
Is it Father Joseph?
Is that your lover?
He listens to me.
- He listens to me and understands me.
- But I do as well!
No, Richard.
You don't listen to me anymore.
Of course! You never speak to me!
Evidently we've got nothing
to tell each other anymore.
This doesn't prevent us
from being a couple!
A couple?
What is "a couple" for you?
It's simple: I'm your husband
and you're my wife!
I was your wife, but it's over now.
What?
Can I help you?
- I've got an appointment with doctor...
- Monnier.
You're looking for Dr. Monnier.
That's right.
Sixth floor, second door on the left.
Thanks.
Thanks. See you soon.
Good-bye.
- Good evening.
Have you got an appointment?
Yes, at six o'clock.
Six o'clock?
Sorry, I'm late,
but I told your secretary that...
It's alright, come in.
Thanks.
My secretary is out.
You are Ms...?
What's your name?
Oh, sorry, I am...
Yes? Hi Jacques...
Not at all...
No, let's talk about it now.
Just a moment, don't hang up.
I have to talk 2 minutes to a colleague.
If you want to sit down
in the meanwhile... Please.
Please.
No, no... I know, I know.
I tell you that I know.
counterfeited balance. To be honest
there's nothing I can do.
No, absolutely nothing.
You know what? Let me address him
to our friend at the Prosecutor's Office.
He's specialized
in those kinds of problems.
Yes... Let's do it that way.
Sorry.
You forgot your purse.
Being your first time, you have to fill in
a form with some information.
- Information?
- Please, sit down.
Your age, profession,
civil state...
Who addressed you to me?
Nobody.
I searched the Phone Book,
I wanted someone near
and so I called.
The first in the list couldn't
before two months.
I had urgency and...
Urgency?
There's a problem...
a personal problem.
May I?
Of course.
My husband doesn't bear it.
I had succeeded in quitting, but...
A personal problem, you said?
Yes.
With my husband.
We've been married for four years...
Sorry.
Thanks.
We don't get along well anymore,
my husband and I.
He's changed much
since he stopped working..
Why, what happened to him?
Health problems.
But do you work?
Yes, I've always worked.
My husband didn't want me to, but...
I'm not the housewife kind.
I'm a shop-assistant in a boutique.
Purses, suitcases...
Will you excuse me.
Yes? That's why I'm here, madam...
See you tomorrow at five o'clock.
See you, madam.
Pardon me, please.
Apart from my husband
I haven't got anyone to speak to.
Not even your colleagues?
No, we only speak about the job.
- Anyone in your family?
- No one.
I'm afraid I'll become crazy.
Have you ever told that
to your husband?
I tried, but...
He treats me like a child.
We haven't got any children.
I wanted a few, but...
It's too late.
He doesn't touch me anymore.
We haven't got sex anymore.
We haven't had sex for more than six months.
No more sex all of a sudden,
while we used to be very close before.
And I miss it, to take pleasure from him.
But not only that.
Also his kisses, his caresses...
His body against mine... Understand?
I'm not used
to speak of myself this way.
I'd rather stop.
So? Will you accept?
Accept what?
My case.
How many sessions will it take?
That's how they are called, isn't it?
I understand, you still don't know.
Is next week possible?
On Thursday at the same time?
Doctor? Did you tell her
you're a psychiatrist?
No, I haven't told her anything.
It's her who believes that.
She has taken me for doctor Monnier.
- Who?
- Doctor Monnier,
the psychiatrist who has
a study on my same floor.
She had an appointment with him.
And haven't you told her
she had knocked on the wrong door?
I realized that when it was too late.
My clients often speak to me
about their personal problems.
I thought that she wanted
to consult me about a divorce.
Can you pass me those books, please?
And what's she like?
What do you mean?
Is she pretty?
I would not know.
While she was speaking
she started to cry, and that...
made you upset.
What have you two spoken about?
Her problems with her husband.
She has found an expert!
Good morning.
I am looking for a book.
Could you give me more details?
"Room" is in the title, I think.
That's really useful.
- Do you still want to meet him?
- Who?
- Luc. He's coming to get me.
- The bodybuilder?
He isn't a bodybuilder, he manages a club.
A club for swinging couples?
A fitness club.
- When you left me...
- Wait a minute, it's you who left me,
and the last time you did, was the seventh.
If she's sick she needs
a real therapist.
You can't go on
lying to her that way.
Call her and tell her the truth.
I don't even know her name.
Here is Luc.
Hi flea.
So... Luc, this is William.
The famous William!
They say you're the best in your field, mate.
I'm not your mate.
He's so witty!
...Business booming, is it?
I don't understand what you mean.
Let's go, flea.
You've got a body-sculpture lesson.
Bye.
Let's hug each other
next time, okay? It's better.
William, when she comes
you'll tell her "I am not a psychoanalyst,
I'm a tax consultant".
Will you tell her?
Of course. Who do you think I am?
According to you, Mr. Faber,
can we contest the partition?
...because the tax inspector told me that...
I told you that the administration
made a mistake with the quotients
assigning two parts to you. Your daughter,
who is eighteen
but still dependent on you,
gives you the right to an additional half.
Have you understood?
Not really, no.
If you could repeat...
Everything will be alright.
I'll take care of your file.
Thanks, Mr. Faber.
- Good day, madam.
- Good day sir.
Your father?
How does it feel to be retired?
When I met him
I still had my confectionery,
the "Ringo Starr".
- Send him my regards, please.
- I will, thank you.
- Thanks a lot and see you.
- See you, Mr. Michel.
I'm done with the typing.
Do you still need me?
No, you can go, Mrs. Mulon.
Enjoy your life!
Do you want me to cook something for you?
No, I'll do it myself.
I know. Poor thing...
- Good evening, doctor.
- Come in...
There's something
I didn't dare tell you the other time.
It's not easy.
I'm supposed to say everything, right?
- As a matter of fact, I wanted to tell you...
- There's too much light, could you...?
My husband doesn't touch me anymore.
Better than being beaten.
But he would like...
I'm sorry.
He wants me to have sex
with another man.
Oh, another man.
Someone you know?
No, it doesn't matter who.
He's getting obsessed by this.
He says: "You have the right
to fuck with anyone".
It's him who uses the word "fuck".
The women who do such things to survive
have no choice but I...
He's the one who needs professional help...
How can you bear it?
We'd better break up.
We can't go on like that.
- Why?
- That's how it is.
I've got to go now.
I'll give you what I owe you.
No, listen...
No, I haven't got enough money, sorry.
I'll pay you next time.
When will it be? Monday, same time?
Listen to me...
- I'm not a doctor.
- Aren't you? I thought that...
But have you understood what I want to say?
Yes, I have.
Not all the psychoanalysts are graduate,
but a degree or a diploma,
is the same to me.
See you on Monday, doctor.
Mrs. Mulon,
- Any phone calls?
- From whom?
- A young lady.
- What's her name?
- It doesn't matter.
- No one has called.
- Good morning madam.
- Good morning.
Sorry for the trouble.
Could I speak with doctor Monnier?
Have you got an appointment?
No, I'm his neighbour,
Mr. Faber. The tax consultant.
Oh, of course.
What would you like to tell him?
A friend of mine had to meet
the doctor at the beginning of the month.
It is possible. And?
Well, we had lost contact,
then we met again in the lift,
but she was in a hurry. I wanted to call her
but I haven't got her number anymore.
What day exactly?
Tuesday 2nd at six o'clock p.m.
Yes, there was a patient.
It was her first session.
- That's her.
- But she didn't come
- without notice.
- It's her.
What's your friend's name?
I don't know, because
I know her first name,
but I don't absolutely know
her family name.
Rather twisted, your story.
But I need to contact her. Be kind.
I'll go and ask the doctor
if he can receive you.
"sofas as deep as graves".
Do you know this verse by Baudelaire?
Face to face will do, for a first session.
But I don't believe that...
I'm listening.
The typical problem of the women
who come to consult me is:
"I don't feel wanted anymore"...
"I think my husband is cheating on me"...
"He got the wrong woman
and I got the wrong door"...
But I'm not surprised
by the mistake of this young lady.
To work on ourselves is not easy.
No, the strangest thing is your behaviour.
You didn't tell her she made a mistake.
The first time okay, but the second...
However the thing is over.
She was supposed to come two days ago,
but she hasn't
and I haven't heard from her.
So everything is alright?
No, because I'd like to see her again.
You are free.
If she had opened
your heart to you at a party
would you have asked for my permission?
Wait a moment,
she has mistaken me for you..
She has. I don't like it
when someone steals my clients.
But I've got to tell her the truth.
I need her number.
I don't know anything about her at all.
You already know too much.
I'd like to know where she lives, at least.
Everyone would like
to know many things, my dear gentleman,
but it's not always possible.
No. I am desolate, but
I cannot give out any information
regarding patients
above all when they're not even my own.
That'll be 120. Euros.
- It's part of the therapy.
- Of the therapy...
I repeat, Mr. Chapel,
that he'll receive you.
- Good-bye.
- Good-bye, madam.
But had said three o'clock,
it has to be three o'clock!
...but please understand...
- Calm down Mr. Chapel...
- But he said at three o'clock!
I'll go get you some water.
Everything will be alright, you'll see.
- I bring you the water. Calm down.
- Alright.
I'm fine, I apologize.
Good morning.
I wanted to say that I'm...
... "Meteo France".
Today, the weather in Paris
will be windy
and rainy for the rest of the night.
Therefore, the temperature
will be rather fresh...
Excuse me, but a person insists to see you.
She hasn't got an appointment, but...
I'll be right there.
Shall we stay here?
No, come in.
Want to know why I didn't come last time?
I have to tell you
that I'm not doctor Monnier.
I know.
I've known it for a while.
I wanted to delay
our appointment,
and when I called
the real doctor Monnier picked up.
His voice was different from yours.
It was a shock.
I thought, if he's not him, then...
...then who is he?
I should have never returned here.
I thought it's disgusting.
That guy knows all about me
and I know nothing about him.
So, Mr. Faber,
you're a tax consultant.
- What's your job about?
- I help my clients to deal...
with their own taxes.
Without cheating?
Yes. Well, yes and no...
You cheated on me.
The appearances are against me.
- Please to forgive me. Will you?
- No.
I could have killed you.
I really could have.
Listen, there's been a misunderstanding.
I am sorry about that.
And I, when I realized
I had spoken about my problems
to a perfect stranger, I felt dirty,
- as if you had raped me.
- Raped...
Yes, raped.
- No one can help me...
- I don't agree...
Nobody can.
I'm coming.
Am I disturbing you?
Are you with the family?
The family? No, no...
I have wandered about the district.
I hate this hour, when it gets dark.
The shops close, the people return home...
I should as well,
but I was sorry
I had left like that.
Never mind.
I came again
because I haven't got your number.
Neither have I, Mrs. De Lambre...
- Did you investigate on me?
- Well, you disappeared...
No, I've only asked my neighbour,
doctor Monnier,
if he could give me your number.
And?
Don't you imagine?
I didn't want him to call me
at home, because of my husband.
...and you gave him the number
of the weather forecasts.
The first one which came to my mind.
We use it at the boutique.
When they say it will rain,
we put the umbrellas in the windows.
On Tuesday at half past six, Mr. Faber?
Yes, of course.
But how can I call you?
Anna, if you want.
- No, I meant by phone...
- Don't you ever call me.
See you on Tuesday.
So? What do you think?
- It has a good bouquet.
- I didn't mean the Bordeaux but Luc.
Tell me honestly.
Well, he is...
...He's very physical, isn't he?
Indeed. Not your kind at all.
You'll have to get rid of my books...
There is no hurry...
Mister Muscle doesn't care that
you're spending the evening with me?
I told him I had a meeting at the Faculty.
- Have you seen her again?
- Who?
- The weeping girl.
- Yes.
- Have you told her you aren't a psychiatrist?
- Of course.
I had to.
Whose makeup is this?
Yours.
- Did you keep it?
- Yes, just in case...
Don't you want to stay?
No, William.
Tonight was just...
just nothing.
Hello? Hello!
Hello, who is it!
- Who was it?
- No one, I hung up.
- Were you waiting for a phone call?
- No.
Which floor?
- The sixth.
- Me too.
Thank you, but I'd rather use the stairs.
- Up to six floors?
- I prefer so.
I'm early.
The first time I saw this sofa
I thought it wasn't bad at all...
Sometimes I take a nap...
I was late today because
the streets were full of people,
and I don't like the crowd.
I had to walk through secondary streets.
Wouldn't it be simpler
for you to come by car?
My husband forbids me to drive.
He forbids you to drive,
he forbids you to smoke...
What else?
Who knows what he does
alone in the house all day.
And how do you spend your days?
I try to survive.
I get up, I go to work...
...and that's it.
Wouldn't you like to do something else,
a more interesting job, perhaps?
I have already done all.
Shop-assistant, waitress, smoker...
Drinker in times of depression.
There's something that...
but it's rather a passion than a job.
When I was a child I studied
classical dance for seven years.
It was fantastic,
hard but fantastic.
My old teacher, above all.
He was the first one
to show some interest for me
Really.
Who knows if I could still...
Why don't you try?
Please, have a try.
Come on...
Excuse me, but...
an urgent fax has arrived.
I'll be back later.
Wouldn't you like to dance again?
A star of the ballet? I'm too old for that.
Age doesn't matter,
if you believe in yourself.
Well... I used to, when I was young...
- When you were young...
- Well, yes.
I have done everything
too soon and too badly.
I left school at 14.
I left home at 16.
"Home" so to speak.
We lived in a camper.
My mother thought it was more practical,
because we travelled all the time.
We were always travelling.
To the south, in the sun,
without love or hate,
I simply didn't exist.
Sometimes, in the evening,
she brought in a man.
She made me go out
and forgot about me.
My mother has never brought anybody in.
I have to go now.
My train leaves in half an hour.
- Do you live far?
- In Switzerland.
In a quiet corner of the suburbs.
Small gardens, small houses...
I imagine that Switzerland is like that.
See you next time?
See you, madam.
- See you.
- Anything wrong, Mrs. Mulon?
- Nothing, apart from the ashtrays I have to empty.
- Is she a new client?
- Yes, why?
I haven't got any file on her.
I'm taking care of her file.
Personally.
The majority of my patients
come here for complaining.
Nobody wants to listen to others anymore.
Not even hairdressers or waiters
have got the patience anymore.
This young woman
has found the ideal listener in you.
But it's not a good thing...
Since she hasn't got
any serious pathologies...
I can't forbid you to see her.
Your job, after all,
is not very different from mine.
We both deal with
the same types of neurosis:
what is declared
and what is kept hidden.
Well, I can listen to her,
but as for solving problems...
The lady's or yours?
Mr. Faber is going to be busy for a while.
You hadn't got an appointment, Miss...
Mrs.
And after that, he has another appointment.
I'll wait.
Can I deduce the customs duty?
Otherwise they'll tax me twice,
and that's not fair.
Last time it was even an old stock.
I can't accept your case,
too many details are missing.
But you have got everything...
Yes, but it's a complex case.
- Yes, but...
- No, I'm telling you your case is complex,
very, very complex. Do you understand?
We'll speak about it some other time.
I'm sorry. After you.
See you.
Talk to you soon, dear sir.
You forgot it here.
Thanks.
It got stuck.
May I?
Thanks.
Isn't it too boring?
The files, all those papers...
Boring? No, not at all.
You know, taxes can tell a whole life,
they tell a lot of things,
births, marriages, divorces,
success, failures and deaths.
My delays worry my husband when I come here.
But what worries him?
He thinks that I meet someone.
- Someone? A psychologist?
- No.
A man, a lover, that's it.
But isn't that what he wanted?
Only if I tell him about it.
I told him I had to stay
at the shop till late.
I don't know why I lied to him.
But tell him the truth...
What? That I go to a psychiatrist's?
That would be another lie.
And, which is worse,
he wouldn't understand what I do in here.
He would imagine other things.
But you aren't forced to tell him everything.
Secrets are allowed in a couple.
In a couple, yes.
Why do you always wear a tie?
Are you forced to?
No, I'm not forced at all...
It reassures you.
- Yes, Mrs. Mulon?
- Oh, never mind.
Could I have something to drink?
Certainly.
Mrs. Mulon, would you be so kind
- as to bring us two cups of coffee, please?
- Tea.
Wait a second...
A tea and a coffee, please.
What does he think?
This isn't a cafe...
My husband, I've seen him dead.
In a dream?
No, for real.
I am very sorry.
When did it happen?
Six months ago.
He was about to die for my fault.
When I was small
I couldn't read, count, walk...
It still happens to me sometimes.
I can't tell left from right,
I confuse the words...
- You get the wrong doors...
- That too.
That evening I was getting
the car out of the garage,
and the electric gate, you know?
No, I don't...
A wrong manoeuvre.
I drove backwards too fast
and I didn't notice
that my husband was there,
hiding in the dark.
What was he doing in the dark?
It's a game between us.
I heard him shout.
Too late.
I smashed his left leg against the wall.
I made him an invalid.
- Wheelchair?
- No, only a cane.
He isn't happy to use it, but
sometimes he falls down
and I have to help him get up.
Thanks.
Thanks, Mrs. Mulon.
He hasn't touched me since then,
since the accident.
According to him, another man
would be a way to bring back his desire.
It's a dangerous game.
What if you fell in love?
With whom?
With the other man.
I should meet him, before.
Who's that sad woman?
I don't know... Nobody.
It makes me shiver.
I used to think that she was
my father's secret lover,
but he's too serious for that.
Even if for some time he had
a crush on Madame Mulon.
- The secretary?
- Yes, she was his own, at first.
She had some kind of vagueness.
Vagueness? I don't know what it means.
It means... she was attractive.
- See you.
- Good-bye.
See you.
I can finally shake a hand,
yours, at least.
- It's a beginning.
- See you on Thursday.
Good morning, Mrs. Mulon.
Jeanne, good morning!
I thought she wasn't coming
to see you anymore.
Even now that she knows
you aren't a psychiatrist...
- Oh, I understand.
- No, you don't...
She only speaks to me about her husband,
a vicious man who makes her suffer.
- She only has to leave him.
- It's not so simple,
he dominates her and she is afraid of him.
Luckily, she met you.
- You will save her...
- Hm hmmm.
I can't believe that!
What?
You said "hmmm" like a psychiatrist.
And how do you know that
psychiatrists say "hmmm"?
Because I've been in analysis for six months.
You too? But why?
- I'm elaborating my mourning.
- Mourning? Has anyone died?
I'm elaborating the mourning of our story.
So? How about the sofa?
The small one,
I have come for it...
I'm glad you're taking it away,
it's useless.
- It'll suit your place much better.
- It is nice, isn't it?
Delicious.
Hold on, take away this too.
You have always said
that you liked it so much...
- Are you sure that you won't miss it?
- No. Leave it to me, Mrs. Mulon...
- Thanks.
- My pleasure.
Hi Willy. This is a men's thing.
Thanks a lot.
- My goodness, it's huge!
- The biggest on the market.
You're so lucky...
If you like it, I can get you one.
The importer works out in my club.
Very kind of you,
but I haven't got the license.
It's a joke, isn't it? Well, come on.
We have to hurry,
The traffic is terrible at this hour.
How strange, I knew you would say that.
- You aren't Zen at all.
- No, I am not Zen.
I have swallowed an umbrella,
and it was open.
You should chill out, mate.
What are you doing here?
Where is your wicked secretary?
It's her day off.
Why do you say she's wicked?
She looks like it.
- Where were you?
- At a client's, for a tax inspection.
- It went on for hours.
- You could have called me.
How could I?
And then we hadn't got an appointment.
- We did, it was for Wednesday.
- No, it was for Thursday.
No, it was for Wednesday.
I haven't dreamt of it.
Oops it was for Thursday.
- Sometimes I get confused, you know.
- Yes, I do.
I have to pee. I can't resist.
It's at the end of the corridor on the left.
Should I take you there?
Thanks, I don't need any witnesses.
On the left...
I've understood.
This house is so tidy...
Everything is in place, perfectly...
- Who cleans up?
- I do it myself.
- Is it a mania?
- No, I just like it.
It was my dad's lighter,
It's all that he left,
besides a photo.
And I don't even know if he's my father.
You're dying to know more, aren't you?
He died in a car accident
shortly after my birth.
My mother was driving.
She killed my father
and I have almost killed my husband.
Now you've got the whole picture.
- How strange...
- What?
The accident which repeats itself,
from mother to daughter.
Did you get rid of the sad woman?
Yes, poor thing.
She had been there for thirty years...
- Have you lived here for thirty years?
- Longer than that.
I was born here,
I have never moved.
This office was my father's.
When he retired he left it to me.
And you put your toys in here...
As you can see.
This is funny.
What's it's name?
Is it a secret?
My taw-taw.
What does it mean?
"My toy"?
I think so.
Careful, please. It's fragile.
And what did your father do?
Same as me.
Oh. Also this repeats itself,
from father to son.
I would never imagine
I'd do his same job.
When I was a teen I wanted to be an explorer
to conquer a lot of women and the world...
and then the world reduced itself
to this apartment.
- But don't you ever travel?
- Yes, for my job.
Last year I went to Belgium.
And how about the women?
Are you single?
We cannot speak about you?
There's a closed door at the bottom.
- It's my parents' room.
- No, I was speaking of you,
not of your apartment.
- Do you live here?
- No, I'm going to see someone.
Me too, my psychiatrist.
Doctor Monnier?
- Are you going to see him as well?
- No, another person.
- Another psychiatrist?
- More or less...
- And is he good?
- Not bad. How is yours?
Like a dentist.
But he hurts me even more.
- I cannot use lifts.
- Why?
I just can't.
Not even a floor, just to try?
No. Doctor Monnier says I'm not ready.
- I wanted...
- I...
- Oh...
- No no...
- No, sorry...
- No no, I beg you.
Please tell me.
My husband doesn't
touch me anymore because...
because he hasn't got erections anymore.
I would not care, really
we could do other things.
but he feels like he's dead.
Well no, not exactly.
He still has obsessions.
For example he likes...
Fantasies
Yes, fantasies.
For example, he likes to watch me wash myself
or go to bath.
Really...
As long as it helps him...
Don't you understand?
No, I can't understand.
I think he should have himself cured.
What you said is horrible.
And isn't your husband horrible too?
Why don't you get rid of him?
I already have.
No, I meant, why don't you
take back your freedom?
Freedom is not for me to leave him,
it's to find him again.
I apologize, I am sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- It's nothing.
Mr. Faber... Were you coming to see me?
- No no, I was passing by.
- Passing by?
- Yes.
- I'm going to lunch. Have you had lunch?
No.
Patients are the ones who make
the investigation and gather the clues.
Psychoanalysts don't know anything.
They only know what the patients
know. Are you following me?
Not really. No, because the more I see her
- and the less I understand what's happening.
- Here's the dessert.
- Chinese fruit's salad.
- Thanks.
- And the bill.
Listen. The knots of your tie are impeccable,
your business is going very well,
but let your unwanted and temporary
contact with psychoanalysis
teach you this, at least:
you haven't got everything under control,
there is something that escapes you.
We aren't in my study
and therefore this isn't a consultation,
but nothing prevents you
from paying for my lunch.
Something's just passed through my mind.
Who tells you that she's really married?
Why would she lie to me?
Didn't you make her believe
you're a psychoanalyst?
What if she's a mythomaniac?
The fake neurotic and the fake psychiatrist.
It could be.
Even better,
she didn't get the wrong door
and rang your bell willingly.
Samantha listen to me!
I beg you, be reasonable!
I can't be reasonable!
I am in love with you!
This is a test, and you have to pass it!
- I cannot love women!
- Because you're a priest?
Excuse me.
- Which floor?
- And you?
- The sixth.
- Me too.
Good morning.
You don't want to listen to me anymore?
If I didn't want to, I would
address you to doctor Monnier.
What does he look like?
He has a typical aspect, no one would
mistake him for a tax consultant.
- And your husband?
- My husband?
What does he look like?
Have you got a husband or not?
- Have you got a cigarette?
- No. What's his name?
Marc. Are you happy now?
- He made a scene.
- A scene? Why? He's jealous?
- He knows that I go to a doctor.
- Why, he followed you?
With that leg? How could he?
No. He must have peeped in my notebook.
He says we have to tell each other
everything, and I so told him everything.
What?
That I've got a lover.
That I go to bed with him after work.
My husband thinks that you're the one.
- Me?
- Yes.
Well, the psychiatrist.
They can have an affair
with their patients, can't they?
But what went through your mind
to tell him that?
He wanted me to meet someone and I have.
I can't understand the way
it works between you two.
Before I met him, I was the cripple.
He lit everything up
with his gaiety.
His gaiety, yes.
It is a word out of fashion, I know.
He was always cheerful,
that's why I loved him.
- You don't love him anymore?
- I feel some affection for him.
If you do, why do you come here?
What are you expecting from me?
I've had enough of your interrogatory tone.
My client... So far my client hasn't
received the transaction for the inheritance.
Well, am I sorry but at this point...
will you excuse me for a second? Don't hang up.
Come in, please.
I'm sorry.
Yes, it's annoying, very annoying.
Look, I'll give you
the 12th as a limit, otherwise...
No, not one day more.
Alright. Thanks for understanding.
See you, lawyer.
Excuse me, you are Mr...
Exactly.
I'm listening.
It's complicated.
I'm used to that. What's the problem?
You.
You know my wife Anna.
I am Marc, she must have spoken of me.
This is where it happens, then...
At first I thought it was doctor Monnier
who fucked my wife.
I sent someone who could
confirm that. Actually
she didn't go to a physician, she lied to me,
which means she has got something to hide.
- Listen...
- I don't think she comes here for the taxes,
but it is alright, she is free.
- What do you want from me?
- I wanted to see your face.
- Is your leg any better?
- She tells you everything!
Not all, but she told me about the accident.
And you believed her?
I understand you.
Sometimes it's better not to know the truth.
You! Make her happy!
Mr. Faber?
Your lift is out of standards.
If the box falls down,
there isn't any safety system.
Let's hope it never happens
when you're inside it.
That gentleman is so nice!
Very.
Having understood that
Father Joseph is homosexual,
Samantha gets depressed.
and tries to put and end to her days,
but Richard intervenes
just in time to save her.
He is ready to forgive her.
Can love between them spring up again?
- Where are we?
- Almost on the second floor.
- How do you feel?
- I feel bad! I feel like shouting!
Then shout!
- Don't be ashamed.
- Careful, I'm going to shout!
Come on!
It's a recurrent dream.
That's why I speak of it,
because when it happens I...
- How do you feel?
- You found me ridiculous, didn't you?
Not at all. I know what that means.
It is a great day for me,
an immense victory.
Also for me, believe me, but you'll see,
next time you'll do it alone.
You won't need
to go to Dr. Monnier anymore.
And why do you go to a psychiatrist?
It is him who needs me,
I am his only patient.
Bye.
Coming here, I thought I was on holiday.
When it's sunny I remember
the summers I used to spend in the south.
People feel free,
they do everything with calm,
they go to the beach by scooter...
- Do you understand?
- More or less.
Is everything alright?
Yes, everything's alright.
For you too, it seems?
Yes, I feel better. Did you notice?
For a few days,
I don't know why, I've felt...
happier.
Even my husband
noticed I've changed,
but of course he thinks
it's because of the sex.
He began again.
He's no longer satisfied
by the fact that I've got someone,
therefore I told him
what the two of us do.
The two of us?
Me and my lover.
And what have you told him?
Sex on the psychiatrist's sofa.
He likes the fact that it's a psychiatrist,
a tax consultant would be
very less stimulating.
No offence meant.
Can I tell you everything?
I think so.
Telling him...
what I do with my lover, I...
Yesterday, while having a bath,
I caressed myself.
It wasn't the first time,
but yesterday I reached the top.
The top of what?
"To have an orgasm" sounds medical,
so I say "to reach the top".
How do you say that?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Do you think I'm sick?
Because you had a bath?
I don't think I can go on.
It's normal, you weren't prepared for this.
Women who speak of their orgasms terrify men.
They wake up ancient fears
from early childhood, but you cannot stop.
It will end when it has to end.
This half-open door on the feminine mystery
can hardly be closed again.
...no, because Mr. Faber
I have to tell you that
your father was totally...
Mr. Fernand,
he was an incredible person,
he was perfect. I understood all...
- How much does she pay you?
- Nothing... Are you crazy?
She has to pay, it's the rule.
How far did you get?
She speaks and you listen? That's all?
- Of course! Does that surprise you?
- Not from you.
You have never been able
to take the initiative.
Curious, this block.
She must be wondering
what you're waiting for...
She doesn't come to me for that.
You think? A woman who tells
a tax consultant about her orgasms?
Do you get excited, at least?
You don't understand anything!
Have you made a vow of chastity?
Wait!
You came to me to ask for advice,
you should know what you want!
I don't know anything anymore!
It's simple, either you
let her go or you fuck her!
- I what?
- You haven't answered me!
- But I can't! I cannot court her.
- Or you don't want to.
- Jeanne, you're jealous.
- So what?
When I first met you
you had dreams and ambitions,
you wanted to write a novel,
and you ended up cataloguing
old books in a library.
The dust has made you acid.
- Good evening.
- What are you doing here?
Your fascinating secretary
said I could wait for you.
I walked around the house. Not bad at all!
There was a naked girl at the window.
You must never get bored here...
But what...
Are you crazy? You're hurting me!
- And you hurt me.
- Get out of here!
Get out at once! I have
no intention to speak with you!
I have thought about it a lot.
We can't go on like this, the three of us.
What are you talking about?
- Of your relationship.
- There's no relationship!
I'm in love with her.
I had foreseen that. I understand you.
And have you told her?
I didn't imagine she would like
a man of your kind,
but she found someone,
it's better than nothing.
But I don't want
you two to hide.
You have to do it in my house.
- You're joking, aren't you?
- Do you think?
Come and fuck my wife at my house.
It excites me.
I'm not dead yet...
Before meeting her, I was a poor jerk.
I didn't know that such a woman could exist.
The woman of my life.
It has to mean something...
Till death us do part.
You are sick.
Love is a disease, yes. Incurable.
How's your husband?
You really care about that?
Yes.
He's okay, he's calmer.
He isn't asking questions anymore.
"The beast in the jungle".
Is it set in Africa,
and deals with fierce beasts?
No, it is set in England
and deals with grey people
and melancholy...
I can lend it to you, if you want.
Thanks.
Is that dress new?
Do you like it?
Yes, it fits you very well.
No... No, please, turn it off.
Thanks.
Excuse me, but there's an urgent phone call.
The notary of the succession Marchand,
insists for speaking to you.
Tell him I'll call him back.
I am busy, as you can see.
Well, I better go.
No, no, why?
Your job is more important than me.
I'll call you.
Bye.
- Do you want me to turn it on?
- No, no, it is alright.
Hello?
What do you want?
Why are you calling me at this hour?
Which window?
See you.
That lady wants you
to call her back at this number.
- How long ago did she call?
- Ten minutes.
- Couldn't you pass her through to me?
- You were on a meeting.
Hello?
You were kind to call me back.
Where are you now? At work?
I have to speak to you.
Immediately?
Yes, immediately. Come here, I'll be waiting.
See you.
The weather forecasts
didn't foresee the rain?
So many unpredictable things
are happening me...
Would you like to drink something?
- A coffee?
- Yes please...
No, I'd rather have...
I don't know, something strong.
I can't find my father anymore...
my father's lighter.
- Maybe I forgot it here?
- I'll look for it.
The other time, going out of here,
it was raining. Do you remember?
And who was on the corner of the road?
My husband.
He was elegant, he wore a new shirt.
I asked him if he had an appointment,
and he answered me that... yes, with me.
He smiled.
He had booked a room in a hotel
nearby, in the district.
I sat on the bed, I didn't know what to do.
He put his hand right here, on my neck...
A violent gesture,
at first it frightened me.
but then he started caressing me,
and at the same time he stripped me.
He caressed my neck, my breasts, my thighs...
He told me tender words.
He seemed a different man.
He pushed me down
on the bed and left the light on.
He took my hand
for me to caress him
and we never left each other all night.
We found each other again.
I won't tell you the details.
On the contrary, don't spare me any detail...
His mouth... his tongue...
his fingers... his fantasies.
Sado, maso, scat...
Penetration?
Vaginal? Anal?
But what's wrong with you?
You can tell me everything
but I cannot listen to everything.
I have seen you tonight, with your husband.
The room was in front of my study.
You didn't notice, I guess.
No.
Your husband came to see me, right here.
I don't believe you.
He came here twice.
Didn't you know it?
- Why did he come here?
- To speak to me of you.
You speak to me of him,
he speaks to me of you.
And why didn't you tell me?
He wanted me to go and fuck
his wife in his house,
that's what he said.
In the end he found more exciting
to fuck her in front of my house.
Last night, at the hotel,
didn't he make a phone call?
- I don't know.
- He called me,
so I could enjoy the show.
Yes?
A client has been here for half an hour.
Should I tell him to wait?
No, tell him I'm coming.
We are over.
You look awful...
Don't let anything poison your blood.
They say that life as a couple
should be a source of happiness,
but I've lived much better
since I've been divorced.
I can watch crappy TV programmes for hours,
eating chips.
Good morning.
I wanted to give you back your book.
It doesn't suit me.
The story is touching, but it ends badly.
Have you found my lighter?
No.
This is for you.
You're very kind, thanks.
Come in, please.
- Only for two minutes, then.
- Come in.
It's our new travelling collection.
Travelling?
You can use it for shopping, if you want.
- We didn't see each other for...
- Two weeks and two days.
I shouldn't have told you
those things, last time.
I didn't want to shock you, but...
I was so happy
to have found my husband again.
At least I believed.
I understood some things,
things that hurt me.
We talked, I spoke my heart out to him
and I feel better.
I want to leave him.
You want to leave him?
What if he doesn't agree?
So much the worse for him.
I'm taking back my freedom.
It was your advice, wasn't it?
What about us? Our conversations...
There's nothing left to tell each other.
Well...
Anna!
I am happy for you to feel better.
Try to be happy.
With anyone, but happy.
Good-bye.
- Hi.
Am I too early?
- No, I've just stopped working.
- Not on Sunday!
It's good for killing time.
It feels so good. With Luc
I only ate vegetables and rice.
Why, did you eat at all?
- Jeanne...
- We broke up.
- Has he left you?
- No, I have.
He is a nonentity... such a nonentity!
Even in his arms I felt lonely.
When you and I broke up,
you told me: There are other men...
Actually there aren't so many others.
I'm sorry. Forget about it, please.
Good morning, this is the Study Faber.
Leave a message. See you.
William? It's me, Anna.
Are you in the house? No?
If you're there don't pick up.
I'm imagining you at your desk,
with the tie. No!
Not on Sunday, at least!
It's over, I have decided
to start a new life,
a lighter life.
I'm not a frightened girl anymore.
I have grown up, I think, thanks to you.
I had never felt so good with anybody else.
We could freely tell each other everything,
without cheating, without lying.
I didn't believe it was possible.
I'm leaving, away from here,
away from everything,
to try and start over.
I owe this to you as well.
I'm glad I knocked on the wrong door.
I wanted to say thanks.
Thanks for everything.
Well, here's my train.
I have to go.
Good-bye.
- Mr. Faber, are you leaving us?
- Well, it's now or never, doctor.
- How about that woman? Do you still see her?
- No, she left Paris,
- and she also left her husband.
- This proves you've succeeded.
- Succeeded?
- It is the purpose of the therapy,
to cut it off, to move.
- Good-bye, doctor.
- Mr. Faber,
we found this under the sofa.
Thanks.
5, 6, 7, 8...
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8...
No, stop, stop, stop. Pascal, stop.
That's not good.
This isn't "Swan lake",
you seem a bunch of elephants...
Once again.
With more grace, children, okay?
Straighten your backs, this way. Good...
Let's start again. In line!
5, 6, 7, 8...
Anna? Someone left you
this message. I couldn't understand well.
Thanks.
Very well...
Vivienne, your head!
We can meet there tomorrow
at eleven o'clock, if it's okay.
Don't forget to bring
the report of your incomes,
we'll need it.
It's alright, agreed. See you tomorrow. Bye.
Good morning.
You came...
The message said that someone
had something for me.
How did you find me?
I called your number.
- Which number?
- The weather forecasts'.
They said it would be rainy
in the north and sunny in the south.
I hesitated, then... No.
I was sure you'd go south.
Deep south, in the sun.
as when you were small,
with the beach and the scooters...
Do you remember all?
The question is "Why? ".
Why have I looked for you everywhere?
I missed our appointments.
So did I.
So? Where were we?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org