Previously on Siren...
Ryn's back.
Why on earth
would she come back?
We need help.
It's getting worse, isn't it?
What's happening?
They're starving them out,
Maddie.
The government's
letting it happen.
They're making it happen.
Seems a young woman assaulted
a 250-pound dock worker.
We need the people.
- Them take!
- No. No, no, no, no!
Whoa!
- Hey!
- Ryn!
Water! Now!
Any sign of them?
You?
Yes, you can trust me.
This Decker guy.
He's the one we gotta
watch out for.
AmericasCardroom.com brings poker back Million
Dollar Sunday Tournament every Sunday.
Aah!
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Maddie, you tell me
story about mother.
That's right.
Your mother is gone.
When Ryn was young,
mother died.
Sister took care of me always.
But now she is alone.
She's hungry and frightened.
Ryn.
She will be out in the night
to find food.
She's hunting?
Yes, she will hunt.
Officer Montero,
what can I do for you?
Just wanted
to give you the heads up, sir,
that the Admiral
was in looking for you.
What'd you tell him?
Nothing.
I got the feeling
you might be following up
on your... suspect,
but noticed that your trip
wasn't on the roster.
Just wanted
to let you know, sir.
I appreciate
your discretion, Montero.
I'm here to help, sir.
You see this?
The Chronicle called out
Pownall Seafood by name
for overfishing.
Your dad's gonna love that.
Yeah. Well,
he'll love it even more
when I tell him he's
gotta bring the boats in.
The government's
giving him free rein.
He's not gonna
back down so easily.
Well, I gotta give him
a good reason to.
Ryn?
It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna work it out
for you and your sister.
My sister not trust me.
Look, if we show her
we can help your people,
get them the food they need,
she'll change her mind.
We just need to be careful.
She attacked someone
at the fishery the other night.
The police could be
looking for you.
Yes... Maddie.
All right, I got one
coffee, sugar and soy.
One fish, head and tail.
All right,
I gotta get out of here.
- Maddie?
- Love you.
I love you.
Okay, so that just happened.
I got one the other day.
Where did you go last night?
You and your sister have
the same mysterious habits.
She's a bit chattier, though.
You don't like it here. I know.
Ryn.
You want to see her?
I can arrange that.
Maybe you can talk
some sense into her.
Every fishery
out there's taking advantage
of these lax regulations.
Why they gotta
single us out by name?
It's unbelievable.
We're the biggest.
Of course they're
gonna call us out.
Are you saying it's fair
that we're being portrayed
as the bad guy here?
We are the bad guy here.
But we don't have to be.
What are you sayin'?
Show them that, even though the
government is lax on conservation,
Pownall Seafood isn't.
That could be a way
to spin this.
No, I'm saying we could
actually do it.
How?
Our product does great
at warehouse groceries,
but we don't sell
to high-end natural markets.
- We're bigger than that.
- You know how much Salmon we sell to Kroger?
Yes, but do you know
how much a pound
of sustainable line-caught
Coho costs at Whole Foods?
Well, we never really romanced
those guys, the high-enders.
Eco-friendly fishing equals
a higher price per pound.
I've checked the numbers.
Our profit margin
goes up six percent.
Six percent?
That before or after
my donation to Greenpeace?
Ben?
Why don't you come to your
mother's event tonight,
her fundraiser thingy?
I can't. I got
too much stuff to do.
She just got turned down
by another clinical trial.
You know your mother
would never mention it,
but her spirits
are pretty low, and...
Well, I know that having you and
Doug there would give her a boost.
Come, and in the meantime,
I promise you,
I'll really think
about what you said here.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Thanks for the call.
How'd she end up here?
I went out and found her.
What is up with you and them?
Well, maybe
they sense my empathy.
The perpetual outsider.
How do you know
so much about them?
There's something
you're not telling us.
There's a lot
I'm not telling you.
Like what? Helen, you need...
Should we be worried?
No more fight.
A tea party?
It's chamomile.
Might calm them down.
Why don't we all sit?
Go.
I talk to sister.
Are you sure?
Go.
Let's let them
work it out alone.
In my apartment?
Damn.
How can I help you?
I'm looking for Ben Pownall.
He's not here today.
Do you know
where I might find him?
Can I ask who's asking?
A fellow biologist
interested in his work
in Steller feeding patterns.
Ben's the man for that for sure.
Yeah. So do you know
when he'll be back?
Not today.
He's got a thing.
A thing?
Yeah. Some big old
charity hoo-ha thing
his parents are throwing.
Thank you.
I'll try back later.
They will help us.
Ben and Maddie.
They will bring back our food.
I see his face
in that place take our food.
That was not him.
That was his father.
Ben will help.
No!
You help him,
not me.
You try to kill him.
So I help.
You
like human.
You...
like...
human.
Drugs.
- Ya think?
- Yeah.
But it must be somethin' new.
Young women, small stature,
similar crimes.
These two might have been
on the same crank.
Tweaked out and flyin' high.
There's some connection here.
Since when does it take two
days to fix an intake manifold?
Mechanics charge by the hour.
Yeah, well, it sucks.
I mean, I just get back to work,
and then your dad's
engine conks out.
Well, sucks worse for my dad.
- That's him.
- Who?
The guy from the military place.
What, the guy
that found you in Alaska?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
What the hell is he doin' here?
And you're sure it was him?
Like Jesus himself, man.
What's he doin' in town?
You think he's lookin' for me?
If he was, you'd know about it.
Tell him what you told me.
Yeah. So, well, in Alaska,
this Decker, he's askin' all
about this psycho nurse, right?
And then as he's leavin', he...
leans in and he...
he asks if she sang to me?
Sang?
Yeah.
Sang.
I mean, this guy's
a total weirdo, right?
I gotta take a leak, all right?
So, you know when I told you
that this... this Decker guy's
after my mermaid?
Yeah, I got
your drunk message, man.
Well, you gotta
ask yourself why.
I mean, why is he here
in Bristol Cove?
I mean, what's he doin'?
So here's my, crazy
not-so-crazy answer.
Decker's here
because the mermaid is here.
He was writing
about the possibility
of aquatic humanoids all the
way back in the nineties.
This is the guy, Maddie.
I know it.
Bounced around several
universities until 2008.
And then?
Nada. Just disappeared.
Okay, so those schools didn't want
Decker and his mermaid theories,
but the Navy did.
I mean, he went all the way
to Alaska to look for Donna.
Now he shows up
in Bristol Cove? Why?
You think he knows she's here?
He's got to, right?
He's connected
to the overfishing, too.
Maddie?
He's not gonna stop
until he finds her.
Babe.
What is it?
Decker asked Chris
if she sang to him.
Sang?
It's something they do.
You know the myths
about a Siren song, right?
Only it's not a song exactly.
It gets inside your head.
I don't know, maybe it's
some kind of defense mechanism.
How do you know all this?
Because Ryn did it to me
the night we met.
And you're
just telling me this now?
I'm sorry.
It was...
I wasn't sure what it meant,
and I'm still not.
What did it feel like?
Honestly, like a drug.
I can't explain it.
It's like something I need.
Would you mind going over
and getting a cup of water?
Your mom's not gonna
be happy to see me.
I totally ditched her
at lunch the other day.
No. I'm sure she's
already forgotten about it.
Yeah, 'cause that's her M.O.?
And I think that was you.
I'm gonna need to hit the bar.
Okay.
Ben! Good to see you.
Bourbon, please.
Hi, Maddie.
Hey, Mr. Pownall.
Call me Ted, please.
Beautiful party...
Ted.
Elaine puts on a hell of a show.
How's your dad doin'?
He's okay.
Been down in Forks with my aunt.
Thanks. She's sick.
Well, sorry to hear that.
That explains the spike
in crime around here.
Excuse me.
Hey, Mom.
Hi, Ben.
- It's so good to see you.
- You, too.
I want you to meet someone.
I was just talking
to the most brilliant doctor.
It's such a coincidence.
He's a marine biologist, too,
and he loves Chopin.
Aldon Decker.
Ben Pownall.
We go back a long way,
your dad and I.
The night Elaine and I
had our accident,
he was the first one
on the scene.
Did you know that?
- He never told me that.
- No? Well, he was.
He didn't leave my side.
He stayed up with me
all night at the hospital
while Elaine was in surgery.
That sounds like him.
He's a good man, your dad.
He says the same thing
about you.
Dr. Decker was just telling
me about his research.
Your mother's referring to a rare
marine creature I discovered recently.
A marine creature?
Its stem cells are remarkable.
Maybe now is not the time.
No. No, no, dear.
It sounds fascinating.
Please go on.
Well, I injected the DNA cells
from the specimen
into a group of paralytic rats.
In the weeks since,
the control rats have all died
due to complications
from the paralysis.
But the others,
the ones I injected
the creature DNA with,
every one of them
regained their mobility.
Mom, need anything?
Apparently some
of those stem cells.
Your home
not here.
In the water.
We will die,
all of us.
No food. We need them.
You need them.
I know man do this to you,
but not Ben.
Not Maddie.
No human help me.
They...
hurt!
Pain!
And you,
sister,
choose them.
They do this to you?
I hunt at top of water.
You follow.
I am sorry.
Sorry?
So your mother told me that
you have a graduate degree
from the University
of Washington,
that you interned with some
of the top marine biologists.
You shouldn't
have said that to her.
Said what?
There's no magic bullet
to cure paralysis,
and you dangling that out
in front of her is not okay.
I'm sorry.
My apologies.
Look, you seem
like a smart young man,
and my research would
greatly benefit your mother.
If you could just
help me with my work.
Beer, please.
I know why you're in town,
and I know what you want.
I doubt that very much.
Thank you.
I know what she did to you.
H... How do you know?
Excuse the interruption,
but Mom's about to get acknowledged
for her fundraising prowess
in T-minus ten.
Sure, Doug, I'm comin'.
Mom comes first.
Sidney, you gotta
get to the church.
Shelter doors close at ten.
It's warm. I'm sleeping out.
I've seen that girl.
She's been around town.
Where?
In the alley one night
with some kids.
Who?
I'm not sure,
but I remember her,
because a while back,
I saw her up on the North Star.
McClure's boat?
Yeah.
One morning I saw her
sniffin' around.
Thanks, Sidney.
Remind me to come
to you first next time.
- Decker's here.
- What?
Yeah. He's looking for Donna.
Ben, he's dangerous.
You think he knows about Ryn?
It doesn't seem like it.
This guy's... We don't know
what he's capable of.
We just gotta stay
one step ahead of him.
Hey, have you seen Dr. Decker?
I was just about
to go look for him.
Excuse me.
Elaine.
Um, Mrs. Pownall, about lunch.
I know we didn't get off
to the best start...
Maddie. Maddie, don't worry.
I just want what's best
for my son.
Just tell me,
do you know where she is?
Maybe.
You need to bring me to her.
Please, right now.
I'd like to help you, really.
I would.
But I need something
from you first.
You do realize
I have the power of
the military behind me?
If all you needed to do
was snap your fingers
and the government
showed up to help you,
then why haven't they?
I think you want
to find her, right?
But you don't want
them to find her.
I think we can make a deal.
You and me.
Stop it.
Call it off.
Starving them, the lures,
whatever else you got planned,
stop it all right now.
That's a big ask.
Hardly comparable.
Really?
'Cause I know what it's like
to have her inside your head.
You can't sleep,
you can't think
about anything else.
She sang to you, too?
Hello, Helen.
You scared me, dear.
How's everything goin' up there?
I haven't heard anything break.
What's wrong?
My sister
is strong.
A hunter,
but this man,
he hurt her.
She will be better
once she's away from him.
No.
Not better.
Sometimes...
something inside you
gets broken,
and no matter what you do,
it can't be fixed.
The feeling stays with you.
You want to see her again?
Tell me what's
going on out there.
Okay.
There's a government trawler
off the coast
of Bristol Cove right now,
out past the Northern Break.
We starve them to the surface,
the lures will attract them,
and the trawler will
start harvesting them.
When?
Tonight.
Hello.
Are Ryn and Donna still there?
Yes. Why? What's goin' on?
All right, listen to me.
Do not let them go out, okay?
There's a man looking for them.
Ryn's sister needs
to get back to the water.
We'll deal with it
as soon as we get there.
Can you just put Ryn on?
It's for you.
Hello? Yes.
Ryn, it's not safe outside.
You need to stay inside.
That man from the lab,
he's here at the party.
- Man?
- Yes!
The bad man who hurt Donna.
He's here. He's looking for her.
You have to stay
at Helen's, okay?
Ryn!
Okay, yes.
Thank you.
Where's my damn mermaid?
Excuse me?
Let me refresh your memory.
Your goons stole her.
From my boat, the North Star?
You have me mistaken
with somebody else.
Here's what I think.
You took my friend Chris
and the mermaid to your place,
lab, prison, whatever it was,
then Chris,
he manages to get out.
Takes that crazy nurse with him,
drives her all the way
to Libbey Beach.
Then, poof!
That nurse disappeared,
and then you,
you spend a whole month
tracking Chris down to Alaska
to ask him about her.
Why?
It's 'cause I think...
I think that that nurse
is the mermaid.
There's no mermaid.
There never was.
- Bullshit.
- A deformed cetacean.
I know what I saw!
Do you?
You believe you caught something
that never in man's 50,000 years
of sailing the ocean's
ever been corroborated.
No one knew there were cavemen,
either, until they did.
No mermaid's skeleton's
ever been found.
No dead one's ever
floated up to the surface.
In fact, there's no evidence
of their existence whatsoever.
That doesn't mean
they're not real.
'Cause you caught one, right?
A live one.
Xander McClure
from Bristol Cove.
Yeah.
And now she's cavorting,
around town with your friends,
driving in cars with them.
Hmph!
You must be a very,
very special man, Mr. McClure.
And have
some very special friends.
Where'd he go?
I don't know.
I'll check outside.
I'm bringin' in the boats.
What?
I asked Marty
to run the numbers,
and you were right...
Six percent.
And it'll help
improve our image.
If I'm gonna be in the paper,
it damn well better be
for something good.
Thanks, Dad.
- Doug?
- No problem.
Hey, Mom?
Have you seen Dr. Decker?
Um, I'm sure he's around,
but, um, would you sit with me?
Please?
Yeah, of course. Of course.
I was turned down again
for another clinical trial.
Did you dad tell you?
Yeah. I'm so sorry.
Did you have something to do
with Dr. Decker coming to town?
Me? No.
Well, he's very enthusiastic
about his research,
but I want you to know,
I don't need it.
- Mom.
- No, I... Let me finish, okay?
I know I'm never
getting out of this chair,
and I'm okay with it,
but I'm really, really touched
that you still
want to help me, Ben.
I thought you'd given up on me.
- Hi.
- Hello.
I'll see you later.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Maddie? Sorry.
- Excuse me.
- What? Sorry.
It's you.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm so sorry
about what happened.
I never meant to hurt you.
I should have found
a better way to study you.
Please just give me
one more chance.
What's happening?
There's two of you?
What's goin' on?!
- Ryn?
- He hurt my sister!
Please. I'm not gonna
hurt you, I promise.
Aah! Aah!
Ryn! Stop!
No, Ryn! Wait!
No! I kill him.
He hurt my sister!
I know. I know he did.
Please!
Ryn? Ryn, wait, please!
You want it to stop?
Call it off!
Whatever's goin' on
out there, stop it!
- Bring in that trawler!
- Ryn, think!
It's not just you
and Donna in danger!
- It's all of you!
- Make the call!
Call!
Admiral, I don't have
time to explain.
Just call in the trawler, now.
Sir, I wouldn't be asking...
Put it on speaker!
It's in motion.
We're not pulling back.
No chance.
You've done a fine job.
- I'm sorry.
- Tonight all that hard work pays off.
No, no, no!
Ryn, Ryn, Ryn! Wait!
You can't kill him!
- Move!
- No.
Why you help the bad man?
- Move!
- No, no, no.
You choose him.
No. Ryn.
You should choose me!
Are you okay?
They can't go back in the water.
The Navy, it's out there.
My favorite part of the evening.
Are you bringing in the boats
to make Ben happy?
I'm bringing in the boats because
if I don't try something new,
I'm gonna become the old guard.
And there's only one end
to the old guard.
Well, I'm happy to hear it.
Ben's got some good ideas.
He does.
I like that girl of his, too.
Maddie.
You do know that's
Dale Bishop's step-daughter?
I do.
I also think she's smart,
she has spunk.
Spunk?
Okay, Mr. Cleaver.
In fact, she kind of reminds
me of a younger you.
You should invite her
to lunch again.
Why would I do that?
Because we like
havin' Ben around,
and Ben likes havin' her around.
Bittersweet that song.
When the darkness comes.
You See?
What?
What we learn in the water
about humans.
It is right.
No.
Yes!
I kill all.
On land, in water.
All.
No!
No?
Kill the bad ones, yes.
Not the good.
You choose human
over me.
I choose not to kill.
Go!
Now!
No.
Bittersweet that song.
When the darkness comes.
Let a sweet thing go.
When the darkness falls.
Hey, yo, Chris!
Finish up, man, come on!
Let's go!
Dude, that's her, man.
That's the nurse! Look!
Look!
Hey.
Hey, Hey! Stop!
Stop!
Come on, stop!
Stop! Just wait up!
Just wait a minute!
Stop!
Stop right there! Wait! Wait!
Hey, stop!
Yo, Chris!
What's the deal with Calvin?
I don't know.
It keeps goin' voicemail.
He's at Janine's.
Just get over there and pull
his naked ass outta bed.
Yeah, yeah, I'm on it.
Hey, it's Ben.
Leave me a message.
Yo, Ben.
What I told you earlier, I...
I was right, man.
Man, I saw her!
Just, um, get down here,
all right?
We're gonna go get her.
- What?
- Aw, Xander's goin' out there, too,
hunting them.
You think Ryn
went back in the water?
I don't know.
I have to get out there.
Now without me, you're not.
She might come back.
One of us has to stay.
Stop right there!