There's a source
- on their Third Floor.
- Strategy.
They say he's been
feeding Pope for years now.
You trust
this man's intelligence?
He has never been wrong.
If Shadow is real,
everything is compromised.
They created a vacancy.
A hightraffic position.
Director level.
Found your little stash.
Thanks for the intel.
You know, we could
help each other.
The Office are watching me,
but they're not watching you.
What about Ian?
Stay the fuck away from her.
I'm sorry.
About what happened
to your other.
I care about you,
and I would never
let anyone hurt you.
You're moving pouches
for Lambert?
To a specific location?
I need the address, Edgar.
A mansion. Potsdam.
Hey!
Okay?
Okay, okay.
Customs.
Why does it always
break down at Customs?
Prince's best work in years.
But you do know he's no longer
alive over there, right?
Now, what do you think
would happen
if this fucking album
were to find its way across?
Ian, please...
We are tasked with safeguarding
the most important
fucking secret
in the history of mankind.
I'm broke.
My kid is sick.
Jovey.
You think I care
about your family?
Here's the code.
Don't, please!
Fuck up the code,
you get fucked up.
Yeah?
Do you remember Edgar Brandt?
That embassy courier
we had on a wiretap.
He was talking too much
to his girlfriends.
Yeah, what about him?
Heard him make a call tonight,
crying about getting shaken
down by Emily for some address.
- Address?
- She was with Howard Silk.
What do you want
to do with them?
Black room. Three months.
No, Ian! Please don't do this!
He doesn't show up.
I cannot work like this.
He comes and goes as he pleases.
This is unacceptable.
Director, are you listening?
Hehe has not been in for days.
- Who?
- Howard Silk.
It was my impression
you were sending someone
to lighten my load.
- Should I be drafting a complaint?
- What?
Should I be drafting a complaint
about Howard Silk?
No, no, don't, no.
I'll, um...
I'll take care of it.
Thank you.
- I'm going out.
- What about your 2:00?
You're alive.
Sorry, I wasn't sure.
I've been busy.
How's your
internal search going?
Brilliantly well.
There's a mole in Strategy.
It's official.
We confirmed it with a source.
Yeah, no shit.
Do you know what section?
No, Aldrich's
looking into it now.
And if you don't start
coming into work,
he's gonna start
looking at you, too.
Is that what you want?
What's this?
This is what Emily
was working on.
Stolen internal documents,
taken from your office,
passed to the outside.
- This is my floor code.
- Yes, it is.
These documents were stolen
from my department?
Yes. As I said, you have a mole.
And when were you planning
on showing me these?
How about right now?
And what about Baldwin?
We will find Baldwin.
This is more important.
You find out
who those came from,
I'm gonna keep going
through all this.
I'll be at the Walcot Hotel.
Not spending another minute
in that office.
You know it's my birthday today?
Supposed to be hosting
a dinner party tonight.
Friends, colleagues.
Who knows? Probably inviting
this mole into my house.
Yeah.
Look into those memos.
Don't you worry,
I'm playing my part.
Play yours.
Ja.
Best pudding in Berlin,
don't you think?
Roast the hazelnuts inhouse.
It's always the little things.
Bit strange...
seeing him
with nothing pithy to say.
Maybe he's having an offday.
Hear the good news, Howard?
Lieber.
Doctor says his knee
won't need any pins.
The limp he'll have to live
with, but no more surgery.
You never did apologize,
did you?
I don't think Howard's sorry
for what he did.
But don't take it personally.
He's a worldclass prick
to everyone.
You followed me here
just to bust my balls?
I want to talk about
Edgar Brandt, the courier.
Been on the phone
whining about you and Em
twisting his arm
about some address.
What are you two looking for?
Maybe you should talk to her.
No, Howard.
It's about time
you and me had a real chat.
Ian said you're trying
to go back to work.
Well, you know
what a shitty patient I am.
No sugar, thank you.
- Since when?
- New study.
High blood cholesterol levels.
Sugar's the culprit.
I'd inherit it from Dad.
Well, that is the only thing
you're gonna inherit
from your dad.
Has he been acting strange
to you lately?
Well...
He did show some...
natural concern
for my wellbeing.
Fuck, Mom.
When you finally decided
to leave him,
it was like any obligation I had
to feel anything for him
had lifted.
And now... I can't believe
I'm going to say this...
But I'm worried about him.
I went to see him yesterday.
What did you talk about?
Everything.
I opened up, and he listened.
He seemed actually
interested in my life.
Maybe he's trying to atone?
You shouldn't put too much stock
into that, you know.
Mom, I promised myself
a long time ago
I was done giving him chances
to disappoint me.
Yeah. Keep that promise.
Sooner or later,
he will be back to his old self.
Clare!
How are you, Ingrid?
Have you brightened your hair?
Thank God for you.
First person to notice.
We'll be seeing you later?
Yes, sure. I can't wait.
- Bye.
Act normal, or I snap your neck.
Look at this place.
Ten euro.
So fucking expensive.
- What do you want from me?
- I finish the job.
Then you pay me,
and I disappear.
- Nadia...
- You do not get to call me that.
You tried to have me killed.
I had no choice.
They put me in a corner.
I'm sorry.
Is this real?
Your shopping and your house
and your little family?
- Why are you doing this?
- To be free.
You escaped. You are free.
100,000 euro...
What you promised.
I finish the contracts, you pay.
Are you mad? They want you dead.
They need me to finish.
If I do, you'll get the money.
Yeah.
I pity you.
Nothing you are is true.
Early.
Punctual.
You seem nervous.
Terrified.
Howard, you remember Kaspar.
Please keep movement
to a minimum.
It's now or never.
No, thanks. Not hungry.
You have no idea
what you're missing.
Read, each card carefully.
"Fred specialized in the job
of making very quaint wax toys."
Next card.
"Five wine experts
jokingly quizzed
- "sample Chablis."
- Next.
"Six big devils from Japan
quickly forgot how to waltz."
Time for new pangrams, mate.
We're ready.
You know the drill, Howard.
I'm going to ask questions.
Starting back at the embassy.
The hour you had with Emily...
What did you two discuss
after I left?
I don't remember.
Not in the mood
to cook up a story?
I just don't remember.
Before she and I left,
you told her to light a candle
at St. Christopher's.
It was a coded exchange.
What did it mean?
I don't know.
May I have a word
with you, please?
Everything's steady.
Not even a pupillary response.
His defenses are getting better.
Best he's ever been.
I can't keep giving handouts.
No. I can pay.
Here. For the other day.
Thank you for being kind.
Yo, an espresso.
Do you know where that is?
Yeah.
It's a beach in Croatia.
Do you like it? I took it.
I like it.
Thank you. I'm Greta.
Nadia.
You're new to the city?
Yes.
Cash like that, you can go
to any restaurant.
Coffee is good here.
No, it's not.
What do you do
while you're here?
Nothing. Just work.
And what do you do for fun?
Well, if you like to hang out,
there's this allday party.
You should check it out.
It's fun.
Is your name Lamar Jung?
Sorry, do we know each other?
I was a colleague
of an old friend of yours.
Walter Atwood.
He was a director at my office.
You knew Walter.
Can we talk?
Please, come in.
I don't recall you being
at Walter's funeral.
He was private,
as a married man.
How well did you know him?
Well enough to know.
Well, at least we can
dispel with the pretense.
You know, you're the first
of his colleagues
who's ever come to me.
Five years after he died.
Why wait until now?
He was 49 years old
and died of a heart attack.
- Right?
- Yes.
The stress of that job.
I used to tell him
he needed to slow down.
Do you remember anything
he was troubled by back then?
It's been years. I mean...
The usual pressures...
He used to complain
he was being pushed out
of his position.
Paranoia.
He was always inferring
he was being watched.
- Watched?
- Yeah.
I just thought he was stressed.
Do you remember
when you last saw him?
I was supposed to see him
that day, Hotel Concorde.
I was...
sitting in that room, waiting.
Walter was always
the one to call.
That was the arrangement.
I didn't find out
until the obituary, days later.
Until then, I just thought
it was his way of ending things.
Are you saying we should be
suspicious about Walter's death?
No.
I'm just tying up loose ends.
I don't know how to do this.
I know you give him
these numbers
so he can contact you
when he's in trouble.
I think you should come over.
Thank you
for letting me come in today.
I realize you've been
talking to Ian, but...
I thought you should
hear it from me.
I confess that,
I have been having some
personal difficulties lately.
Yeah. I know.
And, recently,
it's been getting worse.
So, what am I supposed
to say here, Emily?
I mean, you've been
with the department how long?
You're an institution.
And you do all of this
with impunity,
going over my head
whenever you want.
Yes, I'm very sorry about that.
So, you tell me, Emily,
how am I supposed to react?
Well, you did mention
the possibility
of my having some time off
to get my life in order,
and I think you're right.
Take whatever time you need.
Thank you.
How did that go?
Well, should keep Personnel
off my ass for a little bit.
You look like
you had a rough night.
These boys in Records,
with their posturing
and their competitive drinking.
Could barely hide
their erections.
And did you dig
as deep as you could?
To the very bottom.
We closed the bar.
My condolences.
Look, that address in Potsdam,
none of them has ever
seen or heard of it.
State records say
it's privately owned.
Not by us.
Sorry. Wish I could've found
something better.
Nothing's something.
By the way, I saw Ian
coming through this morning.
He had your ex with him.
He was heading into Oversight.
What's your trick, Howard?
Lying like you do,
so comfortably.
My trick?
Maybe I just really don't kno.
You've dragged Emily
into a mess.
First, it was
that rendition bullshit.
Nearly got her killed.
And now this.
The address you got from Edgar,
what are you two looking for?
I'll tell you
what I'm looking for.
How 'bout
a damn good explanation
why I'm professionally obligated
to tell you anything,
other than "fuck off"?
Look, what you do over there
is not my purview.
Section Two, fine.
But this, here, this is my turf.
Now, what am I missing,
you fuck?
Boy, she really has a type,
doesn't she?
- You think this is funny?
- Well, I mean, look at it.
A few years ago, she leaves me,
a colossal asshole,
by all accounts.
She's free from the worst
husband anyone can conjure.
And what does she do? She runs
off with a guy like you.
A guy like me?
Yeah, the whole
tough guy routine.
It's another version
of the same thing.
Fuck you.
Hit a nerve, did I?
You actually think
we have something in common?
You, always fleeing this life
for the promise of another.
You think we're alike?
I'm a pretty good judge.
Then where were you, Howard?
Where were you years ago,
when she was at her worst,
bottoming out on detox?
Where the hell were you then,
if we're so alike?
I was there.
Sat by her bedside,
reading to her every night.
When everyone else in her life
had given up on her,
I was there.
You've not one inkling
of what it was like
for her and I.
You couldn't begin
to understand.
Now, take some responsibility
for once in your fucking life.
- I'm trying to.
- Good.
Now, what's this address?
You're just wasting time.
You're gonna get her killed.
I would never let that happen!
Do you still love
your exwife, Howard?
Emily, you can't go in there.
Ridiculous!
- Turn this thing off.
- No! Please be careful with that.
Outside now, please.
Have you completely
taken leave of your senses?
Just trying to get
a few things straight.
You bring him in here,
give him a lie exam
- in front of the whole Office?
- You're defending him now?
If you have a question,
you come to me.
I did.
At the hospital.
You told me you would
lay low for a while,
that we'd do
this thing together.
That's what we agreed.
What's changed
between then and now?
He's helping me
with my investigation.
- Are you fucking serious?
- You see? I tell you the truth,
and then you shut me down.
Let me in, Em.
I'm yours first.
What's the address?
It's a house in Potsdam.
Doesn't belong to the Office,
at least not officially.
Edgar is carrying orders
between that house
and the embassy over there.
Max, call your brother.
Get him to bring some mates.
We're going to Potsdam.
Him, too.
I want to order
the lunch special.
And I'd like it delivered.
Yes?
Have I reached the dry cleaners?
No. This has never been
the dry cleaners.
I beg your pardon.
I must've dialed
the wrong number.
Hi.
Are you okay?
You don't normally do
this kind of thing, do you?
I don't like it.
Do you mind if I... if I ask
what happened to your...?
Sorry.
I was with someone, too.
She used to hurt me.
That's a long time ago.
What did you do?
Run.
Came here.
New city, new life.
Fuck her, right?
Lots of people run like that.
It's normal.
Can I?
You took all of these?
Yeah.
It's a hobby.
I like to travel.
I think I would like to travel.
Stay.
It's okay. Sleep.
Nadia.
He left this for you.
Why did they do that to him...
Remove his fingers, his teeth?
They do that so the police
can't identify the body.
But they have his name.
Not his real name.
He talked to me, you know.
He told me what you are.
Spies.
You work for Russia?
The United States?
It's better that you don't know.
You're alive because he kept you
far enough away from all this.
Then why do you help me?
Because he was my friend.
Listen, you need to call
the police.
Tell them you found him
that way.
Don't tell them about the money.
Okay, put this away.
I don't even know who he was.
Did you love him?
It was a lie.
No.
My wife... kept things from me.
Secrets.
When I found out, I...
You want my advice?
If you loved him, truly...
you have to love the lie.
I'm sorry to have to
ask you this right now.
Did you see anything,
in the last two or three days,
unusual?
Anyone you didn't recognize
talking to him?
I need to find out who did this.
You were the only one
who talked to him.
And that handsome young man
you came here with.
What the hell are...
Who the fuck is this?
- What the fuck are you doing?!
- Go!
- How many of these are there?
- What are you talking about?
The hookers... what, do you
fucking keep a rotation?
No. How...?
Do you talk about work
with them?
Of course I don't talk about
fucking work with them, Howard.
How stupid do you think I am?
What is this about?
- Sit down.
- Howard!
Sit the fuck down!
The butcher...
My friend... is dead.
Now, I have gone
to great lengths
to cultivate my network
on this side,
to keep them safe.
I do not expose them.
You and I were the only ones
who went to see him.
Okay, Howard,
you don't think that I...
I'll tell you
what I fucking think.
I think you better
dig hard and fucking fast
to find this mole.
Because whoever is getting
information from your floor,
they're getting it from you.
Do your fucking job.
What the hell?
Do you see that?
You sure this is
the right address?
Something's wrong.
Max.
I hear you visited our daughter.
Stay here.
See if you can find that low
profile we were talking about.
Would he go?
Ian, give me a gun.
Em, what is this?
I don't know.
Darling, are you home?
Just putting her to bed.
I've got some work to finish
before the guests arrive.
I'll be in the study.
Come in.
Sit.
We need to speak.
I visited an old friend
of Walter Atwood's today.
You remember Walter?
Yeah, former deputy director.
He died.
This friend, Lamar Jung,
was his lover.
Yeah, Atwood kept it
from friends and family.
I remember something
about him coming out,
after the heart attack.
What?
Alice was right. There's a mole.
And it's worse than we though.
According to his lover,
Atwood felt
he was being followed.
Weeks before his death.
Atwood died of a heart attack.
Natural causes.
It's impossible to induce that
without putting up
warning signs.
Not impossible.
They killed one of ours
to make room for one of theirs.
And we missed it all this time.
You do realize who replaced him?
He's the perfect spy.
Wellconnected.
Married, smart.
Protected by family up high.
It's Quayle.
It's been him all this time.
So, what are we gonna do
about him?
How was your day, birthday boy?
It was fine.
- Something wrong?
- No, no.
I'm just, I'm jjust exhausted.
Right.
Well, you have
a long night ahead.
Do you mind getting the steak
out of the oven?
I've asked people to start
showing up at 8:00.