HELL
(EL NARCO)
- I'm leaving, Ma.
- Take care of yourself.
Pedro.
- I love you cabrón.
- Don't worry.
As soon as I make a few bucks,
I'll come back for you.
20 YEARS LATER...
Through my mom, I'm Mexican,
By destiny, I am American,
I'm from the golden race,
I'm Mexican American.
I understand English,
But I also speak Spanish,
I'm from the noble race,
I'm Mexican American.
Your money, man.
Gimme your money or I'll kill you.
Come on.
You have it there, your dough, I know it.
Give it, give it.
And the watch.
Zacatecas to Minnesota,
From Tijuana to New York,
The sun and earth countries,
I defend them with my honor.
Two languages and two countries,
Two cultures that I have,
I'm proud of my luck,
For it's God will.
Shit.
How are you, Ma?
I'm Benjamin.
Don't you recognize me?
Benjamin!
Son of a bitch!
Thanks, Ma.
The thing I missed most
about Mexico was your food.
I was sick of
hot dogs and cheeseburgeres.
I really can't believe you.
20 years on the other side and
you didn't even send a dollar.
I thought you were dead.
You were right, Ma.
But if you saw how bad it was.
Have you heard from your father?
I went out to see if he passed by
in the street, but...
The U.S. is such a big place, Ma.
Like father, like son.
Hey, where is Pedro?
Did he go to start working in San Miguel?
No.
Your brother was killed like a dog!
He hung out with the wrong crowd,
and one day he was shot.
They killed him, Ma?
But...
Why didnt you tell me!?
Ah! So now you're
interested in your little brother?
But in 20 years you didn't
even send a postcard.
At least to know where you were!
My Bro!
If you had kept your promise,
he'd still be with us today.
My brother.
- What happened?
- Don't you know?
This is our daily bread.
Remember that we are at war.
War?
Take a good look at those kids.
That's how the assholes start.
Once they start, these idiots.
They'll both end up like him.
Move, Benja, the cops are coming.
Hurry, let's go.
Come on, Ma, let's go.
We have nothing to do here.
Good morning, ma'am.
- Yes, young man?
- I wanted to ask you.
Do you know what happened
to the tire repair shop next door?
- Ah, the Garcia's one?
- Yes
About eight years ago they moved...
...to the new highway, I think at 18 km.
Right next to a junkyard.
And do you know if Rogaciano Garcia
still owns it?
Not that I know.
Everything is so different, isn't it?
Why so many questions?
You from around here?
Don't you recognize me?
It's me, Benjamin Garcia.
Benny.
I was a friend of your son, Beto.
No wonder you looked familiar.
And where is Beto?
I just came from the other side
and would love to see him.
We buried him six years ago.
Oh, ma'am.
Sorry, and may God rest his soul.
And Spirit.
And don't you want to know
how my boy died?
It was your brother, El Diablo,
that killed him.
My brother?
So, if you're planning to stay around here,
be very careful, asshole.
Thanks for the heads up, ma'am...
...and... I repeat: I'm truly sorry.
You can't feel sorrier than I do.
Cochiloco, guess who's back in San Miguel.
How can I help you?
Sorry, Mr., but... "No english."
What is happening Godfather?
Don't you remember your
favorite godson anymore?
What a sight for sore eyes, godson!
Look at you!
You look like shit, you damned pocho!
Look who's talking, Godfather.
Just because I'm so happy to see you...
...I won't beat the shit out of you
like when you were a kid.
Let me get some beers to celebrate.
CRISIS AND VIOLENCE
DEVASTATE THE COUNTRY
Had I known about this,
I'd have stayed on the other side.
You have no idea what
this country has become.
It couldn't be worse than
when I left, Godfather.
Just imagine. Crisis, unemployment...
...violence.
This year there are around 13,000 dead.
Almost, like a Civil War, all against all.
Just like a curse.
Yeah, but tell me how you are.
How were you treated by the gringos?
20 years is a long time, isn't it?
Didn't you make loads of cash?
That... Godfather...
What can I tell you?
Godfather, what do you
know about my brother?
I heard so many things...
The last that I heard,
he left your mother's ranch.
He was sick of being poor.
He came to San Miguel, and got
involved with the wrong crowd...
Very, very bad folks.
Drug dealers, addicts, murderers.
Everyone knew him as El Diablo.
- No kidding?
- Yes
And he became so famous
that everyone feared him.
Until, one day he turned up dead.
They say he was shot 60 times.
60 times!?
- And who killed him?
- It could have been anyone.
In this town they'll kill you for any reason.
Who can tell me more
about what happened?
Your brother lived with a woman
around the time he was killed.
She's called Guadalupe Soliz.
And she works at the Salon Mexico.
A fucking cesspool...
...with a shit reputation in the
Red Light District of San Miguel.
A whore?
Hey!
Are you alone or expecting someone?
I just want "a beer".
- Only one beer?
- Oh, yes.
Gloria!
Move your ass! Bring the Señor a beer.
Sit.
Hello handsome.
Won't you buy me a drink?
Some other day, darling.
But I wanted to ask you...
...if by chance you know
Señora Guadalupe Soliz.
Lupe?
I'll see if she's busy,
and if not I'll send her over.
What's up, honey?
What can I do for you?
Sit down, beautiful.
Can I get you something to drink?
I'm busy just now.
But if you hold on then I'll
take care of you.
No, it's not like that.
I am Benjamin Garcia.
Benny. I'm Pedro's brother.
I don't know if he told you
something about me.
So you're the famous Benny.
I only just found out about what
happened to my brother and...
...I wonder if you can tell me
anything about it.
I can already imagine how it must
have been for you to hear that news.
I'd love to talk, but I can't do it now.
You know, I'll give you my address.
I'm done around 8:00 p.m.
If you want to we can meet then.
What are you doing with my woman,
motherfucker?
Take it easy, babe, he's a relative.
- He was just leaving, right?
- Yes
Hey, brother-in-law.
Here's the address.
Take care of yourself.
What do you want, man?
I'm looking for Mrs. Lupita.
She lives here, right?
She's not here now.
Besides, dickhead, you should know...
...that she doesn't take
customers at home.
Take it easy, pal. I'm a not customer.
I'm Benjamin Garcia.
- Her brother-in-law.
- Uncle Benny.
From the U.S.?
I am also called Benjamin,
I am your nephew!
Come on in, Uncle, don't stand there.
My mom'll be here soon. Come in.
Do you want anything to drink?
No, I better wait until your Ma arrives.
Sit down Uncle, do don't stand around.
Sit down.
Listen only,
It is true that you got rich there "Gringolandia"?
My Pa said that you were
making piles of cash.
More or less.
But tell me about yourself.
How did you get along with your father?
- Do you remember him?
- Of course.
My father was the most badass dude
in this damn town.
They say he was great with girls...
...and even better with guns.
And they say he killed
more than 20 fuckers.
Well, I'd rather hear about you.
How old are you?
Me? 16.
Stop being such a liar.
Actually I'm 14, but I look older, right?
What grade are you in?
Better not talk about that, Uncle.
School's not really for me.
Ever wonder what you'll be
when you grow up?
Of course. What else?
A fuckin' badass like my father.
Hi mom.
Look who's here.
Uncle Benny, the father's brother,
from the United States.
Yes, we already met.
And you guys too?
Yes Benjamin and I were
talking about a few things.
Right.
You did finish your homework?
Sure mom, Uncle Benny helped me.
Right, Uncle?
Yeah, right.
You think you can fool me like that?
Well, get to sleep.
It's late.
See you, Uncle, I have to be going.
See you later, and we'll have some brews.
- Ok, I'm hanging around here for a while.
- Ok then.
How is it possible that my brother...
...could end up that way?
Oh, when I met your brother,
he was a complete asshole.
But despite it all,
I always loved him a lot.
You know who killed him?
No idea.
Your brother had so many enemies.
It could have been anyone.
An how did my nephew take it?
He was really young When Pedro died.
But he's made him into a hero.
In fact, I am terrified that, living in this town...
...he'll want to to follow in his father's footsteps.
And do you think that what you do is...
...a good example for my nephew?
What are you talking about, idiot.
Come on, Lupita.
You think working as a whore...
...in a brothel can be good for a...
You know something Benjamin Garcia?
You're worse than your brother, asshole.
- Lupita...
Get out of here!
Get lost now! Got to hell!
Sorry Lupita. I didn't want...
Go fuck yourself, asshole!
Damn Bro.
See how you ended up, you asshole.
Drug dealer, murderer...
...pimp, and killed worse than a mongrel.
But I swear the by the Virgin of Guadalupe.
I'll... I'll try help your wife...
...to raise your your kid so he can get ahead.
Things happen for a reason, Bro.
I swear that with God as my witness...
This time I won't let you down.
And may I end up in hell if I don't.
Hey, Godson.
And Lupe?
Is she still hot?
Come on, man, she the widow of my brother.
Oh, come on son, one thing is one thing...
...and another thing is another thing.
Now that is true, she is hot.
What's amazing is how my nephew
looks like my brother.
God forbid he turns out the same.
Fuckin' Benjamin Garcia.
Did you miss me, cabrón?
Look at Fat Mata.
How are you?
I'm not Fat Mata anymore, my friend.
Now everyone knows me as Cochiloco.
Hi there, Don Rogaciano.
Cochiloco! What kind of name is that?
What are you up to?
Right now I'm pissed off.
How can you come back...
...and not come to see your best friend, cabrón!
When did you become such a fucking ingrate!?
I swear I was gonna come to say hello Gordo...
...but I'm here with my Godfather...
I am no longer Fat Mata, Benny, my friend.
Now I'm El Cochiloco, clear?
Okay, I got it...
Benny, you fucking wimp.
Just like when we were kids, man.
We're like brothers,
you can call me whatever you want.
Well when you want, man.
Here, these two are my partners...
...El Huasteco Meretito, from Tampico...
...and this fat faggot is called La Muñeca.
Yes, we've already had the pleasure of meeting.
Let's get one thing straight,
you sons of bitches,
Let me be clear with you.
This litte guy, who looks like a fucked up dwarf,
is a brother to me!
If one of you lays a finger on him,
you'll be dealing with me!
- Is that clear!?
- As water Cochiloco.
Well, sorry about yesterday, my friend.
No worries.
And so, let's have some drinks to celebrate?
Well, Cochiloco, I'm working here with my Godfather.
I can't leave him here alone.
He'll give you permission.
Right, Don Rogaciano?
Or will you make a fuss?
No.
- Let's go.
- Let me change clothes.
Fucking gangsters.
There you go, precious.
Thank you, Cochi!
Me and Benny have known each other
since we were kids.
Ain't that right?
Ever since then he wanted to go to the other side,
like a little pocho.
We became friends after he defended me
from an asshole bully.
"Big Ears"
What happened to that guy?
What happens to everyone.
Those who didn't go to
the other side like you, cabrón...
...went into the business and got fucking
wiped out.
May La Niña Blacna and Jesus
keep them in their Holy Glory.
Listen Cochi, tell me the truth.
What happened to my brother?
I'll tell you just so you can
stop thinking about it.
Your brother worked for the
Reyes family like all of us here.
He was a true badass gangster.
But one some other fuckers tried to
take over...
...and he was shot dead.
Sons of fucking bitches.
If it's any consolation,
We paid those cabrones back with interest,
right?
Thanks, Cochi.
Hey, don't get down about it, Benny.
We came to celebrate
and since you brought it up...
Let's drink, in memory of El Diablo, a true bro.
- Cheers!
- A real badass.
Gloria, bring another bottle.
You know what, girl?
Give me that, I'll take it.
I want to say hi to my friend.
Benny, let me introduce Señora Lupita Soliz.
- She was your brother's wife...
- Yes, yes, we already met.
Isn't that right?
What a pleasure to see you "Cowboy."
Especially in such good company.
What did you do to her for her to
treat you like that?
Listen, now that you've returned,
how will you make money?
I wanted to do an English language school...
...but as I see how things are.
I think I'll end up
returning to the other side.
Don't be stupid, Benny.
Go back along with the gringos...
...who treat you like shit?
Look.
This country has a lot of opportunities...
...to make money, cabrón.
Or not?
Look at this, the Holy Patron of pure gold.
And let me tell you, if you need anything,
just let me know...
No, Cochi, thank you but...
Excuse me. Hello?
Sir, what's up?
We'll be there in half an hour.
Let's move, you chimps.
Señor Reyes needs us.
Benny.
Anything you need, give me a shout, okay?
Ok Cochi.
- Hey Cochi, Cochi!
- Put it on my tab, Camilo.
Still angry with me, Lupita?
So?
You want something else or
will you go straight to enjoy the lady?
No, neither, thank you.
If you won't eat or fuck.
Then get the hell out of here, cabrón.
Have a good one, "Cowboy".
Son, this shit gets worse every day.
Not even flies stop here.
Remember that before you went over to
"Gringolandia"...
...I was even planning to open up
a full auto workshop?
Why didn't you, Godfather?
Because in this fucking country,
you don't do what you want...
...but what you can.
Only by a miracle I haven't had to
sell the tire shop to Reyes.
So who are these Reyes everyone
talks about all over the place?
They're cattle farmers...
...that everyone knows as the
Reyes (Kings) of the North.
The head is the old Joseph.
The one directing it all is Don Jose,
a fucking son of a bitch...
...who manages all the shady business
throughout the North.
Trafficking, kidnappings, prostitution.
Smuggling and any fucking dirty business
you can imagine.
But tho old fucker is protected,
from far, far above.
- And the other?
- Hos brother, Don Pancho.
The top boss of San Francisco.
What's the problem between the two?
The thing went rotten when Jose decided that...
...his son, Jesus, would be the successor.
The other Reyes, Pancho was pissed off.
And declared war on his brother.
And since then, they've waging a war here...
...that seems to have no end.
Oh, it would be a good movie.
What fucking movie are you talking about?
This narco war has killed more men
than the revolution.
Your friend Cochiloco offered you a job right?
Godfather, that'd be the last thing I would do.
Look, Godson...
All I have in this life...
...which is this little tire shop, is yours too.
But don't make the mistake of following
in the footsteps of your dickhead brother.
What do you think, Godfather?
But since you said we are partners...
...is there a way you'd let me
borrow some money?
What's up?
To what do I owe the honor?
No, I only wanted to smoke the
peace pipe with you, sister-in-law.
They are very beautiful, thank you.
- Come in.
- Thank you.
That was when we went to Mazatlan.
It was supposed to be a vacation.
He disappeared for 13 days
and when he came back...
...he was shot in the shoulder
and bleeding from head to toe.
We couldn't even visit the Cathedral.
Did you get married?
He offered all the time, but whenever...
...the time came, he found an excuse
not to go through with it.
Despite all of that, I never
doubted that he loved me.
He did have good taste.
Stop playing, you're seeing me at my worst.
But the truth is that when I was younger.
I used to stop traffic.
Ah, you can still stop traffic
and anything else.
Calm down, "Cowboy."
Can't you see I'm confused.
Confused about what?
You feel them same as me.
Come here.
What's up, son?
I can guess where you've been.
- Out.
You've been drinking again, right?
Only one beer, mom.
You go straight to bed and tomorrow...
... you don't wake up until school,
or you'll see what happens!
Yes, I got the hint.
Keep on doing whatever you were doing.
- See you, Uncle Benny.
- Yes.
Have fun with my mom.
What a kid.
Just 14 years old,
imagine when he grows up.
To me, it's chilling that he looks so much
like my brother.
They even talk the same.
You look a lot like him, too.
You know what I was thinking
just now when you kissed me?
Hey, you know Lupita?
I think I'd better go.
Because it's getting late and...
- No, no, no, no,
Don't go away "Cowboy."
I know what I'm talking about.
Come.
You lucky bastard.
Oh my love.
- Oh, you're a pig.
- Oh, yeah?
You'll see, my love.
I'll start working...
...and I'll take care of your kid.
Thank you, my Diablo.
What? Come on, babe.
I'm not El Diablo?
Oh sorry, my mistake.
And where did you sleep last night, cabrón?
I went to visit my mother and...
...it got late, and I stayed there with her.
Oh... your mother.
Of course, your mother...
Think I was born yesterday?...
Your mother's looking for you, asshole.
What it is, babe?
Oh Benny, I have a major problem.
Problem? What happened?
Your fucking nephew did something stupid
and got arrested.
Arrested?
No kidding...
I'm with these guys and I can't go.
Can you fix this for me?
Of course, my love, don't worry.
But I don't have any cash.
Here. I got 3000 as an advance
and 5000 more coming.
I think that's enough.
Yes, yes, don't worry,
I'll take care of my nephew.
Thank you.
Please take care of this.
If I finish early I'll see you at home.
I don't think 8000 pesos will cover it,
Mr. Garcia.
Your nephew's a felon.
Did you know he tried to steal a truck?
And it belonged to mayor.
Your nephew is a repeat offender.
There's no choice...
...but to have have him locked up,
right, Amaya?
I couldn't have said it better, boss.
Chief, I know the kid committed
a serious crime.
But is there any way to solve this?
See, Mr. Garcia,
You're starting to remember how it works
in Mexico.
And, more or less, how much will it take
to solve the problem?
For you, and knowing that you just...
...returned to Mexico, I'll leave it at...
- 50 grand.
- 50,000 pesos!?
Where will I get that kind of money?
Your boy is already booked.
If you don't get the cash before noon,
I'll just have to process him.
So, tell me, Benny, what's so urgent?
Listen, Cochi, I'm stuck with a big,
big problem...
...and I'm gonna need to earn some cash.
Hey cabrones!
Go take a fucking hike.
Come on!
What kind of problem?
You need someone whacked?
No, I'd never do that Cochi.
My nephew is in jail.
And I need 50,000 pesos to help my...
...sister-in-law.
Don’t tell me you're involved with her.
Damn Benny.
I knew about the cousin, but the sister-in-law,
you bastard?
Don’t think badly Cochi,
it's only to help my nephew.
Oh yeah... fucking sure.
Now it turns out you're running
a fucking charity, man.
That broad is smokin' hot, man!
Easy, Cochi.
I really need the dough...
And you said that if I needed to work...
I could count on you and...
Look, Benny.
In the life of a "Narco"...
...there is very good money.
But it's not easy.
You need big balls, cabrón.
I've thought it through, Cochi,
and I see no other way...
...given how bad things are out there.
Done.
I'll introduce you to the boss.
But I warn you, eh,
Once inside, cabrón...
...there is no turning back.
Clear!?
Oh yes, I appreciate it, Cochi.
Look.
Start by getting to know the shit we sell.
This is what we ship up north.
- No, I don't really want...
- Come on man!
Ouch! Cochi!
This is really good shit.
We deal good fuckin' weed.
- It's a real treasure of the Sierra Madre!
- Oh yes.
Ai, Bennny, you don’t know what you're
getting yourself into, cabrón.
We came to see the Boss.
Take it easy, Benny.
The boss doens't bite.
Just listen, and keep your mouth shut.
- Ok?
- Ok
The boss is loaded.
This is only one of their properties.
He made a fortune in this business.
But what he really loves is...
- Cockfights and raising cattle.
- Oh yeah?
Imagine, he gets up before dawn.
Milking cows and feeding the roosters.
He's got more than enough.
Stand up straight.
Try to look tough.
Go iside and wait.
I'll look go and find Don Jose.
Remember, keep your mouth shut!
Señor.
Benjamin Garcia at your service.
Come in.
Sit down, make yourself at home.
Thank you.
So, you're Pedro's brother?
Yes, sir.
The famous Diablo.
A good guy, but too wild and impulsive.
They told me you lived
a long time in the United States.
"Oh yes sir."
So you'll agree with me.
I always say that the gringos
fucked this country over.
And that those fucking yank sons of bitches
robbed us all blind...
...with the help of some our own
fucking lousy presidents.
The only thing they know how to do is
kneel and lick their feet.
Then they turn over and take it up the ass.
According to them, this is capitalism.
They don't realize that that people like me...
We have the means to fuck them up
good and proper.
Oh, Dad.
You speak more like a politician all the time.
The gringos are our best customers.
He shouldn't talk about them like that.
You damned son of a bitch!
You think you're a fucking smart ass?
You know more than me?
Don't ever crack off to me like that again.
Get the fuck outta here!
Fucking kid.
But, of course, I'm to the blame.
I've spoiled him too much.
But sometimes he crosses the line and...
One thing I want you to know.
Those who work with me
are like part of my family.
But in this business,
there are rules and principles...
...that must be followed...
...if you don’t want to end up
shot in the head.
Got it?
Yes. Yes, sir.
One. Honesty.
Two. Total honor.
And Three. Silence.
Absolute silence!
Opening your mouth too much...
...is a good way to get a ticket
straight to hell.
- Is that clear?
- Yes sir, yes.
And another thing I was forgetting.
Use discretion...
...and don’t walk around like a big shot
like these assholes do.
People see them coming from a mile away.
Look.
My son Jesus will be be your boss.
He's my only son and I love him
with all my soul.
If anything happens to him...
...you'll answer with your life.
Is that clear!?
Yes. Yes, sir.
I'll give you an advance
to get yourself equiped.
Soon you will pay me back.
Just be careful, Garcia.
Be careful, there's a lot of profit
in this business.
But there are many temptations.
If you're smart, you'll be careful not to indulge...
...and get hooked on the dope we sell.
As our new Pope already said...
..."Putting garbage in the body is a mortal sin. "
- Of course!?
- Yeah, yes sir, yes.
- May God bless you.
- Thank you Sir.
I promise you I won't let you down.
You're an asshole, son of a bitch, Reyes!
The next time you lay a finger on your son...
...I'll cut off your balls, you asshole.
And you know I'm not talking...
...figuratively, you dickhead.
Oh, my queen, the boy disrespected me.
Don't lie to me, Reyes!
Come here my love, come on.
Your father wants to apologize.
Oh, you fucking prick.
You better to apologize to my son.
Or else you'll deal with me, cabrón.
- Sorry, my son.
- Yes, Pa.
There, you see, J.R.?
You're dad's a sweet cupcake.
My queen...
...I want to introduce you to Benjamin.
The brother of El Diablo.
He's working with us now.
Oh, pleased to meet you young man.
- Pardon us, senores.
- With your persmission.
Oh, thank you my love.
They are beautiful, and the dress.
Where did you find work?
With a cattle rancher. I'm going to
take care of his herd.
The old guy's not bad.
He even gave me an advance.
You've become a gangster,
working with Cochiloco, right?
You know what?
Take your money.
What do you want, Garcia?
To end up like your brother?
Don’t get confused, beautiful.
One thing is one thing
and another thing is another thing.
You saw that I was looking for work.
And around here, this is all there is.
I'm scared. God already took
one man away from me.
No, I promise you that it's only
until we save some money.
We'll pay the debts, and soon the three of us
together are going to the U.S.
But swear that you won't end
up like your brother.
By the Virgin of Guadalupe.
Come here, my love.
Well, Benny.
Welcome to the business,
we're making our first delivery.
Open your eyes, listen and learn.
Ok, Cochi.
Hey, Don Eme.
- Hi, Cochi.
- Why the long face?
Was it a bad week?
I'm fed up with this business.
Five nights working with no sleep,
and I barely broke even, man.
This crisis is really killing me.
Come on, Don Eme.
Every time I drive by your hotel
I see it full of horny bastards.
With or without the crisis,
people still love to fuck.
And this guy?
He's my partner, Benny.
He'll take over for me when I take a vacation
or retire.
Be nice to him.
Benjamin Garcia, at your service, Don.
What'll it be, Don Eme?
20 grams, a quarter of weed...
...ecstasies, a package of heroin, 12 rocks...
...and 200 hits of meth,
since they are so fashionable, right?
I thought the crisis was hitting you hard,
Don Eme.
You don’t want syringes,
Yumbina, some porno?
I've got one of a Swedish girl with a donkey...
- God damn it.
- You fucker.
How much do I owe you?
Oh, man.
Here, keep the change.
Right.
Until next week Don Eme.
Keep your ass clean.
I'll save the water so you can gargle with it,
cabrón.
How much is this briefcase worth, Cochi?
It's worth a shitload, Benny.
But that, for the Boss, is only peanuts.
The real business is in imports...
...and exports on a large scale.
That's where the real money is.
The bad thing is that with this fucking crisis
The competition is really
fucking with us.
Now any little runt
in the neighborhood can get...
...a gun and start shit in our territory.
We're trying not to lose the goose
that laid the golden egg.
Look Cochi.
Quiet, calm down.
Don’t get stressed.
Put the briefcase under the seat.
Hey Cochiloco, how's business?
Very well, Chief.
And you?
What are you doing with that fucking pocho?
He began working with Don Jose
and I am teaching him the business.
Explain to him how it works between us.
Especially how much.
Don’t worry Chief,
I'll bring him up to speed.
Damn right.
See you pricks around.
Ai, Cochi...
That cop scared the shit outta me.
He's a real filthy looking pig.
Hey Cochi, by chance
do you have some speed?
Gotta work the night shift.
Look in the glove compartment
for a brown jar for the Chief, Benny.
Thank you guys,
Be good.
Especially you, fucking Pocho.
Damn Benny, you're as white as a corpse.
Let's have a drink to get your color back.
But not at the Salon Mexico.
If Lupita sees me like this she'll kill me.
I'll take you to a classy place.
Not that hole-in-the-wall
where your girlfriend works.
Is it expensive?
I'm a little short right now.
Here's a gift from the Reyes.
But this money belongs to the boss,
doesn't it?
Of course it does, don’t be a prick.
You think he'll notice if we skim a little bit?
And if he finds out, Cochi?
This is just part of the business,
we don't risk our asses for free.
Just don't get caught
and don’t abuse it.
Thanks for the advice.
COCK OF GOLD
How do you like the place?
Not fucking bad, eh?
It's pretty fuckin' cool!
What do you think of the gig?
Like everything else, it's just a matter of
getting the hang of it.
And how did it go with Reyes?
Was he nice to you?
Actually I thought he would be meaner,
but in fact...
...he seemed like a good guy.
Good guy, my ass.
Don Jose is the most nastiest son of a bitch
who ever walked the earth.
That's why he's in charge.
May St. Jude and the holy St. Malverde...
...protect them for years to come.
Because the day that the Don Jose dies,
we're totally fucked.
If the business falls into the hands
of that asshole J.R....
...the Panchos will take over in less
than one month, and fuck us all over.
True.
You have to watch your back
with those assholes, Benny.
If I ever see one of those Panchitos...
I'll put a bullet right through his ears.
I told you guys my Benny was
the fucking man.
- Cheers to Benny!
- Cheers!
Let's give him a proper initiation,
like he deserves, right?
Hell wants a nice girl.
Lola! Come here...
Cochiloco, if Lupita find outs,
she'll cut off my balls.
Don’t be such damned queer!
Look at this girl, man!
Be nice to him, babe.
I promise you, my love
you won't have to work anymore.
I'll take care of your kid.
Benny, put on your clothes quickly
or we're screwed.
- Hurry up!
- But Cochi, I'm not finished.
Don't be a prick. This is work.
The bosses are waiting. Fast!
Hear that, my love?
Hurry up!
So, what's the rush, Cochi?
First things first, right?
Making me stop in the middle of it...
- The brunette was...
- Take this.
No, Cochi, you know I don't...
Come on, take the shit!
If J.R. and the Boss
see us in this state...
...they'll castrate us.
- Come on, go for it.
- Let's see...
Yes?
Take it easy, J.R.
Yes, were on our way.
Don’t worry.
Yeah, I've got it, the boss wants him alive.
Yes, we'll be there
before the midnight.
Right.
What was that, Cochi?
I'm feeling like new, man.
It's time to be baptized, Benny.
Get ready.
Clean your nose, cabrón.
What's happening, man?
Where is your brother?
- First the money, right?
- Fucking snitch bastard.
Selling your brother for 1000 pesos.
Son of a fuckin' bitch.
Hey, I'm poor, man.
You probably don't remember what it's like.
What's more, my fucking brother
never wanted to give me a hand.
Ah! Stop fucking around and tell me
where he is before you piss me off even more.
He went in a couple of hours ago.
He should be there.
Hopefully he's not so I have an excuse
to take it out on you instead.
I swear he's there, inside.
Fine, you fuckin' rat,
And remember, we'll see you eventually.
Get your gun ready, Benny.
And take the tape.
If someone runs out,
put a hole into him.
Cockroach!
Alright, señora, let's hear it.
Where did Cockroach go?
Don’t be a fool.
Tell me where Cockroach is!
Think about it Cockroach!
If you don't come out in three seconds
I'll waste your whole family.
One!
- Two!
- Calm down!
- Cochi, I'm here.
- Tie this prick up.
No, no, no, please.
Don't be an asshole, Cochi.
For old times' sake, let me say goodbye...
...to my wife and children, huh?
Go, I'll give you one minute starting now.
Give me a blessing.
Take care of my children.
- Let's go, let's go!
- No!
Look, Cockroach.
You know you're already screwed...
...but since we're old friends,
I'll give you the chance to take revenge...
...on the fucking weasel that sold you out.
Thanks, Cochi.
I always thought you were a stand-up guy.
Here you go, but no nonsense.
Or else you'll get it back twice as hard.
Keep your eyes on him Benny.
Panfilo!
Panfilo, damn it, we came into this world together,
and we're leaving together.
Thanks, Cochi.
You're a good man, but...
Don’t take me to the boss.
If you want, shoot me right now
with my brother...
...but don't take me to that son of a bitch.
Sorry, Cockroach.
Orders are orders.
I've gotta take you in alive.
Come on, we're late as it is.
Come on!
Who do you think you are, eh?
We've been waiting two hours for you,
like idiots.
We'll deal with that later.
First things first.
What's up Cockroach?
So many years working
for me without complaining.
I always paid you good money.
So why did you have to go and
talk to the Federales?
No?
What did you tell them?
Look...
If you tell me everything you squealed to them...
...you can still save yourself, man.
I swear it was nothing, Boss.
Nothing.
I hope it's true, because otherwise
not only will I fuck you up bad
I'll fuck your kids too,
What do you say?
By the holy virgin,
I swear I didn't say anything.
We know everything, you fucking idiot!
Okay, okay,
Cockroach.
I believe you,
I believe you.
Only in this business...
...there are rules and principles
that must be respected and fulfilled.
You know what happens to snitches,
don't you?
Cochiloco, give me the knife.
You take the head, hold on!
No!
Open up, open! You little fucker!
And this is for stealing!
Give it to me!
And this is to cure you of stupidity, cabrón!
- Come on, my son.
- Yes, Pa.
What's going on my love?
What happened?
What can I tell you, my love?
Look at my hands?
You probably had to do something horrible, right?
No, not me.
The boss is batshit crazy.
I swear it was the most
horrible thing I've ever seen.
I can imagine, but the way the situation is...
...you need to deal with it and keep working.
- Aren't we better off now than before?
- Yes.
The truth is, I don't know if I can go on,
my love.
In life, we grow accustomed to
whatever comes our way, besides starving.
I don't know...
...there's a limit to what one can bear.
I'll sing this corrido...
...to the two men that were killed,
Without any compassion
they were cruely tortured,
Give me what you stole.
Gimme!
They were run over with a car...
You stole it!
In the neigborhood of El Palmito,
in the city of Culiancán,
There went Francisco Lopez,
and Francisco Beltran,
They couldn't have imagined
that they would be killed.
Francisco Lopez had some bills to pay...
He killed the one who stole his beloved,
FAGGOT BITCHES
A REMINDER FROM THE KINGS OF THE NORTH
But Francis Beltran was not guilty.
The next day they found him at dawn,
They had their guts inside out
and a dog ate them,
Damn, Benny, you have the soul of a poet.
A few moments later the police arrived.
I baptize you with the name of "La Gringa".
In the name of the Father, Son
and the Holy Spirit.
With a band, the people of Sinaloa
were burying them,
and two mothers were crying
without consolation,
Because their beloved children
are now in heaven.
What did he say?
He said that he'll give us everything for $ 75,000.
- Including the grenades and bazooka.
- Everything?
Then, go ahead and tell him "yes".
Let's go, come on.
Let's take everything.
Ladies and gentlemen, social justice...
...was, is and always will be
the eternal debt we owe to our Mexico.
Today, we gather in celebration of
the bicentenary of independence...
...and the centennial of the revolution,
events that gave us a proud homeland.
And thanks to the enormous generosity
of Don Jose and Doña Mari Reyes...
...who, with the big heart and patriotism
that God gave them...
...have donated this wonderful school
for our city.
The whole community
of San Miguel the Archangel.
But most of all, Mexican children...
...who are the future of our country,
will be eternally grateful.
God bless you, Señores Reyes.
What do you think of the new
Heroes of the Fatherland, Cochi?
And now to conclude this solemn event...
...we will respectfully sing our national anthem.
Mexicans, to the cry of war...
...lend your swords and bridle...
...and let the earth tremble at its center...
...the roaring sound of the cannon.
- How's it going, Tex?
- How are you, Cochi?
How's life treating you?
As the saying goes,
struggling, but with my claws out.
- And you?
- I'm well.
Is it all here, or do I have to count it?
Have I ever disappointed you, Cochi?
I've always brought you
high quality merchandise.
Let me see,
I'll give it the test.
Go on, son.
Very good.
- And the opium?
- Look, my dear Cochi.
I'll give you a good piece of advice as a friend.
To trust is good, but not to trust is better.
You haven’t changed over all these years.
Benny, give the man his money.
Looks okay.
Take this, little one.
Hold on to the money for me.
Hey, unload the mechandise!
My man, Cochi.
Always a pleasure doing business
with you, Tex.
Good to see you, so long.
Let's go, little guy.
Take a look at the quality of the shit
Tex sells to us.
Who is this guy?
Is he really a gringo?
He wa born in Brownsville but
his parents are from Reynosa.
The guy thinks he's a gringo...
...but he's as Mexican as a cactus.
- All that dough goes straight to him?
- Yeah, that's right.
The Texan is what we call in the business
a middleman, a coyote.
He spends months in the mountains
buying crops from the peasants.
He buys their poppy and coca and sells it
to the boss at 10 times its price.
All the problems in the countryside
would be solved if...
...it weren't for the fucking asshole intermediaries.
What's up with this idiot?
- Good afternoon, "my friends".
- What's going on Mendoza?
- Why's the road closed?
- It just came in that we had...
...a 3-18 on kilometer 20,
the highway is closed.
3-18, my ass, cut the bullshit
and let us through, you prick.
Let's go, we're in a hurry.
I'm really sorry, Cochi.
A bus flipped over and it was ugly,
it'll be closed for several hours.
Why not cut through that cactus field?
Cactus field, you motherfucker!
You fucking pricks...
Sorry Cochi...
Orders are orders.
Watch out Benny, they're Panchos!
Get cover!
Follow that asshole, Benny.
Don’t let the bastard escape.
Don’t kill me!
I'll give you anything to spare me.
Don't do it!
Give me a chance, man.
Damn, Benny.
I couldn't have done it better.
Look what you did to him.
I thought you didn't have the balls
for this gig.
Respect, cabrón!
We must give thanks to God
for things turned out well.
This merchandise was already
promised to the gringos.
And we couldn't disappoint them.
Now you really showed what balls you have.
Thank you, Boss.
If not for my fucking jealous brother, that cunt.
But now the tide's turning, eh?
I think if we don’t stop uncle Francisco...
...things could get worse.
Yes, my son.
That's why I'll send...
...him the bodies of my nephews.
That should give the fucker something
to think about.
How's that, you fucking pussy Pancha?
Who's the bitch now, asshole?
Enough J.R.
Don’t disturb your cousins.
In memory of your grandmother,
show some respect for the family.
And you guys, to show you how happy I am.
Here you go.
And don’t be stupid, don’t spend...
...it all on the first thing you see!
Do go around boasting like big shots.
Don’t worry, Boss, and again, thank you.
Thank you, Sir.
Come, my son, I'll teach you
to classify the goods.
Benny, now what?
- Hey, Ma.
- Did you win the lottery?
How are you?
Here it is, as promised.
I've been thinking of you,
look what I brought.
It's a TV for you to watch your soaps.
So you can esapce this awful reality.
How lovely, thank you, my son.
Let me see here.
This is for you.
Now you're following the same steps
as you brother, am I right?
No, Ma, why do you say that?
With the way you look,
it couldn't be anything else.
But it's up to you. Just don't give me
as much grief as your brother did, okay?
- Don’t worry, Ma.
- Come in, son.
No mother, I have to get back to work.
And what about your watch?
Won't you give it to me as a present?
Why, of course, Ma.
You only needed to ask.
Okay, I'll be back to visit you.
Wait.
I forgot one thing.
Oh yeah!
I forget to get your blessing, Ma.
No, no. Forget the stupid blessing.
The neighbor's son bought her a "watsman."
You'd be able to get me one, right?
Sure mom, I'll bring you one
with an MP3 and everything.
Oh, great.
Now lean forward for your blessing.
See you soon, Ma.
What do you think?
- Come on, come and check it out.
- It's ours?
Yes.
- Hello, my queen.
- It's beautiful, my love.
Go on in and fix yourself up.
Let's go celebrate.
- You like it, son?
- Yeah, man.
Let go. It's getting late.
What are we doing here?
I don’t like this place.
Come on, my love, it's a surprise.
In memory of Pedro Garcia.
"El Devil"
Remembered fondly by
his brother Benny,
his wife Lupita, and
his son Benjamin.
Rest in peace
My God, honey.
You'll go to heaven for doing this.
Wait, it gets better.
He was a brave man indeed.
He always mocked the police.
Thousands were at his command.
They all knew him as "El Diablo."
Money, power and fame.
Hey son, good night.
- Listen, Uncle Benny.
- What is it?
I just wanted to thank you
for what you did for my Pa.
Well, he was my brother.
And I really loved him.
Uncle Benny, could I ask a favor?
When I'm killed, if you're still alive...
...could you build me a tomb
with a nice song like my father's?
Stop talking bullshit, son.
When you get killed?
On my watch, you will live a straight life.
Whatever it takes.
Until tomorrow, my son.
My love, I swear this was one of the best days
of my life.
Oh yeah?
I still have something else for you.
- Oh really?
- Look.
Give this money to Don Camilo.
And tomorrow you quit Salon Mexico,
what do you think?
My love, this is so much money.
Shouldn't we wait a little longer?
Of course not, my queen.
There will be plenty more
where that came from.
My future wife won't remain as a whore.
Who ever heard of such a monstrosity?
Godson, you've made my dreams come true.
And I was always doubting you.
That's the least I can do for you, Godfather.
When I get some more money together...
...we'll build a car wash, what do you think?
Great idea! Hey, and your wife and nephew,
how are they?
I haven't seen them in a while.
Speaking of the Queen of Rome...
What is it, beautiful?
Don’t cry, my queen, stay there.
Don't do anything,
I'm gonna race over there.
- What is it, godson? Are you okay?
- I'll explain later.
Now, we're just missing the customers.
And then when Don Camilo arrived...
...I gave him the cash, but he said no.
That it wasn't enough, that I still owed interest.
And that I was one of his best girls...
...and he would not let me go
with just any pimp.
Pimp?
That's what he said?
And not only that.
Then that pig tried to hit me.
If the girls were not there to hold him,
he'd have killed me.
Don’t worry, beautiful,
I'm gonna have a little talk with this guy.
Can't you see it's closed, idiots?!
I'm coming!
You motherfucking bastard,
cocksucking asshole.
Son of a bitch!
Let me go!
Let me at him!
Son of a bitch, you asshole.
Benny! Wait!
I have a better idea.
- Oh shit!
- You'll learn about respect.
Shut up, you cunt!
Keep quiet, Don Camilo.
You have to learn to respect the
ladies, cabrón.
Ready? Go.
Benny, remember how the news is
always saying...
...that these nightclubs are a safety hazard?
- Yeah.
- Well, they were right.
- Oh! Son of a bitch!
- Let's go!
The time has come, dear, for
the soul to speak without lies.
- Good morning, my love.
- Good morning.
- You'll never guess what happened.
- What?
Gloria came by earlier and said that
the Panchos torched the Salon Mexico.
- Don’t tell me?
- Yes, I'm telling you.
Don Camilo was found burned to a crisp.
They only recognized him by his gold tooth.
Those fucking Panchos are assholes.
They didn't even leave me time
to talk with your boss.
There's Cochi.
I've got to run.
With this job, you're always on call.
- Thank you, my love.
- No problem.
Look at him, sleeping like a little angel.
Son of a bitch!
Now you're gonna see, you fuck!
Let's go!
What's going on, Cochi?
We're buddies.
Buddies, my balls!
Don't even speak to me, you asshole!
You drive, Benny, while I teach this fucker
a lesson.
Let's go!
Sending us through the cactus field, eh?
Okay, Mendoza, how much did the Panchos
offer you, huh?
I swear they didn't, Cochi.
I swear on my blessed mother's soul.
Don’t play the fucking fool, tell me
or I'll put a hole in you, cabrón.
It really wasn't me, Cochi.
Have mercy on me.
Remember my kids.
And did you remember mine, cabrón?
Don’t be stupid, Mendoza.
If you tell Cochi the truth,
maybe I can help you.
Thank you.
I know you're a good guy at heart.
But tell Cochi not to kill me.
Then answer his question.
6000 pesos.
That's all the Panchos paid you, fucker?!
It's more than we earn in
in a month at the station.
Think, Benny. 3000 pesos per head.
They must be joking.
That's it! Fucking kill him!
Come here, cabrón.
You know what happens to snitches?
Eh?
No, Garcia!
Please, I'm begging you, Garcia.
I can't do it, Cochi.
Fuck, Benny. You're missing out
on the best part of the job.
No!
See?
You know what I realized Benny?
As singer Jose Alfredo said...
"Life is worth nothing".
For 3000 fucking pesos.
That's fucker almost sent us to our graves.
Tell me the truth, Cochi.
Don’t you feel anything,
just killing someone like that?
I mean...
...aren't you afraid you'll end up in hell?
Hell, my fucking ass.
Hell is right here where we are.
Don't you remember what it was like
when we were kids?
How hungry we were? The fucking cold?
The miserable poverty that we lived in?
Or like right now, when guys
are killing each other just for the sake of it.
Only because they can't find a
decent way to live.
I'm telling you, this life we're living
is fucking hell.
Yeah, you're right.
What's up Cochi?
Won't you give me a ride home?
No, we're going to my house
so you get to know my wife.
You know what? I'm still feeling a little sick
to my stomach, just look at me.
Exactly, have a beer and meet my old lady.
Come on.
Come on family!
All in single file, ok?
Let's say hello to Uncle Benny.
Come on.
- Good evening. - Good evening.
This is Baby Bear, this is Princess,
Shorty, the Mariachi.
And my favorite, my firstborn, the Cochiloquinho.
Look.
Here's the future of all my futures.
Benny.
Cochi, Ah!
Señora, very pleased to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Let's go!
- Up to bed, all of you.
- Good night.
Good night Baby Bear.
They are wonderful.
Let's have a drink.
Come on.
Make yourself at home,
Benny, what will it be?
Anything.
Let me see.
Salud compadre.
You have to see it to believe it, Cochi.
One thing is one thing and
anyother thing is another thing, Benny.
What did you think?
That I lived in a cave
and ate human flesh?
No, but... to see you...
Don’t misunderstand me, Cochi, but...
...it's like you are two different people at once.
Well, you see, if I wasn't in the Narco business,
How else would I support my children?
I do this because there's no
no other choice.
There's no question about that.
The boss is pissed off at you.
The very least he'll do is decapitate you...
Listen up! You sons of bitches!
On your knees!
Hands on your head.
Don't try anything stupid!
Now what's the problem with this idiot?
We're screwed, Cochi.
As I was telling you, Captain.
The arrest of these dangerous drug traffickers...
...is a demonstration that the collaboration
between the three levels of government...
...is working very well.
And the struggle being undertaken by...
...the President of the Republic
against organized crime...
...is on the right path.
And now yes, even though
it doesn't look like it, we're winning.
Chief Mancera...
...head of our heroic police force...
...will give you the details on these little gems.
Okay, Captain, first we have
Eugenio Matta. Alias: El Cochiloco.
He is considered the head of operations
of the cartel and he's the main...
...distributor of drugs in the region.
And here we have Benjamin Garcia.
Better known as El Benny.
For many years he's been importing and...
...exporting prohibited substances.
He belongs to a network of traffickers in the U.S.
- Then we...
- Hold on, Chief.
Do you have any evidence to sustain the charges?
Because you make it sound like you have
the most dangerous gangsters in the country.
As you know, Captain, these types of offenders...
...have many resources, prominent lawyers...
...who help them... so...
- Yes, yes I understand.
Could you give me permission to speak alone
with the inmates please.
Yes, yes of course.
Mancera.
So fellas...
I understand that you guys
are more dangerous...
...than "El Chapo" and "Los Aretes" put together.
Look here, cabrones.
What really interests me most are the Reyes.
They say you four are working for Don Jose.
So now, I know that
you won't tell me anything now...
...but I'm making you an offer anyway.
Don’t laugh!
You never know.
Come on, Captain.
Let's hear it.
Don't beat around the bush,
what's your offer?
We have an attractive witness protection program...
...copied from the American model
that works very well.
If any of you want to "sing"
for whatever reason...
...talk to me.
I'm offering freedom and protection...
...in exchange for testimony against the Reyes.
What do you think about it?
Think about it.
You never know...
Life takes many turns,
who knows what's best?
Someday you might need this.
Consider also that...
...it's better to be a fifth-rate snitch
than a first-rate corpse.
Excuse me.
Fucking federales.
You two are nothing more
than a pair of ingrates.
Have you forgotten who it was
that put you in your jobs?
You worthless pieces of shit.
Especially you, Felix.
Do you remember how much I've given...
...in your election campaign?
It would have been better if I had run
for Mayor myself...
...as my wife suggested.
It's true, my love, you'd do much better as mayor
than this little prick.
Please understand, Don Jose...
The Federal Government
is putting us under pressure...
...with the whole business of
combating organized crime.
And... have you seen all the commercials on TV?
"The Federal Government works for you,
in the fight against organized crime."
"Even if it doesn't look like it,
we are winning."
Shut up, Jesus. Stop making all that racket.
You sound like a parrot.
You're being a true asshole, Felix.
The Federal Government can kiss my ass.
Their campaign is only to deceive the people.
And to cover up for their own stealing.
It's just that the federal agent who came
is in charge of the whole region, Don Jose.
And, not only that, but he...
...caught us with out pants down.
Right, compadre?
There is no other way to put it, Don Jose.
And why not arrest my nephews
or my fucking brother?
Didn't you hear that the other day
the tried to...
...rob one of our shipments?
But they fucked themselves over
because my guys...
...are the most badass motherfuckers around.
They fucked them up good and proper,
like real fucking men.
- Isn't that right, cabrones?
- Yes, sir!
So motherfuckers, which one of you two
is turning crooked on me?
No, no, no, don’t think that, Don Jose, please.
It's just that your guys are crossing the line.
The other day they picked up Officer Mendoza...
...and he hasn't been seen since.
Stop being such a liar, Felix!
My guys don't even...
...go to take a shit without my permission.
It must have been the fucking Panchos.
And neither you, nor you has done a thing
to stop them.
But Don Jose, this time it was just
the Federal Police...
...the next it will be the whole army.
Are you really such a stupid prick?
How many times do I have to repeat.
They must have a little arrangement
with my colleagues in Sinaloa.
They just want to make a little show
to look like they're putting up a fight.
But listen to me.
If you don’t want any bloodshed...
...do something about my brother.
If not, you'll be hearing from me.
Is that clear!?
Yes, I promise you that my colleague and I
will get right to work on it.
- Right, Mancera?
- Yes, yes Don Jose.
So cabrones...
Which of you...
...whacked Mendoza without my permission?
No, no one.
What is it, beautiful?
Oh Benny, I'm really worried about my son.
I'll tell you a secret...
...but you've got to keep it to yourself.
For some time now...
...I've been dipping into a little
of the boss's money.
And in a short time...
...we'll have enough to get all three of us
into the U.S.
What do you think?
Benny, you need to be careful.
If the Reyes catch you, they might kill you.
I'm not a dummy, babe.
I'm keeping it well hidden.
Oh my love, may God grant it.
I want us to get as far away from here as we can.
LITTLE BROTHER,
THIS IS JUST SO YOU'LL SEE
WHO HAS THE BIGGEST PAIR OF BALLS.
HERE COME THE PIG, A DICK WITH NO WIG...
Di you see waht they wrote to me here?
You probably can't read anyway, cabrones.
This proves that you haven't got the balls.
You can't handle this shit.
My son is going to bring some guys
from Reynosa who really have big balls.
We'll see the look on you faces after that.
This is fucking war, assholes.
I swear on my blessed mother's grave that...
...I will murder my brother
and his whole fucking family.
He's no relation of mine anymore!
And take this shit down from there.
Take this.
Give $3000 dollars to each widow...
...so that their men can be buried.
Now!
Come on!
You heard my father, bunch of assholes.
Well, take that thing down.
I'm home, my beauty.
Hello Benny, how did it go?
Just fine, my love,
the boss is taking care of things.
What happened my love?
That damn son of mine did it again.
He hasn't come home.
Look what he's been keeping under his bed.
I have a feeling that he's got into
something serious.
Do you think something's happend to him?
No, my love,
We would have heard if something happened.
Don’t worry that I'll go look for him.
He'll have to listen to me.
Hey Benny, got any meth?
What? Do I look like a narco or something,
you little prick?
No, not that.
Hey Cholo, you know anything
about my nephew?
He's been missing since yesterday
and his mother's worried to death.
Tell me what you know
and I'll give you 10 bucks.
I might remember something
if I had some meth. Otherwise...
You're underage, cabrón!
I'm a big boy.
Here. Knock yourself out.
Now spill it.
The guy became good friends with
the Panchos in San Francisco.
He boasts all the time about
working with them.
He's always got money and women.
Damn kid.
Hey, just don't tell him
I told you about this.
Don’t worry, Cholo.
If you see him, tell him
to go straight home, okay?
Sure, Benny. And you know something?
If you want a badass assistant,
I'll be at your service.
What the fuck, kid?
Here, Diablito.
So that you learn. Go ahead.
You're mother is going crazy
ooking for you everywhere...
...and you're wasting your time with...
- Come on, let's go.
- Can't you see I'm busy?
Go ahead. I'll catch up with you...
Look here, Benny, you little prick,
cut the bullshit or I'll drag you home.
Leave Diablito in peace, cabrón.
Are you gonna take on four of us?
Take it easy, Pancho.
He's my uncle, and he's cool.
If you say so.
Saved by the bell, pal.
Let's go, Benny.
Let your uncle give you your fucking bottle,
Diablito.
Fucking thugs.
How are you, beautiful?
Yes. He's with me.
Don't worry.
Kisses, my queen.
Any idea who you're messing with, cabrón?
Are you an idiot, or what?
Or do you feel like a big shot,
acting like a fucking narco?
You have to think that this is not a joke.
Think of your father.
Or me.
If I don’t get out of this business soon
I'm gonna end up dead just like your dad.
What?
Want to follow the tradition of this family
full of fucking dumb pricks?
Listen up, cabrones.
With these guys on our side,
we're really gonna fuck up my cousins.
From now on, we'll work in three groups.
You Garcia, you'll be partners with El Sargento.
Yes sir.
You Huasteco, you work with El Sardo.
Cochiloco, since you're the one
my father finds most reliable...
...you'll work with me.
La Muñeca, and this guy they call of El Mayate
will lend us a hand.
- Are we agreed?
- Yes sir.
Pardon me, J.R., with you permission,
wouldn't it be...
...that La Muñeca and I could...
Stop bitching, Huasteco.
You'll soon have another opportunity...
...to be reunited with your boyfriend.
And you can get back to whatever
you do together.
But right now, you'll do what my son tells you.
- Is that clear!?
- Yes, Boss.
So get a fuckin'move on, we don’t pay
you to stand around like pricks. Let's go!
Come on!
- How was I, Pa?
- Well done, Son.
Keep being a man like that...
...and you'll make a worthy
heir to your father.
Yes, Pa.
Oh, if your grandmother were alive...
...she'd be crying with joy.
True.
I'll tell you straight up.
The owner of the car dealership
owes money to the Boss.
Don Jose's orders are that we put a little fear
into him to clear this up.
- Any questions?
- Negative, whitey.
Come on then.
You can stay here, I can
take care of this alone.
- Okay?
- Okay, okay.
Finished.
Who's next?
- So fast?
- Affirmative.
Hey, Sergeant, if you don't mind,
could you tell me how you did that?
Oh!
Fuck! Damn it!
- Cigarette, Sergeant?
- Negative.
How about a "beer"?
Back there is a "Cooler."
They're icy cold. Don’t you feel like one?
No.
You're not from around here,
right, "Sarge"?
No.
And if you don't mind, Sergeant,
where's are you from?
Oaxaca.
And you were in the army?
Hey man, let's get things straight.
My name is Benito Juarez.
And I like to be called
"Benemerito of the Americas."
And to make it even clearer...
...I didn't leave the army
to go around making friends.
I did it to make a shitload of cash.
That's it. Affirmative?
Eh? And so we don't have any problems...
...you can go on calling me Sergeant, or Sir.
And quit that fucking gringo shit...
..."My Sarge" and all that shit.
Is that clear, whitey?
It's fine, Sergeant.
Hey, Cochi?
Already missing me?
Where are you!?
Hold on Cochi, I'm on the way!
Cochi!
Something happened, whitey?
What happened Cochi?
Are you okay?
The Panchos fucking did us in, Benny.
We fucked up.
But how could they do this?
What happened?
Some son of a bitch tipped them off
and so they caught us eating camote.
I barely had time to react and
kill those ones over there...
But Don Francisco and those little pricks escaped.
Where is J.R.?
J.R. and La Muñeca are in there.
Go take a look at them.
Apparently the boss's son
likes them young and tender.
Look how they left my nephew.
We can't do anything, Sergeant.
We'll have to take him to the Boss.
Now we'll see what he's made of.
Yeah.
I'll fucking finish this garbage,
I promise you my son.
I'll kill them like rats,
each and every one of your kids, Francisco!
Francisco, you son of a bitch!
Tell me, damn it!
What was my son doing?
Where were they!?
They ambushed us on the highway, Boss.
There were too many of them.
But I can say, from the bottom of my heart,
J.R. defended himself bravely.
Bravely, my balls!
You don’t think I didn't know my son?
He was a gentle soul.
But I pity you if you aren't telling me the truth.
- Huasteco.
- Yes, Boss.
Do you have enough weapons and ammunition...
...to wipe out my brother?
Yes Sir, the warehouse is full.
They're fucked.
Don Jose!
We just found out.
You can't imagine how much I regret this.
My most sincere condolences.
Doña Mari
- Doña Mari, I'm so sorry.
- Shut up! Damn it!
What a tragedy.
My God.
This is a day of mourning
for all of San Miguel.
For such a brilliant young man
to lose his life like this...
With a promising future in poltics.
Shut up, you idiot!
Yes, yes, forgive me.
This will be a war, cabrones.
If my brother thinks
this is going to stop me...
...he's got another thing coming,
because I'm going to show him who's biggest.
We must remain calm, Don Jose.
War isn't good for anyone.
I pledge before you and our Lord...
...that I and Chief Mancera
will find who's responsible for this...
...so that justice is done and
the death of his son is avenged.
And what do you have to
say about this, Mancera?
Wasn't it your job to stop my nephews?
- Investigations are...
- Idiot! You're to blame, asshole...
Nobody but you can take the blame
for my son death.
If you had listened to my husband,
this would never have happened.
Doña Mari, sorry but you can't
blame it all on me.
The problem is that your husband
has many enemies in the region.
Thank you, dear.
You always read my mind.
And you Felix?
You have something to add?
Then go fuck yourself and find...
...another police chief who has fucking balls
for a change.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
And you!
You cabrón!
You and I have a lot to talk about,
but in the meantime.
Go screw yourself, and take this...
...bunch of useless assholes with you.
- Get the fuck out!
- Sir.
Holy shit.
Oh my love!
What happened, Uncle Benny?
Have you seen what your pals did?
They Killed J.R. and La Muñeca.
Now let's see if you listen to me.
Benny, you need to be careful.
Something good may come of this.
Don Jose swore he would finish off...
...the Panchos, and I think he was serious.
So, you stay inside...
...until things quiet down, It'll get pretty ugly.
And there's gonna be a lot of blood.
I'm serious, cabrón.
The ways of the Lord, as we all know...
...are inscrutable.
But there are certainties here on earth...
...as in heaven that must comfort us...
...even in moments of pain.
Who would imagine that
such a kind young man...
...with a heart of gold as our dear Jesus...
...would find himself, like Christ,
with the Lord in heaven?
The sky, my children, is not only for the Saints...
...but also for men such as
our dear Jesus Reyes.
Rest in peace, so be it.
Revenge Lord.
Revenge is the only thing that I ask of you.
And I don’t mean figuratively.
And just as you took him...
...take all those motherfuckers
who stole him from me.
You'll have to take care of my children, compadre.
Let's see how life treats my poor orphans.
Don’t think like that Cochi.
Most likely nothing will happen.
Don’t fuck around, Benny.
You saw how the Boss
was looking at me.
You know what hurts me
most about leaving this life?
That I won't even get a chance to
meet your godson.
Let me ask you one question.
If Don Jose is going to declare
war on his brother.
Who here is the most badass
motherfucker with guns?
Stop it man.
With all the money...
...that the boss has,
he can bring in anyone he wants.
From here all the way to Guanajuato.
He'll never forgive me.
And he's right.
Think positive, compadre.
Your children need you.
Cochi, Cochi.
A dark-skinned guy who looks like
a soldier told me...
...you need to get home fast.
- Get lost!
- See?
No, no!
No!
Cochiloquito.
No.
JUST LIKE THAT, A SON FOR A SON,
A TOOTH FOR A TOOTH.
Take care of my wife,
and tell her I love her, Benny.
And I'll leave my kids to you.
Yes, Cochi.
What are you doing?
Justice, Benny, only justice.
Let me go with you.
No, this fight is between that
son of a bitch, Don Jose, and me.
I told you, didn't I?
This fucking life is
nothing other than hell, Benny!
Sorry I'm late, but you know
how the situation is.
I had to do six other funerals.
But, let us pray.
Our Father who art in heaven...
Life is worth nothing,
Life is worthless,
It always starts with crying.
just as it ends with crying.
So that is why in this world.
Life is worth nothing.
Listen up cabrones.
After the disaster that occurred in this family...
...the only thing I want
is to finish off that den of rats...
...my brother and his children.
This is what I promised my son
when his corpse was here in front of me.
And I will keep my promise!
And you, fucking Benny!
I know what's on your mind,
so you better lose the idea right now.
Because your friend Cochiloco
was like a son to me.
He was fucked over by the Panchos.
Isn't that right?
And quit walking around with that
sad look on your faces.
You don’t have any feelings.
You're here only
for the fucking money.
If you only knew what we would give
to have our son back.
My whole fucking fortune.
But as this is not possible...
...I have an offer for you.
I'll give you $100,000 dollars...
...for the head of each asshole
who murdered my son.
Do the math, cabrones.
Each one of you may take home more
than half a million dollars.
You've only dreamed of having that kind of money.
But I'll tell you one thing.
I want the heads of these motherfuckers.
And not just the heads of my nephews...
...but also the head of my own brother.
I also want to head of an asshole...
...that I think you know very well.
The head of the man who betrayed us.
And for that, I'll give
$200,000 dollars more.
But one thing I warn you about...
...I pity the asshole who thinks I'm stupid...
...and tries to betray me.
Beware, because this time
I'll not only kill his child...
...I'll chop up the whole family.
Got it?
Come, my wife.
Boys.
When my husband says that we want...
...the heads of my son's killers...
...it's not a figure of speech.
We really want their heads!
Listen up, white folks.
Don’t get me wrong.
But I take it that you guys
are basically pussies.
I can't take the risk that
you'll do something stupid.
So Sardo and I will carry out
the boss's orders.
It's enough for you to drive us
to where we have to go...
...tell us who we have to fucking kill.
Affirmative?
Speaking indigenous language.
Fucking whities.
Fucking pussies.
Sardo here said not to worry about
your part of the money.
Here's the office of Pancho Macana.
He's a bald guy...
Speaking indigenous language.
- Listen...
- He's a pretty tall guy...
Hey!
Damn.
What's wrong with these guys, Benny.
To me it seems like they
must have been trained by the CIA.
- This isn't them, Sergeant!
- God damn it!
Get out of here!
Where do you think you're going?
Let's move.
Go!
Come on.
Are you sure that's all of them, man?
Sergeant, as I told you,
I know all the Panchos well.
I've known them since Don Jose
worked with his brother.
Only Don Francisco is left.
Okay, motherfucker.
You know you're already fucked.
But if you want to go without suffering...
...I'll give you three chances to
say who was snitch...
...who told you where to find
the boss's son.
One...
Go to fucking hell, you cunt!
Sardo.
Two.
Go fuck your mother...
Three.
Let's go, Panchito.
With your brother I was a nice guy.
And I gave him three chances.
But to you, I'm gonna give only one chance.
One.
Who was the snitch motherfucker.
Ah! Okay! I'll tell you.
It was a guy from San Miguel.
That's better.
Nice and easygoing.
And what is he called?
I swear, I swear, I don’t know man.
I just know that they called him Diablito.
I swear I don’t know more than that.
Speaking indigenous language.
Diablito.
So, whities, you are from San Miguel,
aren't you?
Do you know anyone called Diablito?
Nope.
Really, I don't know, Sergeant.
But it shouldn't be too hard to find out.
Let's fucking find the father...
...to complete the Boss's mission.
Sardo, hand me the machetes to proceed.
Hey, you two!
I know I told you not to do anything...
...but you're getting too lazy.
Bring the bags here to carry the heads.
Wait here, whities.
Okay, sons of bitches,
whoever moves gets fucking plugged.
Stop right there, asshole!
Don Pancho Reyes.
We brought some little gifts
from your brother.
Sons of fucking bitches!
LEARN TO RESPECT THE KINGS
OF THE NORTH
YOU SONS OF COCKS AND BITCHES
Diablito.
Listen to me, what did you say to the Panchos?
- Nothing.
- Don't be stupid!
It was you and only you who told Panchos
where to find J.R.
Behave like a man
and tell me the fucking truth.
You know what guys like you are called?
Snitch! Stoolie! Informer!
Double-crosser! Traitor! Rat!
And if you didn’t know, this is
the worst fucking thing to be the world.
Tell me, what did they give you in return?
A gun? Money? Drugs? A car!?
Why did you do this, my boy?
Because J.R. and that son of a bitch Don Jose...
...killed my father, that's why.
Don’t talk bullshit.
Uncle Benny it's not bullshit.
I'm telling the truth, see!
Where did you get this?
One of the Panchos who worked with my father
gave it to me.
He had it because he was there
when my dad was killed.
Do you believe this story is true?
Benny, I don’t know what to say.
That medallion was what your brother
loved most in life.
But when he was killed,
he didn't have it on him
I'm going out for a moment.
I have to find out the truth.
And only one person can give me answers.
No, don’t leave, don’t do anything crazy!
Prepare a bag for my nephew
and don’t open the door...
...for anyone until I return.
- Who the hell is it?
- It's me, Huasteco, El Benny.
Open up.
What's happening Benny?
What's biting you ass so much that
you come at this hour? Come in.
Sit.
What is it?
- You want a Tequila?
- No, Huasteco.
I'm here because there is something
that is just burning me up inside.
What is it Benny?
Huasteco, I want you to tell me the truth.
Who the fuck killed my brother?
Didn't Cochiloco tell you?
May God rest his soul.
Stop rocking the boat and
go back to your bed.
Don’t play the fucking fool.
Look what I found, you prick.
I warn that I will not leave here
until I find out the truth...
...or put a bullet into you.
You choose.
- You really want to know?
- Down to the last detail, cabrón.
See Benny...
Your little brother was a really cool guy...
...but one day he seriously crossed the line.
And Don Jose and J.R. were not pleased.
They wouldn't forgive him.
You and Cochi knew it all along.
We not only knew, but we were also there
when it happened.
And how did they kill my brother,
those sons of bitches?
Come on, man.
Stop putting yourself through this shit.
What do you want, to know everything?
That's up to me, cabrón.
Well, since you're insisting,
I'll tell you the whole truth.
The Reyes killed your brother
worse than a dog.
You remember the Cockroach, right?
It was just like that...
...but with your brother, instead of his tongue.
Don Jose cut off his balls.
What did my brother do for them
to kill him like that?
It was your brother's own fault, Benny.
He was actually fucking around
with none other than...
...Doña Mari.
The boss's own wife.
- Doña Mari?
- And not only once, eh?
Goddamn Diablo.
Your brother was a real piece of work.
I don’t think there was anyone's wife...
...who had not spent the night in his bed.
Let's hope the Diablito
doesn't turn out the same.
What did you call my nephew?
They call him Diablito, don't they?
You were going turn on me, weren't you?
Don’t kill me, man.
I wouldn't say anything.
You're not like the Reyes,
to kill me like a dog.
You're right, Huasteco.
But I'm not taking any risks, cabrón.
How's it going, babe? Is everything okay?
Sure?
Nothing happened?
Okay, I'm on my way.
You'll be alright there, Huasteco?
Take this cash, son.
I'll send you more later, ok?
Damn, get down!
How is it Benny, where are you going?
How's it going, Amaya?
Don't tell me it's another 3-18?
Let me through.
You surprise me, Benny.
I have orders from the boss.
No one is to leave San Miguel.
Cut me a break.
Benny, you know things are bad.
What is that?
Who's there?
Get out of the truck, I have to check...
- You killed him Uncle Benny.
- I had no choice, my boy. Hold on.
Come on, son. It's time.
Don’t forget what I said.
Remember what I told you?
When you get to Nogales.
Oh, not again...
I go to Rancho Grande and ask for...
...Gordo Lopez and say that you sent me.
He'll help me through to the other side.
When I arrive in Phoenix,
I call the number you gave me.
That's right. You're not as dumb...
...as the rest of us Garcias, are you?
Take good care of the money.
Those polleros are greedy bastards.
Here we are.
I love you a lot, uncle.
Sorry for the trouble I caused you.
You are a pretty cool kid.
Just stop doing stupid shit.
Get going.
Take good care of my mother, like I would.
Hold on.
Take this.
Go.
Everything's fine, my love.
No, he didn't cry. He's a Garcia.
Yes, yes I'm going to be there, my love.
What!?
When did those assholes get there?
Hey babe, get out of the house
and leave San Miguel.
Get help from my Godfather.
Yes, yes, yes.
Take the phone and call me.
Yes.
Yes, my love.
I love you, too.
Fuck...
Damn.
FEDERAL POLICE INTELLIGENCE
Okay, now...
How can I help you?
Remember me, Captain?
Sure, you're Cochiloco, right?
No, that was my friend,
may he rest in peace.
They call me Benny.
I'm Benny Garcia
And how are things in San Miguel?
Still boiling?
It gets worse all the time.
So here I am.
Remember the offer that you made?
Of course.
Have you brought me something good, Benny?
Nothing less than...
...all the details about the life and times of
Don Jose Reyes.
- Interested?
- Ah, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, absolutely yes.
Of course.
You have seen that the policy of our President...
...is to convert Mexico into a country of snitches.
And as you know,
I'd make it worth your while.
Thank you, Captain.
Lopez, prepare the cage, we have a canary.
And so, Captain...
In one night, we killed eight men.
In the few months I worked with Don Jose...
...the guy must have whacked about 40 people.
- How long has it been?
- About two and a half hours.
Check it over.
Very good Benny.
Excellent.
It's great that you have
such a good memory.
- Would you like another coffee?
- No, no, I'm pretty nervous.
Captain, it's okay.
Shall we continue?
No, with what we already have,
we can lock up Reyes for the rest of his life.
Wait outside.
So now I can leave, Captain?
No, let me make a call to my boss...
...and fill out some paperwork.
You don’t want me to wait outside?
This is just routine procedure.
- In a hurry?
- Yes, yes indeed.
Señor Reyes?
Good evening.
Ramirez, from the Federal Police.
Listen, I think I have something
that may interest you.
Do you know someone by the name of
Benjamin Garcia?
Where is Diablito, cabrón!
Garcia.
Garcia!
Don’t play dumb.
Tell us where the boy is and you'll
save yourself all this suffering.
Take him out, I don't want him dying here.
Don Jose wants him alive and kicking.
When you see him,
tell him I'll be there with the tapes.
Yes, Captain.
It's a shame, isn't it?
He was good a good snitch.
Hey cabrón.
How much are they offering for your nephew?
$200,000 dollars.
Holy shit!
What I would do with all that money.
If you don't mind my asking,
how much are you guys getting for...
...delivering me to Don Jose?
Only 5000 pesos.
5000 pesos... Shit...
Your boss will be getting
about $50,000 dollars.
Seriously, cabrón?
Cut the shit. You really believe this guy?
No, I don’t know but...
I've seen that narcos operate at a different
economic scale.
It's true.
There's more:
If you let me go,
I give you each $50,000 dollars...
...and I'll throw in a kilo of cocaine.
Okay.
But no funny business...
...or I'll put a fucking bullet in you.
Chief...
Right here.
You just have to untie me to get the money.
Let him go.
Didn't I tell you these narcos
are really eccentric?
Yes.
Look at that tomb.
Give me a hand, boss.
I'll watch him.
We're set for life, partner.
Hey, come on. We agreed on
$50,000 and a kilo of coke.
It's my life savings, man.
Sorry, cabrón. They say you never know
who you're working for.
You're screwed.
Come on, partner.
Holy shit, man.
I think he died.
And now?
What the hell do we do?
Bury him and get out of here, right?
Holy shit, godson!
What happened to you?
I'll tell you later, Godfather.
Better to take me to my "house"
Wait godson.
Be careful.
Lupita.
Lupita!
No one's here, godson.
Can't you tell me what is happening?
Hold on, Godfather.
My beautiful.
Ah!
My love.
Oh you scared me, my love.
My love!
- Take this, my son.
- No.
- Come on.
- Thank you.
Ma, I'm going.
What will you do?
When are you coming back?
Actually, the truth is I don’t think
you'll see me again.
Take care of yourself.
- May God be with you.
- Thank you.
It's crazy, Benny.
You really don’t want me to go with you?
Thank you, Godfather.
I'm leaving my mother with you.
Take care, godson.
In the truck you'll find all you asked for.
Thank you, Godfather.
Goodbye, Mom.
One, two, three testing.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...welcome to the Independence Day ceremony...
...in which we celebrate
Bicentennial of that heroic act.
And to preside over this solemn event...
...we welcome our Mayor...
...Don Jose Reyes...
...accompanied by his wife,
and other illustrious individuals...
...who honor us with their presence.
Halt... Now!
Delivery flag...
Now!
And now ladies and gentlemen...
...our municipal Mayor will give
the "Cry of Independence"
Mexicans people!
Viva  the Bicentennial of Independence!
Viva!
Long live the heroes
who gave us our Homeland!
Viva!
Viva Hidalgo!
- Viva Morelos!...
- Viva!
Viva San Miguel de Allende!...
Viva!
Viva Corregedora Querétaro!
- Viva!
- Viva Doña Josefa Ortiz!
Viva!
Long live the poor people of Mexico!
- Viva!
- Viva Mexico!