OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
After capturing most of
the Arabian Peninsula
with the help of
the Wahhabi Islamic warriors,
Ibn Saud establishes
the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia.
The Wahhabis
were fiercely anti-Western.
They want to go back in time
to a pure Islam that wasn't
threatened by the West.
It was by chance
that we discovered oil.
We were looking for water.
Despite criticism
of foreign presence in the Kingdom,
the King allows commercial
oil production to begin.
The result is the first union
between Saudi Arabia
and the United States.
To accommodate the workforce
the first Western housing
compounds are created.
The strict Islamic laws
enforced outside of these walls
do not apply inside.
West and East came together in Egypt
when President Roosevelt
and Ibn Saud, King of Arabia...
They want America
present there in the kingdom
because we are their security.
The Saudi elite became notorious
big spenders and lost credibility
and respect among
religious conservatives.
In response to the U.S. Support of Israel
in the Arab-Israeli War,
Wahhabi Muslims pressured
the Saudi monarchy to stop pumping oil.
Those who control the flow of oil
hold the Western world hostage.
Prices quadruple.
Oil was an American
national security priority.
The embargo redefined the balance of power
between the oil consumers
and oil producers.
Iraq's battle-trained army
swept across Kuwait's borders at first light.
As a Saudi national,
Osama bin Laden offered his services
to the Royals.
He told them he could
bring his army from Afghanistan
to repel the Iraqi invaders
from Kuwait.
But the Saudis had a better offer.
A half-million troops
from the United States.
His offer rejected,
Osama took to the streets
and mosques to denounce the U.S.,
the Royal Family
and their unholy alliance.
Osama bin Laden this week
again lashed out
at the Saudi Royal Family.
We were tracking bin Laden
since the early '90s.
We stripped him of his citizenship.
When it became clear
that 15 of the 19 were Saudis,
that was a disaster.
A total disaster.
Because bin Laden, at that moment,
had made, in the minds of Americans,
Saudi Arabia into an enemy.
- We are with you to get to...
- The perpetrators of this cowardly attack.
How dare they say they are Muslim!
This is a nation
where tradition and modernity
are in violent collision.
The Al Qaeda is thought
to have been behind the bombing.
A team of F.B.I. agents prepare
to investigate the attack in Saudi Arabia.
The latest terrorist attacks
showcase the great division
between the pro-U.S. Monarchy
and the extremist Wahhabi militants
within the kingdom.
Yeah, come on! Come on!
- Here we go.
- Let's go!
Here you go, man.
Hey, thanks.
Yeah!
Hey, guys,
you might want to move back!
Is this what you're looking at?
Easy.
Out!
Give it up!
Come on, move it!
We need a hit. Come on!
Here we go. No-hitter.
No-hitter.
Come on. Do your worst.
Hello. How are you today,
Sergeant?
Sun is shining.
Wind is blowing.
How bad can I be doing?
And this is the skateboard
that my Grandma Ruth gave to me.
This is my fish Jaws.
And he's a really neat fish.
And this is the day that my daddy says
is the happiest day of his life.
Can you tell us
about that day, Mr. Fleury?
Yeah. You guys want to hear it?
You want to hear the story?
Do you want to hear about that day?
Well, I'll tell you what.
This is December 4
and we were at the hospital all day
and most of the night.
And we was waiting on
this little man to come out.
And then all of a sudden the doctor
showed up and said, 'He's not coming out.'
'We got to go in and get him.'
Like a search team, right?
So what she did was...
- You sure I can tell this story?
- Yeah, go ahead.
So what happened was,
is they took a tiny little knife
then cut right underneath
the belly button,
and they opened her up
and then took her hands and stuck them
all the way in her belly and disappeared.
And she was in there just rustling
and rumbling and looking for something.
Then she started pulling and pulling
and pulling and pulling
and she was pulling,
and all of a sudden she stopped!
Then she looked at me and said,
'Mr. Fleury, are you ready
'to have your world rocked?'
And I said,
'Well, I guess so.'
And so she starts pulling and pulling
and all of a sudden a head popped out.
And I looked down and I said, 'Kevin!'
And then he looked back at me
- and he said...
- Daddy!
Daddy! Yeah.
And that was...
That was the happiest day of my life.
Say that again!
Roddy!
Get out of the car! Get out of the car!
On the floor!
Shame on you.
Please do not panic,
everything okay.
Come. Follow me, please.
Come with me.
There is no God but Allah,
and Mohammed is his messenger.
All glory to Allah.
- Fran?
- Are you getting this yet?
Slow down. I'm at Kevin's school.
What's going on?
Riyadh. We got a lot of bodies
down here, Ronnie.
Hold on, I'm going outside.
I can't hear you. Where exactly?
The Al Rahmah Western Housing Compound.
Oil company employees.
They hit the compound picnic.
How?
Broad fucking daylight.
They blew up a goddamn
softball game, Ronnie.
I mean, kids and everything.
- You understand?
- When?
An hour ago.
Get them away from there!
An hour ago. One bomber.
Shooter crew for diversion.
Over there! Jesus Christ.
Fran, you okay?
Get them on the far side.
Yeah, I'm fine. Listen to me, Ronnie.
You got to get out here.
Do you understand me?
Don't take no for an answer.
All right, I hear you.
I hear you.
- They're not gonna say no.
- Good.
All right.
Hey. Look, Daddy's got to go to work.
All right?
We're gonna do ceramics.
We're gonna do what?
Ceramics?
Well, we'll do ceramics
when I get back, okay?
Who was that?
That was Uncle Fran.
Uncle Fran? What happened?
Some bad things happened.
A lot of bad people out there?
Yeah. But you are not one of them.
Hey, Rex?
How old were you
when your hat was that small?
Come on, buddy.
You got to get up.
We got work to do.
Well, we got to clear out this perimeter.
We got to...
- I got...
- We got to preserve some of this evidence.
Get Jack and Steve
to cover on the far side.
The initial attack,
involving a suicide bomber
and at least two gunmen...
...was apparently designed
to lure...
FBI, Washington D.C.
...followed by
a massive secondary explosion.
Numbers so far, 100 plus killed,
200 plus injured.
Target was a softball game.
The killers wore Saudi police uniforms.
Special...
Special Agent Fran Manner
was killed.
Grant?
Take a stab at the bomb sizes.
From the craters it looks like they used a high explosive,
possibly military grade.
Twenty, thirty pounds of P.E.T.N.
That's something that they have.
Semtex or C-4 if they could get it.
That there. God knows.
That crater looks like a plane
dropped a 500-pounder.
Sir? I, already know the answer to this,
but is there any chance in hell
we get to go over there
and use our hands?
If you already know the answer,
why ask the question?
Just thought I'd ask.
Look, we're not seeing
this kind of planning and execution
- anywhere else, are we?
- No.
I mean, these ain't
hot-wired artillery shells
waiting for Humvees to roll by.
These hits are coordinated.
The planning, timing in big,
broad-daylight, balls-out ugly.
So fucking greedy.
Do we know if they used the uniforms
in the other two attacks?
No, as far as I know
this is the first time for that.
Then you're saying now they got
access to Saudi uniforms?
I mean, baby Jesus!
Is anybody taking credit?
Anybody seen anything on the web?
Haven't heard anything.
Tom, you got anything?
We haven't found anything yet.
How do we know it's not Saudi on Saudi?
Could be. If it's Saudi,
then it's quite probably the work of Abu Hamza.
Osama wannabe.
Lived in Iraq. Afghanistan.
Sir, not to beat a dead horse,
but if there was ever a time for us
to put boots on Saudi sand,
I mean, don't you think this is it?
There's no way, Adam.
They will never allow it.
Then let's just ask.
The Saudi Royal Family cannot appear
as if they're losing control.
If they lose control of their country,
lose control of the people,
they risk losing control of the oil.
And that is not gonna happen.
State Department.
'We are in agreement
with the Saudi security assessment
'that any additional American presence
on kingdom soil represents reckless risk.'
- Oh, come on, risk?
- Yeah.
What's that?
That's not a reckless risk?
Fuck it.
You hang tight.
I'm gonna go get access.
Keep your bags packed.
Keep your phones on.
Some of you are gonna get some calls.
Everyone's terrified,
so nothing moves.
You and your team aren't going anywhere
and this meeting's
just a circle jerk, Ronnie.
Attorney General Young is gonna go
through the motions
because protocol says
we get an appeal.
We'll be on record,
but you expect nothing more.
I met with Prince Thamer at Saudi Embassy
15 minutes after hearing
this morning's news.
And after speaking with Thamer,
I advised withholding
additional U.S. Personnel,
because a large part
of the religious justification
for these bombs is the presence
of current U.S. Personnel.
More boots on Saudi soil
is only gonna make
an already combustible situation
that much more so.
My two cents.
The Saudis have not asked for F.B.I. help.
They've done the opposite.
This is just going to further complicate
an already deteriorating situation
with one of our few remaining allies
in the Middle East.
Rock solid logic.
Well, we would like to be on the record
as saying the F.B.I. would like
an Evidence Response Team
on the ground in Riyadh now.
Doesn't your team in that country
represent exactly the kind
of target that these masters
would die for?
They'd trade 10 of their own
for one of you.
Not to go after criminals
because they might try to harm you
is really not a policy of the F.B.I.
See, we try not to say uncle.
We try.
Let me put it to you another way.
Al Qaeda lost the first phase
of this war.
And they know it.
So a new zero-sum phase has begun.
'If you're a Westerner
or a moderate Arab
'and you won't join us, we will let loose
the truly talented murderers.'
Men like Abu Hamza.
These are operational commanders
who plan, organize, train, brainwash,
preach extreme violence.
These are the men we're fighting.
Duly noted.
Anything else?
Now, as far as the public's concerned
let's try to view this
through F.B.I. agents' eyes.
Is that clear?
Sir, how do you suppose this is viewed
through F.B.I. agents' eyes?
Pardon me?
I said, in this situation,
how do you feel this is viewed
through our eyes?
It's a variation of vengeance.
When one of your own is killed,
agents lose their analytical skills.
Kind of like a...
Thirty-six hours.
We don't do it in 36 hours,
we can forget it.
Agent Fleury, Agent Mayes,
I appreciate your passion.
Quite spirited.
If you were running the F.B.I.,
you might turn it into Patton's Third Army.
Might be a good idea,
I don't know.
My daddy used to fly a helicopter
up in Saudi Arabia.
Is that right?
Now, where would he sit?
Would he sit either here,
or would he sit over there?
No, he used to sit right here.
And you want to know a secret?
What?
My daddy died in Saudi Arabia.
Yeah. Your daddy died in Saudi Arabia.
You know your daddy was my friend, right?
Yeah.
So that means that now you're my friend.
So, since we're friends
you promise to take me flying
- when you know how to fly this helicopter?
- Yeah.
Good. Good.
What sound does it make
when it takes off?
Yeah.
What about...
Yeah, like that, huh?
That's when it's coming in.
How hard you gonna hit
the Royal Family tomorrow in your column?
I'm gonna hit them
with a fucking sledgehammer.
The bombings or other things?
What's other than the bombings?
I know you've been tracking
our investigation on Al-Haramain, right?
Yeah. Royal Family's donations
that end up blowing shit up.
Yeah. Seat's taken.
I need a favor.
I don't do favors, Ronnie.
Listen, Elaine, when this thing breaks
and it's gonna be real,
I'm gonna bring it to you first.
I'm listening.
I need you to call Thamer at the Embassy,
tell him that the F.B.I. is getting ready
to lay out major Saudi VIP indictments
dealing with charity financing
out of this Boston investment firm.
We're gonna freeze a lot of Saudi cash
and roll out some
hardcore embarrassment.
And you tell them
I'm heading up the investigation.
And I'm not the nicest kid
on the block.
That's accurate.
And all I need is 15 minutes tonight.
Tonight?
Come on. Exclusive.
I know you like exclusives.
I'll see what I can do.
Your Excellency,
Special Agent Ronald Fleury.
- Listen, can we talk inside?
- Sure.
There's too many people in there
that know both me and you.
I would like to keep this
as discreet as possible.
I know you have a busy schedule.
It's just, so many people in there.
Why don't we pull up here and talk?
I had an interesting conversation
with a reporter from the Post.
She exaggerates a lot of things.
Me, I consider myself a friend.
A friend of Saudi Arabia.
I just need a little cooperation,
that's all.
What kind of cooperation?
Like clearance to land
on the Prince Sultan's airport tomorrow.
One month would be as soon as we could.
One month. This is gonna go down
one of two ways.
One, the F.B.I. has evidence that
two Royal Family wives donated
$10 million to three
Arab-American cultural centers
right outside of Boston,
and that some of that money
got to Jakarta
and these mosques,
and they have training camps right next to them.
It's just weird to see little kids playing
and then not-so-little kids
playing with guns right next door.
It's just odd.
Don't you think?
You have no proof of this.
How do you know?
It's gonna be big.
It's gonna be a big story.
I mean, it's not just gonna be
in the metro papers.
It's gonna be in the Omaha Herald,
places like the Terrell Tribune.
You, you ever been to Terrell, Texas?
Good chili.
What is your point?
I want in immediately.
Define immediately.
Right the fuck now immediately.
So, what was Fran Manner to her?
He taught her how to shoot.
She introduced him to his wife.
And he got her into the Bureau.
They celebrated her graduation
at the IHOP
until some townie called Janet something.
I don't know,
something not very nice.
So the townie didn't see Fran
coming out of the head,
but he definitely felt
Fran's uppercut shatter his jaw.
Really?
And he didn't get bounced for that?
No. No, Fleury took care of it.
Yeah, I do know the post in Riyadh
was part of the deal Fleury cut to save Fran's career.
Thank you. Janet,
what did Fleury whisper to you this morning?
Grant's age is a liability.
- Hey.
- Hello, sir.
Thanks for volunteering.
Yeah, actually I didn't.
Well, thank you, anyway.
We're going to Riyadh?
Is that right?
- State Department said yes?
- Nope.
White House?
Nope.
- We bringing security?
- No.
This is really gonna suck,
I think.
All right,
well that's very questionable.
Dog giving birth.
'Whelp.'
W-H-E-L-P-S? Whelps?
Yeah.
Bitch giving birth.
Whelp. Next word.
A dog giving birth.
Right on.
Is that what you thought it meant?
I know what it means.
That's why I played it.
And you didn't think it was
a hit and a scream.
Like a 'welt' and a 'yelp'?
Yeah.
I don't have much here,
don't worry about it.
Hey, what are four people supposed to do
over there in five days, anyway?
Aren't you the one that practically demanded
we go this morning?
I didn't say 'I.'
I said 'F.B.I.'
Let's go.
I got it, I got it!
Here it comes.
False alarm.
What's it like over there
on the ground?
It's a bit like Mars.
- Mars?
- Yeah.
Sounds like I didn't pack right.
Well, I will be looked at with disdain
for pretty much the entire time
we're on the ground.
Kind of like South Virginia.
Hey. Go easy on my kin.
Man, it feels like you got
a beast in there, Fleury.
What is it?
You don't think I'm okay?
I think you're not
entirely clear right now.
Look, you want to go?
We go. I got you.
But you got to check yourself.
I'm checked.
Okay. I'm just checking
that you're checked.
You know, I got 15 ties
in my closet from Fran.
- Every Christmas, he'd give me these ties.
- My God.
Fran sent you ties?
He sent me ties, too.
Ties, yeah. Really?
At least 12, 13 of them.
Some of the ugliest ties
I've ever seen in...
- Hey, good-looking ties.
- What?
Very colorful.
I go fishing with those ties.
I'll take you shopping with me sometime.
I'll show you style.
You'll show me style?
You gotta get your L.L. Bean on.
You got to? You probably buy your car batteries
and your shirts in the same place.
That's good. That's good.
Colonel Al Ghazi.
Special Agent Ronald Fleury.
Special Agent Mayes. Special Agent Sykes.
Special Agent Leavitt.
- You have your vests?
- Excuse me?
Vests. You know, stop bullets.
The vests.
Bullet-proof vests.
Yeah, we, we brought them.
We're good, thanks.
Good. I will ask for
your passports and weapons.
Sykes.
What?
Fuck.
There is an Israeli stamp in here.
Is that a problem?
I've been to Israel three times.
Got a grandma there.
Is that all right?
It's okay.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
Your two fallen comrades.
If you please go to the second vehicle.
It's like 150 miles an hour.
You, like,
doing like a breathing thing?
Like a yoga technique or something?
Do you have a problem with this?
Take the iPod.
Yeah, I have a problem.
I wish that I was as calm as you are.
- I like it.
- If somebody was tailing us,
they'd stick out.
Standard operation speed.
Hey, explain to the driver
I get carsick.
You've got to shut up.
You ever been to the U.S., Colonel?
Yeah, I have been there once.
I spent four days in Quantico.
I also saw Michael Jordan play
for the Washington Wizards.
Hey, Colonel, your people got
portable lights on the scene?
Portable lights?
So we can work at night.
- See what we're doing.
- Lights, yes.
We have portable lights.
But your team cannot work at night.
Why? We only got seven days.
We work around the clock.
Five, Mister. You have five days,
and you're not safe at night.
We're safe during the day, huh?
Listen, were the uniformed bombers
brother soldiers?
I don't know.
Driver, are we late or something?
Is there a...
Abu Hamza.
You think he was responsible
for these attacks?
I don't know.
You don't know
the source of the blast.
if there was uniformed officers.
Listen, Mister, Special Agent Fleury.
Forty-seven of my men were blown
into hundreds of pieces.
That will take months
to collect them.
Eighty thousands of officers
across all the country.
Thousands of people
that can forge identity.
I apologize. I'm very sorry
I don't have definitive answers.
Hey, driver, driver, driver!
It's a camel.
That's, well, it's good practice, huh?
Maybe slower,
next time we'll recognize livestock.
Okay. The bathroom through that door.
We tried to give you some privacy.
Actually, I want to put you in the bathroom,
but if it's okay with you this. So...
And we try to find something pink
but I wish it will make the job.
Okay, tomorrow we will start working.
I will come in the morning.
See you tomorrow.
- Al Ghazi.
- Yeah?
Exactly what time are you coming tomorrow?
- Sunrise.
- Okay.
What time is sunrise?
Excuse me!
When I open this door.
Good night.
That's against fire code.
They don't have fire codes here, Sykes.
You're in the jungle now, baby.
Look sharp.
Axl, do you have any more lollipops?
Blood sugar's a little low.
Don't cross this pink line.
Stay back.
You're real butch after a long flight.
'Contrary to
the State Department policy,
'the F.B.I. has sent
an investigative team
'to Saudi Arabia. In so doing,
I have come before this committee
'with a painful admission.
I've lost all confidence in the F.B.I.
'Especially its uppermost echelon.'
That's you, baby.
'Entrenched and outmoded,
the leadership has shown itself fearful
'of the pioneering thoughts this committee
and I have tried to imbue.
'It is thus an agency at contretemps
hindering our every effort.'
And by 'committee,'
I mean the fucking
Senate Select Committee on Terror.
So you're going before
the Senate Select Committee
and not to the President
who appointed you.
Why is that?
I bet the President wasn't
the audience you thought he'd be.
I'll bet the President realized
that you can't have voters asking
why the second longest-serving
F.B.I. Director got fired for doing his job.
For sending agents to Saudi Arabia just
seven months before mid-term elections.
So you want to bet?
Mister Attorney General,
I obviously already have.
I bet my job.
I'm gonna bury you.
You know, Westmoreland made all of us officers
write our own obituaries during Tet.
When we thought the Cong
were gonna end it all right there.
And once we clued in
to the fact that life is finite,
the thought of losing it
didn't scare us anymore.
The end comes no matter what.
The only thing that matters is
how do you want to go out?
On your feet or on your knees?
I bring that lesson to this job.
I act knowing that someday this job will end,
no matter what.
You should do the same.
Which one of you is Ronald Fleury?
Damon Schmidt, State Department.
I'm here to make sure
that you get out of here okay.
- Is this your team right here?
- Yes. All three of them.
Hey, everybody, you're gonna need these.
Electrolytes.
Good to see you.
Some electrolytes for you.
Take that.
You don't want to drop in this heat.
Do you have any idea
how much trouble you're in?
My boss hates you.
He's furious.
When you get back home, you're done.
If you make it back home.
Now here comes the Prince.
You hold onto his hand and you make sure
you don't let go of it until he does, okay?
That's good.
We got to dial down the boobies.
We need to cover these situations.
No verbal response.
All right, everybody,
here we go.
Your Excellency,
Special Agent Fleury
of the Federal Bureau of Investigation
and his colleagues.
You will honor me with
your presence tomorrow at my home.
I'll tell you why this is a win.
You documented it and you're still alive.
I got a plane.
It's fueled up,
it's ready to go,
it's got your name on it.
You guys want to go,
let's do it.
You talk a lot.
A little too much.
You wearing a vest?
You got nothing.
You got nothing, big boy.
- You want to tighten up the Kevlar. Okay?
- All right.
Offer still stands.
I'm always ready to go.
So what'd the Prince say?
That there are more rules
than just not working at night.
Rules? What rules?
It's a slow roll.
This whole trip's gonna be
like deep sea fishing in Florida.
We need more security here
before we go on.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You got a fucking army.
I'm not kidding you, okay?
And don't talk to me with this language.
You pay 700 bucks for a boat,
sit on your can out in the ocean.
Crew jumps around, screams, points,
throws out fish bait, you catch nothing.
Okay, let's go inside now, please.
This is the kind of radical circumstance
that could have seriously upped
Shaq's free throw percentages.
I mean, you take a man,
you ship him off to Riyadh.
- Grant.
- No cell phones, no girls, no booze.
Look at this website.
Nothing but being locked in a gym.
He could have been shooting,
what, 70, 80 percent?
Lakers would still be together.
Kobe and Shaq, lovers forever.
I don't know about that part.
Kobe's a hater.
Fleury, come here and look at this.
It's a website that went up
about a half hour ago,
Al Saha dot something.
They so love to flaunt their work.
Time to go.
You won't need your gear.
Not yet.
That's what I thought.
The remaining rules.
You cannot touch evidence,
please leave it.
You cannot question anyone
without me present,
touch a dead Muslim,
or leave my sight at any time.
Your safety is my primary concern.
I thought your primary concern
would be the investigation.
And you would be mistaken.
I think this is one of those
'something happens to us,
'his head comes off' kind of deals.
You're our babysitter, right?
We call that a babysitter.
Yeah. Who's running the investigation?
General Abdulmalik.
He has given us permission
to walk through the crime scene.
- Walk through? Shit.
- Walk through?
You kidding me?
- Where are you going, Mr. Fleury?
- You're not in charge.
I'm gonna go find somebody that's in charge,
so I can get
some clarification on what's going on.
Okay, there is nothing to clarify.
Yes, the hell there is!
You think I flew over here for 18 hours,
and you gonna tell us we can walk through?
I don't know what kind of game you playing.
I'm not that guy!
Listen.
This is not a game show, Mr. Fleury.
And definitely there are no deals made here.
There is me telling you
what you may or may not do.
And there is you doing it.
- You gonna tell me what to do.
- That's it.
You will be permitted to
walk through the crime scene
when we determine it is safe,
that's it.
Any questions?
By the way,
I don't like your jokes.
What about witnesses?
The witnesses?
So you haven't interviewed
the witnesses?
Not yet.
Can we do that?
We didn't really see anything.
It was so fast and so loud.
So nobody saw anything?
I hit the deck.
The place was going Rambo.
Guns, guns, guns.
We went into our safe room.
- Safe room, what's that?
- That room right there.
Earl got an allowance of about $15,000
when we moved here to build it.
We stayed in here,
till we heard the screams.
Yeah, those kids were screaming,
all right.
That's what got me out of the house.
Them kids.
Which kids are those?
Tracy Jackson.
She lived next door.
She was murdered looking out of her own window,
in front of her children.
Jacksons didn't have a safe room.
Mr. Jackson?
Mr. Jackson. Aaron Jackson?
Yeah.
You keep him away from me!
Hold on, hold on.
Special Agent F.B.I. Ronald Fleury.
You know what?
- That's...
- Whoa, whoa.
They're the ones that attacked us.
We don't know that just yet.
That's what I'm here for.
I just need to ask the boys
some questions about maybe something
that they saw the other night.
What do you want to ask my boys
about the other night?
I told you...
What do you want to ask them about?
You want to ask them about
watching their mother bleed to death?
Is that what you want to ask my boys?
My 5-year-old boy, when I got home,
had a box of Band-Aids
and he was trying to put
his mama's mouth back on.
Is this what Mohammed the prophet...
Oh, come on, man,
let's not have a fight.
- Is this what Allah wants?
- You know that, this isn't...
This isn't gonna bring your wife back.
Does Allah love your kids
more than he does mine?
Does Allah love your wife
Leave me the fuck alone
and do not come back to my house!
I'll leave you alone, but just...
I should have went home
a long goddamn time ago!
This is the big explosion.
About one hour into the rescue.
Where did the water come from?
They hit a water main?
Water main?
Yeah, where'd the water come from?
From a water pipe?
They break one?
No, it's from the tanks
of this fire engine.
This is the water that didn't,
how you say it, evaporate in the blast.
This truck used to be here?
We think so.
This hole is the case.
Your men are contaminating this.
You understand evidence?
Little things that are clues.
Clues can be very helpful
to a fellow trying to solve a crime.
You want to go into the hole?
Yeah! Absolutely.
No.
All right.
Who was running security?
Security here is a combination of police
and National Guards of...
Mr. Sykes! Please come back.
Please.
This vehicle was stolen.
A team outside the blast radius,
shooting at anything, everyone.
Sergeant Haytham ended this part.
Were any of the shooters your men?
Real Saudi police?
No, they weren't.
Nice work.
There were two officers in the car.
Both of them were executed.
And those were your men.
I'm sorry.
Car was parked here,
backed in?
Yes.
They were attacked from the front,
so they must have assumed
they were fellow officers.
These guys been identified yet?
Not yet. It's likely that the four men
prayed in the same mosque.
That's enough to identify them?
If it's in Suweidi, yes.
Suweidi?
Suweidi's a known militant stronghold.
Al Qaeda could recruit from the storefronts.
Is there any way we can check out
those surrounding buildings.
Like especially that one right there.
- Why?
- From the posting on the Internet
the attack was filmed from a high vantage point
and that building right there
looks over the whole crime scene.
It's outside the walls.
Come on now,
this is damn insane.
We got enough security to
invade North Korea and Suweidi...
You don't know
what you are talking about.
Can we just ask?
Okay.
All right.
We'll be in the Community Center.
How many virgins
will be available to you upon entry
into the afterlife here,
if you follow what the zealots follow in this stuff?
Seventy.
That's incorrect.
Hey, buddy, how you doing?
I'm in Saudi Arabia.
Yeah, you remember
where I showed you on the map?
Well, right now I'm sitting
in the gym-slash-hotel.
What?
Yeah, Fran is, Fran's around.
We, we...
Yeah, I saw him.
He is...
He's, he's tall as ever.
Yeah, and we're looking for the bad guy.
And I'm gonna get some sleep.
Yeah, I'm gonna go to bed.
I love you, too.
All right, bye.
We have permission.
Really?
Yeah.
- There's the building. That's the rooftop.
- Yeah.
We have a problem.
What's the problem?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
All right, easy, easy, easy.
Fleury, stop Fleury. Careful. Leave it!
Fuck! Al Ghazi!
Tell me he didn't blow out my eardrum.
Is it fucking bleeding?
It's all right.
There's no blood.
Come on, you okay? Let's get up.
Janet, you okay? Let's get up.
- Are you okay?
- Come on, Janet.
- No, are you okay? He slapped you.
- I'm good. I'm good.
- You sure?
- Thanks. Okay.
- Let me look at you.
Thank you.
All right.
Come on, let's go up.
Fleury, look at this.
There's the front gate,
the police car and the bomb site.
And look.
That's about the same angle, right?
Yeah. Al Ghazi,
have you seen the video on Al Saha?
Look. Look right through there.
Same exact thing.
This is too pretty of a plan
to be hatched in just one day.
He had to come here a couple of times.
This man is a Saudi.
See, if foreigners were here,
someone would say something.
- So maybe Abu Hamza?
- Could be.
Yeah. Then we should ask around.
Get out of here and some people...
They won't tell you anything.
Why not?
He's like Robin Hood to you.
People feel sympathy to him.
Well, we know two things.
We know he was Saudi,
we know he was here.
That's two big answers
in two minutes.
Imagine if we had a couple of days.
General Malik,
he's got his heart in the right place,
but he is clearly not an investigator.
Now listen.
Let me help you.
It's a detonator. Where you...
Yeah, it's a gift from us to you.
We found it at the bomb site.
Run with that.
- Leavitt!
- Yeah?
Hey, where,
where are you going?
You got a lot of evidence here.
We'd like to bag it.
No, no we have five minutes...
Fucking bullshit.
We're here to collect evidence.
Why you say this bad word?
We're not fucking tourists here,
all right.
Why you say these bad words?
I'm getting the kit.
Fleury, talk to this guy.
I would bring a soap
and wash your mouth!
What do you think?
Leavitt!
Yeah, it's Leavitt,
not Livette.
I'm not a goddamn French-Canadian.
Tonight we have the dinner
in the palace.
Miss Mayes, she can't be there.
- It's only men.
- Only men?
Yeah, you know, tradition.
That's gonna be boring.
No women?
No. Just men.
No women allowed. All right.
- Only men.
- Yeah.
- You wait.
- No.
Janet.
He wants to tell you something.
What?
How's your ear? It is good?
It's the right one or the left?
How many princes are there?
Over 5,000.
Does every prince get a palace this big?
Some get bigger.
And who pays for all this?
Exxon? Chevron? Shell?
Serious now,
the Prince will talk to you like subjects.
If he gives you to hold his raptor,
do not flinch.
It is a compliment.
His what? Hold his rapture?
His talons slice bones.
That right?
That's my most prolific hunter.
I try to teach his friend over there,
but I fear it is something
you are born with or not.
You agree, Mr. Ronald?
Innate or not at all?
I do.
What have you seen so far
in our kingdom?
I know that I can arrange a safari
for you and your colleagues.
Safari?
Well...
I'll tell you what I've seen.
I've seen...
I've seen that the man that planned
the worst crime in your kingdom's history
is without a doubt Saudi.
If you walk three kilometers
from the compound,
you will find the rooftop
where the attacks were planned.
I've seen a person in this room
who's 'born with it.'
Colonel Al Ghazi. Everything that I'm telling you
Mr. Al Ghazi told us
while he was observing the crime scenes
and protecting us.
He wasn't even on duty.
So I agree with you that instincts like
this cannot be taught.
Not to falcons,
and definitely not to SANG generals.
I know you want him caught.
We want him caught.
So let us help you.
America's not perfect, not at all,
I'll be the first to say that,
but we are good at this.
Allow us to help your men
go catch this criminal.
The rules for tonight still stand,
but tomorrow is a new day.
All right, Ghazi.
Look at you Mr. Al Ghazi.
- Coming through.
- You feeling your power, huh?
- Yeah, of course.
- You feel his power? He's real powerful.
We made a success tonight,
correct or not?
We need to party.
Okay.
Okay. Give him half, you keep half.
Tell him pass them out
around the compound,
see if they recognize anything.
Let's go.
Need a little check? Huh?
You big queer.
I can... Never mind.
Gonna have to get a little dirty, people.
Yeah, you got to get dirty.
Nasty, filthy!
All right, fellows, what we need to do
is get this water out of here.
So we can see what's really
going on down here.
You understand?
See, something drivable blew up.
Let's dry up this hole to see
if we can't figure out what she was.
All right?
Who's got a pump?
Pump?
Yeah, a pump.
Pump out the water.
You cannot touch any Muslim.
So tell me what to do,
I'll do it.
Yeah, come over here then.
Take this.
- This finger also? I push it?
- Yes, please.
Really clean on the...
That's what's important.
Okay. Good. The non-Muslim bodies,
where are they?
We have them in the next tent.
I need to see them.
Just take a look at these and see
if you recognize any of them please.
Oh, those are horrible.
No, I'm sorry,
I don't recognize either of them.
You know, that chair outside
looks like it gets a lot of wear.
It looks comfortable.
Yeah, it is.
That's my mom's chair.
She spends a lot of time out there?
Yeah, all day.
All day, huh? Where is she?
She's sleeping now.
Then let's wake her up.
I've seen him.
When?
Like a week ago.
Twice, I've seen him
watering with the garden crews.
And I thought that was funny.
Funny how?
He was a Saudi, I'm pretty sure.
The gardener.
- Yeah?
- Well, Saudis, like Americans
don't do manual labor.
Blowing leaves is beneath them.
The gardener. We know who he is.
I want to take you somewhere.
Where?
Someone who can lead us
to catch the big dogs.
More like the big fish.
Big fish?
Yeah, big fish.
A dog... A dog is more bigger
than a fish.
Yeah, I don't...
I didn't make it up.
Don't count on me
to do the things I've done before
So why'd you get into this,
Al Ghazi?
Into what?
Being a cop.
Why'd you get into being a cop?
I mean, with all this violence and chaos,
it seems so crazy.
It's because of...
- The Green Beast.
- The what?
The Green Beast.
What the hell is the Green Beast?
It's a TV show when I was kid.
You know, a man who turns green
when he's very angry,
he turns green and...
Oh, oh, oh, yeah, the Hulk.
Yeah, you know. He was killing just bad people,
because they did wrong.
Yeah. Yeah, 'Don't make me angry.
You wouldn't like me when I'm angry.'
Ah, you know also Steve Austin?
Yeah, Six Million Dollar Man!
Now, that's my shit.
That's my shit.
What? You need bathroom, you mean?
No, no, no.
- I can stop here if you want.
- No, no, no.
Cause when those lights go on at night
And light up the playgrounds then
Sir? Thank you.
Something cooking.
That's a gurney.
Son of a bitch.
Oh, God. You know what
those sons of bitches did?
They blew up an ambulance.
Oh, man. Now that is nasty!
Low-down.
I'm 42 years old.
I have two daughters and a son.
Beautiful son.
And I find myself in a place
where I no longer care
about why we are attacked.
I only care that 100 people woke up
a few mornings ago,
had no idea it was their last.
When we catch the man
who murdered these people,
I don't care to ask even one question.
I want to kill him.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
So, is your first name Colonel?
What?
Your first name.
What's your first name?
Faris.
Yeah.
Officer Faris.
Friend, hold up!
Shit. Give me that shovel.
Oh, we got something good, man.
That grapple?
Get the keys to it.
I need it down here.
Thanks, bud.
See that man, through the window?
Yeah.
Izz Al Din.
He joined bin Laden when Al Qaeda
brought the fight to the Royal Family.
- Does he know where bin Laden is?
- No, no, no, no, no.
'Cause that'd be a real big promotion for me,
if I could get that one.
He turned himself in last year
during an amnesty.
He's now part of a new government effort,
to balance the experience of Saudi youth.
- Oh, he's doing community service.
- Yes.
- Okay.
The man who made war on Al Rahmah
is someone his age.
A man who can plan mass murder
of women and children
and then go home and sleep soundly,
that kind of man
is supremely difficult to catch.
How does he know he slept soundly?
Because he hasn't stopped.
You stop only when dead faces
don't let you sleep.
Is that why you quit?
Seventeen days without sleep
will make you quit anything.
American military detonator.
Yeah.
How would they get it?
There are several ways to get
this military equipment.
But not everyone can get it.
Could Abu Hamza get 'em?
Absolutely, yes.
Then ask him if he knows
where I can find Abu Hamza.
Did you say something funny?
'Cause I didn't say something funny.
Abu Hamza, he is like ghost.
Abu Hamza like a ghost.
Yeah, I got that.
I understood that.
You need...
Yeah, prayers, luck and...
Handshakes.
Every bomb maker at some point
gets bitten by his own work.
Okay, chief.
It's hospital identification.
- You know it?
- Yes.
Call it in.
Look who got the big clue!
It's some pretty soft skin,
I'll bet you, too.
You know,
that mud looked pretty good.
Hey, hey, come on,
that's my only shirt, Grant!
The ambulance was stolen
from King Fahd Hospital,
three days before the bombing.
Okay.
I got 20 men that rotated shifts
on the stolen ambulance.
One of them is very important.
He's in our interest.
His name is Muaath Al Abdullah.
This is Fahd Al Abdullah, his brother.
The one that Haytham shot.
So where's Muaath?
We are going now there.
Let's go.
Bring your vests.
Fingerprints are on the other side.
I'm not looking for fingerprints.
Then what are you doing?
Fingers.
Pictures of the compound.
American Embassy.
Japan.
It's the Coalition.
All these countries have troops in Iraq.
This is meaningless, man.
This is pointless.
What he say?
- The Prince.
- Fuck.
Ghazi.
Was anyone hurt?
No, nothing.
Everything under control.
- Relax.
- Were there any pictures taken?
No picture. Nothing, the team was safe.
Everything good.
I'm taking them out of here.
They're getting on a plane
as soon as the Prince leaves, all right?
Where are they right now?
- They are inside.
- Are they?
Hello. Yes, sir, everybody's safe.
No, I'm next to the corpses right now,
but I don't think
this is the end of this, sir.
To me this doesn't feel anything
like senior leadership.
Yeah.
Yes, sir, I do. I do.
Fleury!
Hey.
- Schmidt, you all right?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
- Mmm-hmm.
All right.
Don't throw up on your tie.
- Want some water?
- No, I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yes!
You lucky bastard, Fleury.
Congratulations.
You won the hand on the river card.
Schmidt, we didn't win anything.
These are just teenagers.
Kids. Insignificant.
I'm looking at one, two, three,
four bad guys, a whole lot of guns.
This is good stuff.
You did good. Pack up.
Revel in the fact that when you get home,
for a few weeks,
your shit's not gonna stink.
All right?
Turn those frowns upside-down, people.
This will be pitched as a stunning
Saudi-only counterpunch,
killing those responsible
for Al Rahmah.
The Al Jazeera is gonna play up the fact
that there's an F.B.I. presence here.
Hello. Put that down.
Put it down.
Yeah. You got it.
It's time to go home.
The four of you are on a plane now.
Four vehicles will be left behind
when the Prince and the press leave.
You'll convoy straight to B.A. Flights
into Dulles.
Last-minute fares come out
of all your pockets.
I tried to get you an upgrade.
Doesn't look good.
Check at the counter. All right?
You guys are heroes. Fly safe.
I'm going straight
to Diamond Dan's
and I'm gonna order six P.B.R.'s.
Pabst, Sykes? Really?
Yeah, first thing.
Best beer on the planet.
Is that how you get laid?
You go and you take a couple Pi-Phi's and you...
So, Al Ghazi, what do you think?
What's going on in that head of yours?
- Haytham, you guys drink that stuff, Pabst?
- Amateurs.
- What is it?
- It's a small win.
It's beer.
Reminds me of when they hit the towers,
first time, in '93.
You remember how they caught the cell?
- Car bomb.
- Yeah.
He went back to get his deposit
on the rental car.
$400. Stupidity.
Then nine years later
they come back.
I got a feeling I'm coming back too.
Yes, you will.
I didn't even know
you could still buy that.
It only comes in keg form,
doesn't it?
Oh, Schlitz, Pabst, sure.
Do you think they just hand
that blue ribbon out? Do you?
It's not just some cute little name.
It was just Pabst.
And then they won a ribbon.
- And now it's Pabst Blue Ribbon.
- You ever have canned beer when
- you're doing sensitive work?
- Haytham?
You guys have Pabst Blue Ribbon out here?
Oh, you don't even have
- beer out there.
- No, you can't drink beer.
- They don't have beer.
- No pork, no beer.
Yeah, I used to do
keg stands in college.
Oh, yeah?
Well, what, does that mean that you
don't like things
that are awarded the blue...
Brake!
I'm still locked in.
Get me out.
- What are they doing? Hold onto him!
- You gotta take that.
Hey, Leavitt, hold on!
Don't do it!
Hold on! Hold on!
Come on, Leavitt, hold on, baby.
Fuck you!
I got you!
Shit!
Fleury! Fleury! Fleury!
There's more of them!
Fleury! Fleury!
Leavitt!
We gotta move!
Al Ghazi, you've gotta put your foot
in this motherfucker. Let's go!
I put it! I putting foot!
Motherfuckers!
I'm gonna fucking kill them!
We cannot lose him, you understand?
We can't lose him.
If we lose him, he's dead.
Give me a MAC. Give me a MAC.
I see it!
There he is right there,
let's go!
Yes, yes.
Let's move. Let's move.
Take the left, take the left, take the left.
- Let's go, let's go, let's move.
- Come on, faster.
You've lost him!
Damn it, you lost him!
I have not lost him!
I see him! He is in front!
There he is, there he is!
Punch it! Punch it, Al Ghazi!
Watch it, he just turned,
he just turned.
He's up there.
He's right there, don't lose him.
Watch out, watch out,
watch out, watch out, watch out!
Khaled! Khaled!
- He went to the left!
- Take a left!
You're gonna lose him!
Do not fucking lose him!
No, no, it's Suweidi.
This is not good area.
We shouldn't be here.
We shouldn't be here!
Suburban to the right.
Mercedes. Mercedes straight ahead.
All right.
- We're in it, we're in it, we're in it.
- You got it.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Reverse! Reverse!
Move, move, move.
Grenade!
Cover!
Move, Al Ghazi!
- You good?
- I'm good.
Go!
Cover me!
There's a blood trail!
There's a blood trail
going into the building!
- Are you good?
- Yeah, yeah, fine.
We gotta get backup.
Look, we don't have time.
We need two to backup here.
The other three go inside.
- Haytham.
- Okay. You good, Sykes?
- Yeah, I got backup!
- Go, go.
- Let's go.
- Go, go, go, go, go!
This is very bad neighborhood.
Yeah, no shit.
Which side of the door
you think Allah is on?
We are about to find out.
Fuck!
It's okay! Malesh! Malesh!
Stay here! Malesh! Malesh.
Stay here! Stay here!
Leavitt! You okay?
Haytham! I got this!
Go inside and see how they're doing.
You okay?
Oh, I have something.
Abu Hamza.
Get out!
Put it down! Put it down!
You put that fucking gun down!
- Put it down.
- Put that gun down.
- Put it down!
- Put that fucking gun down!
- Put the fucking gun down right now!
- Put the gun down!
Ali.
Fuck.
Go, go, go, go.
Hold on. Fuck.
Hold on, buddy. Hold on.
Hold on. Hold on. Breathe, breathe,
breathe, fucking breathe.
It's okay. God, he's just a kid.
He's just a kid.
It's all right, I got you, I got you,
I got you, I got you. I got you.
I got you. Just calm down. Relax.
Relax, relax. Gotta breathe.
You gotta breathe, you gotta breathe.
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
Relax, relax. You gotta breathe.
You gotta breathe.
Let's get a fucking ambulance!
We got 'em. We got 'em. We got 'em.
We got 'em, okay? We got 'em all.
Just relax. Relax, baby.
Come on,
you gotta stay with us.
You gotta stay with us.
You gotta...
Faris! Faris!
Yeah. We got 'em, baby.
We got 'em.
- My condolences.
- Thank you.
This is his son, Sultan.
Sultan. Hey.
Tell him that his father
was a very brave man.
He asks if you know his father.
Yeah.
I knew your father,
your father was a good friend of mine.
All right.
Thank you, Sergeant Haytham.
Thank you.
Thank you, man.
This is to keep away your worries.
Thanks, man.
We testify next Tuesday.
Fleury goes first.
But I'm gonna go through it
with each of you one-on-one,
in advance, just to make sure
we're all on the same page.
If they ask you, if we've talked about
any of this, the answer is
unequivocally no, okay?
You did outstanding work over there.
You hold your heads high.
Fleury.
Tell me what you whispered to Janet,
in the briefing, to get her to stop crying
about Fran, you know, before all this,
before we even got airborne.
What'd you say to her?
You remember?
I told her we were gonna kill them all.
www.moviesubtitles.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org