Scalped.
I saw something similar when
I was ranching in the Dakotas.
Look for any mention of patients
with a connection to the West.
"Dirtier than a Red Injun."
It's in the letter he wrote
to Mrs. Santorelli.
He's witnessed these things
probably as a child.
Here's another one...
Of the patients who match
our description that have
spent time in the West...
These four were sent to
St. Elizabeth's Hospital in Washington.
I think he may have been
a soldier.
- Have you told Kreizler?
- You'll have to tell him.
Come on. We'll go together.
No. Has something
happened between you?
- You're in well over your head.
- You don't scare me, Connor.
I'd very much like if you would
join me for dinner.
Wonder what's gotten into her?
I'm curious how you
propose to gain access
to Bunzl's records.
Laszlo?
Yes, John?
Your attention certainly seems
to be drawn elsewhere
this morning.
If you're referring to the fact I've not
asked about what happened to your face,
it's only because I wanted to
spare you the embarrassment.
What if I told you I'd met
an old friend for a drink?
That resulted in two black eyes?
Sometimes, Laszlo, there are
words spoken between people
that are to be left private.
What about Julia Pratt?
Julia Pratt?
Your former fiancée.
She lives in Washington,
doesn't she?
Will you not take the time
to see her?
Why should I take the time
to see Julia Pratt?
Because you were
in love with her.
I rarely think about
that time in my life.
I've decided it's much better
to look to the future
than dwell in the past.
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
There's a French alienist
named Broca I came across
when I researched
Mary's aphasia.
He believes there's a certain section
of the brain responsible for speech,
another for empathy,
even one for love.
Love resides in the heart.
Nonsense.
The heart is simply a muscle.
Love isn't a mystery
any more than cholera.
- Cholera is a disease.
- The point is,
each part of our brain
has a function,
and that function
is developed or impaired...
== Synced & corrected by MaxPayne ==.
They may as well
blame me personally
for these murders.
I'll soon find myself
tarred and feathered,
and it won't be
metaphorically, either.
Dr. Kreizler is on his way
to Washington,
if it's some consolation.
Your Indians proved
illuminating, sir.
He believes there may be
some connection
between our killer and the West.
Go on.
I believe I should have gone
to Washington myself.
But that's not why you're upset.
I'm not entirely insensitive
to the hidden currents
between people.
Dr. Kreizler may need
your assistance
to gain entry into certain
Federal institutions.
I have a friend there.
He knows everyone in town.
- Hooker's Division.
- How's that?
I was referring to
the neighborhood.
During the war,
General Hooker and his men
used to frequently enjoy
the hospitality offered here
in their offduty hours.
Your finest whiskey, darling.
And bring yourself back here
as soon as possible.
- No.
- Make it two.
Mind if I ask
what the other fellow looks like?
I'm sorry. The other fellow?
Commissioner Roosevelt said
you work at
the Bureau of Indian Affairs?
Commissioner.
Theodore certainly has
a way of falling up.
Falling up? Yes, well, there are
some men who have a way about them
that even when they fail,
they succeed.
My friend Moore here
is hoping to examine records
of unsolved massacres that
took place out West. Unsolved?
Not many of them,
I can tell you.
We'd like to have a look anyway.
Would you care to dance, Mister?
I'm afraid I have two left feet.
I would only embarrass myself.
You look like the kind of man...
Thank you, but, no, thank you.
You got a taker here, sweet pea.
Come by my office
in the morning.
You're Dr. Kreizler.
I heard a rumor
you were on the premises.
I saw you speak at Johns Hopkins
some years ago.
Dr. Ignatius Blunt.
It truly is an honor.
May I ask the... the purpose
of your visit?
I'm looking for someone who was
once a patient here.
- His name?
- Rudolf Bunzl.
Yes. He was a soldier.
Served in the Army of the West,
if I recall.
Tall, early 30s.
I believe he suffers from
some sort of facial deformity,
something congenital
or acquired in his youth.
No, in that case,
I'm not sure he's your man.
There was someone else
released years ago.
I don't recall his name.
He had a most, um...
horrific tic.
A tic?
Yes, intermittent
and violent contraction
of the ocular and facial muscles.
What happened to him?
Iggy?
What have I told you about
bothering our visitors?
I was just speaking with
Dr. Kreizler about a patient.
You know we never discuss patients.
But he's a doctor.
Iggy?
It was a honor to meet you,
Dr. Kreizler.
Army surgeon.
Hacked off a few too many limbs
at Gettysburg.
Never quite the same.
I'm afraid I've some bad news,
Dr. Kreizler.
The patient you were
inquiring after is dead.
Our records indicate that
Rudolf Bunzl died
and was buried at Arlington...
let's see, four months ago.
I'm, sorry to disappoint you.
Dr. Dillman, was there
a patient here some time back
who suffered from a facial tic,
one with intermittent
and violent contractions
around the eyes?
Doesn't ring a bell,
but then, I'm fairly new here.
Do you mind if I have a look
at the records?
Dr. Kreizler, I was instructed
to offer you assistance.
I believe I've done
what was asked of me.
I'll be searching within a very
narrow range of indicators.
We have over 10,000 records
stored here.
I've all afternoon.
The type of mutilations
tells you which tribe
is responsible.
These were... Well, it's hard
to tell from a photograph.
What's that in his mouth?
That, my good man, is what
every fella thinks with,
and I'm not talking
about his brains.
We were the same,
took our fair share of peckers
and ears along the way.
Boys will be boys.
Chops?
Shh!
- Chops?
- Lunch.
There's a splendid place
on the Hill that serves them.
Good beer, too.
I think I'll poke
through the rest of these.
Just leave them on the table
when you're done.
Teething. I'm sure that's what it is.
She's at that age.
Well, is there anything I can do?
Clove oil.
Dab a bit on your finger and
rub it into your baby's gums.
- It acts as a mild analgesic.
- How much?
Don't worry.
It's only a bit of clove oil.
I want to pay for it, Mr. Freewater.
I can take care of my
daughter alone. Here.
I'll take this one. Here.
I can tell by the expression
on your face
you were as successful as I was.
- How successful were you?
- I found nothing.
Every unsolved massacre
was inevitably attributed
to marauding Indians.
They seem to have become a symbol
for all forms of savagery.
What did you find?
The man we came to inquire after
is dead.
- Dead?
- As a hobnail.
Upon further investigation,
I found another soldier,
one who fit our circumstances,
but had never served
further west than Chicago.
And I found a murder
that fit our circumstances
but took place
in upstate New York.
The local constabulary
investigated
and attributed it
to marauding Indians,
supposedly seeking revenge
on a minister and his wife.
Where? What town?
New Paltz.
What is it?
Look at this. The other soldier
that drew my attention...
Corporal John Beecham.
Suffered from
a most noticeable facial tic.
Look at his place of birth.
New Paltz.
Coincidence?
I need to see the official
records, of course.
In the meantime,
ring Miss Howard.
- Let her know what we've found.
- Me? Why don't you tell me
what happened between
the two of you?
She's to use her authority to find out more
about this massacre from local officials.
Miss Howard? Telephone.
- Police headquarters.
- Yes, sir.
This is Miss Howard.
Sara? Listen to me.
We've found something.
There was a massacre
in New Paltz.
It's possible it was committed
by a man named Beecham.
John Beecham.
Go on.
16 years ago,
a minister and his wife,
savagely murdered,
supposedly by Indians.
They had a son that survived, and
he lives not far from Boston.
Kreizler and I intend to go
speak with him.
- His name's Adam Dury.
- Shall I meet you?
No, no. Kreizler feels you'll
be more useful where you are.
He'd like you to contact
the authorities in New Paltz
and see if they have any more
information on the murders.
But I can't just stay here.
Why isn't he calling me himself?
What?
Sara?
- I'm here.
- There's one more thing.
You're to inform the Isaacsons
they're to be
on the first train west
to rendezvous with John
Beecham's former commander.
I'll let them know.
- Sara?
- Yes?
Be careful.
Do you think we'll
see any buffalo in North Dakota?
If they haven't all been killed.
What about Indians?
You know, why should I care
if that's Esther's baby?
- You don't believe me, do you?
- Believe what?
That I don't have feelings
for Esther.
I came into this world
two minutes before you did.
I know you better than anyone.
I know you better
than you know yourself.
You're in love with Esther.
Do you regret
not visiting Julia?
We hardly had time.
One makes time
when one wants to.
Then there's your answer.
I can't believe
we're bypassing New York
and going straightaway
to Godknowswhere.
Newton, Massachusetts.
May I ask, why are you
so interested?
Adam Dury lives there.
I meant in my seeing Julia.
I remember
when you first met Julia.
Your company was rather dull
because you could think
of nothing else.
What does it feel like when
you're in the first throes?
Restlessness, above all.
Your mind is never still.
You wait at a street corner in
case she happens to pass by...
attend a party
that you'd otherwise dread
in hopes she's been invited.
And you try to bring
every conversation back to love.
Are you Miss Howard?
- Yes.
- I'm Eliza.
Mrs. Kirkpatrick sent me
to fetch you.
From the boarding house?
Yes, Miss. Let me take your bag.
It'll be dark soon.
Mrs. Kirkpatrick said
I should take you
over to the old Dury place
in the morning.
What do you sell?
What do I sell?
Most of the boarders
we get are salesmen.
I work for
the New York Police Department.
I never heard of a lady working
for the police,
especially in New York City.
I'm the first.
Excuse me?
What are those mountains?
You mean the Gunks?
The Gunks?
Shawangunks. Locals call 'em
"Gunks" for short.
Do people climb them?
Yes. I climb them myself.
You?
Why shouldn't I?
Newton, Massachusetts.
I believe there's a factory
there that makes a biscuit
my grandmother is very fond of.
- Your grandmother?
- Yes, made with figs.
Ghastly sounding,
but she swears by them.
I think it best
we stay the night
and attempt to speak
to Mr. Dury tomorrow.
And no mention of
the Dury name to anyone.
You think there might be trouble?
Let's just say, I'd rather
he wasn't expecting us.
It's not respecting the dead.
- What isn't?
- This. You're sightseeing,
acting like a ghoulish tourist
visiting a gravesite.
People visit the pyramids.
They're gravesites.
That's different.
This is Sitting Bull.
Battle of Little Big Horn.
Custer's Last Stand.
Are you the men waiting to see
Captain Miller?
Yes. I'm Detective Sergeant
Marcus Isaacson,
and this is my brother...
You've come all this way to
inquire about Corporal Beecham?
- You remember him?
- Remember him?
It's been 10 years, and I can't
get him out of my head.
His army records state
that he was sent
to the Government Hospital
for the Insane
after being found unfit
for service.
It says you were the officer
who relieved him of his duty.
It was the Regimental Surgeon
who declared him unfit to serve
and sent him back east.
Would you say he was
a good soldier?
At first. He was disciplined,
attentive to detail, efficient.
Didn't get on with the other men,
but I put that down to him
being religious
and disapproving of
their whoring and drinking.
I've seen men driven to
bloodlust out here in the West.
Never in a place like Chicago and certainly
not in the course of a labor riot.
You're talking about the Haymarket riots?
That's right.
We were called in
to keep the peace,
but the violence got ugly.
A bomb thrown amongst police,
rioters shot and killed.
I mean, you must be halfcrazy
to do what he did that day.
What exactly did he do?
I came across him
sitting astride a dead striker,
Young man... boy, really...
İn a back alley.
He was stabbing at the body
with a knife, over and over.
That wasn't the worst of it.
He was naked.
Naked?
From head to foot,
drenched in blood.
Down there, between his legs,
he was stiff as a flagpole.
Jesus!
That child ever stop bawling?!
Well, it'd have helped if
her father took her for once.
That's enough from you, woman.
Let her suck on some candy.
Thank you, Mr. Byrnes,
but she's got no teeth.
Why don't you give it to
your namesake then?
Here you
go, young Thomas. You take it.
Got a tongue in your head,
haven't you? What you say?
- Thank you, sir.
- You're welcome, young man.
Go on, git.
All o' ya.
They was two days
snooping around Washington,
in and out of various buildings
and such.
Do you know what
they were looking for?
Cowboys and Indians, it seems.
Whoever does solve
these murders,
one thing's for certain...
İt's not going to be...
- That alienist?
- I'm not going to let him throw
30 bloody years of police work
out the window.
Do you understand me?
I'll let the Swede know
of your concerns.
You knew them?
The Dury Family?
I knew them.
The whole town knew them.
The reverend and his wife,
Adam, their oldest.
My brother went to school
with the youngest.
Japheth.
He was the one
kidnapped by Indians.
That's what the papers
said at the time.
Whoa.
Can't keep the Sheriff waiting.
House is this way,
what's left of it.
You the gal from the city?
I'm Miss Howard of
the New York Police Department.
Well, I can't say Mr. Roosevelt
is a popular man in these parts.
Thank you for agreeing to meet.
My pleasure.
Sheriff Early, are you familiar
with what happened here?
I was a deputy at the time.
I seen what was done to 'em.
And what was done to them?
Butchered.
Like hogs.
This here's
the Adam Dury farm, gentlemen.
Ho, now. Ho. Thattaboy.
Hello?
Mr. Dury?
Anybody here?
Mr. Dury, we only want to talk.
Don't suppose you know
where your master might be?
Good morning, Mr. Dury.
Mr. Dury, my name is
John Schuyler Moore,
and I work for
"The New York Times."
We've only come to talk.
We know you'd already left home...
when the event occurred.
"Home."
That's a poor description of it.
You ask me, old Reverend Dury
couldn't save anyone's soul
with his hellfire and damnation,
let alone redskins.
He weren't a missionary
very long 'fore he was
driven off the Plains
and back to civilization.
And when he come back here,
he brought pictures with him
of dead white folks...
Folks he'd seen mutilated
in the Minnesota Massacre of '62.
Pictures?
Photographs.
Awful, they were.
Used to show 'em
to the town children,
tell 'em that's what would happen
if you're not Godfearing.
Nobody liked him much...
or his wife.
And nobody blamed them Injuns
for coming all the way back here,
stealing their boy Japheth
and getting revenge on 'em
for whatever they done out West.
You really think it was Indians
that killed them?
That's what the record say
happened 16 years ago,
and that's what I say
happened 16 years ago.
So if you have no more questions,
I'll be on my way.
Don't believe a word he says.
Mr. Dury, we were hoping
to ask you some questions.
I don't speak ill of the dead...
even if they deserve it.
That is why you're here,
isn't it?
We've no intention of disparaging
your parents, Mr. Dury.
It's the police investigation
of their deaths
that we believe was flawed.
Perhaps you'd care to talk about
a different aspect of the case.
Tell us about your brother.
Japheth?
What do you want to know
about him?
He'd be in town sometimes
after school,
fetching something
for his mother
or running errands
for his father.
He didn't have any friends,
not with that condition of his.
What condition was that?
His face was always twitching,
like he was in terrible pain.
Adam Dury didn't want
his parents' house. Nobody did.
I don't blame 'em.
It's full of ghosts.
I taught him
how to hunt with snares,
skin animals.
Thought it would do
some good, but...
but even then, he couldn't
escape her shadow.
"Her shadow"?
My mother. She was a...
A woman with no heart.
With me, it was mostly indifference,
but, with Japheth...
with Japheth, she was
at him all the time.
Telling him that he wasn't hers...
İt was maneating savages
left him on our doorstep.
She said that he was the bastard
child of the Red Injun.
And the only time
my poor brother's soul
knew any peace was when he was
in those mountains, climbing.
The spasms in his face
would stop,
and it'd be still as a pond.
He stuck to the rock face
like a lizard.
I never seen anyone like
Japheth Dury.
You said he had no friends.
Did he climb alone then?
Mostly, though there was a time
someone else climbed with him.
Another fellow, a farmhand.
Older. Took a liking to Japheth.
I trusted him
to look after my brother.
He betrayed that trust.
Mr. Dury, what do you think
happened to your brother?
Japheth came home one night.
He was upset.
Sobbing, cursing...
Bleeding... down there.
I'd have ripped that man's throat out
myself, I'd ever gotten the chance.
This man... İs he still around?
In a manner of speaking.
- What manner is that?
- In a manner not of this Earth.
He died up in the Gunks.
Fell off a thousandfoot cliff.
That was right around the time
the Durys were killed.
Do you think it was an accident?
An accident?
His throat was cut from ear to ear.
His eyes were missing.
Do you remember his name?
I won't never forget it.
Beecham.
George Beecham.
Extra! Extra!
Come and get your newspapers!
Theodore.
I recently had a meeting
with Chief Byrnes.
ExChief Byrnes.
Excuse me. Could you box
that up for me, please?
Certainly.
Look, there's
no reason for you and Byrnes
to butt heads over
this child killer.
People aren't ready
for this new highfalutin
form of investigation.
They just want
this son of bitch caught.
It'd scare the people
if they were to find out
that an alienist could figure out
who the killer was
before their
police department could.
Why are you telling me this?
Because faith is a terrible thing
to take away from a man, Theodore.
It's like
taking away his future.
You can't stop the future.
The facial spasms,
the hunting, the climbing...
İt has to be him.
I don't know why, but...
I almost feel sorry for him.
The better angels of our nature.
Laszlo, are you all right?
I don't believe it's hit bone.
You need to tie it off.
Why do you think we've been
followed all the way up here?
Because we know too much.
John, if I don't get away
and you do,
I need you to give someone
a message.
You'll have to deliver
that message yourself,
as I have no intention
of either of us dying today.
Laszlo, we must hurry.
I think it's best
if we stick to the woods.
Is the pain better or worse?
Hard to tell.
I think my brain has
already habituated to it.
What did you want to tell me?
Your message.
It's nothing.
I'm not a fool, Laszlo.
I've been in love enough times
to recognize that look.
"Dull," I think you called it.
Does she know how you feel?
Not the extent of it.
And is it reciprocated?
Yes.
Of course, I...
I suspected it all along, but
to actually hear you say it...
She's wonderful.
She'll make you very happy.
Look after her, Laszlo.
I shall do my best.
Well, I suppose I can brag that
I introduced the two of you.
I'm not speaking of Sara.
Who then?
Mary.
Mary?
I know it's hard to comprehend.
I've questioned my own feelings
many times.
I told myself it's concern
and duty on my part,
dependence on hers.
And naturally, I realize
how inappropriate it is, but...
there are certain things
a man cannot control.
I told you,
love resides in the heart.
Nonsense. It's still physiology.
My brain reacts to qualities
in her that I lack in myself...
Kindness,
warmth,
courage.
Humility.
That, too.
No one deserves it more.
You were jealous.
Come on.
Thank you, Mary.
If I didn't know better,
I would think that you never
wanted your room back.
Must be the Doctor.
Good evening, Miss. Um...
Pardon us
for letting ourselves in.
Is, the good Doctor home?
I mean, certainly,
he must be home by now.
We'll just have a look around.
Dr. Kreizler?
Where is he?
Upstairs?
I'm sure you've spent many
a fine evening up there.
Cat got your tongue, has it?
Fine.
I'll have a look for meself,
so...
What do you think you're doing?
Answer me.
Run, Mary! Run!
Run!
Kreizler!
Kreizler! Where in the name
of God is he?
It's like that, is it?
Come here, you filthy shag!
Me Leg!
Aah!
Come here. Aah!
Give me that. Aah!
Aah!