Who are the real-world Illuminati ?
Find out @ saveanilluminati.com
WOMAN: Of course,
I've known the family for years.
I've watched the children grow up.
And I can honestly say
they've been the perfect neighbours.
They've been no trouble at all.
So, I can't believe...
..anything like this could happen
right on our doorstep.
Listen, they've had their ups
and downs. Who hasn't?
But I never, ever dreamt...
..it would end like this.
WOMAN: Well, they moved down
from London, er...
..over 40 years ago now
to start a family.
Mum, Dad, three kids.
Well, it's the perfect place
for kids to grow up, isn't it?
Vivien was pregnant
when they arrived and...
..even then,
she managed to look good.
And she worked, too. She had
a hairdressing salon in town.
Of course, she had to give all
of that up when Terry got ill.
And over the years, we've become...
well, not just neighbours,
but friends.
Hi, Mary.
Hi.
MARY: So, Helen is the eldest child.
And the cleverest.
You always knew Helen would do well.
RINGING TONE
Hi.
How are you getting on?
Finished the back wall?
Yeah, almost.
It's going to need replastering,
though.
'Is Lily back yet?'
Yes, she's just walked in.
Say "hi".
She says "hi".
'Did you get something for tonight?'
Yup.
Yeah, I got the wine.
'You didn't forget my stuff?'
And the dry-cleaning.
'Can you take my shirt
out of the drier, please,
'and hang it up straightaway
so it doesn't get creased?'
Yeah, straightaway.
'Thanks, bye.'
OK, bye.
MAN: Two, three, four and lunge.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Into side. One...
MARY: Jake was born four years
after Helen.
Oh, he...
He was a naughty little boy.
But deep down,
he had such a good heart.
You could forgive him anything.
And he's turned into a lovely dad.
One. Come on, push.
Hold the butt.
Three...
MARY: Natalie was the baby
of the family.
First, she was going to be a dancer.
And then an actress.
And then an artist.
But it all came to nothing.
And she ended up
in just an ordinary office job.
PHONE RINGS
MOANING
RINGING CONTINUES
HE MOANS
Shh...
Hey.
Yeah, he's busy at the moment.
Can he call you back in ten?
Great, OK. Bye.
Oh, Christ...
Ah!
Oh...
How do you do that?
Yeah, well, don't worry about me.
Hey...
Who was that on the phone?
Your wife.
Mmm, these are good.
Did you make them?
Huh!
Mary next door.
I mentioned that you were all coming
over and, suddenly,
she appears with a plate of...
HELEN: Coo-ee!
Ah, finally!
I'm sorry we're late.
Like London buses.
Oh, you look nice.
Sorry, my fault.
Crazy work day.
Hi.
Hi, Mum.
I would much appreciate it
if you would all clear your rooms
of everything that you want to keep
because I want to...
How's work?
OK, thanks, although a bit...
Stressful, yeah.
What are you head of now?
I'm acting CEO.
CEO, what does that stand for,
Chief of Eating Out?
Oh, here we go...
She is in charge of three hospitals.
You're right, that is a big deal.
Do you want to tell us about that?
Well, I've been brought in
to turn round this Trust,
which is failing so badly.
HE FEIGNS A YAWN
OK, OK.
Thank you, very funny.
Now, just stop it.
Because I want
to tell you something.
Wine, or are you still on the wagon?
Er, no, still rolling along.
Stop it, please.
Make it a large one.
Shh!
Just stop it.
Now, there's something
that I want to tell you all.
I have met a new...
friend.
A man.
As in a...?
A boyfriend?
Well, yes.
What?
Bloody hell, Mum, you dark horse!
Hey, why didn't you tell us?
Well, I'm telling you now.
I, you know,
didn't want to say anything
until I was sure of my feelings.
So, you mean, you're in love?
Nats, for God's sake.
Shush, shush for the minute.
Who is this person?
What's his name, this lover boy?
His name is Mark,
and he's a retired doctor.
A surgeon, actually.
CAR PULLS UP
Dad's only been gone a year.
It's over 18 months.
You expect her to sit around
mourning for the rest of her life?
No, that's not what I'm saying.
Dad wouldn't have minded.
Well, he's not here to say, is he?
No, we just want her to be happy.
We only scattered his ashes
in March.
Oh, Jake, shut up.
Why should I shut up?
Dad would be perfectly OK
with Mum...
I don't care what your father
would have thought.
God, he was no angel.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing, nothing.
It's just that...
Look, this is not about your dad.
It's about me.
FRONT DOOR OPENS
MAN: Hello!
Oh, my God, that's him.
What?
It's Mark.
What, he's coming tonight?
Up here!
Oh, he's got a key!
Mum, what the fuck is...?
Mark!
Sorry I'm a bit early.
SHE LAUGHS
Would you...?
Would you like a biscuit?
Er, no, thanks.
Did Mark's arrival in the family
cause any rows or upset
amongst the siblings?
Well, they...
..they'd not long lost their dad.
And they'd plenty going on
in their own lives.
So they were...
you know, they were rattled.
HELEN: Do you think she meant
Dad had affairs, then?
He was on a dating website for
widows. I don't like it.
I just think he's got
a really strange hold over her.
It's way too soon.
Is it? I mean, she's known him
for six months. It's not...
Six months?
Six months is not a long time.
How could she trust him
after six months?
She knew Dad for 45 years.
Turns out she couldn't trust him,
either.
That's not fair, is it?
We don't know what Dad did,
and he's not even here
to defend himself any more.
Are you saying Mum's lying?
No, I'm not saying that.
I'm just saying we don't know
all the details, do we?
You know,
I don't want to think about it.
But it could be something,
you know, like a fling, sex, just...
Oh, and that makes it all OK (!)
No, but it makes it more forgivable
cos men can do that sort of thing
all the time and there's no feelings
involved.
It doesn't take away from
the love of your wife.
There's always more to it
than just the physical.
NATALIE: God, you're both
so cynical.
Look, people do fall in love.
It does happen.
I liked him.
VIVIEN: I'm sorry about
the kids' behaviour last night.
I really should have told them
about you before.
My fault for being early.
They were fine.
No, they weren't.
They were frosty.
They were protective of you.
My daughter would be the same.
And all those questions.
As if you were applying for a job.
They'll get used to the idea.
They're adults.
Well, they don't act like it
sometimes.
Especially when
they're all together.
Don't worry about it.
Are you not a bit hot in this?
A bit.
SHE CHUCKLES
I could do with a summer one,
really.
SHE CHUCKLES
MARY: I think the last ten years
of Vivien's marriage were...
..not happy ones.
But she wasn't one to complain.
I don't think the kids realised.
They were so full
of their own lives.
Which I gather were in some turmoil.
MARY: Well, I don't like to say.
But I do know Jake and Leila were
having...
yeah, a bit of a tough time.
Ah...
Right.
Mum, Dad's taking us to Disneyland!
We're going to Paris!
I'll be in in a sec.
I hope you can deliver on that.
Yeah, well, they deserve a holiday.
I'll get the money.
This is the rest of your stuff...
..from the attic.
I'll see you Monday.
Leila, please...
Can I just come inside
and talk to you? Please, just...
Just a chat.
Not now.
Put your size four boot
up Connor's arse
and get those corrected drawings
ASAP, yeah?
So, anyway, before he arrived...
..Mum said Dad was no angel.
And that can only mean he had
affairs, can't it?
There's never been any hint of this
before.
I mean, he was away a lot
travelling for work, but...
But it just casts Dad
in a completely new light.
Are you listening to me at all?
We've all got secrets.
Look at us.
It doesn't make him any less
of a father, does it?
Everybody lies.
Even your mum, probably.
Do they?
Were there any family feuds
that might have had a bearing
on what happened last night?
MARY: Well, I mean,
all families row, don't they?
But, no, nothing.
I mean, not to the point
of such a terrible tragedy.
No.
CAR PULLS UP
Ah!
Exquisite.
Thanks for the cheese straws, Mary.
Delicious.
Oh, my pleasure.
How did it go, then?
Oh, a few sticky moments.
But they'll get used to it.
Of course they will.
Are you off on a trip?
Yup, just a couple of days.
Back Sunday night.
Oh, where to?
I don't know, actually.
It's a surprise.
Oh, well, that's...
That's lovely, isn't it?
HE TOOTS THE HORN
Oh!
I'd better go.
I'll keep an eye on the house.
Have a great time.
MARY: 'But I worried, after Terry
died, that Viv would get very low.
'So I suggested we go out
on a few outings to cheer her up.'
SHE SIGHS
But, well...
I should have known a woman
like Vivien wouldn't be single
for five minutes.
"Good for her," I thought.
JAKE: 19. One more.
Keep it up.
20.
Very good.
Oh, a cheeky bonus.
THEY LAUGH
Well done.
Very, very good, lady.
How do you feel about once more
around the park before we head home?
Oh, God...
All right, then.
Yeah?
Go on, then, I'll catch you up.
Come on!
Coming!
Of course, I take this report
very seriously.
And I want to apologise,
on behalf of the Trust,
to any patient who has waited
too long for treatment.
As you know,
there have been some significant
resignations on the management team.
And my task now
is to get this Trust back on track.
SHE SIGHS HEAVILY
DOOR OPENS
Helen...
"Significant resignations"?
What about "brutal dismissals"?
Oh, Meera, I...
I don't think you're supposed
to be in this building.
I was pushed out of my job
because you needed a scapegoat.
Come on, Meera, your department
was consistently failing.
After years of hard work,
my professional reputation
is destroyed...
..like that.
How do you sleep?
DOOR CLOSES
SHE MOANS
THEY LAUGH
Oh, did you book that trip
for your kids to Disneyland?
Yeah.
Yeah, I did.
Thank you for that.
You must miss living with them.
Yeah.
Well...
..I'd better be off.
Oh, it's in the drawer.
Thanks, Stella.
That's very generous.
My pleasure.
Literally.
Ha!
HE CLOSES THE DRAWER
HE SCRUNCHES THE MONEY
What...?
What's this?
You don't have a fear of flying,
do you?
Er, no.
No.
But where are we going?
Oh, just a short-hop flight over the
Channel to Le Touquet.
You told me you went there once
as a teenager.
I thought you might like a revisit.
It's just a tiny plane.
Half-an-hour trip.
Viv...
..why don't you say something?
Er...
I haven't got my passport.
# Ta-da!
Er, I found it yesterday
when you were getting ready.
You were looking through my things?
Oh, dear.
Sorry.
I wanted it to be a surprise.
SHE LAUGHS
It's OK, I'm sorry, I...
It's just...
Just a bit of a shock.
Good. Let's go.
I can't believe you remembered
me telling you about that trip.
HELEN: He's just so different from
Dad, though, isn't he? NATALIE: And?
That's what I couldn't believe.
I mean, so...
I don't know, gentlemanly.
Dad was gentlemanly.
Oh, not like that.
Mark couldn't stop looking at her.
Filling her glass,
touching her arm, smiling at her.
Are you jealous?
No.
I'm perfectly happy with George.
You?
No, I'm very happy on my own,
thanks.
JAKE: He's wet.
He's too wet for her.
I mean, Dad was a force
to be reckoned with, wasn't it?
He had character.
He was no angel.
HE SCOFFS
That...
Oh, I think that's nothing.
I bet that was just, like, one-off.
Some one-off event.
Look, you know, the most important
thing is that they stayed together,
didn't they?
All those years, over 40 years,
they stayed together.
That's bloody impressive.
Hey, come on, you'll get Leila back.
Of course you will.
Hmm.
Yeah.
The thing is that I got pregnant
with Helen...
.before Terry and I got married.
So, it was more a marriage of...
..necessity than choice.
Well, I don't think that Charlotte
and myself had the perfect marriage.
Not by any means.
But I'd always wanted to be...
part of a team.
Someone by your side...
rooting for you.
And I hope that, one day...
..we can be a team like that.
What?
Oh, is that what all this is about?
A proposal?
Because, Mark, nothing could
be further from my mind,
at this moment, than marriage.
Nothing.
A square.
A TV!
OK, Maddie, what else?
Hm.
Hm, hm, hm.
Large...
Climbing.
Up the stairs.
Growing up.
Good.
James And The Giant Peach!
Don't look at me like that.
You haven't said anything to Helen,
have you?
No.
No, of course not, but...
Oh, I don't know,
I just hate to think
of you hanging on like this
for a man who might...
..might not come through for you.
Thank you.
But I can look after myself.
I know, I know.
But you could so easily find
a great guy who adores you.
Please, George.
And wants to have kids, like you do.
Oh, Jesus...
I shouldn't have said anything
to you.
I'm sorry, I didn't...
Beauty And The Beast!
Jack And The Beanstalk!
Yay!
THEY CHEER
Well, it's your go, then, Maddie.
Up you come, yes, yes.
Guys, guys, right, wave to Grandma.
Get a photo!
Wave to Grandma!
Cheese!
ALL: Hi!
MARY: I reckon that was the first
Sunday lunch
Vivien had missed since Terry died.
I mean, family traditions
are important, aren't they?
I mean, she began spending...
..all that time with Mark.
I think that's when things
started falling apart.
Oh, hello!
Did you have a good trip?
Where did you go?
Oh, just over to France.
Yes, it was lovely, thanks.
Everything OK?
Yeah.
Sorry, I can't stop, Mary,
I'm off to get my hair done.
I'll catch you later.
OK.
MARY: I knew Vivien
about as well as anyone.
I mean, you can't live next door
all those years
and not get to know a person,
can you?
We always helped each other out
whenever we could.
HE KNOCKS ON DOOR
Oh, hello?
She's out.
But I can take it for her.
Oh, great, thanks.
Thank you.
Cheers, bye.
But although we'd been neighbours
for so long,
we didn't live
in each other's pockets.
No, I kept myself to myself.
Always have done.
It's just who I am.
So, what do you think?
Oh, good God, we're not going
to knock this down, are we?
It'd be a crime.
Stables.
Four-car garage.
Six beds.
A billiards room.
Well, what's this about?
Us.
You and me... living here.
I've been on the lookout for ages.
I haven't found anywhere I thought
you'd like.
Until now.
So, you're actually
finally going to leave Carla?
And this is for us?
You've been so patient, Nats,
all this time.
If you like it...
..I'll put in an offer on Monday.
I promise.
Mum...
Hi, darling.
Have we got any photos of Grandad
from when he was in hospital?
I don't think so. Why?
I'm doing a post on death.
What?
It's for my followers.
I should have taken one of him just
after he died.
That would've been cool.
Yeah, no, that would have been
incredibly disrespectful.
Well, you didn't respect him.
You were always arguing with him.
No, I wasn't. You used to shout
at him all the time.
Just like you shout at Dad.
You're always angry.
I am not...
Lily...
people argue all the time.
It doesn't mean they don't love
each other.
Yeah, right.
I just...
I want our little family back.
I want you back.
And the money?
Look, I'm working all the hours
God made.
Leila, I'm paying back the debt
week by week.
When will you be clear?
Six months or so.
It's going to be quicker, if I can.
A lot can happen in six months.
I don't really want to discuss it
until you've paid back every penny.
Jake...
No.
MARK: I've been thinking about
that conversation we had in France.
Me, too.
And I realise it was far too soon
to mention marriage.
Erm...
It was stupid of me.
No, it's OK.
I'm really sorry.
I messed up.
It's just that...
SHE SIGHS
..after a lifetime
of looking after other people, I...
..I like the independence
I have now.
I understand that, of course,
completely.
It doesn't mean
that I don't love you.
Can I just ask...
..does this mean that marriage
is out of the question for you...
..forever?
No, no!
SHE CHUCKLES
But we've got years ahead of us,
don't we?
Do we?
Well, hopefully, yes.
It's just I wouldn't
like to think...
you'd rule it out completely.
Come on.
Hi, darling.
Hey, Natalie.
Hey.
Ruby, come on!
DOG BARKS
How are you?
Oh, yeah, great, thanks.
Time for a cup of tea,
or a glass of something?
Oh, no, I've got to get back.
Aw...
Well, we haven't seen you properly
in ages.
Even the girls are asking after you.
Aw.
We should have her round for dinner
one evening, shouldn't we?
Yeah, yeah, that would be lovely.
We'll arrange something.
I'll email you some dates, shall I?
Oh, yeah, lovely.
I know what you're doing, Natalie.
And you can never win.
Never.
Bye!
CAR STARTS
STELLA: Jake, I'll see you
downstairs.
Oh, erm...
One of my rentals
is due to come vacant soon.
The top floor flat.
That might work for you.
Yeah, well, it sounds lovely,
Stella.
It also sounds very expensive.
And I'm trying to save every penny
I can at the minute, thank you.
Erm, actually...
..I thought you could have it
rent-free
in exchange for the personal
training sessions and the odd...
..evening here.
I mean, we could...
do away with all of this.
Oh, er...
Well, bloody hell.
Er...
No.
I don't think I can accept that,
Stella.
OK.
I mean, it was just an idea.
I thought I could kill two birds
with one stone.
But no pressure. I totally
understand if it doesn't feel right.
I'll see you Thursday.
Er, yeah.
Yep. See you Thursday.
DOOR CLOSES
TELEVISION ON, CHUCKLING
SHE GIGGLES
Oh, God...
VIVIEN: Mark's on his way over
and he's bringing some supper.
We're going to watch a film.
Why don't you stay?
He always makes far too much.
No, no, I'll leave you two lovebirds
alone.
But, erm, before he gets here,
I wanted to ask you something.
I've been thinking about what you
said about Dad.
Oh, God...
"No angel."
Does that mean...
He had affairs, didn't he?
Just the one.
But it went on for some years.
Jesus...
But you didn't leave him.
Why not?
I...
I said that, if he gave her up, then
I promised I wouldn't tell you kids.
And he did.
Do you know what happened
to the other woman?
No, I don't know.
And I don't care.
Yeah.
Look...
Why don't you pop in again soon, hm?
And we can talk properly.
Yeah.
You really like him, don't you?
Mark.
You think he's all right?
I think he's great.
Really great.
Because he makes you so happy.
All right, bye.
Hello.
SHE SIGHS HEAVILY
So...
that's a no, then, is it?
I'm just near
the end of the chapter.
Or you're in the middle of a
chapter. Or the start of a chapter.
Or you're...
You're very stoned or...
Don't, Helen, please. ..tired.
Well, it comes to something
when your own mum's
having more sex than you.
You never initiate anything.
That's because you're the initiator,
aren't you?
You're the boss
and I'm just the employee.
If I'm not performing, well,
we'll have to get tough, won't we?
Oh, come on...
I'm not a project for you to manage.
Sex isn't like that.
And it doesn't respond to demands.
PHONE BUZZES
Hi, Mum.
This is late for you.
Is everything OK?
Oh, Helen.
It's Mark.
I'm calling from the hospital,
I'm afraid.
Oh, my God, what...?
What's happened?
It's your mum.
She's collapsed.
MARK: Ah, she's awake.
Hello.
How are you feeling?
Fine.
Actually, I slept well, Doctor.
Your pulse is regular.
Drink this.
You need to keep your fluids up.
And you might want
to take one of these.
What are they?
It's a very mild tranquilliser,
just to get you through lunch
with the kids and everything.
It's up to yourself.
Only take it if you're feeling
the need.
Thanks.
You're being so thoughtful.
Nonsense.
But I think I could...
run to a nice slice of toast
without burning the kitchen down,
if you felt up to it.
Yes, please.
You're going to be fine.
I promise you.
BEDROOM DOOR CLOSES
VIVIEN: I mean,
it was the oddest thing.
One minute, I was fine,
and then...
MARK: Then she collapsed.
NATALIE: But you were fine
when I left here.
So, what is it, then?
Well, we can't be certain, but...
I'm sorry, I'd like to hear from my
mum, please.
Oh, well...
They're not sure if it's
just a one-off thing
or a symptom of something serious.
I mean...
Oh, God.
They've done a raft of tests
and now...
we just have to wait
for the results.
Well, look, I think we should
set up a rota system.
Yeah.
One of us coming in every day.
Yeah, that's a good idea. I can do
that, just to keep an eye on you.
Yeah, we'll cook a meal
or something. It's no trouble.
No, no.
No, no, it is trouble for you, so...
Well, actually...
Mark has very kindly said
that he'll come and stay for a bit.
Here, in our house?
Just for a week or two.
You know,
just till the results come through.
And I'll be in
the best medical hands.
So, none of you need worry.
But, Mum...
No offence, Mark,
but we don't know you very well yet.
And naturally we...
Well, we don't know him at all.
And, Mum, that is our job.
Look, let's calm down.
I don't want to tread on any toes.
Look, and if
there was another episode,
then Mark would know exactly
what to do.
I could monitor the hospital tests,
make sure they haven't missed
anything.
Well, that is important.
Oh, come on.
We can do that.
I'm sorry if you feel uncomfortable
about that.
No, no, no. Look, what is important
is that Mum's happy.
Isn't it, Jake?
Thank you.
And I am, hundred percent.
INSPECTOR: And then Vivien suddenly
became unwell?
Yes, and that was so...
..out of the blue.
How did the children react
to their mother's illness?
Well, you know,
they all rallied round.
A large gin and tonic.
Thanks.
So, that's two drinks here,
one at Mum's.
That's almost six units of alcohol.
You're just jealous because I can
hold my drink and you can't.
No, you think you can.
That's what alcohol does for you.
Oh, stop it, you two.
Anyway, back to Mum.
I hope you're not considering
driving home.
We don't really know
her financial position.
You were the one helping her with it
all after Dad died, weren't you?
Surely you've got some idea.
Yeah, well, I know she owns
the house outright
and there are some savings.
But most of what Dad left
is in shares,
which she said have been doing well,
so she's certainly...
She's loaded.
You don't honestly think that he's
only after her for her money?
You only have to look at them
to see that they're in love.
Oh, come on.
Bullshit.
They hardly know each other.
It's infatuation.
He can't get his hands on her money
anyway, not without her permission.
What? Of course he can. You know
what Mum's like with security.
He's probably already got all of her
PIN numbers and passwords.
Yeah, one of us should have
power of attorney
in case she has another one
of those episodes.
For God's sake, you two. Look, this
is about two people being in love.
We should be cheering them on,
not obsessing about the money.
Money might mean nothing to you
because you haven't got
any dependents.
You think nothing of spending £1,000
on a handbag.
Oh, she doesn't pay for those bags.
What the fuck do you know?
You don't go short on anything,
either.
That's not fair.
Wages in the public sector...
And you've got George at home
waiting on you hand and foot.
I've had to work bloody hard
for where I've got.
What, and I haven't?
As I recall, Dad gave you
the deposit for your flat.
Did he?
Yeah.
Whereas Jake and I
had nothing to get us started.
Oh, for fuck's sake,
that was ages ago.
Anyway, it was only ten grand.
Ten grand?
Do you want me to divide it
all up and write you a cheque now?
Is the money really that important
to you?
It's not the amount,
it's the principle. It's the amount.
Yeah, I will have a cheque.
Oh, you two are unbelievable.
Sorry, Dad gave her ten grand,
you knew about it
and you didn't tell me?
Fuck it. We should all get
ten grand, shouldn't we?
What, so you can spunk it all
on a horse at the bookies?
Wow, wow, wow...
You really are such a little bitch,
aren't you?
Do you know who I pity?
George.
TONY: 'Hi, I can't come to the phone
now,
'but if you leave a message,
I'll get right back to you.'
'Hi, I can't come to the phone right
now, but...'
COUGHING AND RETCHING
Oh...
SHE VOMITS
COUGHING AND RETCHING CONTINUES
Oh...
PHONE RINGS
Hey, you.
Hey.
Listen, I've been thinking about
your, er... your offer.
'Of the flat.
'If it still stands, erm...'
It will be temporary.
Yeah. Of course.
Yeah?
Yeah, that's great.
That's...
It's perfect.
RINGING TONE
TONY: 'Nats, what the hell are you
playing at?'
I need to talk to you.
'Well, I can't talk now.
'I've got ten people at dinner.
Are you OK?'
I've, er...
I've done a test and it's positive.
'What?'
I'm pregnant.
'Jesus, Nats, what are you...?
'Look, I...
'I can't talk now, OK?
'It's not the right time. I'll see
you on Monday. We'll talk then.'
HE HANGS UP
Urgh!
Thank you for being here.
Most men would have run a mile
in the scenario.
No question of that, Viv.
I'm yours.
This is it for me.
Your...
..question still stands, then...
..about marriage?
Of course.
Whenever you're ready.
INSPECTOR: Thank you, Mrs Bennett.
We'll be in touch regarding a more
formal statement
at the police station.
Formal statement?
Yes.
A person is fighting for their life
in hospital.
But...
But it was an accident.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
But if it's not...
and the news from the hospital
isn't good...
then it's murder.
Oh, thank you for the tea.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org