Previously,
on "Resident Alien"...
My mission was simple:
drop my device onto their planet
and head back home.
I had no intentions of getting
close to any of them.
In order to complete my mission,
I would have to somehow fit in
with the human life forms.
Dr. Harry Vanderspeigle,
we had a murder
in town last night.
Need you to come down
and take a look at the body.
Sam Hodges was poisoned.
He tried to give himself
a tracheotomy.
- There is a killer out there.
We still need your help.
In a town of 1,000 people...
There is a kid
who can see my true form.
- You're just different.
I know what that feels like.
Sometimes just feeling human
is alien to me.
Maybe there's
something redeemable
about the human race after all.
Unfortunately for them,
when I find my device,
I will finally
complete my mission
and kill them all.
♪ ♪
All beings of the universe
are different.
For instance,
my people are brilliant.
Humans, on the other hand,
are so dumb
that they think
the leading cause of death
is heart disease.
It's not.
It's almond milk.
Even the Grey aliens
won't touch the stuff.
Despite their differences,
there is one truth
that connects all beings.
Life doesn't ever go as planned.
♪ ♪
Whoa!
Oh!
What the hell?
Help!
Somebody!
Help me!
Help!
Somebody!
♪ ♪
Finding an object
the size of a suitcase
in the Colorado Mountains
is like looking
for a needle in a haystack.
I've been searching
for my device
every day for months.
I haven't found it yet,
but after searching
a half dozen mountains,
I finally found the haystack,
and that's all that matters.
Well, that and being on time
for my first day of work.
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
- Max!
Max!
Ugh!
He went out the window.
Of course he did.
What the hell happened in here?
- The kid went nuts.
- What?
Why?
I have no idea.
I'm going to cut your head off!
I think he has emotional issues.
Well, we need to get
this place cleaned up.
There hasn't been
a doctor on duty in days,
and we have a bunch
of patients coming in.
Well, don't just stand there.
Okay.
Ugh.
- Max, okay.
- Count of three, bud.
You are getting filthy
under there.
Listen to your mother, Max.
He's just looking for my wallet.
He's a good kid.
We're good parents.
The alien from my bedroom,
he's in there.
He's the new doctor!
- Okay.
- Max, I saw the new doctor.
He didn't look
like an alien to me.
He's already gotten
inside your brain.
- Come on, buddy.
- You're as good as dead.
Let's go.
You are going back in there,
and you are letting that doctor
take a look at your sore throat.
And while I'm in there,
you can buy a four-foot coffin.
Okay, look, that's enough.
I cannot hear about
this alien stuff anymore,
but he can come to work with me
and lie on the couch.
If his throat
doesn't feel better,
I'll bring him back, okay?
- Oh, now you want to die too.
Make that three coffins.
I'm serious.
If he keeps this up,
we're getting rid of him.
Sounds good.
Oh, vanilla, thank God.
You I will keep.
- Oh.
- Love you.
Whoa, whoa, what are you
doing with these?
Look, do I need to remind you
that this side
is the mayor's office
and that side
is the sheriff's office?
We got a murder to solve.
I got to make room
over there for murder stuff.
Yeah, well, there's no room
for those boxes in here, so...
Well, the laws of physics
would tend to disagree with you
since there they are.
Sheriff, I'd like
to file a murder complaint.
- I know who killed Sam Hodges.
- What are you talking about?
Is that so?
- All right.
- Sure, have a seat.
Go ahead and lay it on me,
little deputy.
- It's the new doctor.
He's an alien.
Okay, on that note,
I'm gonna need everyone out.
Kid's a little delusional
with a fever.
- Maybe no talking for a day.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
An alien?
What you mean?
Like, he ain't got
a green card or something?
No, like, alien-alien
from outer space.
- Outer sp...
- And shoot me.
What the hell are you
teaching this kid, huh?
You know I could lock you up
for lying
to an officer of the law?
That is a crime.
- You're committing crime.
- Got a sick kid, okay?
Gonna need everyone out.
Got a sick kid.
- Just...
- Yeah, he's sick all right.
Let me ask you something.
You got HBO in your house?
Here's what I want you to do.
I want you
to watch "Oz" season one,
and then come back and tell me
if you want to go to prison.
Talking about some alien shit.
- I'ma go get me some more boxes.
- Uh, no.
I really wish that you
wouldn't do that, Sheriff.
Okay, okay.
Hey, I know the sheriff can
seem kind of mean sometimes,
but he's just a teddy bear...
With severe control
and anger issues.
But he didn't believe me
when I told him about the alien.
Nobody does.
Well, look,
maybe he didn't believe you
because he can't see
the alien, right?
It's probably putting up
some kind of mind shield
that only you can see through
because you're special.
Yeah, that makes sense.
One of my skills as a deputy
is to work as a sketch artist,
so if you describe
the alien to me,
I could draw a picture of him.
Great, then I
can get the word out!
Okay, start with his eyes.
They're, like, alien shape.
And then he has
these scales going back...
Like, blue scales
with little circles.
Ooh, okay.
♪ ♪
Human doctors
have to go through years
of medical school
to perform a procedure
as simple as burning off a wart.
I was a scientist on my planet,
so this is easy for me.
All I need is the Internet,
and I can graduate
in five minutes.
Okay.
Let's take a look
at that nasty thing.
Hm.
You're not a 12-year-old boy
with a wart.
Mm, not a 12-year-old boy.
- Ah, yes, Harry, sorry.
This is Judy.
She's in need of a pelvic exam.
We had to move her up
from tomorrow.
Oh, okay.
Pelvic exam.
So, big guy, you into sports?
No, but I am into
putting my pants back on
before the breeze
dries out the lettuce.
Yeah, Harry,
she doesn't have all day.
- Oh.
- I'll be right back.
Oh, yes.
Of course.
Okay, I see your problem.
You sat on an earring.
- No!
That...
- Sorry.
- That's supposed to be there.
Uh...
Here we go.
Let's just get
into this, mm-hmm.
Oh, yes, examining.
Uh, yes.
Oh, uh...
Did you just take a picture?
♪ ♪
It was a selfie.
My first day.
Huh.
The day didn't get any better.
Oh.
Well, it appears that you
are in excellent health.
Concerning your breath,
did you recently eat
a dead rodent?
You should be
more careful next time.
Your parents
don't have insurance,
so if you get hurt again,
they'll probably lose their home
and have to live
outside on the street.
She just found
a lump in her breast.
Why don't you try to be
a little more calming this time?
I know what I'm doing.
I see you found
a lump in your breast.
Yes.
I'm glad that you came in
and that you've been so diligent
with your health.
As you know, self-examination
along with
appropriate screenings
can greatly increase
your odds of early detection,
so I don't want you to worry.
Many women find lumps
in their breasts all the time,
and most of them
are nothing, okay?
- Okay.
- Good.
Now let's get
a look at that tit.
I discovered that the woman
does not have cancer.
I also discovered that "tit"
is not the preferred term
for breast.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Harry, this is my father Dan.
Harry's a doctor.
He's been helping us out
at the clinic.
Hello.
Sorry, he doesn't like doctors.
Dad, what are you doing?
I have a bad feeling.
There's something
wrong with that man.
Oh, my God, are you kidding me?
You have a bad feeling
about every man
within ten feet of me.
I don't have a bad feeling
about him.
- That's the problem.
- What are you talking about?
When I look at him,
I feel nothing at all.
♪ ♪
Asta's large father
does not like me.
Can he somehow tell
I am different from them?
This day cannot get any worse.
♪ ♪
Shit.
Oh, mm.
♪ ♪
- This kid is a menace.
He just won't give up.
Where was that effort
from the humans
when we were helping them
build Stonehenge?
A bunch of idiots just
sitting around drinking mead,
making us do all the work.
Lazy druids.
I can't leave.
I'm too close
to finding my device,
and I'm not turning
into someone else.
It took me weeks to figure out
how to get this body to work.
♪ Life was short
and life was sweet ♪
♪ I was thinking
as I hit the street ♪
♪ I could hardly believe ♪
♪ I could scarcely conceive ♪
♪ But I had
gone out the window ♪
♪ I had gone out the window ♪
♪ I had gone
out the window ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Oh, catch me,
we are falling ♪
♪ Catch me, we are falling ♪
♪ ♪
I have to be smart.
I can't just kill this kid.
It will draw too much attention.
Hello?
Hi, is Max there?
Who's this?
I'm a friend of his from school.
My name is... Elvis.
- Yeah, okay.
Max, friend from school.
- Hello?
- Hi.
I saw your poster on the street.
Yeah?
And I saw that alien
on a bus leaving town,
so you don't have
to worry about him anymore.
Are you sure it was him?
Yes, he was very handsome
like a young Jerry Orbach.
Who?
Wait a minute,
I don't know you from school.
You're right.
I'm a post office man.
I'm good with my eyes,
and I saw that alien,
and he's gone.
If you're a man,
why do you have a kid's voice?
- Tricycle accident.
- Uh-huh.
If you work at the post office,
how much does a stamp cost?
- $100.
- I knew it!
- You're him!
- $1,000.
I know it's you,
and guess what, alien,
you can't kill me.
My parents know you're after me,
and if I die,
they'll know you did it,
and you're dumb.
Stamps are, like,
30 bucks each, stupid.
Don't call me stupid...
you little shit.
S-H-I-T is a bad word, stupid.
- That's it.
I'm going to kill him.
What do you want?
♪ ♪
I didn't know babies
had a laugh button.
Oh, there you are, sweetheart.
Oh, Harry,
this is my cousin, Kayla,
and this cute little guy
is Sage.
- Hi.
How are you?
Okay, I'm gonna see you
this weekend.
- Okay.
Mwah.
Bye.
Let's go.
Oh, Jay, didn't you have
something you wanted to say
to Dr. Vanderspeigle?
Ms. Twelvetrees
wanted me to apologize
for calling you a douchebag.
And I apologize
that your birthmark
looks like a bug.
Douchebag.
Yeah, glad we cleared that up.
Okay, Harry, this is
your temporary office.
Can you please grab
Harry's things
and set him up
in the nurse's office?
I don't want anyone
in Sam's office.
Sure.
So how are you,
you know, with Sam's death?
- I'm fine.
- Okay.
When I was your age, I didn't
have anyone I could talk to
when I was sad,
so if you ever need someone...
I said I'm fine.
Okay.
Why couldn't you talk
when you were sad?
- Oh, no, I could talk.
I just moved out.
My father and I
didn't get along very well.
Why did you move back?
Um...
I guess I missed home.
Home.
You know what I just realized?
I don't know anything about you.
Where are you from?
I'm hungry.
♪ ♪
Okay.
This human form
is confusing to me.
I am often struck with
a sharp emptiness inside me.
I eat food, but the emptiness
doesn't go away.
♪ ♪
Well, hello there.
Oh, you are the woman
that I danced with.
- That's right.
You remember.
I'm D'arcy, by the way.
- Excuse me, I just wanted...
- What?
We don't have Wi-Fi.
I just wanted a napkin.
Oh, fancy man wants a napkin.
It looks like you're
wearing a napkin,
so maybe use that.
Get out of here.
Go away.
Do you want me
to get you anything?
I was hungry,
but now that I am here...
- for some reason, I'm not.
- Sounds like stress.
I'm a big stress eater.
I ate a whole bag of Doritos
the other day... family size.
Maybe you want some
of this local whiskey
- that you love.
- No.
No.
Last time I drank that,
I tried to kill someone.
Really?
Well, was that your first murder
or is that something
you do a lot?
Wasn't the first,
won't be the last.
Okay, wow.
So you, like, a knife guy or...?
I like to use my hands.
Me too,
except not for murder as much.
But, anyway, if you're gonna
go around killing people,
you should at least
make it look like an accident
'cause if you get arrested,
you can't take me bowling
tomorrow night.
When I kill that kid Max,
I can make it look
like an accident.
Then I won't get caught.
That's a great idea.
Great, yeah, it's a date.
I've never gone bowling
with a murderer before.
It's been a goal.
♪ ♪
What is bowling?
I'm glad my husband and son
are here with me in my home.
- Makes me fulfilled.
- I am your husband.
- This cookie is delightful.
- I'm here too.
I'm a younger person.
Let me turn on
the cooking stove.
It's funny.
All I hear is a hissing noise.
♪ ♪
I hope that smell in the air
isn't propane gas.
♪ ♪
- Explosion is a good option.
It looks like an accident.
So, uh...
You know, it is nice
talking to someone who cares.
You know?
And I love that you're
writing things down.
You know, Sam, he didn't
really ever take notes.
Well, no one cares more
about people than I do.
Yeah, Sam gave good advice,
but he wasn't exactly qualified.
This town is lucky
you started your career
as a clinical psychologist.
Lucky for me too... so lucky.
It's just all this stress
has a bit of a tendency...
- Mm-hmm.
- To just build up.
Sometimes I think about
being a kid again.
It just makes me feel good.
It's better being a kid.
Sometimes.
So...
Why do you like thinking
about being a child, hm?
Things were simpler.
I had no worries, I guess.
You know, when I think about it,
I get this pit in my stomach.
Describe this pit.
Is it like
you're hungry all the time?
Kind of, but it's not that.
I...
♪ ♪
Just feel empty?
No one should be in here.
- Is it true what I'm hearing?
You think my Sam was poisoned?
- Sorry, I tried to stop her.
You can't be here.
I can't talk to you right now.
I am busy with the mayor
doing psychological therapy.
Isn't this
supposed to be private?
He's telling me he's a man baby.
- I didn't say...
- It's fine.
I'll wait, and I'm going
to get his things.
- No, you're not.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Ben Mm.
Tell me more about
this hole in your stomach.
Um, well, it's...
One second.
You have no right
taking Sam's things.
Well, they're my things now.
- Can you be quiet?
I am trying to be a doctor.
This is Sam's office.
He just died,
and it's a crime scene.
Nobody comes in here.
What is this?
I was hungry and wanted
a quiet place to eat.
This is Sam's chicken
from the refrigerator.
- He is not going to eat it.
- God, Harry!
No, leave it.
Stop it.
- You cannot take...
- I am not leaving it.
You have no right to come
in here and take everything.
These are my things now
and I'm taking them home.
Pathetic humans
letting their emotions
dictate their behavior.
These two are distraught
by something as small
as a loved one
being poisoned to death.
I wonder if I
can get that chicken
while they're fighting.
♪ ♪
I need to know what you're doing
about the investigation
into Sam's murder.
I'm sorry.
Do I come up to you
on the street and ask you
what you're doing
about Mr. Dougan's catheter?
Abigail is at the clinic
right now
taking all of Sam's stuff
out of his office.
Isn't that evidence?
You know, she's the wife.
- Maybe she killed him.
- Maybe you killed him.
How about that?
Say that again,
and you'll be wearing that hat
inside your ass.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I like watching her
when she's angry.
We looked into Abigail,
and she has an alibi.
She's got a rock solid alibi.
She wasn't even in town
the night that he died.
And I already took care
of Sam's office.
I got prints.
I got photographs.
I got everything.
You need to stay in your lane...
The bike lane.
Oh, wow, how long did
it take you to think of that?
- That's what I said.
- That's so clever.
I can read the emotions
on their faces.
Sadness masking as anger.
Weakness masking as superiority.
♪ ♪
This one's like a pet rabbit
that you yell at so much
its hair starts to fall out.
My people don't have
stupid emotions
to get in our way.
♪ ♪
All we need is food
to fuel our body.
That's easy.
You can find food
almost anywhere.
♪ ♪
♪ Tiny bubbles ♪
♪ In the wine ♪
I'm in human form now,
and I'm feeling
that pit in my stomach.
Is it possible that,
when I took on the human
molecular structure,
I somehow was infected
with their emotions?
Or is it just hunger?
♪ ♪
Never mind, it's just hunger.
Hello again, Mrs. Cow.
♪ ♪
♪ Till the end of time ♪
- Sorry.
I'm leaving.
It was consensual.
♪ Every day, every night ♪
♪ It's all you,
it's all you ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ Every day, every night ♪
♪ It's all you,
it's all you ♪
♪ It's all right,
it's all right ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Every day, every night ♪
I was beginning to think
you weren't gonna show up.
Octopuses also
change their color.
♪ ♪
Oh, yeah.
I was gonna stop with
just the hair though, so...
♪ ♪
Excited to bowl?
- Let's get some shoes.
- Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
- Ugh.
- So we meet again.
Do I know you?
Yeah, you had your hand
inside me the other day.
- Uh, narrow it down, Judy.
- Uh, eat a dick, D'arcy.
I'd have to pry it out
of your cold, dead hands.
♪ ♪
- You're a 12.
- How did you know?
Oh, 'cause D'arcy
only dates size 12s.
- Real classy, skank.
- Whore.
Oh, are you going
to Cookman's bonfire
- on Saturday?
- Yeah, I'll be there.
- Nice.
See ya.
♪ ♪
Well, well, well,
look who came into my house.
You live here.
On Tuesdays and Thursdays, I do.
I league it up with my boys.
Okay, shouldn't you
be out solving crime?
Yeah, the only crime
in Patience tonight
is gonna be this double homicide
when I murder you both
with my superior bowling skills.
Let me show you how it's done.
♪ ♪
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
You hear that?
That there's the sound
of inevitability.
Aha, X marks the spot.
Let's see what you got.
Come on.
Okay, all right,
all right, okay.
♪ ♪
All right, not bad.
Okay, let's see
what the good doctor's got.
You up, Doc.
♪ ♪
Go Harry.
Let's see what you got,
Dr. Harry Vanderspeigle.
♪ ♪
- You got this.
Knock 'em down.
- This is easy.
I've got this.
It's all just math.
If I can land a spacecraft
on an asteroid
travelling 50,000 miles an hour,
I can roll a ball on some wood.
Oh, son of a bitch!
- That's a strike.
- Ain't no damn strike.
That's assault
with a deadly weapon.
You know, I could arrest
your ass for that,
but I don't want
to embarrass you
for all this wayward bowling.
Ow, shit!
♪ ♪
He's fine.
- You know, he was wrong.
I never feel embarrassment.
- Wow, that's cool.
Well, I do.
When I was at Stratton,
I had this recurring dream.
You know, I was running naked
through the hallways.
It wasn't a dream.
Ambien.
That's embarrassing.
You've lived here a long time.
I have a question.
It doesn't mean anything.
When does the snow melt
on the mountain?
Ooh, it would depend
on the weather.
It's spring,
so if we get a good rain,
- it'll be gone in a week.
- A week?
- Yeah.
- That's very soon.
Do you want to go heli-skiing?
- It's rad.
- No, don't go up there.
What?
You're a skier?
Yeah... well,
I used to ski, like, a lot.
I wanted to go to the Olympics,
so finished second in the worlds
and then 2006 I went to Torino.
- And then this happened.
- How did you do that?
Well, it was
my second mogul run.
I heard my knee pop.
It was before the jump,
and I couldn't stop,
and I landed, and I heard
a bunch of bones crack.
I could see my tib fib
sticking out
of my competition suit.
They said I could have
lost my leg or even died.
Whew, fun day.
- Couldn't stop?
- Yeah.
- Almost died.
That's great.
So I found a new perspective...
- I've got to go.
- We're not done eating.
That's where it usually ends.
Aw, another date night
just you and a hot dog?
Actually, I have two.
You could have one for each hand
just like in high school.
I learned that trick from you.
- All right, slut.
- Hoe bag.
- Want to bowl?
- Yeah.
Let's do it.
♪ ♪
The kid has to ride
his bike down this hill
on the way to school.
Without brakes,
he'll never survive.
It's a good feeling to know
I am the smartest person
on Earth... ugh!
Get out of the street,
you idiot!
♪ ♪
Sorry.
Hm.
I liked Sam, but he was always,
"Don't eat this.
Don't eat that.
Your diet's gonna kill you."
Well, what you eat is important.
I don't agree with that.
Oh, no?
No, there are ten things on here
that are going
to kill him sooner
- than eating bad food does.
- Harry.
- No, I want to hear.
Sam never mentioned that.
Tell me when.
Look, I just turned 80.
You can give it to me straight.
How long do you think I have?
- Do you like Christmas?
- Yes, very much.
Celebrate it before June.
Oh, okay.
Oh.
But between now and Christmas?
You can eat anything you want.
I like you.
This is the first time
that a doctor's
been totally honest with me.
This town is very lucky to have
a doctor as good as you.
Yes, you are lucky.
You certainly have
a particular style.
That's impressive.
He doesn't like anyone.
- Ben Hawthorne's here.
There's been an accident.
- An accident?
- Yeah.
- Hello, Mayor Hawthorne.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Uh, what loss?
This little guy fell
on his bike in the driveway.
I think he's
gonna need stitches.
♪ ♪
- Come on.
- Okay.
Stitches... stitches, that's it?
Don't sound
so disappointed, weirdo.
♪ ♪
It's okay, buddy.
I'll be here right next
to you the whole time.
You're, like, 600 feet away.
Yeah, well, I don't want
to get in the doctor's way.
See, just stay strong,
okay, pal?
Thank you, nurse.
I hear you had a little
bike accident this morning...
Very little.
Your son is very shy.
You can look at me, Max.
I don't bite.
Actually, I do.
You're lucky your brakes
failed on the driveway
and not on the main road.
This should have been
a lot worse.
How did you know
it was my brakes?
I just assumed.
We get a lot
of failed brake accidents...
All kinds,
cars, wheelchairs, boats.
Mm, can we hurry this up?
That smell of gauze
is just something else.
Luckily, we have Novocain
for good boys.
I can numb this up,
and you won't feel a thing.
So tell me, Max,
are you going to be
a good boy?
Of course.
♪ ♪
No, never.
Well, then I have my answer.
Let's put in
a couple of stitches.
Go right ahead.
♪ ♪
How is it, Max?
It's fine.
Is there a mosquito in here?
'Cause I think I just got
a tiny bite on my arm.
This is deeper than I thought.
We might need three stitches.
How about five?
♪ ♪
- Well, I guess that's it.
- Really?
- I didn't feel anything.
- Huh, good for you.
I did.
Okay, let's go.
Yes, yes.
Remember, if you're not careful,
something horrible
can happen to you.
- Oh, don't worry.
I can take care of myself.
By the way, your shoe's untied.
Made you look, you dummy.
Wait, I... look!
It... it is untied,
so ha, ha, ha!
♪ ♪
I know Sam and you were close.
There are things
you can do that will help you.
You could cut your hair
to honor the deceased.
I can handle it.
♪ ♪
Maybe you should start
letting me live my own life.
Worrying about every man I meet,
making me dinner every night...
I'm not 16 anymore.
Mm, it's okay.
The dinner part is nice.
If you were 16,
you wouldn't even be here.
You'd be in Denver.
Oh.
Good one.
Now that I live at home,
you're gonna start
being my father?
Well, you never
stopped being my daughter.
♪ ♪
I hope you're this upset
when I die.
Jesus, Dad.
♪ There's gotta be
some hope ♪
♪ ♪
♪ There's gotta be some hope ♪
♪ There's gotta be some way ♪
♪ For you to send
your dogs away ♪
♪ And to leave
the land alone ♪
♪ ♪
♪ It's gotta be a crime ♪
♪ Somewhere in your heart,
you'll find ♪
♪ ♪
♪ We're fighting
for our right ♪
♪ To keep the future bright ♪
♪ And protect
the ones we love ♪
♪ ♪
♪ In the river is our sisters
and our brothers ♪
♪ ♪
♪ We are camping out
for each other ♪
♪ ♪
Did you burn your scrubs
from the other night?
No.
♪ ♪
You know you should.
You've got to release
Sam's spirit from this world.
- Otherwise, he'll linger.
- I know.
♪ ♪
♪ I've been
thinking about you ♪
Shut up!
♪ Been thinking about you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I've been taking
my time with you ♪
♪ Been taking
♪ But falling quickly too ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And sometimes
how I lose my mind ♪
♪ When I am feeling fine ♪
♪ Since I have been with you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Was 14 straight into 1,013 ♪
Hey.
♪ ♪
Mrs. McGill has a crush on you.
It's not a crush.
She's 90 and comes in every week
because she's a hypochondriac.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- Uh-huh?
A little gin rummy?
Oh...
I'm gonna have
to take a raincheck.
Big day tomorrow.
Oh, but I'll beat you next time.
You wish.
♪ ♪
There's no one sitting there.
Dan's not my real father.
My mom left when I was one.
Dan took me in,
and he raised me.
He gave me everything.
But I never really felt
like I fit in.
Sam was the only one
I could talk to about all that.
I never should have left
that night he died.
I was tired.
I just wanted to go home.
He was always there for me.
I should have
been there for him.
He was poisoned.
- You couldn't have helped him.
- Maybe.
At least he wouldn't
have died alone.
Do you want to play a card game?
Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
I'll put my stuff in my office.
This is your office now.
♪ ♪
I did not want to play cards,
but I knew Asta wanted to.
♪ ♪
She was sad.
I could feel it.
♪ ♪
I should not be able
to feel an emotion
that is inside somebody else.
♪ ♪
Tellurium.
I know that they are all
connected by these feelings,
these emotions...
♪ ♪
Feelings of devotion...
Sadness...
♪ ♪
Love.
In Greek mythology,
there exists this legend...
♪ ♪
Maybe I am more connected
to them now
I had an emptiness
that no amount of potato chips
or hot dogs would cure,
but when I found the tellurium,
the ache went away.
It wasn't coming
from my stomach.
It was coming from my heart.
Human emotions
are growing inside of me.
I think the one I feel now
they call lonely.
♪ ♪
In the same way Asta
misses Sam Hodges,
I miss my planet, my people.
But having found the tellurium,
I can finally
heal my broken heart
because, once I
detonate my device
and fry every human being
on Earth,
I can fly home.
Now I just need
to find my device
without being discovered.
♪ ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org