She's been asking to go home.
Well-- Well, did you tell her?
Not yet. I thought
it best you do it.
No, she has to understand,
this is her home now.
I can't keep her here.
But we agreed, Aunt Ida.
You said
you'd look after her.
I am paying you
to look after her.
Hello there, Charles.
Sister.
Good to see you.
That's a nice suit
you're wearing.
Oh, yeah.
Perfect fit.
You're always
such a spiffy dresser.
So you...
come to take me home?
No. No.
Well, it's business, Maud,
financial matters.
Oh, good.
Well, I'm a natural at math.
Remember?
Heh. Always used
to check your numbers
when you were in school.
Didn't I, Aunt Ida?
I wanted to drop off
a few things for you.
Lordy.
You cleared out my room.
Why?
I sold the house.
What?
Our house?
Maud...
Mom left it to me.
No.
You can't-- You--
You can't sell our house.
Charles, you can't sell
our house.
I'd-- I'd--
I'd look after it.
I'd be more than happy
to have my own place, Charles.
You can't
look after yourself,
let alone a house
and a yard and--
I'd get a job.
I'd get a job or something.
A job? A job doing what?
I don't know, Charles!
I'm sorry, Maud.
It's done.
No. Wait. Charles.
Charles.
Charles, wait.
Don't. Don't.
Goodbye, sister.
You can't--
You take care of yourself.
No, wait. Charles.
Maud.
Come get your tea.
Charles! Charles!
Wait!
Gonna do
some painting out here.
Too messy.
Why don't you put your things
away in your room?
Why don't you
leave me alone?
You better not tell me
you were out at that club.
Wasn't gonna
tell you that.
Where were you?
At the club. Heh.
Wasn't gonna
tell you that.
Only looking
to meet friends.
That's what you said
the last time.
Look what happened.
You should try it
sometime.
You might like it.
This is new.
Well, well, well,
look who's gracing me
with their presence today.
What can I do for you, Everett?
I'm looking for a woman.
A what?
Uh, a...
hou-- Housemaid.
Looking for a housemaid.
Not the kind of thing we sell.
Am I--?
Am I an idiot, huh?
No, I wanna put up
a sign, you know, a--
What do you--?
What do you call them?
Well, I need you
to write--
To write a sign.
Yeah.
Okay.
Looking
for a housemaid.
Must have her own--
Oh, shit! Her own--
What's the word I'm looking for?
Sense of humor?
No.
Cleaning tools.
Must have her own
cleaning tools. That's it.
That'd do it.
Yeah. And then you--
Contact Everett Lewis.
Yeah, sign my name. Right.
Here.
Give it to me.
That's it.
Need a hand,
that's all.
Hello, big boy.
Beautiful. You are.
Hey. Hey.
You a guard? You a guard dog?
Hey, hello.
Hello.
Um, I'm Maud.
Dowley.
Yeah. That's right.
I was--
Got your ad at the store.
The one you posted,
looking for a housemaid.
Yeah. Well, I'm answering it.
Looking for a woman.
Well...
what do you think I am?
So...
Well...
Well, I--
I walked here from Digby.
Wouldn't mind a cup of tea.
You can tell me
what you're looking for.
Thank you.
So...
This all yours?
Th-- This house?
Nice.
Used to be
Captain John Ryan's.
But I moved it here
from the wharf.
Guess how many oxen
it took to move it.
Two?
Not two. No. Seven.
Heh. Seven oxen.
That's a lot of oxen.
It'd be nice...
for you to have someone
around here.
Yeah, must be hard
to do it all on your own.
You got that right, ma'am.
Got that right, you know.
What is it you do?
Sell fish.
Sell chopped wood. You know.
Work at the orphanage.
Lordy.
How do you keep it straight?
Got a lot on my plate.
Yeah.
I'd like the job.
You walk funny.
You a cripple?
No.
No? You're not sick or nothing?
No, I just--
I just walk funny.
It don't stop me.
I can do the work of five women.
You got an ashtray?
Flick 'em on the floor.
Thanks.
Ouch.
Many women apply for the job?
You finished with your tea?
Well...
might as well say it.
I'll put it...
Well--
You do need the help.
I can see that.
A long walk home.
I bet they'll throw rocks
at me again.
Who throws rocks?
The kids. They don't mean it.
They don't mean it.
I don't care.
Some people don't like it
if you're different.
It's a lot of work to break
in a new shoe.
Heels are galled
right off.
This is far as--
Far as we go.
Oh, okay.
Uh-- Wai-- Eh--
Come on.
Everything okay,
Everett?
Thinking about hiring a woman
help around the house,
but slim pickings
applied for the job.
Someone actually applied?
Might be better
with one of these boys.
These kids are
too young, Everett.
Oh, when I was their age,
did the work of 10 men.
Cleaned this yard,
chopped wood, built that fence.
Yes, but you were here,
around people.
Everett?
If someone applied
for that job, hire them.
Hi.
Nice day out.
I suppose
I'll give you a try.
That'd be nice.
Be nice.
Maud!
You gonna stand there all day?
No, no.
What do you think you're doing?
Yeah.
Coming. Coming.
You're neglecting your chores.
Yeah, I know.
God in heaven.
Yeah.
I'm a grown woman now.
I'll go off and find
my own place.
You can't look
after yourself, Maud.
I know you think that.
You are determined to put
a stain on this family name.
If you leave now,
you are never coming back.
Do you know that?
Yeah, I know. I know that.
Sorry. Got a job now.
You been good to take me in,
but I gotta go now.
He's waiting for me.
Bye, Aunt Ida.
Go.
I'm assuming--
Assuming I'm working
for room and board,
but...I was thinking
an extra 25 cents
spending money as well
a week?
There you are. Heh.
Thought you left me
for a minute.
What do you want me
to do first?
If I stand over you all day,
I may as well do it myself.
No--
You going through
my stuff?
No. No, just...
pretty.
Well, you think that's why
I brought you
out here, so you could
go through my gear, huh?
No.
I made you soup.
What is that? Huh?
Turnip.
I don--
I don't eat turnip.
You haven't even cleared
the table.
I was just-- I was just--
You want me to pay you money
but you don't know a click
about cleaning.
No, no, no.
No, no, not gonna work.
No, no lazy arses around here.
No lazy arses around here!
You get your stuff and get out!
No, no. No, no. No!
No! No!
Why you do that?
Where do you want me
to go, huh?
Should've thought of that
when you were sitting here
going through my stuff.
I didn't know what you wanted.
I don't want to have
to look after you.
I want somebody who's
gonna do the looking after!
Not some
crippled-up woman.
Now get out! It's my house!
I'm getting out!
My house!
Yeah.
Hello.
Yeah, it's time.
You know.
You know, don't you?
Hey, gently.
Hey, hey. I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Hey, hey, hey, it's okay.
I know. I know. I know.
Oh, come here.
Oh, dear, it's okay.
It's-- It's all right.
Oh, dear.
It's all right.
Yeah, I know. I got you.
I'm sorry.
Here we go.
Shh. Shh. Shh.
I know. Sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
That's my chair.
Want a bowl of stew?
Where'd you get the chicken?
Killed it.
You killed it?
The big one.
So...
I'm gonna stay,
where do I sleep?
Are you gonna follow
my rules?
You cleaned?
Clean upstairs?
No.
No?
There's only one bed
up there.
Oh, you're a princess,
eh?
When I was at the orphanage,
they put us six,
seven to a bunk, hm.
Elbows in my back.
Feet up my arse.
If you're too fancy
to pile in,
then you can take
your little knickknacks,
put them in the red wagon
and get out.
No, I'm--
I'm good up there.
I'm not too fancy.
Bad dogs!
Down. Get down.
Down. Yeah, good boy.
Who told you you could talk
to them dogs like that?
What--?
They gotta learn.
Them dogs been here longer
than you. More useful too.
I'm only-- I'm only trying
to feed 'em.
Let me tell you how
it is around here, all right?
There's me, them dogs,
them chickens, then you.
Everyone's talking.
He has you barred up in there
as his love slave.
It's disgusting.
Everett
with a love slave.
Would it make it more proper
if I married him?
Maybe people won't talk
so much.
Aunt Ida?
You wanna come visit me
sometime?
I wouldn't be caught dead.
I wouldn't even drive by
that house.
Suits me.
Love slave.
What are you gonna do
with all this, Ev?
Sell it.
Or just leave it.
Sell it?
Who'd buy that?
Hello.
Hello there.
It's a nice day.
Everett got himself a woman?
Get back in the house.
What's this now?
Ah, she works for me.
Need somebody to mind the house,
else I get robbed.
So you got yourself
a tiny, little woman
to guard your house?
Couldn't you get
a meaner dog?
Or a gun?
Wait.
Come here.
I'm Frank. I'm the fisherman
he tries to cheat every day.
He wouldn't cheat you.
He's a good man.
Oh, so-- So you don't
know him well, I see.
Yeah.
I'm Maud.
Dowley.
Well,
it's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
So you're
working here, then.
Yeah. I'm-- I'm living--
That's enough.
So you got yourself
a live-in maid, do you?
Out all day. Work hard.
I deserve to come home
to a clean house.
Don't I?
Where do you fit?
There's more room in there
than you think.
We find it cozy
in there, don't we?
Get back in the house!
I'm in charge of this house.
If she don't know it,
she'll learn it.
Nobody in their right mind
would put up
with that for very long.
Well, she's not
in her right mind.
That's one thing I know.
Learned your lesson?
Do you want me here
or don't you?
Because I'll go.
I'll walk out right now.
Well, do you
want me here or not?
I'd like my pay, please.
You haven't paid me yet,
not once.
Two months.
Yeah, aye.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Are you
the fish peddler's wife?
Some snazzy shoes there.
No. Sorry.
Well, is he around?
He's-- He's out
on his rounds.
I paid for fish,
and he never delivered.
Oh, well...
sometimes he forgets.
I paid him,
plus a handsome tip.
Now, I'm here from New York City
for the next few months
and I can give him
my business or not.
You-- You sure he never
dropped off the fish?
May-- Maybe a dog
ran off with it.
I don't have a dog.
Or a cat.
Cats love fish.
I don't have
a cat either.
Well...
Well, I'll tell him
you came by.
Say...
Yeah?
Did you paint that happy,
little chicken?
Actually, yeah.
There was a chicken
out in the yard.
Real fat.
I wanted to remember
his happier days, so...
painted him.
Well...
I'll tell him to square up
with you when he gets home.
I'd appreciate that.
What's your name?
Maud.
Nice to meet you, Maud.
I'm Sandra.
Nice to meet you, Sandra.
Hey, those
snazzy shoes...
They comfy?
Ah...they're not bad.
No. They're not bad.
All the way
from New York City.
Who told you you could paint
fairies on the wall, huh?
They're not fairies.
They're birds.
Well, who told you
you could do that, huh?
Well, you did.
What?
You said-- You said:
"Make the place look
all right."
I think
it looks all right.
No painting
in this corner, huh?
I don't want paint on my boots.
No paint on my gear.
The rest is fine.
Birds or fairies,
I don't mind.
I won't do that.
Good?
Long day?
Must be hard running
a business.
My brother Charles used to run
one of them jazz clubs
for a while.
People always on his back
for money he owed them.
I never owe
nobody nothing.
Charles said
the same thing.
Couldn't prove it, you see.
People are stupid.
You're not.
You keep track
of it all in your head.
Most people can't,
you see.
That's why you gotta
write it all down.
I can write it down
for you, if you like.
I'm good at writing.
So...
Who
owes
Everett
Lewis?
Donovan.
Owes me for six fish.
Six fish.
That is a bird.
What?
That, I don't know what that is,
but it's not a bird.
That is finished.
It's got
a beak on it.
That ain't got
no beak on it yet.
Are you gonna do that?
Are we ready to get married?
Costs money.
Foolish.
Only if you invite people
and stuff.
Give them supper.
You gotta pay a fee
for a license.
Yep.
Charles had
a fancy wedding.
I thought
I wouldn't do that.
I'd do it cheap.
Wouldn't invite anyone.
Wouldn't do what Charles did.
Why you talking about him?
Well, you plan on doing
what you're doing,
think
we should get married.
I don't wanna get
in that sort of trouble again.
What kind of trouble?
I had a baby.
Baby died.
She was real deformed.
They buried her when...
When I was sleeping.
Here.
You wanted
three fish.
I owed you for two.
So...
now you owe me for one.
It's a card.
Well, we-- We figured it out
on the card.
We're rendering accounts.
So, you know,
it won't be a mix-up.
And how do I know
this is right?
Because I said.
We could maybe start clean
from now on.
Keep track.
Maybe.
Give me a moment.
I am the boss.
Yeah, you. I know that.
Who's in charge?
You are.
I bring in the money.
Right?
Yeah.
Yeah, so who's
in charge?
Yeah. You are.
Yeah. Right.
Don't forget it.
Yeah.
I can't--
Can't forget it.
I'll pay you, if you make me
some more of these cards.
I don't know.
He's in charge, so...
ask him.
Throw in
an extra 5 cents?
How about 10 cents a card?
Sounds good. Suits me.
Good.
And I'll take my fish.
I look forward
to these cards very much.
Thanks. See what I can do.
Wait up. You're good, Ev.
You know?
Really know what you're doing.
Asking for that money.
Pretty house.
Let's get her
in second gear now.
She liked my card.
Hey, kettle's on.
Cup of tea?
Come in.
Sure.
I got it here for you.
You got--? Got--?
Got any boards?
Take a look around.
Good morning.
Well, three more.
I don't know why people
pay money for these.
My 5-year-old
could do better.
Maybe.
Maybe he could,
but he didn't. Maud did.
Brushes, please.
Well,
you're an idiot.
You're an idiot.
Stupid.
Know-it-all.
Whoever it is,
you tell them to get.
Get out.
Get out?
Yeah.
It's suppertime.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Hello.
May I come in?
Well, we're...
Come in.
Oh, thank you, Maud.
Would you like a bowl of soup?
Oh, no, thank you.
No?
Here. Sit down.
Like a cup of tea?
I'm fine, Maud.
The reason I'm here is,
I'd like to see
one of your larger paintings.
Oh, well, heh.
Well, I-- I don't do
larger paintings.
Just the little cards.
I'm willing to pay
your price.
Yeah, she does.
Yup, we got some fine gobs
of paint here,
splashed on these boards.
No.
Yeah, these will be
right up your alley.
There.
Look at that.
It's a lovely winter scene.
There's some deer.
Well...
Isn't she beautiful?
Yeah, I haven't
finished it.
And this tree has red leaves.
This one has green.
What season is it?
Uh, well,
I guess it's--
It's everything that's
pretty about all the seasons.
Yes, it is.
Well, how much, hm?
How much?
No.
What's your price?
Five dollars.
Done.
No. No.
Uh, I'm not--
I'm not selling it.
It's all right.
Yeah.
No.
I'm not selling that one.
Already sold.
I haven't finished it.
I have-- I haven't finished it.
Well, I was just pulling
your leg now.
It's a joke.
This one's not for sale.
You know, I have
an even better idea.
Why don't I commission you
to paint me something?
You can paint me anything
on a board, just like that.
Just whatever you want.
And I'll pay you for it.
You can send it
to me in New York.
Show me
how you see the world.
For five dollars?
Five dollars.
Uh, to New York?
That's a long way.
Does that include postage?
Thank you. Goodbye.
Goodbye, Maud.
Sandra.
You guys are
best friends, huh?
S-- Sold a painting.
Better get painting.
Dishes come first, yeah?
Six dollars.
Yeah.
Boy, she's an idiot.
Give her one
of the ones you already done.
No, I wouldn't do that.
Everett?
Do you like 'em?
My paintings?
How am I supposed
to know, hm?
Do I look like
a woman? Hm?
No. Heh.
But I know what that is.
It's a cat.
No. That's my name.
What's my name doing there?
Well, you know...
figured we're
in business together.
The painting's half yours.
Your name
should be on it too.
Well...
Not forgetting about
your housework now, are you?
No. No chance of that.
I just gotta finish
this one first.
You don't wanna neglect
your chores.
I won't.
Well...
I'll do the sweeping,
but I'm not
doing everything. Hm?
No. No, no, no,
no, no, no.
You'll get dust on it.
It's not dry.
It's still wet.
Do that,
close the door.
You tell me
when you're finished.
No, no.
Why?
No.
You're trying to claw your way
into my life like that.
Well, then you're wrong.
As soon as you stop
doing your work,
then you're out
on your duff.
I'd rather stick it
into a tree.
Want some tea?
Not your tea.
Well...
if you don't know
what I'm like by now,
then you are stupider
than you look.
We live together.
We lay down together.
Why not
get married?
Just because I don't have
women banging down my door
doesn't mean I gotta marry
first one comes along.
We've been living together
for some time now.
That's what
most people do.
I don't like most people.
They don't like you.
It's true.
I like you.
You need me.
Hey.
You look nice.
Thank you.
Well, I don't know
if I should offer
congratulations or condolences,
but give us a hug, Maud.
And you.
Be nice.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not crooked enough.
I'm still gonna be contrary
tomorrow.
Yeah.
I know.
We're like a pair of...
odd socks.
And I'm the stretched-out,
misshapen one.
The one with lots of holes.
No.
Yeah.
Crusty and gray.
No.
And I'm...
the plain,
white cotton sock.
Yeah.
No.
You'd be...
royal blue.
Canary yellow.
Wiseass.
That's better.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. No, over. No.
Yeah. There you are.
It's okay?
Don't nail it.
No, not gonna--
Not gonna nail it.
Just don't want it
to fall over.
There we go.
I can see you.
Yeah, I see you.
Good?
"Her paintings can be found
on display at her home
"in Marshalltown,
Nova Scotia,
where she lives with
her husband, Everett Lewis."
See? Do mention you
in here.
Let me see that.
"A local fish peddler."
"Everett Lewis.
A local
fish peddler."
There it is.
There you are.
Can I help you?
Charles?
Sister.
What are you
doing here?
Well, I heard--
Read about you.
Wanted to come
see for myself.
An artist, huh?
You never called me an artist
when we were young.
No different now.
Want a cup of tea,
Charles?
Oh, no, no.
Thank you for asking,
though.
So, uh, where's your, uh...?
Your man?
Out on his rounds,
I suppose.
Be back soon,
if you wanna meet him.
Oh, I don't have much time.
I just wanted to...
come by and maybe get one
of your paintings, huh?
Yeah.
Aunt Ida said you don't see
a nickel of money
from these paintings.
That right?
Yeah.
What's he doing
with your money, Maud?
Why isn't he building
onto the house?
Getting the place wired?
Why would he wanna
do that?
It's his house.
His choice.
Yeah,
but you're capable
of making decisions,
aren't you, Maud?
Oh, yes.
Yeah?
Yes, I am.
You know, Maud,
you need someone
to give you advice
on how to handle
your money.
Someone a little more
savvy than him.
Someone who--
Like you?
Well,
I know money, yeah.
You know debt.
Selling Mom's house.
You like money too much,
Charles.
Hello.
Everett.
My brother, Charles.
Hello.
He come to buy
a painting.
Just, uh,
which one, huh?
Big ones are $5.
Are you gonna buy one,
or what?
Yeah. Just grab one.
That one's $6.
Price gone up.
Six?
I only...
It's-- It's lovely.
Bye, Charles.
Goodbye, sister.
Get out.
Got a letter today.
From Vice President Nixon.
What'd he want?
A painting.
A painting?
Unless he sends money
for a painting,
won't send him any.
Good.
That's good.
Maybe then we can afford
a screen door.
Don't need
I'm the one working
14 hours a day
so you can just sit there
in the corner and paint away.
My paintings earn money.
Yeah.
Bring in a few pennies.
But I'm the one
doing all the work.
Right?
Yeah.
You can't even
keep the fire going.
I want a cup of tea
when I get home.
Gets hot in here in the day.
Yeah, so?
Open the door.
Then the flies get in.
That's why we need
a screen door.
No screen door.
Can I get you to hold it up
a little bit higher, please?
Thank you.
All right.
How long did it take you
to make this painting, Maud?
Two-- Two or three days.
Two days? Two or three days,
yes?
Do you enjoy painting?
Oh, yes.
I've been doing it
all my life.
Mr. Lewis,
come out, please.
Join us.
Can I get you to look towards
the camera this way, Mr. Lewis?
And smile, maybe?
Nice. Thank you.
Now, you've painted
most of the house.
Well, I started with the birds
and the flowers.
Over there.
And he didn't tell me
to stop, so...
kept going.
Everett, you must feel
very lucky
to have Maud
as your wife.
Maud Lewis has been an artist
most of her life.
Her paintings have even been
sold to Vice President Nixon.
This happy couple,
who only live
with the bare necessities
of life,
and yet somehow,
they flourish.
I chop the wood.
I do the dishes.
Now all she does is paint.
Paint a picture a day.
Paint all seasons.
I told her a wife is supposed
to mind her husband.
She does as she likes.
Who would have thought
this little, arthritic woman
living on the fringe of society
would have such incredible
and far-reaching success?
You can find Maud Lewis
still selling her paintings
from the front steps
of her little house here
in Marshalltown, Nova Scotia.
Take it easy there, Ida.
Hold my arm. That's it.
There we go.
Door.
I'm good.
I saw you.
On the news.
You lucked into it with her,
didn't you?
She's all smiles,
and you nothing but grumbles.
Wait.
I want you to tell her
to come see me.
Please.
I can do it.
I can do it. Go.
Never you mind
about how sick she was.
I asked you a question.
What--?
Oh, what?
Was I nasty on the TV?
No, Everett.
Well, everyone's giving me
queer looks.
Talking about me
behind my back.
Never mind what other people
are doing.
Everyone thinks
you're as sweet as pie.
They don't know. They don't know
what you're like to live with.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Get up.
What? Where are we going?
Where are we going?
Aunt Ida's.
No.
Yeah.
Putting my foot down.
Not going.
What?
Everett!
What if she dies and I didn't
get to say goodbye, huh?
What if I die
and you're not here,
and you didn't
get to say goodbye?
You're being silly.
No. Not taking you.
I don't need you.
I can get there
on my own.
You don't even-- You don't even
know how to drive.
Well, no.
I know how to walk.
Give me that.
Good to see you, Ida.
I watched you on the TV.
Did you?
What did you think?
You're the only one in our
family who ended up happy.
Well...
Yeah, suppose I did.
I don't wanna die...
full of regrets.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
I regret...
not letting you hold her,
at least.
What's that?
Your baby.
I know.
You did it to protect me.
I know that.
You know, she was...
real deformed,
so, you know.
She wasn't deformed.
She wasn't deformed?
Why'd she die, huh?
She didn't.
What?
Charles sold her.
He did what?
He sold her to a good home.
Older people.
We didn't think that you'd be
able to take care of a child.
Charles and--
And I decided.
I was told she's--
She's been well-loved.
Is she crooked or what?
She was fine.
I gotta go now.
Never asked for this.
Get up in the morning.
People.
Come home from work.
Got my face on the TV
for all the world
to laugh at.
Everett, listen to me. Ida--
No, you listen to me.
You think that you're
too good for me.
That you don't
need me anymore.
Well, that's fine.
You go find someone else.
Fine. If that's what
you want.
My baby, Charles.
They sold her.
Give up on that
goddamn baby!
Nothing but that baby,
the brother, the baby!
Nothing but misery.
My brother, my baby.
She lived.
I thought she died.
More pain.
Ever since you stepped
into my life.
Nothing but pain.
I was better off
without you.
What, are you gonna get out?
Yeah.
Well, good riddance!
Come in, Maud.
Thanks.
Sorry.
I've made up a bed
in the spare room.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Maud...
can you teach me
how to paint?
No one can teach that.
If you wanna paint,
you paint, I suppose.
I don't go nowhere, so...
paint from memory,
I suppose.
I make my designs up.
I've known you
for years, Maud.
Yeah.
It's true.
I know.
And I'm still trying to figure
out what makes you tick.
Don't know.
Don't-- I don't want for much,
you know?
As long as I got a brush
in front of me, I don't care.
A window.
I love a window.
A bird whizzing by.
Bumblebee.
It's always different.
The whole of life.
The whole of life
already framed.
Right there.
Something up, pal?
Well, she left me.
About time, eh?
You'd never last here.
It's a seven-mile walk
to the store.
I mean...
Harder to look after
than a dog.
I'm better--
I'm better than a dog.
What?
Hey.
Hey, see that cloud?
That one.
It kind of looks like a woman
with a big arse.
Bald on one side
of the head.
See?
You see her?
She's looking right at you.
I don't see her. Mm-mm.
You don't see her?
I see you.
What do you see?
I see you as my wife.
I always have.
I just...
I don't want you
to leave me.
Why would I do that?
Because you can do
much better than me.
No.
I couldn't.
I got everything I want
with you, Ev.
Everything.
What are we
doing here, Ev?
Why are we stopped here?
That's her house.
The white one.
Whose house?
Her.
Your girl.
My baby lives here?
A woman now.
How'd you find her?
She lives here?
Looks great.
I'm gonna go wash up for dinner.
Okay. I'll be in shortly.
She's so beautiful.
She's perfect.
One...
You got a big bunch
of mail there.
Oh, same as yesterday?
I can't go
any further, Ev.
Can't go any further.
Here. Here.
I don't know what's wrong
with my legs today.
It's cold, huh?
Yeah.
Guess I won't be skiing
this winter.
Everett.
Ev.
Okay, breathe.
Breathe.
You haven't given up smoking,
have you?
Give it up sometimes.
You have emphysema, Maud.
You can't smoke.
Won't be smoking anymore.
I'll tell you that.
Yeah.
I have arthritis.
It hurts.
Yeah.
It's hard to hold
a brush now.
Can you get me anything
for my arthritis, please?
I'll get you something.
Thank you.
And, uh...
air the place out a bit,
Everett.
Air's too thick.
Is he gone?
Yeah.
He's gone.
Silly.
There you are.
Tea.
Yeah. Thank you.
There you go.
I got it.
You should have kept
more dogs.
Don't want any dog.
You like dogs.
But I got you.
You know...
should get me
some more dogs.
Hey.
Are you drinking
all my tea?
There you go.
Share it.
Yeah.
Maud?
Maudie?
Whoa, now.
What is it?
Can you get in there? Yeah.
Yeah.
All right.
There you go.
Everett. Everett.
Everett.
She's going to be all right.
We'll look after her now.
No!
You're gonna be fine.
I knew you were
getting sicker.
But every time I'd ask,
you'd lie to me.
Wonder...
how I ever thought
you weren't perfect.
Shh.
Come here.
I was loved.
I was loved, Ev.
The whole of life...
already framed.
Right there.