Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Ciao.
- Bye.
Hello!
I'm Leo. You must be Nancy.
That's right.
May I come inside?
- Yes, of course. Yes, of course.
May I kiss you on the cheek?
Yes, that would be fine.
You smell wonderful.
- Thank you.
What is it?
- Coco Chanel.
Nigel la Lawson wears it.
Ah, Nigel la. So sexy.
Don't you agree?
Yes, no, I... I was waiting
for you to say, "for her age".
Most people say, when a woman's over
about 42, that she's sexy "for her age."
I was waiting...
I was waiting for that.
Ah, right. Uh, no, Nigel la Lawson
is empirically sexy, at any age.
Hey, Nancy?
- Yes?
We're gonna have a great time.
- OK.
OK.
I tell you what
I'd love right now...
What?
- A drink.
A drink, of course,
of course. Sorry.
What can I get you?
How about a glass of fizz
to ease us into the mood.
A glass of fizz. Hold on.
Allow me.
For you.
- Thanks very much.
To being empirically sexy.
Yes. I'll drink to that.
A very fine vintage.
It's just from the minibar.
Oh, you meant me.
Me.
- I'm just teasing.
Righto, righto.
- Shall we sit?
Yes, let's sit.
So, what would you...
- So, you enjoy music...
by people?
Yeah, I do.
What kind of music do you like?
Oh, I don't know.
All sorts, um...
Sorry, I'm a bit
distracted cos, um...
cos up close you really are
very good-looking.
Mm.
- Thank you.
Even more than in your photo.
Ah, I'm better in 3D.
Mm.
I hope that you received, um...
the contractual.
Oh, the money?
The money, yes, sorry. I didn't
want to be crass and just say it.
There's nothing crass about getting paid
for your work, Nancy, trust me on that.
And thank you,
it's all received.
Are you Irish?
- Yes, I am.
Have you been doing this long?
A little while now, yeah.
Long enough to know some things.
Do you enjoy it?
You know what? I love it, Nancy.
Meeting all kinds of people,
getting up to all sorts of things...
mutual pleasure.
You don't feel... demeaned then?
Not at all.
Or degraded?
- No.
But what if you meet someone
and you really just...
don't want to do it?
Hasn't happened yet.
Really?
- Really.
I find that astonishing.
How many have you...
- Oh, a gentleman never tells.
Oh, of course, yes.
You don't have to worry, Nancy.
This is just about us tonight.
So, what is your fantasy?
Um...
I'm not sure you could really
class it as a fantasy as such.
It's a bit mundane for that.
OK, well, what
would you most desire?
I mean, desires
are never mundane.
Um...
to have sex...
tonight, um, with you.
That's about it, really.
For the moment.
Great.
- But do you mind?
Do you want... I mean, am I...
...a disappointment,
so to speak?
OK?
OK, OK.
- Top-up?
Yes, please.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, I just can't bear
the suspense.
Can... Could we...
Would it be alright
if we just did it now?
Right now? And get it over with?
Get it over with?
- Yes.
You're meant to enjoy it.
No, I know that, I'm just not very
good at waiting for things to happen.
I'm much better when they've
happened and I'm... recovering.
You make it sound like it's
an ordeal. It's not compulsory.
Shall we just sit and chat
for a bit?
Oh no, I don't want to do that.
I don't think we'd
have very much in common.
You might be surprised.
- I am very rarely surprised.
I like to plan things properly,
specifically
in order to avoid
being surprised, if I'm honest.
Fine, but I hope
I can surprise you anyway.
N... No, I don't want anything
like that.
Anything like what?
You know, anything perverted.
Oh, no, no, no.
Not that kind of surprise.
Oh good, I don't like anything
going in to places
that are designed for
things to come out.
You're talking about anal sex?
I don't like that phrase.
Nancy, I won't be doing anything
you don't want me to do.
I've never done
anything like this before.
I've never bought
anybody like this for my own...
Pleasure.
- ...use.
Nancy, listen to me. I choose to do this.
- Yes. Right.
You know, you haven't bought me,
you've bought my service.
I set a price and you agreed.
I'm not being exploited.
I can't bear the suspense.
I can't bear it.
The anticipation?
- Yes...
of disappointment.
Why do you assume
you'll be disappointed?
Because I've always been
disappointed before.
I need to... Well, actually,
I'd like to tell you something.
OK.
I've never had an orgasm.
With a partner?
- With anyone.
Or by yourself?
- No. Not even by myself.
N... Never.
That's right.
Right. I see.
It's not meant as a challenge.
- I haven't taken it as one.
Cos you won't be able to achieve it.
- Fair enough.
Your confidence is endearing,
and no doubt necessary to the job
but I feel I must warn you
it is misplaced.
Um, and I don't want
you to feel bad about it
because I won't be faking it.
I don't do that. Not anymore.
Um, I made a decision
after my husband died
never to fake an orgasm again.
When did he die?
Uh, two years ago.
It was premature.
And is this your first...
Encounter since then? Yes.
In fact, if we do this, you will...
...only be the second man I have
ever had sex with in my entire life.
There, I said it.
Well, thank you for telling me.
If you want to leave now, I'm very
happy to pay half of what we agreed.
I don't want to leave, Nancy.
Nothing is
making me want to leave.
I won't leave unless I'm clearly
instructed to
or I feel I'm
in physical danger.
Has that ever happened?
- Yeah. A couple of times.
With a woman?
- Yeah. Once with a woman.
Well, her husband, he thought...
He wanted a threesome.
But it turned out he didn't.
Did she?
- No...
but she did want to meet
one-on-one a week later.
And did you do that?
- Sure.
Wasn't that dishonest?
- Of her?
Of you.
Why? I mean, I'm not the married
one. I'm just doing my job.
Wow.
It's all quite an education.
I hope it continues.
You're being saucy.
"Saucy"? My grandmother
used to say the word "saucy".
I'd rather not think about
your grandmother right now
if you don't mind.
No problem.
- I just... Anyway...
I just wanted to let you know
about the orgasm thing.
I'm not expecting one, so um,
you can relax.
I am relaxed.
This was a terrible idea.
Do you feel you're somehow
betraying your husband?
His memory, I mean.
What? Oh no, no, no, no, no.
No, it's nothing like that.
- Then what?
It's just not very "me", I'm a
teacher... Well, I was a teacher
I... I used to set my pupils essays on
the moral issues surrounding sex work
and here I am... participating in it.
- Nancy.
You're probably a very vulnerable
young man, maybe you're an orphan.
I'm not an orphan.
Yeah, or perhaps you grew up in
care, you've got very low self-esteem.
I didn't grow up in care.
You could've been trafficked
against your will, you can't tell
just by looking at somebody.
- I wasn't trafficked against my will.
Well, then I simply don't understand it.
- You don't understand what?
Why you're doing this.
Oh. Oh, well, if
you really want to know
I'm... I'm using the money I make
doing this to save up for college.
Oh.
Oh, how wonderful.
Are you really?
No.
Oh.
Nancy, you need to stop worrying
about me...
...let's move this
back to you.
OK. Oh, God.
- Now, Nancy...
This is crazy, it's terrible, it's wrong.
- Nancy.
My son... My son
would be appalled.
Nancy.
- Yes.
Let's go to bed.
- OK.
OK?
OK.
- Good.
Come here.
- Mm-hmm.
Is this OK?
OK?
- Mm.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Listen, er, if you, um,
need to take anything
that's fine by me.
I'm fine, Nancy.
I mean legal things, you know,
to help...
with it all down there.
- No, I assure you, it all works.
I know, I mean, I just...
No, I know what you mean, but
I don't need any little blue pills.
Never?
- Never.
But what if you
don't fancy the person?
I mean, you can't force
yourself, surely, if you don't.
There's always
something to fancy.
No, there isn't.
- There is.
Oh.
What's the oldest person
you've ever done it with?
That's a bit reductive, Nancy.
"Reductive", that's a good word.
I like it.
Yes, it is a good word.
I'm glad you like it.
I chose it just for you.
But seriously
actually I really do
want to know, how old?
Eighty-two.
- Eighty-two?
Yes.
- Eighty-two!
Yeah.
- Eighty-two.
Nancy.
OK, I'm feeling a bit better now.
- OK.
Um...
So, what's the
little thing about me
that you can hold onto
with all your might?
To make you come alive
in the moment?
Come here.
I like your mouth.
I like the line of your neck,
down to about here.
And this...
it's so elegant.
Um, just... hang on a second.
I'll just, um... I'll just go
to the bathroom and change.
OK, but don't change too much.
Oh, God.
Ta-dah.
Ooh!
You look great.
Oh, um, everything OK?
Yes, it's just, I don't like
Mars bars. I can smell it.
It's a bit off-putting.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I'll go and clean my teeth.
Would you mind? Thank you.
What's this?
Very nice.
- I've changed my mind again.
I don't want to do it. I'm
sorry to have wasted your time.
You... I'll still pay.
But you can get dressed and go.
This isn't about
the Mars bar, is it?
No, it's not about the Mars bar.
Do you not find me attractive?
Don't be ridiculous.
You're clearly...
aesthetically perfect,
and apparently nice enough.
What did you picture happening,
I mean...
why did you book me
if you don't want to do it?
I don't know at this point.
A moment of madness, that's all.
That's all.
Do you regularly have moments
of madness like this?
No.
Do you usually
make rational decisions?
Yes.
Then why would
this be any different?
I mean, you must
have had a reason.
Something that made you do it. I bet
you thought about it for days before.
Weeks... Well,
months. Years, perhaps.
Well, then it's
not a moment of madness.
This is what you want, Nancy.
And now that you have it,
why won't you take it?
Why won't you take what you want
when it's right here, within reach.
Oh, I don't know.
It feels controversial suddenly.
I don't find it controversial.
To want something
like this. Even to want it.
If it's just sex you want
aren't there a dozen men around
who'd love to hook up with you?
If it's all too much...
I mean, surely they want to.
Oh, yeah... Yes, they do, um...
Yes, they made that very clear
actually since Robert died
but um, it's
me, I don't want to.
Why not?
They're all old.
Old men. I don't want an
old man. I want a young one.
A young body. And no of fence, I
have to pay for that, of course I do.
Well, I'm here,
and I'm not offended.
Actually, why
are you still here?
I've just offered to pay you to spend
an evening doing whatever you please.
Why are you still here?
I'm interested.
- In what?
In you.
- Oh, for Heaven's sakes
no need to patronise me.
- I'm not.
You're conflicted.
Conflicted is interesting.
You've never met a woman who can't make
up her mind before? I don't believe that.
I've met women who can't decide
which sandwich to have for lunch
but if we've ended up in a bedroom
together, they usually know what they want
at that point.
Well, young women are different.
Yes, I think they are.
Different to how we were...
well, how I was when I was young.
I wasn't actually
a social renegade, anyway.
A couple of my friends were,
but we lost touch after school.
But London was a
different country back then.
The rest of us were stuck
in the 1950s, it was repressive.
Sorry.
And I wasn't brimming
with sexual confidence
like they all are now
with their thigh-split dresses
and salsa classes and whatnot.
I mean, people do pole dancing
for a hobby.
I've read about it,
I read an article about it.
I mean, a hobby?
Wh... I...
Christ, I sound so old.
I know I sound old, but
Leo, did you ever meet anyone
who does pole
dancing for a hobby?
I think that's
mainly for posh girls.
Yes, you're probably right.
I mean, I know pole dancers
but they wouldn't pay to do it.
That's just some fucked up
economics, do you know what I mean?
Not really, but I mean,
I can imagine.
It's not a world
I know much about.
Says the woman who booked a
hotel and a sex worker for the night.
Oh, God. Oh, oh, you're right.
Oh, God, I'm just
a seedy old pervert.
Just go. It's disgusting. I feel
like Rolf Harris all of a sudden.
Rolf Harris?
Never mind.
Come on, let's get in the bed.
Let's get under the covers.
Why do they
make these things like...
getting into a straight-jacket?
It's ridiculous.
What do you really want to do
with your life?
I'd like to see, er,
Venus before I die.
OK.
I'm just curious about
what it's like for you.
You're clearly very bright.
What makes you say that?
Well, I'm a teacher, and I know
there are some people who use
the word "empirically"
in a conversation, and
there are very many who don't.
And the clever ones are
those that do.
Did I use it?
Yes. Nigel la. "Empirically
sexy". And "reductive".
Oh, yes, you're right. So I did.
So, what, you don't think this is
a job for clever people, is that it?
No! No, no,
I didn't mean that. No.
No, I was just asking about
qualifications and...
Did you go to school?
Of course. I mean, my mother was
a very strict Irish Catholic.
And what does she think about
what you're doing now?
You want to talk
about my mother? Really?
Well, you brought her up.
- Well now I'm dropping it.
But seriously...
She doesn't know.
You know, this
looks so sexy on you.
What does she think you do?
If I tell you, can we drop it?
Because you really
do look good in this.
I promise.
She thinks I work on an oil rig.
An oil rig?
Yes, an oil rig.
In the North Sea.
No, but... But do...
Do you keep in contact?
Do you send her updates
about life on the oil rig?
- Now, Nancy, you promised.
But how do you know what happens
on an oil rig?
I Google it, you know.
I found a website where there's
stories about life on an oil rig
and I copy and
paste them sometimes.
Ha. That's amazing. What a life.
Oh, dear. Meanwhile, my son's
doing his Masters at university.
Are you not happy about that?
Oh, yes, no, I am,
of course I'm happy.
It's great.
Why wouldn't I be happy?
It's just what's expected.
Why do you sound
so ambivalent about it?
"Ambivalent", that's another good word.
- Mm-hmm.
So... your son?
Yes, well, I...
I... I... Oh dear.
I've never said this to
anyone before, this is awful.
It's OK, who am I going to tell?
Come on.
I... well, the truth is
I find him boring.
You find your own son boring?
Yes. That's awful, isn't it?
I've just never heard anyone
say that before.
Have you always
found him boring?
No, not always.
No, he's a very nice boy.
He's just very predictable,
like his father.
What's he studying?
Chemistry. Please
forget I said that.
Just forget it, he's a lovely
boy and I love him very much
and I should be grateful because
he's turned out very well.
Any other kids?
Mm. Daughter. Older.
We don't get along.
Oh, why not?
She thinks I'm cold.
And what do you think?
I don't think I'm cold.
I mean, I don't feel cold inside
but maybe I'm cold with her because
she's so over the top all the time.
So the opposite to her brother.
She lives in Barcelona,
in this bohemian set-up.
They're all artists, although
I've never seen any actual art.
Unless the art consists of burning
your parents' money, which...
Actually, it's not
out of the question.
At least she's not boring.
No, no, there is
that. There is that.
So your children have
disappointed you, Nancy.
Yes. But when did
you last see your mum?
Why?
Cos I'm interested in
where you come from.
I don't come from anywhere.
You know, I was actually found
under a little patch of mushrooms
size of a bean,
raised by friendly wolves.
Oh, go on. Tell me something.
I'm in awe of
anyone who becomes a mother.
Hardest job in the world.
Did you get that off Mumsnet
or something?
Sorry?
It's a bit general.
Not all mothers are good.
Well, I wouldn't know.
I've only had one.
Yeah, we're all stuck with
whatever we get, aren't we?
Parents and children alike.
At least I know what mine
are up to, though.
Haven't you ever wondered if
your son is lying to you about his life?
No.
- Why not?
Maybe he doesn't
want to disappoint you.
Has he got a partner?
Yes. Nice girl, also boring.
Training to be a primary school
teacher. Boring, boring, boring.
I thought you said you were
a schoolteacher?
Yeah, but I was
a Religious Education teacher
in a secondary school. That's
a very different beast to...
colouring in with six-year-olds.
They say primary education
is the most important.
Well, they're wrong.
Do you know what proportion of
secondary school students think
that Religious Education is worth even
an ounce of their time and attention?
I mean, I...
- No, well, exactly.
Exactly. So there I would be,
year after year
spouting the same old stuff, unable
to break away from the curriculum
in case I got complaints from
the head and unable to ask them
anything real
in case we lost time
and just
battling through the work
and getting
them through the exams
and then you just start again
the following year
doing the same old stuff.
It was just stultifying.
I think I may
have killed the mood.
I'm not sure there was a mood.
I'm sorry, that was rude of me.
- No, it's true.
No, but you're not paying
for the truth, though.
You're paying for a fantasy.
At this moment, I'm not
sure what I'm paying for.
I can show you.
I don't doubt it.
What would get
you back in the mood?
Hmm?
What would your husband do
to get it all going again?
Um...
Well...
He... He would, er...
take all his clothes off,
and lie in the bed
without putting his pyjamas on.
And I would take
all my clothes off
put my nightie on
and lie in the bed next to him
and then he would rub my
shoulders and breasts a bit
and then he would climb on top,
do the business
kiss my cheek, roll off,
put his pyjamas on
and go back to sleep.
That's it?
- That's it.
Always?
- Always.
No deviation for 31 years.
And that's the
only sex you've ever had?
Correct.
Wow.
"Wow" indeed.
No oral?
No oral.
- Not even on him?
No, he said it was demeaning.
For you?
- For him.
OK...
OK, and I presume it was
the same for him on you?
Yes, he said that was demeaning
for him too.
So, you've never had...
No, I've never had.
Never given.
Do you want to?
Yes, I do. I want to.
I want to very much.
I always have done.
Sorry.
I'm sorry to cry.
It's stupid.
I, um...
I think that...
Well, when I was a... a teenager
my parents took me
to Greece on holiday
um, it was a once-in-a-lifetime
trip, for them, anyway, and...
um...
at the hotel there was this
waiter, I think he was about 20
and he looked at me like I was...
the most delicious thing he'd ever seen
and I felt my body go to water.
And one night, he was
hanging around after his shift
and um, I was hot
so I went out into the garden
after my parents had gone to bed
and he was there,
smoking a cigarette
and, um... I stood
in front of this little bush
covered in tiny pink flowers
looking out to sea...
and without a
word, he came up and...
...kissed my neck
and put his hand under my skirt
and into my knickers
and I could feel him
sliding around down there
and I was pushing
myself back into him
and it was the most crazy,
exciting feeling I'd ever had
and... and, um,
then a car started up
and the headlamps came on
and he was startled
so he dashed away.
And the next day we went home.
And I wished we'd just stayed
one more day.
Hello.
- Hello again.
Thank you.
This is a very nice surprise.
Is it?
It's the same room.
I mean, I booked the same room
cos I didn't want to
be thrown by a new layout.
Oh, no, I mean
you booking me again.
Oh.
- I mean, you must've been satisfied
the last time, so
I'm happy about that.
Yes, yes, I was satisfied. Yes.
But?
Oh, it sounded like there was
going to be a "but".
No, no, not particularly.
I, um, I've got a little bit
of feedback
and a couple of attainment goals
for this time.
Right, I see. Sure. OK.
Would you like a drink?
- Yeah.
That sounds great.
Cheers.
So, I've made a list of things
that I'd like to get through.
Oh, that sounds sexy.
Don't mock me. I'm a teacher.
Old habits die hard.
What's first on the list?
Number one:
I perform oral sex on you.
Number two: you
perform oral sex on me.
Number three: we do a "69"
if that's what
it's still called.
Uh, I don't know.
Um, four: me on top.
- Doggy-style.
Well, that all
sounds very achievable.
Oh, does it? Oh, good.
Good, cos I'm...
I have no frame of reference.
I've tried, um, looking on the
internet, but it's alarming, frankly.
I mean, if you type
in "classy porn" to Google
up pop 12 windows of erections.
I mean, there's no build-up at
all. Have I booked enough time?
You want to do it all today?
Yes, if possible.
I mean, it's just,
you're quite expensive
and I'm not sure if I'll be able to
afford another session after this.
OK.
I understand, um...
Isn't there something else
that should be on that list?
Like what?
Well, I'd love for you to feel
completely satisfied...
if at all possible.
Oh.
The big "o", in fact.
Yes.
No, I like a list that can be
fully ticked-off.
Achievable goals.
That's the path to happiness,
there's no point in wishing for
the moon.
Well, it's an orgasm, you know,
it's not a Fabergé egg.
People have them every day.
Right. Do you know what, you're
right. That all makes sense.
I just... I want to feel
a sense of achievement.
Yes.
- I don't want to walk away...
from this feeling unresolved.
May I?
Do you know what?
We'll do as much of this
as we can today.
I think we'll certainly make
a significant dent in it.
Good.
That's good. Good.
You want to
start with the blow job?
Yes, I think so.
Get the big one
out the way first.
Should I kneel?
Well, I could stand on a chair,
but that's not how it's usually done.
Mm-hmm.
You don't have
to do any of this.
No, I know, I... but I want
to be a woman of the world.
I mean, there are nuns out there
with more sexual experience than me.
It's embarrassing. Do
you want me to brush my teeth?
What? No. Nancy, you can just...
you can just let go.
Let go? What am
I letting go of, exactly?
I mean, we need some
sort of plan, don't we?
I don't want to swing from the
chandeliers and make loud animal noises.
I'd like to see that.
You're letting go of the
thing inside that grips you.
You know, that judges you.
That watches
you from the outside.
Christ, if I let go of that,
anything might happen.
That's the only thing keeping
my life together.
Keeping it
ticking along... Here?
Over here.
What am I just supposed to do?
Just float around like
some sort of free form jellyfish
you know, waiting for something
to come up?
No, but you're...
- Do I undo your belt?
Do you undo it?
What's normal?
Well, it's more a matter of...
- Well, I'll do it.
OK.
No, I just... I just want
to do a blow job.
I want to get that sorted and then we
can work through as much of the rest
of the list as we can in the allotted time.
- Like we've got a double lesson
timetabled for oral, and then we
can see what's left of the afternoon?
Exactly.
- And shall I ring a bell
at the end of the session?
Do you use a bell?
You didn't last time.
Oh.
Very funny.
Um...
Oh...
Sorry.
I'll be back to all this
in just a second.
Hi, darling. Hi.
Sorry about that.
- Everything OK?
Yes. My daughter. She's just in a bit
of a pickle at the moment, shall we say.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Well, it's not the first time,
won't be the last.
She used to ring her father
about all this, but anyway...
Um, shall we just try
and get through what we can?
Before the exam?
- Um, yes.
Nancy.
There is no exam.
It's all a dance.
I don't know the steps.
An improvised dance,
we just go where it takes us.
There's no timetable,
there's no bell.
But I've only
paid for two hours.
Well, then let's enjoy them.
Every single minute.
OK, come on then.
Do you want to start with the blow job
or go with something else on the list?
No, I think I'd like
to go in order.
I feel like I'm prepared
for the blow job now.
Robert, my husband, he never...
he never wanted to try anything new.
He planned everything, I mean,
even his own funeral, actually.
I was terrified
he'd turn up on the day
and tell me I'd put the
wrong ham in the sandwiches.
It wasn't a...
furnace of
passion that burnt out
our relationship,
it was more like, um...
the bottom drawer of an AGA.
A what?
Um, it's an old-fashioned stove.
You can't turn it off.
It keeps on chugging away,
and at the bottom
there's a kind of
cooler drawer thing
that you can push things
to the back of...
Mm.
- ...you know, to cook them slowly
like a bowl of stewed apples
or something.
I see.
- Do you?
Er, not really.
But, um, I think you mean
your marriage stewed slowly
because you
pushed it to the back.
And then forgot about it.
Mm.
- Mm.
Well, anyway.
He's gone, it's all gone.
Ancient history.
And I want to try something new.
Then, good.
So, I need to get that blow job
under my belt.
Your belt, obviously.
OK.
OK?
OK, OK, look.
I have an idea.
You like dancing, right?
Only when nobody's watching.
OK, well then we're gonna
change the mood.
I'm gonna put on some music
and you're gonna dance
like nobody is watching.
Come on, Nancy Stokes.
Come have a dance with me.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God, God.
That'll be my daughter again.
She always rings twice.
She always forgets the most crucial
bit of information and has to ring back.
OK.
- I don't want to answer it.
Then don't.
- But I always answer it.
Even when you don't want to?
Yeah, especially when I don't want to.
- OK.
Well, what am I gonna say?
"Hello darling, I'm sorry I can't talk
now cos I've booked this man for the night
and I'm trying to work up the
courage to perform oral sex on him".
Well, you don't
have to say that.
Shall I answer it?
"Hello, darling.
I'm sorry but your mother has
something in her mouth right now."
Shh!
- "I could take your message
if you would like."
Listen, darling, I...
Yes. Oh, did he? Oh, God. Yes.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Oh, I am so sorry,
yes, I do understand.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Listen, darling, I really do...
Pamela?
Oh, she's gone.
Just like that? No goodbye?
Well, either her battery ran out
or she's been abducted.
Is it serious? Her pickle?
Well, it can be sorted,
that's the main thing.
I see.
Matthew will provide the
grandchildren, I've no doubt of that.
If Pamela can just keep
herself alive, I'll be happy.
You don't sound very happy.
Well, it's very stressful being
a parent, Leo.
It's a stress
that never leaves you
it's... it's like
a thumb on a bruise.
Sometimes my children feel like
a dead weight around my neck.
I'm not sure I'd have done it
if I'd known.
What do you mean?
I mean, I could've done many
other things, if I hadn't been a mother.
What else would you have done?
- I dunno.
Crossed the desert on a horse...
started an artists' colony
on a hot little island...
had a... had an orgasm...
Would you find a massage
patronising at this point?
No. No, I wouldn't.
Do you think your
kids could feel it?
Your disappointment in them?
I don't know Leo. I doubt it.
They mostly
didn't notice me, I think.
I mean, do you notice
when your mother's disappointed?
Are you worried that she'd be
disappointed if she knew what you do?
I'm not sure what you mean.
There's nothing disappointing
about an oil rig, ma'am.
Anyway, there's
still time for you.
Oh, that's
sweet, but there isn't.
This is it.
My final attempt at a life.
For the orgasm, I mean.
You might have to abandon riding
a horse across the desert.
Can I ask you to
do something for me?
Mm-hmm.
Would you mind
taking your shirt off?
Sure. OK.
Can I touch you, for a moment?
You're just so...
I never thought I...
Can I touch your shoulders?
Yes.
And your arms?
And your chest?
Yes.
Oh. Put that back on then.
You want me to put it back on?
Yes, if you want to.
I thought things were
progressing quite nicely.
I was suddenly overwhelmed.
By what?
Some wave, something of...
Lust.
Maybe. Sorry, I just feel
a bit sick, actually.
Tiny bit faint.
- Put your head between your legs.
I can do that on my own time.
I'll just, just, um... maybe
step away for a moment.
Catch my breath.
Have a drink.
It's just, I, er... I've never
felt anyone like you before.
Like me?
- Yeah, muscular, fit. Like a model.
I work out.
I'm sure you do.
- I work hard.
Don't you ever feel sometimes
it's a bit shallow?
Yes. But my
clients like it, you know.
And I like being wanted by them.
When I'm here with you, being
looked at by you, I feel good.
God, I can barely imagine that.
Come here and stand with me.
I've always been ashamed
of myself. My body, I mean.
Always?
- Mm.
Always been aware of
what's wrong with it.
You know, stubby
thighs, fat tummy...
boobs come down to my naval now,
my arms wobble...
they have done
since I was 20, actually...
and if I didn't pluck here
and here
I could join a
circus after a month.
Oh, I've plucked it.
- Mm.
Don't be fooled
by the muscles, Nancy.
I sometimes feel ashamed too.
That's hard to imagine.
Well, if I didn't look like this
you might not have chosen me,
or wanted me.
Can I unbutton this?
Yes.
Can I take this off?
- Mm-hmm.
Your body is beautiful.
I wish you could see that.
I have always
quite liked my calves.
They're not completely awful.
I can hear my mother...
"Vanity is a weakness, dear."
It's not vain
to enjoy your body.
To love it.
But I know that voice in your
head, the one that talks shit at you.
I have one too.
It gets tiring...
so boring.
Oh, I'm sorry to bore you.
You're not...
You're not boring me, Nancy.
Hm... Is Leo Grande
your real name?
No.
Is Nancy Stokes your real name?
Do you know, sometimes I wonder
whether what you young men need
is a war.
Excuse me?
Well, you're all
just so fit and...
bursting with energy and killing
pretend soldiers on your computers
but actually, underneath it all,
you're really quite anxious
and not quite
sure of yourselves.
Perhaps that's what
every generation needs.
A war. It's self-correcting.
It makes us all nicer.
My generation of men, they never
had a chance to prove themselves.
I mean, I think they felt actually
inadequate in front of their fathers.
And I think it's caused
a whole lot of bother
and I'm worried your
lot are gonna be even worse.
My brother's in the army.
Is he? Oh, sorry.
I didn't mean to imply...
Is he older or younger?
He's younger. He's 24.
Huh. Which bit of the army?
Artillery.
Mm, oh, the big guns.
Yeah, well,
might as well go all in.
If I was in the army,
I'd want big guns too.
Do you see him?
- Not much.
Miss him?
Of course.
I love him.
And he doesn't...
He doesn't know about all this?
No.
He thinks I work at the oil rig.
Uh-huh.
Not sure he believes it.
So, you're not close?
Can I top you up?
Yes... please.
Thank you.
Not for me.
Or I won't enjoy myself as much.
You wanna play a game?
Like role play.
We could work the blow job
into the game, it might help.
How about teacher and student?
We could have an RE lesson.
Like the Garden of Eden...
the fall of man...
Come on, Miss.
Teach me about original sin.
You know,
I've been very bad today, Miss.
You might have to keep me behind
after class.
You have to stop wearing
those tight skirts because I...
I can't concentrate on my Bible.
And, er, when you lean down
over my desk
I can see right
down your blouse.
And last night in my bed, I...
OK, stop it.
- But, Miss...
No, we shouldn't be doing this.
- No, I know, Miss, but...
No, no! Safe word,
safe word, safe word.
What?
- Safe word.
We don't have a safe word.
I didn't think we'd need one.
Oh, It's OK, we can stop.
Look, I've stopped.
I'm just not into
all that, OK? My God.
OK, sorry. I didn't mean to...
I-I know what this looks like.
But it's just not the point.
I don't want to dominate you.
I don't want to teach you.
- It's only play.
Yes, I know, but I don't want
to play at that.
I want to play at something else. I
want to play at feeling young again.
I want that feeling back.
That feeling of...
having it all before me.
You want to be 16 again?
No, I don't want to be 16 again.
Being 16's bloody awful.
I want the
feeling of being 16 again.
That power...
God, I didn't know I had it.
It was wasted on me.
But some
of the girls I taught...
they knew what they were doing.
With the men, I mean.
What do you mean?
I tried to tell them, the girls
but the skirts just kept
on going up and up and up and up
until you could practically see
how clean their back teeth were.
They just didn't care.
Why should they? They can wear
what they want, surely.
Men can't always control themselves,
Leo. They're not all like you.
Some of those male teachers were
like lambs to the slaughter, poor sods.
Or maybe they
were in the wrong job.
Or maybe they should have realised
those girls weren't there for them.
Have you ever been...
you know, in trouble?
Been in trouble?
Mm. I mean, isn't
selling sex illegal?
No, soliciting
money for sex is illegal.
I don't solicit
money for sex, Nancy.
No, I sell my company.
I provide
interesting conversation.
I can dance, I can
make 20 different cocktails.
Whether or not we have sex
is our business.
There's nothing
illegal about that.
I mean, as well as the blow jobs
it's also quite nice
to get to know each other.
Yes, I suppose so.
That's why I tend to recommend
more sessions.
Sorry?
It makes it more
satisfying, you know?
I'm actually looking
for more regular clients...
Oh, I see.
- What?
I see where this is going.
- It's not "going" anywhere.
Here it comes. The hard sell.
Is it like driving lessons?
Do I get 10 for the price of 9
if I book in advance with
the Leo Grande School of Sex?
I don't know what other
kind of clients you have, Leo
but I am not a rich woman.
No, I know but...
- And so, you know
I'd like to wind up
the sales chat before my time
and money and
patience run out, so...
please, Leo Grande,
or whatever your name is
just give me my bloody blow job
and we can all go home.
Why don't I sit on the edge here
and you could kneel on a cushion
in front of me?
How about that?
OK. If that's... optimal.
Do I just... get it out?
That's right.
Oh, it's pathetic. I'm pathetic.
That list
was such a stupid idea.
You know, you don't have to
do any of this. At all.
I'm scared. That's the truth.
Of what?
That I won't like it.
That you won't like it.
Maybe you won't.
But you can try and see.
It's no harm.
Unless you're gonna bite it off.
In which case I
probably won't like it.
Nancy, everyone
needs something different.
Maybe you just want to talk?
You know, I have a
regular client who just likes to
hold hands and
watch TV together.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I also have a client
who likes me to walk in
without a word
have sex with her as quickly
and silently as I can
and then leave.
I actually quite like that one
because it only takes ten minutes
but she pays for the full hour.
And there's a guy who wants me
to dress up as a cat
and then ignore him for an hour
and go home.
What, and have no sex?
- No.
I think you'd make a
very good cat, for what's worth.
Thank you.
What I'm trying to say is,
I don't judge my clients.
You know?
Unless they're total arseholes.
And you're definitely not
a total arsehole.
Well, that's nice to hear.
I have a client who can't walk.
And I bathe her.
But what she really wants
is dirty talk while I do it.
And then I join
her in the water.
It's what she wants.
Hmm.
- Everyone wants something different.
You sound like
some sort of sex saint.
Are you real?
Oh no, I really fancy her.
It's quite hot.
And I look forward to it.
It's what she needs.
You make it sound like it should
be available from the local council.
Like a public service.
Mm. Can you imagine how much
less bullshit there would be?
As long as they
don't put the rates up
cos people are furious enough
about that.
They'll still collect the bins.
It's different for women, though,
in your line of work, isn't it?
More dangerous.
- It can be.
Well, I've been called some choice
names and been slapped about a bit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, come on.
You know that. You do.
Yeah, you know
I used to set this exact essay
question in my ethics lessons.
"Should sex work be made legal?"
And every year, 30 essays
came back, all exactly the same.
What did they say?
Uh, that although the moral
issues remain up for debate
the legalisation of sex work
would ultimately provide protection
for sex workers and help
eradicate trafficking and abuse.
Sounds like Wikipedia.
It is Wikipedia. They all
copied it out, word for word.
Every year. Except this one boy
Lucas White
who wrote, um...
"Sex work should be made legal
so your mum pays
tax on her earnings."
Which did provide
a bit of light relief
if I'm honest.
Oh...
I think it's...
much bigger than that,
the whole idea.
Just think how civilised
it could be
if it was just available to all
there's no shame attached,
there's no judgement.
You want sex, and you're frustrated
you can't get it for whatever reason.
You're shy, you're unwell,
you're grieving
you're physically struggling...
so you just hire someone
like me.
It's all regulated and safe.
For you, for me,
better for everyone.
And I help you...
Or I pleasure you.
Even better.
The... thing is, lots of people
like the secrecy.
They get off on it,
or they just want the fantasy.
And that's totally fine
but... I quite like the reality
and it's my actual job, so...
You know, one thing I love, Nancy,
is just to watch someone's face
when they feel pleasure.
When they let go,
when they succumb
when the body goes with it
and that heat,
and that feeling...
Everything just loosens.
It's...
It's just so, so great.
Mm.
Oh!
You do like it.
Thank you for
telling me that, Leo.
I mean, not only because
it was very interesting
and enlightening...
But also...
do you mind if...
Go for it.
Mm.
Mm!
[SHE SIGHS
That was a surprise.
A good surprise?
Yes, very good.
I wasn't sure about it.
You know, whether I'd like it,
but it's...
like bathing in a warm sea.
I may have dropped off
for a moment, actually. Sorry.
It's no problem.
But also no...
- No, no orgasm, no.
I wonder what noise I'd make.
Apparently
sneezing's a very good sign
of how loud
a person is when they orgasm.
Really?
- Yeah.
My mother sneezes very loudly.
But some people sneeze
like cats.
You know...
I... I can never rid myself
of the notion
that they must orgasm
like cats too.
If cats orgasm.
I don't know, do they?
Nobody knows.
How did you fake it, with your
husband? What noise did you make?
Um, oh, God...
Wait. I've got to think...
think it through, um...
Hm-hm-hm-hm.
That was very convincing.
Anyway... that's number two
ticked off the bucket list.
Or "licked off
the fuck-it list".
Quite. And I'm
very happy about that.
You are very good at
this whole business, you know.
I hope you know.
People should tell you.
Thank you.
That's nice to hear.
It's a sort of
mysterious gift you have.
It's not so mysterious.
I just make the effort.
And I like you, so it's easy.
See, see? You always know
the right thing to say
when to make the
move and all that.
You learn to read people.
I'm not sure I ever have.
You have to want to first.
Yeah, I probably don't want
to enough to put in the work.
I just pay attention.
And what about you? Is there
someone who pays attention to you?
You know, is there someone?
- Someone?
Yes, you know, a special person,
a particular person.
What, other than you?
Oh, stop it. I mean a
girlfriend, or boyfriend
or, you know, one of those fluid
arrangements you have these days.
Nancy.
- Leo.
It's all about this moment,
in this room, right now.
It's all about you.
Forget everything else.
That's the whole point.
Yes, but who are you in there?
Who are you out there?
That's what I want to know.
Now I've rebooked you.
- And I'm very glad you did.
And I am too, but I just thought
maybe we could personalise it a bit.
If it's gonna
be a regular thing.
I thought you were happy
with what I'm doing.
Oh my goodness,
believe me, I am.
My body is no longer the carcass I've
been heaving around for thirty years.
No, it's now a thing of wonder.
"A playground of delight",
as you say.
Did I say that?
Mm, perhaps not.
But what about you?
The real you?
I'm whatever
you want me to be...
here, in this moment.
Hmm, but what if I want to know
who you are without me?
When I'm not there.
Wouldn't that be OK too?
Nancy, I hope I've given you
what I said I would give you.
You said we should
get to know each other.
Nancy.
So you're not going to tell me.
Hey, have you ever considered
using sex toys?
You know,
I actually brought some with me
because some people find it much easier...
- Actually, in that case
I've got something to tell you.
Oh, yeah?
- Yes.
Well, go on then.
Well, you know, if you're not
gonna tell me anything yourself
long nights alone...
one's curiosity
gets the better of one...
Does it now?
- Yes. It does.
I know who you are.
Sorry?
I know who you are. I found
out who you are in real life.
Don't know what you mean.
This is who I am.
No, I mean your real name.
I found out your real name.
I was gonna tell
you earlier, but...
But...?
But I thought it was best to...
To... fuck first?
Well, it was just a minor bit
of sleuthing on my part.
You know, on my
credit card statement
there's a company listed
to your website
and you just go to
the company's house website
and you can find the name
of the director of the company
and that's how I found
out your name, you real name.
Hang on.
Hold on, what's going on?
No, I'll... I'll tell
you my real name, if you like?
I don't mind.
- No, thank you, I'm not interested.
Well, it's not so bad, is it?
For me to know, I mean, it...
It's not as if we're strangers.
I have boundaries.
I've asked you to respect them.
You haven't
so I'll be going now. Please
don't attempt to book me again.
Oh, come on now.
Come on. It's not so bad.
I'll... I'll forget I mentioned it.
No.
I'll still call you "Leo".
You won't calling me anything
because I won't be here.
OK, Connor.
Don't you call me that.
My name is Leo Grande.
You booked Leo Grande,
and you got Leo Grande.
And from what I could tell
by the moans and the sighs
you have no complaints
with Leo Grande, am I right?
Yes.
- Good.
So we're clear on that.
This is Leo Grande. I
made him, and I'm proud of him.
And by the way, "Nancy Stokes"
I could find out
who you are myself, you know.
How do you think
people would react if they knew
their ex-RE teacher was hiring
young men
to lick their
pussy in a hotel room?
What? Is that a
little too real for you?
Cos that's just what we've just been
doing, so don't get squeamish now.
I honestly didn't think
you'd react like this.
What?
- Well, I thought you'd be pleased.
Pleased?
Well, I thought we'd
built up a trust, a real trust.
I mean, I was ready
to tell you who I am.
I thought we could maybe continue
outside of here, have a coffee
or a drink or something.
Why can't we?
Why can't we be friends?
I mean, is it cos I'm old?
Cos old ladies aren't allowed
to participate in anything
where have to be kept quiet
and cosseted
until... oh, until
you need our money
and then you'll turn up
and do anything.
Look, I know that's how it feels
with your kids
but I have never treated you
or thought of you like an old...
I thought you
were proud of your work.
Why are you ashamed?
I'm not ashamed.
But you're lying about it, you're
hiding yourself, and your work.
Even from those closest to you.
You're deluded.
You're crazy and deluded.
Why can't your mother know
the truth if you're so proud?
If you're not ashamed.
- You know there's a word for this.
It's called cyber-stalking.
And nutters do it.
Crazy, sad, desperate
nutters like you.
Oh, well, I am so sorry that
I had the audacity to find out
the true identity of the man I've been
having sex with for the past month.
Why don't you tell me more
about your life on the oil rig?
Why do you have to lie to me
about who you are?
I am not lying to you, Nancy!
This is my professional name.
I provide a service, a fantasy,
and I told you that very clearly.
Well, all that stuff you said
about it being a vocation.
Is that lies?
- No.
She would be proud of
you, surely. She would.
Why are we
talking about my mother?
I could talk to her. I was always
very good with the parents.
I could explain it to her,
I could make her understand.
No, thank you.
I think it's important. Let me do it.
- I don't need you to do that.
Well, let me try.
I think it would be good for you
for your life.
Nobody is explaining
anything to my mother
because far as she's concerned,
I'm dead.
Sorry, what? What? What?
- Yeah.
That's what she tells everyone.
There.
Do you feel sexy now?
Feel like that's
what you're paying for?
No, I didn't think so.
Look, Nancy, I'm sorry that
your son is so immensely boring
and that your daughter has
a more exciting life than you.
You said your kids are like
a dead weight around your neck
so let's not pretend you're exactly
"Mother of the Year" yourself, right?
But why would she want you dead?
Why? What did you do to her?
Fuck off, Nancy.
Alright.
Don't talk to me,
I just forgot my phone.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Leo, please. Please.
- Fuck!
You wanna know if my
mother would be proud of me?
Yeah, she disowned me.
She left me to fend for myself.
How old were you?
I was 15.
Why? Why did she disown you?
What did you do?
What did I do?
I just disappointed
the fuck out of her.
Hello?
No, yes, no, no, no. It's fine.
It's my friend, he, um...
he fell,
actually, hurt his knee. Yes.
Absolutely, no, of course.
We'll keep it down.
Yes, yes, sorry. Thanks.
Bye.
You know, my
mother was like you.
She did everything right.
Food on the table, clean clothes
in the drawers, all that, but um...
I don't think she ever...
ever actually saw me.
Or if she did,
she didn't like it.
You know, she tried
to hide her repulsion
but I could just feel it...
vibrating
through the walls, and...
I just... I wasn't what she wanted.
What she imagined for herself.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, well, you
can quit judging me
you know, my life, my work.
You don't actually care about
the truth of my life.
You just wanted
something... exotic.
A broken little whore.
And I guess you found him.
Well done you.
I'm gonna leave now, Nancy.
You can have a refund
on the time.
Can I get you anything?
No, thanks, I'm
waiting for someone.
OK.
Can I get you anything?
- I said no tha...
Oh, sorry,
you're a different one.
Thanks a lot, I'm
waiting for someone.
Can I get you anything while you wait?
- Nothing, thank you.
Can I get you...
- No, thank you. Sorry.
Thank you, no, I'm waiting, I
will wait, I will wait for my friend.
Oh, you used to teach me.
Sorry?
- Yeah.
Mrs Robinson. RE.
Oh, keep your voice
down a little, would you?
What are you doing here then?
Um, ah, well, I'm
meeting a friend. Yeah.
Cos the parking here's so good.
Well, it's certainly better
than the coffee.
I'm Becky Foster,
do you remember me?
Um, no, actually.
I... funnily enough, I don't.
Sorry.
- Yeah, you used to teach me in Year 8.
Did I? I can't have
taught you very well, could I?
Why's that?
- Cos you're working here.
Hello.
Oh!
Where did you come from?
Um...
- This your friend, then?
Yeah, well, he's...
Well...
- Uh, I'm trying to sell my car.
Um, this good lady is interested
so we thought this was a great
place to meet to have a look at it.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
Cos the parking's so good.
Well, it's certainly better
than the coffee.
We'll take two of
those coffees, anyway.
We'll take the risk. Thank you.
Shall we sit?
Yeah.
You came.
You booked.
I didn't think you would.
I wasn't sure I would either.
But we both know the deal today.
Still, I'm very glad that you
decided to come, just to talk.
Lovely.
Thank you.
It's a powerful thing.
Sexual fulfilment.
It makes you feel... Well,
it made me feel invincible.
I hadn't realised.
I wish I'd known sooner,
when I was younger.
I'd have made
the necessary changes.
At least you've done that now.
Yes. Yes.
And you know, I have felt more alive
and more powerful in this last month
than I can ever remember.
I mean, I see my friends...
fading away at the edges.
Just shrivelling up
over the years
and I think...
actually, you're right, Leo,
this should be a public service.
You told a couple of
them about me. Your friends.
Yes, I have made recommendations
for the great Leo Grande.
I told them you're the
master of the menopause.
I'll put it on my business card.
I've been very
discreet of course.
I've only told the ones
I thought could really use...
Need it... You... Need you.
Well, I appreciate that.
Mm.
Uh...
Leo, my name, my real name
is Susan Robinson.
Such a boring name, isn't it?
Mrs Robinson. Hmm.
That's cute.
I've never done anything
interesting or remarkable in my life.
Um, this is it.
I always obeyed all the rules
fell in line.
I never drank too much, never
overshadowed my husband at parties.
I was always
the designated driver.
Ate my five a day.
Even before they were called
"five a day."
And I always, always
answer my phone when it rings.
You're the only adventure
I've ever had.
The only freedom, and...
I wanted it to be real.
I wasn't
thinking about it properly.
I was mad with some fever...
lust or whatever.
It made me mad.
I never... I've never...
I'm sorry, Leo.
I'm so...
That's it.
- Mm. That's it.
I just wanted to see you,
see you were alright.
Tell you what
you've done for me.
To thank you and to say goodbye.
Everything OK
here, Mrs Robinson?
Yes, um, thank you.
We're just wrapping up here now.
Mrs Robinson used to
teach me RE at school.
Oh, yeah?
Thank you, Becky.
Yes.
- Was she a good teacher?
She was alright. Bit uptight.
Not as bad as some of the others.
- Uh-huh.
Yeah. Except
for this one time...
Thank you, Becky,
for that glowing report.
She got all us girls together
for a special assembly.
Becky...
- No, no, go on.
And she told us
we were all sluts.
I don't think that's quite
what happened, Becky.
Yeah, she said girls
should look respectable
or we would go around tempting
the men and get ourselves into trouble.
She said if we looked like
sluts, we'd be treated like sluts.
Well, it was to do with
the length of the skirts mostly
which had just got
out of control by then.
Said if we spent as much time
on our studies
as we did on our hair,
we'd all be a lot better off.
Well, actually, I do... I
stand by that. I stand by that.
"Concupiscence".
Always remember that, too.
She used to make us say...
Said she liked the sound of it.
I did too.
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
It's a good word.
What does it mean?
- "Lustful desire".
Oh. Well, well.
Now you're talking.
Mm. Yes, St Augustine of Hippo
coined the term
in his doctrine of original sin.
He believed that it underpins all
the suffering and sins in the world.
So Becky, could we
please have that bill?
Well, I don't think I can
go along with that
cos it doesn't make any
"Concupi-sense" to me at all.
Longest word I know.
The bill, please, Becky!
My legacy. As an educator.
"Concupiscence".
It is a good word.
It's a new one on me.
Oh, well, I'm glad to
have found one you didn't know.
I was hoping I would.
I... I told my brother.
About what I do.
What did he say?
Well, he was surprised
to hear me say it, out loud.
But he guessed I made money
with something like this.
He, um, he said he
kind of already knew.
And he never believed
the oil rig stories.
He said Mum would
never talk about me.
About what she saw.
About what happened.
Mm.
Guess I was a
bit wild for my mum.
A lot for her to handle.
There was this one night,
back then when I thought...
uh, she was gone out
for the weekend.
But I was wrong, um...
I had some friends over
to hang out after exams
we put on some
music, drank some wine...
Next thing I know, she and a neighbour
are walking in on me and my friends
and we're all...
bodies wrapped up together,
bit of everything going on.
Um... exploring each other.
And I'll never forget her face.
Just humiliated. So ashamed.
We tried for weeks after
to patch things up, but, um...
her disgust was
just all over her.
I... had to leave.
She, um, said she
was glad I was going
and that she would never speak
my name again.
And from that point on
she told everyone that that
was the day her son had died.
Mm.
Surely, surely,
time's a great...
Healer? Yeah.
- ...healer.
No, Nancy, she... she meant it.
I even saw her a couple
of years ago in the street.
She just... she walked
straight past me.
Yeah, just cold.
Would you do
that to your own son?
Well, only because he's so
unremarkable I might not notice him.
I should probably stop saying
things like that about him.
Yeah, you probably should.
No, he's a good boy
and I'm very lucky to have him.
She was wrong, your mother.
There is nothing disgusting
or disappointing about you.
Thank you, Becky.
Becky, could you wait a moment?
Becky, I would
like to apologise to you.
What?
- Yes.
I owe you an apology.
For calling you a slut.
That was wrong.
That was not a word
or idea I should have used
with a group
of impressionable teenage girls.
I thought I was doing
the right thing at the time...
trying to
protect you, but now...
But now, I...
Becky...
I am not here
to buy this man's car.
OK.
This is
Leo Grande and he is a...
I'm a sex worker.
Yes. Yes.
And we have been meeting
for sex regularly
for the past few weeks.
That's right.
- That's right, that's right.
And, um, I recommend him highly
cos from anything else he's an
absolute marvel with his tongue.
And, um, Becky, you
may already know this
I hope you do, but
pleasure is a wonderful thing.
It's something
we should all have.
Um...
If you'll excuse us
uh, I have a
room booked upstairs
and um,
Leo and I need to get going
if we want to fit a session in
in the remaining time
cos, um...
...there's a couple of things
I'd like to try.
It was great to meet you, Becky.
I hope maybe we'll run into
each other again sometime.
Keep the change.
Take those off, Nancy Stokes.
I can't bal... I can't balance
like this. I can't balance.
OK.
Oh-oh...
Did you?
Stop asking.
OK.
- You're fixated.
I think you should drop it.
I know, I know, I just...
There's no pressure, of course,
I was just hoping.
Maybe all the others are faking.
Have you ever thought of that?
No.
- I'm joking.
We'll try one
more time. Just for fun.
Oh, OK. If you must...
Close your eyes.
Hang on, I brought something
with me
that you might like to try.
Oh, you know what?
Leo, I don't think I can.
I... I think I'm done.
I thought I brought
the little bugger.
It usually works.
Here it is.
Mm.
Was that...
Leo, I think this should be
the last time we meet.
I'm glad you booked me.
I'm glad you came.
- I'm glad you came.
Right?
I'm very satisfied customer,
put it like that.
I shall be ticking the big green
smiley face on the feedback form.
OK.
Well...
Good bye, then, Leo Grande.
And good luck to you.
Good luck to you.
Take care, Nancy.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/a7b2c
Help other users to choose the best subtitles