I serve as an equalizer.
I'm the one you call
when you can't call 911.
Previously, on
"Equalizer (2021)"
♪ Work it out
What kind of charity
needs a consult
after 9:00 at night?
The international kind.
The CIA wants you back, Robyn.
You're the best they had.
♪ Work it out
This is Melody, one
of my oldest friends.
- Enjoying being dead?
- You got him
out of one life sentence
and straight into another.
Why do I have a feeling
this is not a social call?
I need those freaky-ass
superpowers of yours.
My pleasure.
We'd be happy to
accommodate your new hobby
if you came back to the fold.
I'm ready to deal.
Freelance only.
Rest of the time, they
can just stay out of my way.
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
Look what I found.
Give it back!
Why? You can't play.
But I can.
One shot. If I make it,
you make the girl a
regular in your games.
And if you miss?
Well, then I guess I'm
buying the girl a new ball.
Yes!
Hey.
You want to play with us?
No.
But she does.
You do bar mitzvahs, too?
Why'd you want to meet me?
Company needs a favor.
A British doctoral
candidate on a federal grant
overstayed his visa;
He's in the wind.
Call ICE. Dorian Endicott.
College mathematician.
Loudmouth. Drinks too much.
Could be on a bender.
Call his sponsor.
His family's connected.
They don't want him
to embarrass them,
so they reached out to MI6
who reached out to the CIA
who then reached out to me.
Look, I'm sorry, Bish.
I got a spa weekend
with my aunt planned.
So, wait, whoa,
whoa. So grab him.
Drop him off at the
British, Consulate,
and then go get your
broccoli emulsion.
- You know that's not a thing.
- Look, hey.
Company asked for
you, Robyn, by name.
Do this, they'll give
you some rhythm,
at least for a while.
Don't you think I'm
a little overqualified
for a lost-and-found detail?
Well, maybe our friends
are just trying to remind you
that they're still
pulling your strings.
It's a milk run.
Not worth kicking up dust over.
It's the end of
the fiscal quarter,
and one of the charities
I'm consulting for is slammed.
They sent up a flare.
I understand. I'll be
there by, like, 5:00.
6:00, latest.
Robyn.
I would feel better if
you made me feel worse.
I mean, I-I had a month to plan.
And you're presenting later.
It's a creative
visualization seminar,
not a gender reveal,
and you're my guest,
so the room's comped anyway.
Just get there
when you get there.
Tonight. I promise.
Is that all you're packing?
What? I just need my homework.
I've got enough
clothes at Dad's.
Well, don't forget about
your community service
hours this weekend.
Okay. I only skipped
once, all right?
Yeah, and lied about it.
Yes, but I was still
planning on doing it
when I told you I did it.
But if you want
to be technical...
No, I want to be honest.
And every time you lie to me
makes me wonder what
else you're lying to me about.
So.
Don't.
'Cause I'll find out.
Get a massage, Mom. Please.
I swear I am.
Bye.Bye.
So that doctoral candidate
you're looking for
I don't think he's
just on a bender.
He, deleted all his
social media recently.
He hasn't been on his
cell phone in three days.
And he hasn't
accessed his email.
So he just ghosted?
Yeah, full-on Casper.
It's like the guy
suddenly dropped off
the face of the earth.
And then he
started erasing himself.
Well, I think I know where
his grant money went.
Expensive Scotch.
Fine cigars.
What did you say
he was studying?
Heuristic algorithms
as applied to
stochastic systems.
English, Harry.
It's a way to account
for uncertainty.
It's used for
financial modeling,
insurance risk assessments.
Random systems.
Sexy.
Yeah, if your idea
of sex is Java script.
I happen to be more
of a Python man,
but you know that.
Keep your Python to yourself.
Got a letter here from the
NSF about his research grant.
I wouldn't be too impressed.
They tend to toss those
things around like confetti.
Well, it looks like the party
was over for Mr. Endicott,
'cause it's a notice of
the grant's expiration.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Sue Wachtell.
NSF grants committee.
I'm here to get an update
on Mr. Endicott's research.
Phillip Moss.
Chair of the Math Department.
I'll save you some time.
The climate change
algorithm you've been funding,
I doubt he got off square one.
Why do you say that?
He's a unique personality.
Half the time he didn't show.
The other half he...
Well, here.
His students compiled these
for HR.
Anyone?
This is completely pointless.
None of you will ever get
jobs that don't involve a spatula.
Let me put this in terms
you can understand.
You're an imbecile.
My.
Is he drunk?
I'm tasked
with notifying him
of his suspension.
If I can find him.
Well, he must have friends.
Someone who would
send him an orchid?
Orchid, no.
Arsenic, yes.
If you find him,
send him my way?
Who would send
flowers to a guy like that?
Violina's.
Hi, my name is Shirley Kane,
and my boss got these
orchids, but I lost the card.
And so he can't
send a thank you note.
And if I don't tell
him who sent it,
I'm out of a job. I'm
already late on my rent.
I just, I... Calm down, ma'am.
What's the name of your boss?
Endicott.
Dorian Endicott.
The sender was anonymous.
And all that was on the
card were these numbers.
Who sends an orchid
with a bunch of numbers?
Maybe it's a nerd's
idea of foreplay.
Or a code. I'm
running the three series
through a program that
matches up the numbers
with known cryptographs.
It could be a
decimal-based cipher.
A multiple encryption
numeric system.
Try dropping a period
after the initial two numbers
in the first two groupings.
- Whoa.
- What?
Longitude and latitude.
Here in New York.
Mel, the third grouping.
Military time.
18:30 is 6:30.
Yeah, 03 is March, and 26 is
the day... that's today.
That's now.
Secret meet. Already began.
This is about more than
just some missing lecturer.
Run those coordinates
and get me an address.
All right.
Orchid.
Welcome to Chef Django's
Pop-up Dining Club.
Can I help you?
Do you have your
orchid invitation?
I believe my party is
popped up right there.
Finally.
What do I have to
do to get service?
Disembowel myself?
- I'm sorry?
- You should be.
What's this in my consommé?
Chervil, meaning
it's not consommé.
Take this swill back.
See if there's a dog
you want to poison.
Then try decanting something
that doesn't come in a box.
That's not chervil.
It's Queen Ann's lace.
Perfect for consommé.
As for the wine,
I'm sure you can arrange
for a sommelier on your flight
back to bonnie old England.
The Consulate sent you.
Who are you? Some
low-rent diplomatic aide?
I'm the person who gets
you where you belong.
You're an errand girl
dispatched by dilettantes
to pester a connoisseur.
I paid a ransom for this
seat at Chef Django's pop-up.
And I'm not moving
until I have tasted
the last petit four.
Understand?
Perfectly.
Assault.
False imprisonment.
I just ripped your shirt, so
add destruction of property.
Get down, get down!
Who are they?
- How should I know?
- You're lying.
Dorian?
Dorian?!
Damn.
You snake.
*THE EQUALIZER (2021)*
Season 01  Episode 05
Episode Title: "The Milk Run"
Aired on: March 28, 2021
Madam Director.
I see you're still
going for the heart.
I'm a romantic. Yeah.
So, how's the gig?
You'd have loved it.
Too bad you called the
Director of National Intelligence
a rock-licking moron.
I like to tell it like it is.
Which makes one of us.
So, that milk run that
you sent McCall on
turned into a firefight.
As far as we knew, it
was a standard retrieval.
And now Endicott's in the wind.
Thanks to McCall.
Is that really how you want
to play this, Suri?
Who is this guy, anyway?
What's going on?
You don't know, do you?
Look, tell McCall we're
sorry how this went down.
Okay?
And given the
evolving situation,
it would be best if she
brought Endicott directly to us
instead of the Brits.
Yeah. Okay.
So, Nash says
sorry you almost got
your ticket punched,
but
do us another solid.
I think that'll play well.
We'll make it worth her while.
Wait.
So, I bring in Endicott,
and my account is
squared permanently
with the CIA?
No more looking
over my shoulder?
Straight from the
director's mouth.
Director Nash is not the
type to sweeten the pot.
I think the stakes have changed,
and I think something
big's going down,
but they're not sharing.
I'm in.
Be worth it to have
them out of my life.
But I've been burned
by Nash before so
I'll deliver Endicott after I
know I'm not being played.
I still have contacts
in British intelligence,
so I'm gonna ask
some questions, okay?
Thanks, Bishop.
Is that the shoot-out?
Yeah, from a security
cam next door.
Hang on, zoom in on that guy.
That tat.
Sharpen the res?
He's Triad.
What are Chinese gangsters doing
trying to kill a
British math whiz?
They're not.
Harry, trace the trajectory
of the shots fired Dorian's way.
They weren't
shooting at Endicott.
No, they were shooting at
me. They wanted him alive.
Harry, you got to track
where Endicott went.
What do you think
I'm doing here?
It's like Where's Waldo?
With smoke, gunfire
and low-res video.
Well, that's why
you're the best.
Where you going?
Chinatown, to see an old friend.
Geez, I didn't know people
still read newspapers.
What's the latest?
"Man's Serenity Shattered
by Uninvited Intruder."
Well, relax, I won't
overstay my welcome.
What do you know about
a British mathematician
who might've overstayed his?
I'm a retired antiques dealer.
Why should I know anything?
Because you like to
stay out of the headlines,
and I know a thing or
two about killing a story.
Word is that said mathematician
might have discovered
something that's a matter
of urgent British
national security.
How urgent?
Such that if someone were
to find said mathematician,
they would be wise
to bring him directly
to the British Consulate
and leave him in
their rear view mirror
if they want to see old age.
Now
if you'll excuse me,
this is my hour of Zen.
You know
those things'll
kill you someday.
So will associating with you.
It's always a pleasure, Glenn.
Meaning this is not
entirely a social call.
What do you need?
Intel... on the Triads.
Specifically what they want
with a British grad student.
Yeah, news of your little
escapade is making the rounds.
The Triads don't want him.
The Chinese government does.
Endicott has something
they want to buy.
A source tells me the item has
national security implications.
Which explains why
Beijing farmed it out.
They don't want their
fingerprints anywhere near this.
Be careful, Robyn.
Word is, whatever
that guy's selling,
there are a lot of
interested parties.
What kind of parties?
The kind that shoot first
and ask questions later.
Hey, so I was able to
track Endicott from the alley,
stitching together ATM,
traffic cam and satellite footage.
He ducked into this computer
store on 54th and Broadway
before I lost him. You lost him?
He went into the subway.
That's why I'm down here.
It's hard to find me.
You know, you lost
him too, by the way.
Well, people were
shooting at me.
Yeah. What's he typing?
I hacked the
computer he was using.
But he erased everything...
Hard drive, meta data.
There's no protocol...
Run back the video.
Why?
There's more than
one way to hack that data.
Zoom in on his fingers?
One of my first
assignments was surveilling
a Serbian diplomat
through his hotel window.
Now, we couldn't
get into his laptop,
so I had to go old-school.
I learned to copy
his keystrokes.
So play that again, and put
what I'm typing
up on the screen.
So whatever this threat
to national security is,
he was gonna sell
it to the Chinese.
You got in the way and
now he's found another buyer.
Yeah, and I got 19
minutes to stop him.
Watching fingers typing?
That's analog...
I don't do analog.
You'll get 'em next time, babe.
This is it.
As promised.
Right, yes.
Check it.
It's good, yes?
Da, very good.
The money then?
And the other payment?
Nice doing business with you.
Who are you meeting
with and what did you sell?
I don't know what you're...
That's Gregor Shostakovich.
Russian intelligence.
You think you can do business
with them and they won't bury you?
They're coming back for me.
- We have to get...
- Tell me what you sold if you want my help.
I promise whoever you're
working for won't want me dead.
Please, they're coming!
Come on!
You broke my clavicle.
I'll break more than that
if you don't tell me what
you sold the Russians.
You really don't know
anything, do you?
- I know you're a traitor.
- Hardly.
That piece of software
they just bought,
after I demoed it, I activated
a self-delete feature.
So it's software.
Yes, fine.
It's software.
Only what I just sold
them no longer works,
meaning I just defrauded
an enemy of this country.
Which makes me
a hero, not a traitor.
You're welcome.
You just ripped off
Russian intelligence.
That just makes you stupid.
At least I didn't
kill one of them.
I have rights.
I demand to know who you
are and where you're taking me.
Like I said,
I'm the person who gets
you to where you belong.
And right now that
destination is a toss-up.
'Cause we are equidistant
between three places.
A CIA black site,
a Triad dog fighting kennel,
and a Russian bathhouse.
Take your pick.
Okay.
What I have has to be destroyed.
That's why I swindled
those Neanderthals.
So I could get enough
money to disappear
and protect the world
from my discovery.
That's all you need to know.
- Okay, I'm taking you to the CIA.
- No, wait!
I can't tell you,
but I can show you.
I have a place in
Brighton Beach,
where I stashed
a copy of the file.
Take me there, I'll
show you everything.
And then you can decide
whether to turn me in.
If I'm lying, it's two
hours of your life.
If I'm not, you might
just save the world.
I'm supposed to be having a
hot stone massage right now.
Figured you'd take the
deal... you want to know why?
♪ Hit 'em with a 20 piece...
Because your skill set suggests
you once were
part of the system.
One you're not rushing
to return to.
Your culinary sophistication
suggests a degree
of worldliness.
And you recognized
a Russian operative on sight.
I thus conclude you're
a former international operative
now plying your trade
as some sort of...
low-rent mercenary.
Quod erat demonstradum.
- My turn.
- ♪ Wiz Khalifa, man...
You're a stone-cold narcissist.
So whatever
you discovered
is not for the benefit
of mankind,
unless by accident.
You're well into your 30s
and still chasing a doctorate.
Which means you're
lazy, undisciplined...
And if you touch
my settings again,
I will break your hand.
All that's relevant is
my discovery.
A breakthrough even a troglodyte
could deploy
for world domination.
A weapon any government
would kill for.
The product of a lazy
and undisciplined mind?
I beg to differ.
So it's an easy-to-use
piece of software
with defense applications that
any government would covet.
Check.
I have low blood sugar,
so unless
you plan on ministering
to a diabetic coma...
Even a condemned man
gets a last meal.
Or didn't they teach you that
at kidnapper
finishing school? Fine.
There's a place nearby that
has pretty good cuisine.
We'll make a stop.
A mini-mart? You're joking.
The chili dog is
aged to perfection.
Oh, pairs nicely
with a cherry Freeze.
You'll love the bouquet.
Fine.
I'll take pistachios,
unsalted
and in their natural state,
not dyed that ungodly red.
And a Flake Bar.
And if they don't have Flake,
a Curly Wurly will do.
- Or a Yorkie.
- Do I look like your personal shopper?
Oh.
Thanks, bro.
Chocolate raisins?
Can we at least discuss this
like civilized adults?
- What, you never had...
- Mom?
Delilah?
And Kelly, wow.
Hey, Robyn, uh...
what a coincidence.
Yeah, Mom,
what are you doing here?
Just...
stopped for some gas.
Well, I-I don't...
I just, I thought you...
Uh, Dee told us that you were
going on a retreat with Vi,
but got slammed on a project?
Yes.
Um, something popped up
with one of my charities.
Gonna introduce us, Robyn?
This is my colleague,
Frank Brady
from accounting.
Frank, this is my
daughter Delilah.
And this is my ex's
new wife Kelly.
Nice to meet you, Frank.
Oh, the pleasure's
all mine.
So, we were just, um...
- Working late.
- Yeah.
Reconciling the books.
A nightmare,
but we hacked our way
through it.
But wouldn't you know it,
my car broke down.
Thankfully, Robyn offered
to drive me home.
And she's so kind,
so thoughtful.
What brings
you to this
delightful emporium?
Headed to the Knicks game.
Bringing our stash,
the good stuff.
Ah, red pistachios, delightful.
Yeah, Kelly,
we should go.
You know,
we'll miss tip-off.
Yeah, you guys go.
I'll take care of it.
Yeah, I got you.
Yeah, well, um,
I'll tell Miles you say hi.
Thank you.
Yeah, nice meeting you,
Mr. Brady.
See ya.
Bye.
Thank you.
I believe in being courteous
even to my captor.
Speaking of courtesy,
Robyn,
may I use the bathroom?
Go ahead.
So you'll uncuff me?
Not a chance.
What you got for me?
Well, I'm glad
you're still alive, McCall.
I wish I weren't.
I just ran into my daughter
and almost blew my cover.
That's the dangers
of working close to home.
But that's not the only danger.
Your boy was telling the truth.
He ripped the Russians off,
big-time. $50 million.
Wired to his account.
Doesn't make sense.
A guy as smart as Endicott,
why didn't he try
to hide the proceeds?
Greed makes people careless.
And now everybody's
hunting for him.
Which means
they're hunting me, too.
You know what my advice is?
Throw him in the trunk,
put a brick on the accelerator,
and let him drive
into the East River.
Can't. I owe too much
on my car lease.
Bad news.
They didn't have
anything you'd want.
These are
absolutely vile.
Enjoy.
You're a good mum.
Buttering me up
won't work.
I don't butter.
Your daughter said
it was nice to meet me
when it clearly was not.
That's good breeding.
You raised her well.
Kelly's lovely, by the way.
Must be tough being replaced
by the newer model.
I can see why
your marriage soured,
given how controlling
and unreasonable you are.
You know, I don't see
a ring on your finger.
Which is surprising, considering
how much of a people person
- you are.
- I don't have time to cater
to the sensibilities
of my inferiors.
Some of us are too busy
trying to change the world.
Aunt Vi, hey.
I'm just checking on you, baby.
I feel really bad
that you couldn't slip away.
Oh. Me, too.
How'd the seminar go?
Packed to the gills.
But now that I'm done,
I should come back.
Keep my girl company.
No. No way.
No need to ruin both
of our weekends.
Call if you change your mind.
Don't work too hard.
All right.
Lying constantly
to everyone
you care about...
must be tiring.
Oh...
We're here.
What are you doing?
- You don't need that.
- Like you never lied to me before. Open it.
It's okay.
I'm sorry. It's okay.
I'm sorry.
She's a friend.
This is Anya.
My son, Titus.
You have a son?
How did we miss that?
I've gone to
great lengths
to keep this part
of my life a secret.
How's my
favorite boy?
Nice to meet you both.
All right, look.
I got you here,
so I kept my end
of the bargain.
Time for you to keep yours.
The flash drive with
the software on it...
is here.
The only thing
in this apartment
is my girlfriend
and my son.
And I am keeping you
until they get away.
Because you think
she has these?
I took the diamonds off you
at the gas station, genius.
That pouch you
slipped her...
Gummy bears?
How did you...
The 50 million
the Russians paid you...
it was too easy to find.
You wanted people chasing
it while you slipped away.
Because the real payment would
be something untraceable.
Something that could be sold
anywhere, any time.
Perfect for someone
planning to disappear.
Which is why you're going
to give them to me.
Not until you tell me
what's going on.
You're in no position...
This is your last chance,
and then
I am taking you in.
Please, I beg you.
Just let us go.
You know I can't do that.
Then let them go.
You're a parent, too.
All I want is a future
for my child,
even if I don't have one.
Lock me up
and throw away the key.
Only, please, just
leave them
out of this.
Whatever it is you're hiding,
these people will not stop
hunting you for it.
And your family.
You want to save them?
Then you need
to trust me,
because right now,
I'm the only one
who can help you.
Mummy's the boss,
little man.
I love you.
Promise they'll be safe?
You have my word.
Now let's talk.
I need a drink.
You really shouldn't be
out in the open.
You wouldn't begrudge me
one last pleasure as a free man.
Start talking. Now.
I met Anya at an A.I. conference
a few years ago.
But her father was
a prominent Soviet physicist.
I didn't think the U.S. would
appreciate the relationship,
so I kept it secret.
Well, what does the relationship
with your family
have to do
with people chasing you?
Nothing.
But it has everything to do
with my discovery.
The grant didn't
pay enough,
so I started a new
side project.
And I discovered
something big.
Unfathomably big.
Two vodkas.
Mm. Vodka?
Please.
I loathe vodka.
It's tasteless.
It's not for you. I figured
a sophisticate like you would
have a more discerning palate.
There you go.
They're not for me, either.
♪ High off love
when you lookin' at me ♪
♪ I'm the type of chick
you put on repeat ♪
♪ I'm a bad girl,
I go hard like a freak ♪
♪ Trust me, baby, you don't want
a problem with me ♪
♪ Red octagon
when you try to stop me. ♪
- Who are they?
- Russians.
The word is out.
They're coming for you.
I really am gonna die.
Nowhere's safe.
There's one place.
Come on.
A secret lair.
How original.
Who's this?
Your Alfred?
You're right.
He is an ass.
Yeah, he is.
Sit down.
This is my associate.
And you're going to tell
both of us what you discovered.
I'll need a Scotch first.
Now.
Philistine.
Like I told you,
living grant to grant
wasn't cutting it.
As you now know,
I have expensive tastes
and costly responsibilities.
Occam's razor.
The most
efficient way
to make money is
to create it.
A cryptocurrency.
Well, he's not as dim
as he looks.
So this whole thing is about
cryptocurrency?
No. See, the trick to crypto
is making sure the encryption
can never be broken.
My day job is basically
machine learning
applied to random systems,
like climate.
So you modified the software
to test the encryption.
Yes. And it decoded it
instantly.
I assumed the currency
was a flop
until I ran the software test
against Bitcoin.
It decrypted it instantly, too.
No. That's impossible.
No, it's reality.
I wanted to create
a new currency.
Instead, I made
the most powerful
decryption tool known to man.
A master key that can access
any information
on any network
anywhere in the world.
I call it the God Algorithm.
Because...
what, you're God?
Well, it is my creation.
So you're saying
you can hack into any network,
anywhere?
Nuclear codes,
world banking systems?
I'm not "just saying."
It's a fact.
Well, if that's the truth,
then anyone who owns that key
owns the world.
Which is why I erased it,
and why people
- are trying to kill me.
- Oh.
Yeah, I-I'm not buying it.
Uh, you destroyed
your masterpiece?
I mean, DaVinci would never
destroy the Mona Lisa.
He would if he kept a copy.
And the most important copy
is right here.
Okay, so,
you made it,
you're gonna recreate it.
Want me to risk my life
to save yours?
I want to know who
and what I'm protecting.
Done.
What do you want me
to hack into?
Try the Fed.
Okay, the Fed.
Don't worry,
it's the most secure
financial system
in the world.
There's no possible
way he could...
No.
No, that's just...
that's just not possible.
Shall we see
how America's strategic reserves
are doing?
Get off that site, now.
Like I told you,
we're untraceable.
Hey.
How about a real challenge?
Assuming you have
the imagination.
Yeah, maybe.
Uh... NORAD.
Hack NORAD.
It's the most
firewalled security network
on the face of the earth.
Not even
a coordinated cyber...
Shall we play a game?
Oh, my God.
Now you're getting it.
The God Algorithm
can decrypt anything.
And anyone who has it
can play God.
Yeah, making it
the ultimate weapon.
Which is why I tried
to keep it a secret.
But given
my obvious bona fides,
I was probably being monitored.
And once word of
my pièce de résistance got out,
my fate was sealed.
So I drank some great wine,
ate some great meals,
and prepared for the end.
No one can have the algorithm.
Ever.
Which means
no one can have me,
because, like it or not, I'm the
most dangerous man in the world.
Guess we better get you
that Scotch now.
- What do you think?
- What do I think?
I mean, do you have any idea
of the ramifications
of this?
This is
Oppenheimer territory.
"I am become Death,
the destroyer of worlds."
I mean, he's right.
We can't let anybody
have this. Or him.
I mean, there is only one
logical conclusion.
Which is?
He has to die.
No one's dying,
not on my watch.
You back?
Yeah, and the CIA knows
you have Dorian.
She's got a red letter out
on you. So do the British.
So do the Chinese. Not to
mention that Russian kill team.
Especially after that
little tea party
you had with
Gregor Shostakovich.
Don't worry about it, though.
I cleaned it up
like I always do.
But now everyone knows
what he has.
I can manage the situation.
Well, maybe you shouldn't.
What are you suggesting?
That I turn him over to Nash?
We both know what
she'll do to him.
Well, it's better than leaving
Endicott with that algorithm.
- He won't use it.
- Well, not today.
What about tomorrow?
You know what they say
about absolute power, don't you?
No. He has a son he loves.
He'll do anything to
make the world safer for him.
And you're basing this
on what?
- His say-so?
- On 20 years
of betting my life
on my ability to read people.
I'm not feeding him
to the machine.
Listen, you play ball,
and you can put the Company
behind you forever.
But then what does that make me?
The whole world is looking for
this guy, Robyn.
How're you gonna hide him?
Same as the Clockmaker.
We get him
across the border.
Set up his family.
Keep him off-line.
Weekly touch-ins.
And if he even tries
to pull anything,
I will find him
and press the button myself,
but I need your help,
Bish.
I need your resources.
So are you in
or are you out?
You know, this humanistic
streak of yours
is gonna get me killed
someday.
I'm in, damn it.
Goodbye.
You sure about this?
I trust him with my life.
Bish?
I'm sorry, Robyn.
Too much at stake.
It's got to be
this way.
Thank you, William.
Let's go.
So, where you
taking him now?
Not your concern.
To a black site?
To all those dirty tricks
I walked away from?
Just like Ed and Michelle
in Venezuela.
Ends justify the means.
Everyone's expendable.
Including you.
Hold it.
We had a deal.
She walks away from this.
Russians.
Will! No!
No!
Get these cuffs off me!
You just executed
an innocent man.
You knew what he had.
We couldn't afford
to let anyone else have it,
especially the Russians.
There was another way.
You think that,
you've gone soft.
I'm off your call list.
I'm done.
Finished.
The hell you are.
This whole thing imploded
because you went rogue.
Meaning you
still owe us,
and we intend
to collect our debt.
Clean up this mess.
Nice, fellas.
Oh, that was awesome.
I have to admit,
that was kind of fun.
Fun?
A dislocated rib cage
is fun?
Not to mention
the fact I could've been...
what's the term
of art? Killed.
Nope.
Double-tap to the chest,
her signature,
just like I told you.
My field involves
the study of randomness.
Variables you can't control.
I could've been shot
in the head.
Hey, take it easy.
Everybody thinks you're dead.Ow.
No one's gonna be
hunting you anymore.
Operational incompetence.
How you lot ever won
the Cold War...
So, anyway,
how long do I have
to stay mad at you for,
uh, "betraying me"?
Give it a couple months.
This is my friend Lou.
He'll take you across
the Saint Lawrence into Canada.
Friend of mine will
meet you there, set you up.
Take you to the Yukon.
And you and your family
can disappear.
Oh.
You're gonna need these.
Ease up on the cognac.
It should last the three of you.
Who are you, Robyn?
Like I said...
I'm the one who gets you
where you belong.
I could always
look you up.
- I have a pretty good program.
- If you reconstitute
that algorithm, I'll find you.
And I'll kill you.
I believe you.
Take care of your family, okay?
Nothing is more important.
God, I hate this country.
Good luck, Dorian.
Good luck, Canada.
So, I hear you had
quite a weekend.
Delilah?
Got an earful when I
picked her up from her dad's.
How she busted you
on a date.
Robyn.
Now, look, if you'd rather hang
- with some guy, you know, just...
- Hang?
- Hang? I wasn't hanging.
- Just tell me next time.
I'm a big girl.
I can handle it.
It's nothing to handle.
Okay?
He was just a colleague.
An annoying one.
We spent the whole weekend
crunching numbers.
Is that what the kids
are calling it now?
Listen, I'm just glad
you had some fun.
I did not have any fun.
I had no fun.
Mmm.
But you may want to connect
with Delilah.
After all those lectures
on lying you gave her,
she is not as understanding
as I am.
Well, that was awkward.
You want to talk about it?
Nope.
Just makes
me wonder, Mom.
You were lying
about that...
...what else
are you lying about?
Captioned by Media Access Group
at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Synchronized by srjanapala
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6y25e
Help other users to choose the best subtitles