Previously on Ghost Wars...
They'll come at you
and I can't protect you.
You leave town right now
or we'll do things
the oldfashioned way.
Just take him in.
Come on, Doug.
Stop it.
Let's go.
You're damning us all to hell.
He's just not acting
like himself.
Marcus is showing definite signs
of demonic possession.
Marcus!
Cast out every onslaught
of infernal adversaries!
You killed him.
They're not my best.
Normally I use butter but we're
practically on war rations
so I had to use apple sauce.
It's only a week expired.
Wow, these look delicious.
Thank you, Carol.
Listen, there was something
I was hoping you could
help me with.
So I need someone who can keep
an eye on things.
Keep me informed
about what's going on.
You want me to spy on people?
No, no.
Think of it more like
a neighbourhood watch.
Yeah.
Winston!
Hey, Doug.
Why are you closed in
the middle of the afternoon?
Nothing left to sell.
Lambda swooped in after
the 'quake and cleaned me out.
Can't exactly get
any stock in, either.
But you're one of
the only stores in town.
Not anymore.
Sophia.
I'm sorry to hear about Marcus.
Do you have a wrench?
I just need the blood to stop.
Sophia.
It's not blood, it's rust.
Your pipes are really clogged,
but if I put some new filters
in all your taps
then you won't have
to walk around in the street
looking like Bloody Mary.
Ok?
Thank you.
I got you now you mother-
Roman, there's
someone I wanna talk to.
Let me guess.
You're having
communication issues.
Obviously.
Well, these new ghosts,
they don't wanna have anything
to do with me.
They don't wanna talk to me.
You should be happy about that.
Well, I need to know.
I need to know what they want
so I can try to fix this.
I can't help you.
Sorry.
Shh.
Jesus!
Told you.
Let's get a pry bar, Rodney.
Alright.
You may wanna move.
I'm not moving.
This is my spot.
Besides, anything gets in
my food it's free, right?
Pain in the ass.
Be careful.
What the hell?
Jesus Christ!
Yeah, that's weird.
How is that possible?
I heard about this.
Bunch of rats get their tails
all twisted together
and then they die
because they can't get apart.
This is considered
a very bad omen.
I hear Lambda's up there running
secret experiments
on this town.
After what happened to Marcus
it's gotta be some kind of
end of times biblical shit.
Apparently Sophia's
cracking up, too.
She drained Marcus's body
and bathed in the blood.
Who told you that?
Bake sale Carol.
Are people still calling
me that?
Everybody should just shut
their collective mouths
and stop speculating.
We all need to quit ignoring
the obvious.
This town is haunted.
Norman.
That's a load of bull.
Remember that old ghost story
that they used to tell us
when we were kids?
The whistling man?
Come on!
I've been hearing-
What a load of crap.
And not to mention blasphemy.
No, no, no. I'm serious.
My aunt's second husband
saw him once.
Well, let me guess.
He was whistling.
Jesus!
What the hell, Carla?!
Rodney, are you alright?
There's a bunch of exposed wires
up there.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Be careful, Carla.
I swear I've never seen
these before.
No wonder those rats were
so fried.
How're you doin'?
I'm alright.
I think I need a beer.
Carol?
People are starting to gather
out there.
You sure we can't do this
in here?
Sophia was adamant it
not be in the church.
After what happened
I don't blame her.
It wasn't the Father's fault.
I'm not saying it was.
So how's the neighbourhood
watch going?
Is there anything to report?
Yes, a lot.
Great.
Thank you.
Um...
Darcy May is pregnant?
And keeping it.
This isn't exactly what
I had in mind.
I've been busy scraping
Rodney Doyle off the floor
after he electrocuted himself
at the Chieftan.
He what?
He was extricating some
rat monster from the ceiling.
And you didn't think
to add that to the list?
It's fine.
Thank you.
You're doing a great job, Carol.
Everyone's staring at me.
They all must think
I'm a terrible mother.
No one thinks that, Sophia.
They've all come here
to grieve with you.
What happened to Marcus
is not your fault.
I couldn't protect my son.
Marcus, he misses you, too.
Thank you all for coming.
Before I turn things over
to Carol
I'd like to say a few things.
I know this is a sad day
for all of us.
But even in the face of tragedy
we're still the same people
we were before.
We stick together and we support
each other no matter what.
So let's come together now
and support Sophia
by remembering what a great kid
Marcus was.
Carol?
Thank you.
A reading from
the Book of Wisdom.
"The souls of the just are
in the hands of God,"
"and no torment
shall touch them."
"They seem, in the view
of the foolish, to be dead"
"and their passing away
was thought an affliction."
Marcus?
Jesus Mary and Joseph.
My god!
Coward.
Hey, Rodney. Come on in.
So how was the funeral?
It was a total shit show,
actually.
A lot of weird stuff went down.
Coffin opened up.
Everyone went nuts.
It was-it was pretty f@♪$ed up.
Well, Sophia shouldn't have
to go through that.
Nope.
You got a new batch?
Yeah. Yeah.
Reinforcements.
Good.
I hope this batch is better
than the last one.
I think the last one
had sand in it.
Poor Sophia.
She deserved better than that.
Are you ok?
I want you to tell me
about the wiring.
I don't-I don't have a clue
what you're-
The exposed wiring
above the bar?
Rodney almost electrocuted
himself doing some repairs.
I never thought anyone
would look up there.
What the hell is going on?
It's electrical currents.
We figured out that it keeps
these things away.
So... only Lambda knows
about this?
Yeah.
What about the rest of the town?
Well, there's not enough
supplies at Lambda
for the whole town, ok?
So I-I shouldn't have even
taken the ones I did.
You're unbelievable.
I was just trying to keep
you safe.
I need your help.
Maggie, please don't
ask me again.
I'm out of options, Roman.
I'm torturing him.
I can tell.
I can't go up to Doug Rennie
and say
"hey, I got a message
from your dead daughter."
That's not gonna happen.
This is important.
And you're just being a baby.
You don't get it.
People loved you.
They're scared of me.
My dad needs you.
Not him. Please, not him.
Anyone but him.
I'm not a saint.
Then you're no better
than he is.
The kind of person you choose
to be
is the one thing
you have control over.
You were given a gift
for a reason, Roman.
Now's your chance to use it,
before it's too late.
Before all you have is regret.
You think you get death?
You don't.
If you help me I'll...
I'll tell you more
about the others.
I want to go on record saying
this is a bad idea.
Maggie, this is a very bad idea.
I could shoot you for
trespassing, you know.
Just stay calm.
I have a message for you.
He can smell fear.
Who in the hell would be
stupid enough
to send you over here
with a message for me?
Your daughter.
You get the hell off my property
and you get off now!
This is about Maggie, ok?
Tell him to stop being a dick.
She's worried about you.
Listen. I said tell him to stop
being a dick.
Hey. I didn't buy this hippy
voodoo shit from your mother...
Roman tell him!
So you think I'm gonna
buy it from you?
Not a prayer.
Ok. I-I-she says that
you should stop being a dick.
What did you...
His middle name is Herman.
Just say to me?!
Your middle name is Herman.
What did you just say?
Your middle name is Herman,
right?
Am I right?
How did you know that?
I'm just trying to help you,
you bigot.
Roman.
Go.
You wanna see a bigot put
a hole in your head?
Go.
Now!
Maggie says that she loves you.
You get the f@♪$ outta here!
You stupid f@♪$!
Closin' up, hon.
Time to go.
What?
You want me to give you a ride?
No.
I'm walking.
Alright.
No funny business.
What did I just say?
What are you looking at,
Winston?
Don't look at my cards.
I'm getting antsy here.
Don't touch until we're done.
Hey, Maggie.
Hey! Maggie.
Hey, dad.
Guys.
Hey, come on and have a drink
with the old dad.
Come and play
some cards with us.
You can't afford to lose
to me again.
I want my money back
is what's what.
Come on.
Shots, shots, shots,
shots, shots, shots!
Yeah!
Mags?
Maggie?
Come on.
Mags.
Mags?
Mag-Mags?
Ma-Mags?
Maggie?
Maggie.
You look like shit, Doug.
A little hair of the dog, Doug?
Hey.
I heard he's been offering
his spooky services
to people in exchange
for supplies.
Come on, man.
He's not that bad.
Whatever.
What, man?
He saved my life.
I need your help.
I'm begging you.
What is that?
It's a Ouija board.
I know we have to summon her
or something.
She's already here.
She wishes that you would
quit smoking.
And I guess she wants me
to stop drinking, too, right?
She's a realist.
How do I know she's really here?
Where?
One second.
She stole a watch from you.
Um, where?
She thought you were gonna
get drunk and pawn it off
so she hid it underneath here.
Here.
She says she's sorry about
missing Friday night pizza.
It's not her fault.
Will you tell her
it's not her fault?
You just did.
She can hear me?
Are you telling me the truth?
Yeah. Just talk.
Maggie.
Maggie, the first thing you need
to know is that it's my fault.
That night you came in and
we were all drinkin', and I...
I gave you some and...
I just kept drinking and I
didn't pay any attention to you.
She doesn't understand.
You need to tell her.
It's my fault.
Doug. Doug!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey.
Hey, Doug, Doug.
Look at me.
She forgives you.
She forgives you!
Doug, you don't need
to do this, please.
I love you, dad.
I love you.
Um... hi?
Everything alright?
Yeah, I just...
wanted to know how much
I owe you for yesterday.
Nothing.
Forget about it.
I'm having a little get together
tonight at my house
in honour of Maggie
because I could never give her
a funeral.
I could never face it.
Doug, are you inviting me?
What, do you want a goldplated
save the date card?
Um... I'll be there.
Ok.
And I painted over the graffiti
on the side of your house
this morning.
You didn't have to do that.
Yeah, I did.
'Cause I'm the one
who put it there.
Whoa, Sangria...
Yeah, I am surrounded by friends
'cause they're drinking
the truest drink.
Dougie.
No. No.
Doug.
I'm passing on this one.
This is really nice,
she would have liked it.
Yeah, she would have loved it,
honey.
She would have loved the party
except for that picture.
Exactly.
Here's to Maggie.
To Mags.
Yo, buddy.
I like the Port more
than Sangria,
I am waiting for that.
I am proud to call you dad.
Bastard!
Roman.
It's Maggie.
Rodney!
No! No!
Noooo!!!!!
Let me out!
No! No!
No!
Let me out!
Wait, wait wait!
Wait, stop!
Maggie, please don't,
please don't, please don't!
You gotta let me out!
Please, please, please, Maggie!
Don't! Don't!!
You wanted it!
Hi.
Ready for another?
I think I've had enough.
Come on.
This one will make you
feel good.
Ok.
I got you.
Thank you.
No, you don't.
What?
Come on.
Maggie.
Maggie?
No, Maggie.
Maggie, Maggie, Maggie,
Maggie, Maggie,
don't, don't, don't.
Don't do this.
Maggie.
It's ok.
No, Maggie, don't do this.
Maggie!
Doug.
Get him outta here.
No!
Jesus.
Still scared of me?
Yeah, I thought that
you might have left
after what happened last night.
As soon as I knew what
that creep did I...
could have gone.
I wanted to say bye.
My god.
You are totally gonna miss me.
Yeah.
I'm not exactly swimming
in friends here.
Well, you seem to be turning
that around.
So what happens now?
Bye, Maggie.
You can't save them.
You think if you can
figure out what they want
you can help them.
But you can't.
You have to find a different way
to stop this.
Bye, Roman.
You don't understand.
I was a different person
back then.
Shut up.
Just... let me explain myself.
He said shut up.
You're going to jail, Rodney.
And if you're lucky someone
will remember to feed you.
Val, don't do this to me.
You owe me due process, right?
I know the law.
Look around, you piece of shit.
We are the law.
You ok, Doug?
Maggie?
Yeah, I think she got
what she needed.
I'll see you around.
It's ok.
Doug.
I know I have no right
to ask you this.
You want me to forgive you,
right?
Yes.
Shit!
Doug... come on.