You'd think with all we've lost,
that defeat would break us.
But the only reason we're here
is we refused to die in the first place.
We're as persistent as the cold,
forever trapped beneath the ice.
We keep our eyes on the floor,
dig our nails in,
and prepare to brace.
Do you think I wanna be here? Eh?
That Mr. Wilford wants me to be doing this?
Snowpiercer is all that's left of the world.
- Mommy!
- Please, no, no.
Each of us has a personal responsibility
to the Engine Eternal.
You Tailies barely have to do anything.
Yeah?
Just sit around and don't rebel.
- This is your fault.
- Mom.
- Let's get it over with.
- Please don't. Please.
Do it to me instead.
Where's the logic in that?
She's just a little girl.
Yeah, a little girl
who helped to kill six men.
I'm her mother. It's my fault.
I let her help the rebellion.
Finally.
Someone with the moral fortitude
to take responsibility for their actions.
All right.
Oh, baby. Oh, come here, baby.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay, honey.
You're so brave.
It's gonna be okay. Look at me. Look at me.
Go to your brother.
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
Be strong, Winnipeg.
I love you.
Unticketed passengers,
Mr. Wilford has found you guilty
of insurrection, murder
and disturbing the order of the train.
As stowaways, you have no right to trial
or the established appeals process.
Layton, keep your promise. You hear me?
It is only by the largess and mercy
of our Engine Eternal
that you have been allowed to live thus far.
It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay. It's gonna be okay.
So by the authority of Wilford Industries,
you are hereby sentenced
to indefinite suspension in the Drawers.
May God have mercy on your spark.
They can take our limbs,
our children,
our leaders.
They keep trying to take our dignity,
but any survivor will tell you
they check their dignity at death's door.
The more they steal from us,
the more human we become.
Humanity will fill our bellies one day
when we eat the rich of Snowpiercer,
One thousand and one cars long.
Easy, girl.
We're facing
Class Four tracks and...
- That's why I reconfigured the plow.
- I can't see conditions here.
Good morning, engineers.
Good morning.
Our speed keeps triggering avalanches.
Second one in an hour.
This stretch gets rougher every revolution.
With a storm like this, Mel,
it doesn't matter how many satellites I hack.
We're basically running blind right now.
Keep the speed up.
I'm gonna be busy downtrain today.
It's gonna get hairy.
How's your murder in Third?
It's two murders in Third,
an uprising in the Tail,
and drama in First where they're acting
like there's a mob at their door.
Guys, back to the Engine, please.
Do not highball this terrain.
I recommend we throttle back 12 percent.
Javi, I can't announce blackouts. Not today.
Well, you can slow for safety,
or you can have electricity.
Maintain speed.
She'll hold the track.
How long do you think she can keep this up?
Well, Javi, we're going on seven years
and counting.
Attention all passengers.
Wilford Industries wishes you good morning.
- The temperature outside is minus 100 degrees.
- Get up.
How you feeling this morning, Brakeman?
Sit down.
Don't get used to it.
Yeah.
She might be experiencing some PTSD
symptoms because I saved her life.
You were in it to save your buddies.
I don't owe you a thing.
You two are gonna have a great day.
- Sanitation!
- All right, back it up!
You know the drill.
Sanitation detail.
Uptrain, you'll keep your eyes down.
You will not interact
with ticketed passengers.
- Watch it, Tailie.
- You can just ask nicely.
Your people killed their friends.
I don't think you realize how unpopular you are.
Yeah, well, they killed 14 of mine.
Layton, come on.
It was a good, clean arm.
It shattered very nicely.
But, no, that's not enough for the Folgers.
They're with Sharma.
She's worked up a nice head of steam.
I'll handle her.
Oh, wait a minute.
- Oopsie.
- There you go.
You're the First Class Committee Chair.
Table it or I will.
How are everyone's train legs?
Did we miss our Gravol this morning?
Actually, Melanie, we don't think that Gravol
is the best prescription
for a rebellion in the Tail.
I think "rebellion" is overstating it.
Commander Grey had it contained in minutes.
Six dead. Security forces
don't grow on trees, Melanie.
- And we have a second concern.
- The murder in Third.
You keep quiet because you called up
a Tailie to assist the investigation.
Mr. Wilford picked the person for the job.
He's a former homicide detective.
- There's a policeman in the Tail?
- There's a bit of everything back there.
Don't worry, Mrs. Folger.
Upgrading this man in the middle
of a rebellion, it sends the wrong message.
If Mr. Wilford needs help,
I was a lawyer for 25 years.
I'd be happy to share insights
if you share details of the investigation.
Well, as a lawyer, you understand
that information is privileged.
And I didn't know that Finklestein,
Branxom, and Folger did murders, Mom.
Go ahead and laugh.
My family may not think
I'm capable, Melanie,
but the Freeze taught us all
we have the capacity to kill.
Which is why everyone is a suspect.
Even you.
Do you want more coffee, Lilah?
Well, enjoy your breakfast.
And it's a good day to stay seated
and ready to brace.
- Thank you.
- Can I get you anything else?
How's your breakfast? Wonderful. Thank you.
Tailie tossed coming through.
Buddy, keep moving.
You ready to detect, detective?
- Tunnelman Jakes Carter.
- Come on.
He's the guy who found the body.
- I'm working a double. This is my break.
- I'll join you.
Hey, small for me. He's good.
I know you. You're that Tailie detective.
Look, I already told what happened once.
I'm the Train Detective,
and Mr. Wilford asked me
to come hear it from you directly.
Do you have a problem with that?
No. No problem.
I was doing routine maintenance
under Ag-Sec.
It was just another day,
round and round we go, right?
I pop a floor panel, and there he is.
No arms, no legs and no dick.
- Who has access to the sub-train?
- Pfft. Hundreds of people go through every day.
Workers, passengers, all classes.
What are the checkpoints
like between classes?
Don't answer that.
I am trying to assess
how far you can move a body.
All right.
That's it?
No, one more thing.
What's that you're eating?
Mm.
This is the best beef noodles
on the train right here.
Hey, if we need you again,
don't be an asshole.
Okay, stay on point.
We got two hours until the autopsy,
and Nikki Genet is still unconscious,
restricted access.
Well, when you're done with your beef,
we'll take a trip to the Night Car
where she used to work.
Scene of the first crime. It's good.
Is the issue with the suspension formula
or the duration?
That's a complicated interplay.
I've taken very good care of her.
I'm trying to figure out
if she's gonna come out of it.
Slowly. I hope.
You should recommend
Mr. Wilford put the entire program on hold.
No.
Tell Mr. Wilford I'll get to the bottom of it.
Please.
Then we better go look at your data.
Night-Night Car.
Welcome to the Night Car.
♪ Say it ain't so, Joe, please ♪
♪ Say it ain't so ♪
♪ That's not what I wanna hear, Joe ♪
♪ And I've got a right to know ♪
♪ Say it ain't so, Joe, please ♪
♪ Say it ain't so ♪
♪ I'm sure they're telling us lies, Joe, please ♪
♪ Tell us it ain't so ♪
♪ They told us that our hero
Has played his trump card ♪
♪ He doesn't know how to go on... ♪
Miss Audrey.
It's her place.
♪ And determined smile
But the good ole days are gone ♪
♪ The image and the empire
May be falling apart ♪
♪ The money has gotten scarce ♪
♪ One man's word held the country together ♪
♪ But the truth is getting fierce ♪
♪ Say it ain't so, Joe, please ♪
♪ Say it ain't so ♪
♪ We've pinned our hopes on you, Joe ♪
♪ And they're ruining our show ♪
I found Nikki in the room with Edward,
her regular.
She had no idea what was happening.
Drugged, I'm sure, by the real killer.
But Mr. Wilford needed a quick resolution.
A body in a Drawer.
This time will be different.
Just for context, what was Melanie Cavill's
role back then?
That's a good question.
It's her lips to God's ear, isn't it?
On the house.
Old-world spirits.
A little something special for your service.
What service is that?
You could reverse a Wilford injustice.
That hope is in short supply in Third.
I've been wondering for a long time
what exactly it is you do up here
in the Night Car.
We offer epiphanies, darling.
Let him go see for himself.
I can't let him out of my sight.
If you want this to be different than Nikki,
he needs to understand what she did.
You can have 20 minutes.
I'll be waiting right here.
What is it about this case you couldn't
tell me in front of a Brakeman?
Patience, Mr. Layton.
You wanted to know what we do here.
You gonna give me the good stuff?
The Night Car's never actually
been a brothel, Andre.
When the world ended,
most people needed something else.
To grieve, to connect
with everything we've lost.
I've developed the Night Car Experience
so we could heal,
individually and collectively.
You a therapist?
Relax, Andre. Clear your mind.
Remember how we used to meditate
in the Tail?
- Yeah, I gave that up when you left.
- You're in good hands.
I'm sure we'll meet again soon.
Close your eyes.
Do you remember the water, Andre?
I remember.
Falling.
Free-flowing.
An element still awake.
Hear the wind.
Earth is still alive.
The birds.
The leaves.
Remember the trees.
The grass,
the sun.
I can feel it.
Where are you?
I'm home.
I see you.
Excuse me, ma'am?
- Yes?
- Yeah, I'm gonna need to see some identification.
Oh, I...
Oh, whoa.
No reason to be nervous.
- Don't let the badge intimidate you.
- Oh, don't worry.
It doesn't.
Mm.
I missed you.
Where are you?
I'm hungry.
- I'm starving.
- I got you.
Ooh.
- Doughnuts!
- Mm-hm.
Old-school. Weber's.
Your favorite.
- I love you, Andre.
- Mm.
What?
Zarah Ferami...
...you wanna do this thing?
Get married? You know, make it real?
- We are real.
- I know, yes, but realer.
Say the words...
Hold, cherish, sickness,
health, all that shit.
I'm not worried about us, Andre.
- I'm worried about the world.
- I got you, Zarah.
- In good times and bad.
- I know, Andre.
I do.
I just wanted to hold you forever.
To be clear,
this is not how it usually goes.
What'd you want to tell me?
Wilford's people aren't telling you
everything about Sean.
I think he was a snitch, because he was lucky.
Like, he got perks.
- What kind of perks?
- We won the Baby Lottery.
That kind of luck usually means
you have a friend uptrain.
I was gonna do it.
I was gonna have a baby with Sean.
- Did you love him?
- It's Snowpiercer, Andre.
Look, I'm not gonna let them pin
this murder on you, Zarah,
but while I'm up here,
I have a responsibility to the Tail.
Would it be so terrible
if you stayed up here?
With me?
Time's up.
Uh-huh.
Not what my Night Car trip looked like.
Unfortunately.
You were supposed
to be getting context on Nikki.
That's called taking a mile.
Sometimes detective work
requires a personal touch.
Just to be clear,
I've never done an autopsy before.
But I'm ex-Navy Medical Corps,
so I do know how to look for trauma and...
Oh, and diagnose PTSD.
I guess we've all got that now, don't we?
I formed out of Afghanistan for a one-year gig
on Wilford's Dreamliner as a medic.
Who knew the world would freeze
and the job would last forever?
This lividity here, that's pooled blood.
Means he lay facedown for a while postmortem.
They moved him later.
What else did you see yesterday
and not share?
You tell me.
- Okay. Multiple ligature marks.
- Yeah.
Choked in and out. They wanted
to drag out chopping his dick off.
Stumps look sawn off.
Looks like this way, down.
Hacksaw maybe?
So the limbs were removed
after he was faceup.
Oh, looks like with a different tool.
Machete?
Cleaver?
You guys really don't go there?
What?
Okay, who has the tools for this?
Those noodles you had earlier,
there were meat scraps in them, from where?
The butchers.
- You're not saying this is cannibalism.
- No.
We don't do that up here. We all know
the rumors about the Tail, but we...
Oh, those aren't rumors.
First couple of years, there were Kill Cults.
One gang in particular,
they would kill anyone, eat anyone.
Had no choice.
The rest of us, we ambushed their leader,
each of us ate a piece of his heart
so that no one could say they were innocent.
Anyway, your lunch was good?
Hold on.
- What do you want?
- Open up, please.
- We need to look in your freezer.
- It's a restricted area.
- Brakeman's business.
- I don't give a shit. It's a restricted area.
If you want in, get the Notary.
Nice knife.
Bet you could cut my leg off with that.
We're butchering today.
- Come back with the Notary.
- Come on.
I assume it's due
to how long she was under.
I agree, but pinpointing the complex
matrix of titration, duration, isolation.
- It's gonna take...
- More research, yeah.
Or subjects. It's the catch-22...
This is bad.
She may have suffered
permanent neurological damage.
We can't justify...
I've got a seismic alarm. How bad is it?
Mierda. Mierda.
The whole slope is coming down.
Oh, shit.
It's a Class Three.
We're not gonna get through the debris.
Hold on.
Brace!
Brace for impact.
We got a breach. Ag-Sec, Cattle Car.
We have a breach. Ag-Sec, Cattle Car.
Javi, take over.
Got it.
You okay?
Keep moving back.
Let us back in there.
We gotta search the freezer.
No, it's an emergency. Out of the way.
Out of the way!
- Jackboot!
- Breachman.
All right, two minutes.
Close the door.
Check this out.
Oh, I got it.
- Hey, hey! Relax.
- Oh, yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Here's the beef.
How about this one, huh?
Seven years she work hospitality
for Mr. Wilford,
and now she comes downtrain
to be engineer.
Wilford asked her
to check it personally.
Okay.
Breachman Bojan Boscovic, at his service.
It's an extinction event.
Sorry.
Window job first.
We need to know if it's structurally sound.
I've been given the okay
to reduce speed 10 percent.
No, no. That is too fast for mountain work.
You give me 25.
Battery banks. We don't have
the terrain ahead to make it up.
I can probably get you 12.
Mm.
No Jacuzzis in First.
Okay.
So we're on rolling blackouts,
starting with the Tail.
What's 20 plus five
for our little ones in the group?
Twenty-five?
You got to give everyone a chance.
You got 26.
Yep.
- Freaking hell.
- Come on.
Hurry up.
They'll send more Jacks for this blackout.
Someone's coming.
Hang on, hang on.
The medicine.
But no painkillers, just Kronole.
I'm not giving that crap to my mom.
Okay, but it kills the pain.
Of everything.
Patterson, how?
Here you go. Open up. Open up.
Good girl.
Okay, Suzanne. There.
Let's stop now.
We can't ration any more power to Ag-Sec
unless we start canceling crops.
We're not breaking rotation.
Water won't flow for a couple days at least,
not until the crack in the hull is sealed.
Then we only have what's in the reservoir
for Third, Ag-Sec and Tail.
We ration the people, not the crops.
Third and Second will get 15 minutes
of running water a day,
and the Tail will have to survive
on what they've hoarded.
Is this what the start of a resource crash
feels like? Starving the train from the Tail up?
It's not just the beef. It's manure for fertilizer.
It's bovine cultures. We use their methane.
I know. It's bad.
But how bad stays between us.
In the meantime, we press ahead
with selecting the new apprentices,
and we bolster faith in Wilford
to get them through.
Despite your violence yesterday,
and the grave hand of fate
hanging over our heads this very second,
Mr. Wilford believes
that children deserve an education
in skilled or unskilled labor,
and so we are proceeding
with apprenticeship selection.
The names are as follows.
Mikala Mwanza.
Mia Kaisheck.
And the boy they call Miles and Miles.
Should your families choose
to accept his invitation,
you have one hour to get ready
for your new lives uptrain.
Two legs and one arm.
- Left arm.
- Can you hang up?
What?
- No, all the butchers are dead, Roche.
- Hey, look, the butcher didn't kill Sean.
- Think it through for a second.
- Okay.
If you're gonna retail him for meat,
then why the torture?
Okay. Uh...
Whoever did it got off on castrating him.
But the arms and legs were the exact opposite.
No emotion at all.
So the butchers come second.
He puts arms and legs
in my fricking noodles.
Tailie.
- Easy.
- Back off, douche.
Tail-sucker.
- There is no use getting us both shit-kicked.
- What do you care?
Blame the butchers
and claim your Third Class cabin.
First off, I don't want Third Class.
I wanna go back to the Tail.
And second...
Guess I'm still a cop, after all.
I was assigned to the first murder too.
They had Nikki guilty out of the gate.
Fast tribunal.
Took all of three hours.
Nothing I could've done for her.
You still care about getting the right guy?
I finally got into the freezer
and recovered your limbs.
- Pretty good day.
- Thanks.
She's good at this part, by the way,
patting down the boys on the corner.
Good night, detective.
Keep it moving.
Eyes down until you're back in the Tail.
Eyes down.
Keep moving.
Come and get me, asshole!
Down! Get down!
- Get down!
- Hey, get off! Get off! Hey!
Layton!
Get on the ground!
Do you remember your mom, Miles?
I...
I remember...
She smelled good.
That's all?
I only remember the train.
You're my Tail mom.
Miles and Miles.
Miles and Miles and Miles,
Miles, Miles, Miles.
You were so little when we started.
I'm not anymore.
Well, then, you better decide
for yourself, don't you?
Layton says we need our people uptrain.
He's right.
We need every department,
friends high and low.
You see? You are a good listener.
Miles...
I swear to you,
I will not stop fighting from the back.
But you're going uptrain.
- And that means we might never see...
- Yes, we will.
After the revolution, like Layton said.
All right?
Love you.
What do you see when you look at this train?
I see a fortress to class.
Is that all?
Well, I see 3000 souls surviving
on a planet that's determined
to freeze all life in place.
We're still in motion, alive and kicking,
and it's not thanks to chance
or fate or God.
It is thanks to order,
meticulously maintained by Mr. Wilford.
A balance of need and greed and speed,
and you Tailies, who seem to have forgotten
that it is 117 degrees below zero
outside of this metal tube,
and Mr. Wilford is awake 21 hours a day
just to keep the goddamn heat on!
Guess that's why it needs informants
like Sean Wise.
Wise was a Wilford rat.
He got paid in perks
like the rigged Baby Lottery.
Why else would you care so much
about a Thirdie's murder?
So, what you really wanna know is,
when he was tortured,
what Wilford secrets did he spill?
Y'all got killers and cannibals
and God knows what else up here.
So don't you lecture me about balance.
My people found ours years ago.
Okay. Very perceptive.
No wonder Mr. Wilford
wants you as Train Detective.
But that's the only reason
you're still here now.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org