Subtitles by explosiveskull
Who are the real-world Illuminati ?
Find out @ saveanilluminati.com
There he is.
Is this your first job?
- My first job?
- Hm.
I've never killed a man
if that's what you mean.
It's not as hard
as you might think.
- Depends on the man.
- Which man?
The target, or the man
doing the killing?
Both.
Tell me, friend, what did you
do before the war?
I was a baseball player.
You know baseball?
Oh, baseball.
Like Joe DiMaggio.
Did he ever kill anyone?
Not that I know of.
Good luck, my friend.
You'll be fine.
Just do it before
the Gestapo figures it out.
I'll try.
Two out top of the third,
man on first.
Moe Berg still in the catcher.
Fifteen years in the league
and still standing.
How long can this guy go on?
Runner takes his lead.
Moe calls the sign.
Okay, now here's the pitch.
The runner goes.
Berg throws down to second.
Got him.
Hey, don't shake me off.
I don't wanna a change-up
when somebody's stealing.
I barely got him.
How'd you know
where he was goin'?
I just knew.
How you holding up?
What do you mean?
Sooner or later
I'm gonna need your spot
on the roster, Moe.
- Make it later.
- It is later.
I've been asking
for two seasons
to hang up the cleats
and coach.
I like it out there.
You hardly play.
All the more reason
to hang on.
Look, I didn't want to
stop playin' either.
So, what do you say?
Finish out the season,
then coach?
I could go to Detroit.
Mickey'd let me play.
Mickey's an idiot.
So are you,
for letting me play.
You get a call
about the Japan thing?
Yeah.
- You goin'?
- Absolutely.
- Who else is going?
- Uh, we got Murderers' Row.
We got Ruth, Gehrig, Averill,
Gehringer, Gomez.
Am I the only bum?
They like
the Professor Berg thing.
They also like
that you speak Japanese.
Who said I speak Japanese?
Kieran, in one of his columns.
- Interesting.
- Say..
Barker House? Steaks?
No, thanks.
Okay, mystery man.
What you staring at, rookie?
What's the story with Berg?
- What do you mean?
- Uh, he seems strange.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I don't know.
He just seems odd.
Mind you own business, Dalton.
Does he, does he bat lefty?
How the hell should I know?
Why should I care?
It's just I don't feel like
showing my dick to a queer.
Well, don't show it
to him, then.
Somebody ought to find out.
You're Moe Berg, aren't you?
Who?
Moe Berg,
the baseball player.
Oh, no. You know,
but I must look like him.
Everybody says
I look like him.
You're kidding.
No, I ain't him.
But I sure as hell
must look like him.
Ha!
Where am I dropping you?
A couple more blocks.
I'll walk from there.
It's fine.
Suit yourself..
...Mr. Berg.
Actually, you know what, stop.
Here. That's good.
I wouldn't have
been able to tell.
Really?
Well, I was on my third
martini by that point, so...
You flatter me.
So, what did you think
of the place, honey?
Mr. Dalton,
you live around here?
Man, fuck you!
I didn't catch your answer.
Do you live around here?
- Do you live around here?
- No! No.
Do you know what the word
"Hypothetical" means?
No? It means, let's suppose.
Let's suppose there was
a baseball player
a rookie, who intruded on the
privacy of another ballplayer
who was reaching
the twilight of his career
and really had nothing
to lose at this point.
Are you following so far?
You fucking faggot!
You think you know everything,
don't you?
I don't know anything,
alright?
I..
Now, you'll be pleased
to know Cronin..
Cronin is considering
putting you in the lineup.
Show some improvement
and you got a shot.
Good luck.
Don't stop.
That's beautiful.
You're a liar.
And you're late.
I had some people to see.
Play.
Where did that come from?
The way you looked at me
when I came in.
Any normal man would've
done the same thing.
I didn't look at you.
I had my back turned.
And the reason
that I love you
is that you're the farthest
thing from a normal man
that anyone would
ever think of.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's time for..
The Information Game!
Yes, the show
where the elite meet
to mete out the meat
of their minds.
Tonight, our special guest
is Moe Berg
catcher for the Boston
Red Sox, and for those of you
who actually read
John Kieran's articles
will know him
as Professor Berg
top graduate
from Princeton University
also holding advanced degrees
from Columbia University
and the Sorbonne University
in Paris, France.
Welcome, Professor Berg.
Thank you.
Moe will do.
- Happy to be here.
- Well, Moe it is.
And, Moe, let's play ball.
Our first question is for you.
- Excellent.
- Thank you.
Very well done.
And I'll see you next week.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Bye-bye.
Trick question? Me?
The Canary Islands
aren't named for a canary.
The name is derived
from the Latin word canis
which means dog.
The islands were named
for the wild dogs
that are found there.
Right you are.
Well, so far, Moe Berg
is batting a thousand!
So, Moe, tell us a little bit
about yourself.
Is there a Mrs. Berg?
Ah, yes, she's married
to my father.
I meant is there
a Mrs. Berg in your life?
Does this count for points?
Wow, you sure wriggled
your way out of that one.
Moe Berg, the walking enigma.
That is..
Well, that's the case
with old Whitby.
- Very similar.
- Was it always?
Always. Because of that,
people...
How do you know
all of these things?
Well, it's common knowledge.
Well..
Oh, I'm going to Japan.
An exhibition tour
after the season.
Oh, Moe, I have always
wanted to see Japan.
I'll take some pictures.
Or you could take me, and I'll
take the pictures myself.
- Oh, Estella, come on.
- I'd really like to go, Moe.
It's just a series
of exhibition games.
And I'm sure the other players
are taking their wives.
You're not my wife.
Mm.
I didn't mean
anything by that.
I was simply stating it
as a fact.
It was more than that, Moe.
It wasn't more than anything.
- Estella.
- What?
Why do you not want
to take me to Japan, Morris?
I would just rather go alone.
Well, that wasn't so hard,
was it?
Tokyo is host of Babe Ruth
and his barnstorming
American baseball team
on their goodwill
exhibition tour of Japan.
Jesus Christ.
He know their languages.
That makes 12.
Welcome to Japan, Mr. Berg.
I'm sure you're going
to enjoy it here.
My name is Isao Kawabata.
It's such a pleasure
to meet you.
The pleasure is mutual.
Move it, move it!
Don't they know
he only batted 235?
Right.
- Oh!
Please, tell me
all about baseball.
It looked like
such as interesting game.
You don't know anything?
Nothing.
Well, baseball's a game
where people fail
a lot more often
than they succeed.
Sounds very much like life.
Yes, it does.
So, what do you do?
I am a professor of history.
Now that sounds interesting.
So why would a professor
who doesn't know anything
about baseball be at a game?
Maybe you don't fully
understand, Mr. Berg.
This visit is very important.
It goes beyond sport.
Our cultures are very different,
and growing further apart.
If we don't stop to learn
about one another, then..
Then what?
There'll be no more games.
You're happy here?
I am.
Why?
When I was growing up
my first baseball team
was a church team.
But I'm a Jew.
Now, I was never
a practicing Jew
but I was different
than the other boys.
I never even told them
my real name.
I tried to blend in.
I wanted to hide.
And it worked.
Do you like to hide, Mr. Berg?
I do.
I don't fit.
Even now, I have no real home,
I have no wife.
Do you have a wife, Isao?
I do.
And six children.
She's very fertile.
I like to hide too.
Now, can I ask you
an important question?
Yes.
You're a professor of history.
Will there be a war
between our two countries?
Yes.
It has been progressing
step-by-step.
It is quite inevitable.
Everything will change.
And we'll all play our part.
I also think
after this visit..
...we will never
see each other again.
I hope you're wrong.
As do I.
The attack yesterday
on the Hawaiian Islands
has caused severe damage
to American naval
and military forces.
I regret to tell you
that very many American lives
have been lost.
Hello, Jerry.
Moe, nice to see you.
Been a long time.
I was hoping you'd be here.
Oh, yeah? Why?
I understand you're working
in Washington.
Where'd you hear that?
One of the guys.
I can't remember who.
- State Department?
- Uh, yeah, sort of.
How'd you come to get the job?
There's room for people
with languages.
That's what I figured.
- How are your knees?
- What do you mean?
I figure a professional
ballplayer's getting 4F.
Bad hinges.
My knees are as passable
as my Italian.
Have you heard
of Bill Donovan?
Yeah, sure. Yale, football.
Medal of Honor, 1918.
He's my boss.
We're setting up a small adjunct
to the State Department.
Here's the number.
- Give this man a call.
- Thanks.
First time I've seen you
at one of these things.
Well, first time
I've come to one.
Gentlemen, may I have
your attention please?
We are at war.
In light of what lies
before us
the challenges, the sacrifices
the losses.
I ask you,
gentlemen of Princeton
to join us in the singing of the
"Battle Hymn Of The Republic."
♪ Mine eyes have seen the glory
of the coming of the Lord.. ♪
Sorry for the song choice.
What?
♪ Where the grapes
of wrath are stored ♪
♪ He hath loosed.. ♪
At least it's not
"Onward, Christian Soldiers."
♪ Terrible swift sword.. ♪
That would have been fine too.
♪ Marching on ♪
♪ Glory glory hallelujah ♪
♪ Glory glory ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ Glory glory hallelujah ♪
♪ His truth is marching on ♪
♪ I have seen Him
in the watch-fires ♪
♪ Of a hundred
circling camps ♪
♪ They have builded Him
an altar ♪
♪ In the evening
dews and damps ♪
♪ I can read
his righteous sentence ♪
♪ By the dim
and flaring lamps ♪
♪ His day is marching on ♪♪
Thank you, gentlemen.
Interesting film
you brought back, Mr. Berg.
What made you make it?
I happened to be in Japan.
A lot of people
happen to be in Japan.
Not all of them go to the top
of a building in Tokyo
and make home movies of the
harbor and naval shipyards.
I had the opportunity.
It seemed the sensible
thing to do.
How did you know then that
we would be at war with Japan?
"The Journal
Of Oriental Society"
was filled with articles
about going to war with Japan.
You read the "JOS?"
Ah, uh, well, that wasn't
apparent from what I just said?
Yes, yes, I suppose it was.
But no one in the government
or the army
asked you
to make the film?
No.
You did it
as a private citizen?
Yes.
You're an unusual man,
Mr. Berg.
Yes, so I'm told.
Have a seat.
Not married, no children.
Odd for a man your age, no?
Never occurred to me.
May I ask you
a very personal question?
You may.
Are you queer?
I'm good at keeping secrets.
You're also good
at some other things.
You speak
seven languages fluently
another three or four
to a lesser degree.
In addition,
you're an athlete,
which means you're more than up
to the physical requirements
of the job.
What job?
Any job we might care
to give you
in the event that we
bring you into the fold.
Moe, Jerry Fredericks
speaks very highly of you.
We're looking for people
who can keep secrets
but not from us.
We're fighting a war here.
It's very serious business.
Now, personally,
I don't care who a man fucks
as long as he can help us
win this war.
If it comes down to it
I'm willing to die
for my country.
They say that patriotism
is the last refuge
of a scoundrel.
It isn't they.
It's Samuel Johnson.
And it's not the last,
it's the first.
Welcome to the OSS, Mr. Berg.
There were many new developments
today at home and abroad.
The headlines, Germans claim
victory in the Crimea.
The Russians report gains
around Moscow and Leningrad.
President Roosevelt signs
the Neutrality Law.
And then captive coal mine
strike ties up production.
And Congress prepares
anti-strike legislation.
And in France,
the Germans advanced
along the Saint-Michel salient
taking in the town
of Saint Ramelle and Toulon.
On the southern front
allied advances
continued in Sicily.
Great report on
the Serbian border unit.
Thank you.
I'm going crazy.
I am not made
for desk work, alright?
You got to get me
out onto the field.
- You're useful here.
- Well, I hate it, alright?
I'm used to being
on a ball field all day.
If I stay cooped up in here,
I'm going to kill somebody.
Maybe myself.
Oh!
- Oh!
Mr. Berg!
Yeah?
Someone chasing you?
I don't know.
Well, it's good
that you're here.
Come with me.
Where are we going?
Be careful
what you wish for, Berg.
Because you just might get it?
Because it could get you
killed.
Gentlemen.
Moe Berg. Bob Furman.
Hi, nice to meet you.
This is Professor
Sam Goudsmit.
If you would.
Bob, Moe, Sam.
We have something for you.
Since this war began..
...we've been engaged
in a massive research
and development program,
called the Manhattan Project.
The purpose of which
is the creation
of a fission bomb.
Now, if initial calculations
are correct
one bomb would be enough
to wipe out an entire city.
The war could be decided
in a day.
We have reason to believe
the Germans are also working
on such a bomb.
Sam.
The scientist leading
the atomic fission program
is Werner Heisenberg.
So, we must get to him
and find out how close
the Germans are to a bomb.
Now, he has left Berlin.
And we don't know where
he is or what he is doing.
But, uh, he has remained
in contact
with an Italian physicist
with whom I worked,
uh, Eduardo Amaldi.
So we'd start in Italy,
the three of us.
Sam for the physics,
me, military
and you, OSS.
- Where in Italy?
- Rome.
Our fifth army is
moving north.
They should take the city
in a week or two.
We'll go in, find the
physicist and interrogate him.
Uh, interview him, please.
Amaldi is my friend.
Uh, if the Italian physicist
has any value
won't the Germans take him when
they pull out, or kill him?
Well, that's why we'd actually
go in with the Fifth Army
to prevent that from
happening.
It's not desk work.
No, it's not.
Could be fun.
Ah, an athlete's
uncomplicated hubris.
I do not speak of fun,
Mr. Berg.
Figure of speech.
If the enemy intercepts
your communication
they can easily discern
what you have written there
simply by holding
the paper over a flame
or treating it
with a reactive chemical
such as sodium carbonate.
The German MP 40.
Very effective weapon
for close combat.
Never hold the gun
by the clip when firing
as that can cause
the gun to jam.
Cameras used by both
civilians and military
depending on the situations..
♪ Don't wake too soon ♪
♪ Don't look too long ♪
♪ Don't peer
beyond the moonlight ♪
♪ Cling to me sing to me.. ♪♪
How's work?
It's just work.
And when do you go back to DC?
I, uh, I'm not going to DC.
Not for a while.
Well, how long do I have you?
Hm?
Till tomorrow.
- Why am I not surprised?
- I'm sorry, Stell.
I'm..
...going overseas.
You brought me here
to say goodbye?
- I'll be back.
- Who knows?
Y... you know that I love you.
Simple yes or no.
D... do you know
that I love you?
I really wanted us
to be perfect.
That's all.
We are.
Liar.
Difficult?
- May I?
- Hey. Come in.
Tell me about Heisenberg.
Well, he's a somewhat
complicated man.
Yeah, just before
the war started
uh, we were together
at the conference
at the University of Michigan.
And Furman and I begged him
not to go back to Germany.
- But he went.
- Yeah.
But to save German science
from the Nazis.
And now he's the head
of the atomic bomb program.
Could he build a bomb?
Could he or would he?
Both.
The could of it would require
enormous physical
and financial resources
perhaps more than Germany
has at its disposal.
But with the resources,
he could do it.
Yes.
And the would of it?
I don't know.
So you were friends?
You knew him well?
Yeah.
Do you still
consider him a friend?
You are a Jew, yeah, Mr. Berg?
Jewish.
A... after the Nazis
occupied Holland
my parents were taken
to Auschwitz.
Now, I contacted Heisenberg
and I asked him
I... begged him
to do what he could.
And we haven't spoken since.
I don't know
if they're dead or alive.
Thanks.
I'm not comfortable with this.
We'll be alright.
What if there are Germans
waiting for us?
Then we'll probably
get shot and killed.
This has all the
variables of a disaster.
Sam, stop your whining.
- Ah-ha.
- Here we are.
Welcome to Italy, sir.
Be careful!
You doing alright?
- You don't look so great.
- Nah..
Quite well, thank you.
Who the hell are you?
- What's up there?
- Goddamn Germans.
Left the rearguard division.
Paying for every inch.
What's the safest way
to Piazza Leone?
Why don't you drive
south 30 miles
find yourself a nice hotel,
wait a week?
We can't wait.
Alright, fine. Your call.
Look, stay on the Via Appia
as long as you can.
Stash your Jeep
when it gets too messy.
But as of this morning
that whole area
was crawling with Krauts.
- And good luck.
- Thanks.
Alright, let them through.
- Yes, sir.
Follow me and stay down.
Duck.
There's still
Krauts everywhere.
Ready? Move out.
Yeah, come on.
So you're the guys
they told us about.
You guys are crazy.
Yeah.
Alright, let's move out.
Go, go, go.
Look at me. We'll be alright.
Alright?
Get down!
Get ready to run
to that wall.
Wait till I call.
Okay, go!
Get down! Get down!
- Grenade!
- Go, go, go!
- Get down!
- Aah!
Go, go, go, go!
Uh, come on.
Panzer! Panzer!
- Move out!
- Get up! Move!
- Let's go.
- Whoo!
Move! Move! Move!
- Aah!
- Move out!
Roll, roll, roll!
No, uh.. Uh, that's Amaldi's.
Upper floor.
Behind me.
We got to go.
- Go, go.
- Yeah?
- Wait, get back.
- Yeah!
Let's go.
Go! Go!
Shit.
Gracias.
Halt!
You okay?
You're good, come on.
Hold position!
It looks like we've got
the city up past the Vatican.
The Germans have pulled back
their rearguard.
- Alright, alright.
- Thank you.
You'll be fine, buddy.
They don't have it,
they're still building
carbon molding frames
instead of shaped housings.
He's writing about heavy water
absorption rates.
This letter,
he asks Amaldi for help
with casement tolerances.
Here, he says
he's doing
large-structure analysis.
Everything points to a reactor
instead of a bomb.
How do we know
these documents aren't decoys?
Plants?
Uh, they're letters.
Personal letters.
These men are friends.
The physics is, uh,
intertwined with the intimacy.
Hmm, we have to be sure.
Then have the British review it.
They are physicists.
They will confirm what I say.
Alright.
We'll have
the Brits weigh in.
Donovan will be here soon.
I'm kicking this upstairs.
- Mr. Berg.
- Hello, sir.
- How's it been going?
- Going well. Yes, sir.
And the industrial complex
at Hechingen
has only a containment vessel
and a cycle stack
both signs of a nascent
reactor facility.
And the uranium
separation facility?
Consensus in London is
that's just a carbon separator
of some sort.
An attempt at shale
extraction.
- Coal?
- Apparently so.
I concur.
So, where does this leave us?
London is certain.
No German bomb.
Degree of certainty?
There's no such thing
as a degree of certainty.
I mean, something is
either certain or it is not.
Hmm.
Thank you, gentlemen.
- Good day, sir.
- Good day.
So, what are the alternatives?
Bombing Hechingen
is unlikely to be effective.
If they are developing a bomb
the work, the materials
will be spread out
at facilities
and other factories.
So our British allies
tell us 100% no German bomb.
My people tell me
a 20% possibility.
More likely ten or
five percent.
- Perhaps less.
- But not zero.
It's Probability 101.
You multiply the likelihood of
the event by the consequence.
Five percent chance you're
going to stub your toe in the
dark
you take the chance,
walk to the bathroom
without turning on the lights
and waking your wife.
A five percent chance of losingthe
war to a weapon like this
you do what has to be done.
Which is?
We kill Heisenberg.
What if he's on our side?
Why is it that the Germans
haven't developed a bomb?
Heisenberg has a team of
at least
a dozen capable physicists.
What have they been doing?
What are you saying?
He's dragging his feet?
Intentionally slowing
the program?
I do not think
that Werner Heisenberg
would want to be remembered
as a traitor.
The man who lost the war
for Germany?
We are not absolutely
sure of that
nor do we have
any actual evidence
that he's secretly
working for us.
There are millions of lives
at stake.
I'm sorry.
Werner Heisenberg..
Pioneer in the study
of subatomic particles.
Winner of the 1932
Nobel Prize in physics
for the creation
of quantum mechanics.
Equation 56 is known
as Heisenberg's principle
of uncertainty.
The principle shows
that one can never observe
both the position
and velocity of a particle
at the same time.
One cannot be certain
where something is
and where it is going.
And thus, Heisenberg proves
that no one knows anything.
We live in eternal
uncertainty.
A man after my own heart.
You like libraries.
Why?
Here is a belongingness
I find in few other places.
On a ball field?
There too.
That's gone now.
I have to ask you
a question
and I need a real answer.
If it comes down to it
are you going to be able
to kill him?
Yes.
There you go.
You wanna play?
Huh, good.
You, uh, got a choice?
- Catcher?
- It's all yours.
Oh, shit.
- The guy's a pro.
- Yeah.
I know who that is.
That's Moe Berg.
Home plate, home plate!
- Yes!
- Alright.
Uh-oh. Move back, move back.
Don't worry,
245 lifetime.
Yeah, yeah, just don't hit it
down my throat, okay?
Oh!
That's a hit!
Jesus Christ!
Moe Berg, thanks.
Oh, no. Don't thank me.
Thank you.
Hey, do you mind,
uh, signing the ball?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks a lot, Moe.
You know, I saw you
a dozen times at Fenway.
- You were great.
- Me? Great? When?
Uh, well, I saw you.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Zurich. It's a short train
journey from Hechingen.
A break from the grim
atmosphere of Germany.
He will be tempted.
And I know someone in Zurich.
Paul Scherrer.
He and Heisenberg
are good friends.
- They play chess by mail.
- He's anti-Nazi.
Exactly, but he and Heisenberg
are still close.
And he gonna help us
lure Heisenberg to Zurich?
Such a word, "Lure."
Heisenberg has been there
twice since the war started.
We simply have Scherrer invite
him to deliver a lecture.
Can Scherrer be persuaded
to work with us?
Yes. Scherrer will arrange it.
And so the madness
becomes real.
We have to kill
Werner Heisenberg
and I am to be a part of it.
No one wants
to kill Heisenberg.
Yeah? Then kidnap him.
Send in spies to Germany
and kidnap him.
You've read too many
spy novels.
I've never read a spy novel.
It's not that easy
to kidnap somebody.
Ah.
Yeah,
you mean killing is easier.
My God.
You'll have about 30 miles
on foot to the Swiss border.
I'd hold on to your gun.
I have some reservations
about your guides.
Reservations?
Like what?
Reservations like
they might kill you.
You might have cared
to add that to the report.
There's your guides.
Wish me luck.
I don't wanna hear you
depending on luck.
Figure of speech.
Thank you, Sam.
Thank you, Moe.
Now we rest.
Riposo.
No.
- Hi, are you okay?
- Yeah.
Who came up
with that sheep nonsense?
- I don't know.
- I felt like an idiot.
So did I.
Switzerland?
Yes.
Let's go.
That's Heisenberg.
It's good to see you..
And that's Professor Scherrer.
Scherrer looks way to nervous.
I guess this isn't his thing.
What?
Treachery.
- Professor Scherrer.
- Mr. Aziz, please come in.
Thank you.
My name's Berg.
Oh, so who is Mr. Aziz?
A cover name.
I prefer you and I
tell each other the truth.
I'm Morris Berg.
Oh.
Sam Goudsmit
sends his regards.
Ah, well.
I was hoping
he would come here personally.
Please, please sit down.
Well, he, uh..
He sent you something.
Heavy water.
Nordstemmen impurity.
Oh, thank you so much.
No, you don't know
how much I appreciate this.
Thank you so much.
You don't worry
I give this to the Germans?
We trust you, professor.
I may be mistaken, but..
I don't think
Professor Heisenberg
will reveal anything
in his lecture.
Hmm.
Well, then perhaps I could
speak with him privately.
Are you hoping he'll defect?
Yes, I am.
Good luck.
Excuse me one moment.
Got to listen carefully.
There may be one moment
that tells you
whether the Germans have a
chance at a fission bomb or not.
One moment, and you'll learn
all you need to know.
You understand me, catcher?
I understand you.
In that moment,
without hesitation
you will shoot Heisenberg
dead on the spot.
Did he accept
your dinner invitation?
I prevailed upon our
friendship. He'll be there.
Good.
What if he doesn't tell you
what you want to know?
I'll do my best
to be persuasive.
There's always a possibility
that you will learn nothing.
But at least
we will have tried.
Mr. Berg..
Is there something
you're not telling me?
No.
Do you plan to kill
Professor Heisenberg?
I have no intention
whatsoever.
One last thing.
Heisenberg will have undercover
Gestapo agents watching him
and you can't allow yourself
to be captured.
I don't know what God
you believe in, Berg, if any.
But I'll be asking mine
to keep an eye on you.
Your call is being
connected, sir.
Let me know
if there's a problem.
Hello?
Hi, Estella.
Morris?
Are you alright?
I am.
Where are you?
Uh, I can't say.
And I don't have much time.
But I wanted to call and..
I wanted to hear your voice.
I'm here, Moe.
I have to go.
I love you.
Thank you.
Who is that, Paul?
I saw him at the lecture.
What's he doing here?
Yeah,
he's a good friend of mine.
I think you'll find him
very engaging.
You know he carries a gun.
Yeah.
No need to worry.
Let's eat.
I just don't understand how you
could have stayed in Germany.
Oh, please, no politics.
No war.
There is a war,
whether you like it or not.
What are you suggesting?
I like the war?
I am suggesting that unlike
many of your colleagues
you elected to stay
in Nazi Germany.
I elected to stay in Germany,
which happens to be Nazi.
Do I hear politics
from that end of the table?
One hears what one
wishes to hear.
Please, we are all friends.
Let's talk about old times,
or better times to come.
Yes, please.
Aziz?
Aziz.
I understand we have a
bad weather tomorrow.
Rain.
There is no avoiding
political matters.
We can try.
Is that what you've been doing
as the head of
the Kaiser Wilhelm Institute
and the Heereswaffenamt?
I beg of you, we are completely
separate from politics.
Oh, I forgot.
The citizens
of the world, yes?
Once, and hopefully again
someday.
Tell that to the Poles,
and the Danes
the Belgians, the Jews.
Please,
I'm not a military man.
We don't know
what sort of man you are.
Yes, we do.
He's the kind of man
who is helping the Nazis
fight their war.
Building Hitler's super
weapon.
See?
He doesn't even deny it.
I feel the war
will be over soon.
Maybe.
- And Germany will lose.
- Whatever you say.
You disgust me.
Please, please, please.
Professor Heisenberg
is my guest.
Well, then the two of you can
lament Germany's loss together.
Ugh!
Please forgive me.
Werner, please stay.
I really must go.
I've endured enough of this.
Do I have a choice?
Yes, of course.
Should I run, perhaps?
I wouldn't recommend it.
We must finish our game.
I believe it's your move,
professor.
- Knight takes rook.
- Bishop takes bishop.
Pawn takes knight.
And so,
in three exchanges
only my king will survive.
It seems to me
this game is nearly over.
I cannot mount an attack
with my king.
So it is over.
Who are you?
A student.
A student? Really?
A student of what?
Of you.
I see.
Now, how are we supposed to
ascertain the truth here
Mr. Berg?
Will Germany lose the war?
Is this really a secret?
I'll ask him myself.
I think you mean,
am I a traitor?
Is that what you wish to know?
And if I think he's lying..
...then I'll kill him.
Like me..
...you are free to choose.
Your move.
Goodnight,
Professor Heisenberg.
What did you say
your name was?
I didn't.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6eqep
Help other users to choose the best subtitles