Police are looking for Robert Zeuthen's
9 year old daughter Emilie
If the kidnapper wants justice
for Louise Hjelby, we need to hurry.
You don't know if it was him.
-Go there.
Your daughter deserves that her killer is
brought to justice, whoever it is.
Emilie is located in an air-tight container
with a limited amount of oxygen.
What does Maja think? She doesn't think that...
-We know that you are innocent.
Ussing's accusations
about the government's
relationship with Zeeland
have been proven false.
We won't celebrate until
Emilie is found safe.
You knew my son, Benjamin?
-He had all of his photos removed from our server.
What kind of photos?
-He had a backup.
You're not wearing your watch in
the photos from the surprise party.
It broke when you killed Louise Hjelby.
I haven't done anything!
-We have to let him go.
Promise me that the murderer will be punished
and I will show you where Emilie is.
The Killing III
Thursday, November 17th 9:57pm
The Norwegian police will escort them to
the spot where we hope to find Emilie.
I will make sure to keep leadership
informed of any developments.
How do we know that the
girl is in Norway?
The kidnapper says that he shipped
Emilie in that direction.
In a container. It was the escape
which he had prepared for himself.
This explains the container list.
Isn't she in a decompression chamber?
-Yes.
Inside the container. He placed Emilie
there so no one could hear her.
Can't we find that container?
Not fast enough.
Hundreds of containers have already been
transported to various cities in Norway .
He didn't write the name down.
Emilie only has enough oxygen for 24 hours.
And you have approved a tour
led by a criminal.
We promised that the murder of his
daughter will be thoroughly investigated.
He changed his mind when we found evidence
that it couldn't have been Zeuthen's assistant.
I don't know why he cooperates. He
certainly doesn't trust you.
Thanks to us, the kidnapper was caught and
he had reason to suspect Reinhardt.
But not for long. I told you
the notebook didn't matter.
The Minister of Justice has
criticized us in a press conference.
His take on Lund is disastrous.
It doesn't matter which party
wins the election tomorrow...
We'll be out of our jobs if
that girl doesn't show up alive.
Why do I have to sit on the car while
Lund and Borch are in Norway?
Patience. Have you gotten
in touch with Zeuthen?
Zealand says he's unreachable.
I can still go, you know.
Why can't you reach him?
Is the baby well?
-Yes, she's so beautiful.
She's 44cm tall, and weighs 7 pounds.
She has all her fingers and toes.
So it's a girl.
-It all went great and Mark was there.
He's so cute when he holds her.
Wanna talk to him?
I can't now, maybe tomorrow when I'm
back. Will you send me a photo of her?
Will do. She just woke up.
I'll talk to you later, okay?
Here's paperwork confirming our commitment
to investigating your daughter's death.
We're looking at all possible vehicles
in the area, especially black ones.
Does Zeuthen know we're travelling?
-Why?
I've informed Emilie's parents and
I'll keep you informed of our investigation.
Now it's your turn to keep up your end
of the bargain and tell us where Emilie is.
We're landing.
Where to? Between Havn and Stavanger?
-Along the coast.
So the container was transported along the coast from Stavanger?
I will lead you to the girl.
-Just tell us where the container is!
Brix here. There is a problem.
Zeuthen's plane has landed in Stavanger.
But we can't get in touch.
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
Welcome to Norway. We're
ready to assist.
Is that our car? We'll take Loke,
so he can show us the way.
What did he say? Where is she?
We will go along the coast.
You should wait here for Emilie ...
I'm coming with you. She had 2 days worth of air, and you've wasted half already.
That was unfortunate.
Now we must focus on this.
You have to get inside.
Zeeland does a lot of business
in this area, we know it well.
We'll stay back and help where we can.
I should be there.
Do whatever the Norwegian
police tells you to do.
Did he say how long you have to drive?
-No, how is Carl?
He wants you to come soon so we could leave.
Give him a kiss. I'll call again soon.
Any news?
I have to go. Make sure we have a
helicopter and doctor waiting in Stavanger.
The kidnapper is in Norway.
The police have all the information they  need.
Thanks.
There's a lot of empty buildings and closed locations.
Because you moved everything overseas to Asia.
Come on, Carl.
We put as much press as we could
on the police to find Emilie.
Come on Carl, you should go to bed.
When all this is over, you
should take care of your family.
Maybe you don't care, but this is about us, not Zeeland.
It's your money and your business.
Do you think Robert is
going to be busy at work
to make more money when
Emilie is back home?
Carl, leave that ship alone, let's go.
Can you confirm that the police
are in Norway to find Emilie?
This is our final televised
debate, but if you're so eager to
know, the Minister of Justice will
be speaking about it tonight.
This isn't the first time the
PM has given us false hope.
He's putting up a smokescreen
in front of the case.
He'll need it if he wants to implement his crisis plan.
The PM can't achieve any of
his promises without Zeeland.
Zeeland has cut funding until Emilie is found.
All of the accusations you've
made have been proven false.
Nobody believes the deputy prosecutor
acted of his own volition.
Can you be more specific?
In a moment -- Rosa Lebech, what can you
draw from Ussing's criticism of Kamper?
We'll leave the dirty
work to everyone else.
That's probably how you get
all the important seats.
We want to support the one person who
is most in the middle politically.
It's as if you want the voters to think
the deal with Zeeland is certain.
We've been crystal clear about our deal with Zeeland.
Zeeland has threatened to
move its operations abroad.
Zeeland will not move abroad,
they're committed to contributing.
Time is up.
If everyone contributes, it will
bring only good things to Denmark.
We have every reason to believe we
will endure this crisis safely.
That was it. I thank you
all very much for coming.
Ussing's accusations are influencing the
voters, we're 2% behind in the polls.
And Norway?
The kidnapper is taking them to a container
with a decompression tank inside.
When will it be over?
-Hopefully soon.
He's cooperating and Zeuthen is
there to take his daughter home.
We can't wait.
Rosa Lebech and the Central Party had its chance.
I suggest we invite the right parties tonight to the ministry.
Did you find anything?
-No.
They're keys to a padlock. Not one
of his friends knows anything.
Well they fit somewhere!
Benjamin gave them to his girlfriend and
told her it had a backup of his pictures.
Can I see?
-We already know what it says.
Karen got money from Reinhard to
finance the campaign. It's nothing.
Still, someone had all pictures deleted.
-That's Sally's explanation.
Their server provider was nearly bankrupt, other customers lost all their files.
Well I want to know what was in there, okay?
And someone knows what that key unlocks.
Yeah well tomorrow is the election, it has
nothing to do with Benjamin's suicide.
I'll figure it out. If it means so much
to  Kristian, we should find out.
Brix says 70 containers were sent
north from Stavanger.
One of them has to be on Loke's list of containers.
He planned it all on that ship?
-We have examined everything.
It won't matter if
he leads us to the girl.
Even if we find the container,
she may be dead already.
She should still be alive.
Suppose we find the container and she's still alive.
Will you let me move in with you?
That much you owe me.
Because of the deposit the other time.
I'm not going to live with anybody.
And you're married. And I ...
You just became a
grandmother, it's time.
You're sitting here whining and all I want
is to move into that little shack of yours.
That's not gonna happen.
I'm with Juncker. We have information
out of cell towers in Jutland.
There were 50 black cars on the road
that day, in addition to those in the booklet.
Germans and Poles and ...
We'll talk to them all.
Verify their alibis.
Are we sure of the date?
-Which date?
The report says Louise dissapeared
on April 21st...
Forget it. The deputy prosecutor
tampered with the date.
We need to look at April 20th.
What's going on over there?
Are you there yet?
Get in touch with the watchmakers.
Louise's dental injuries came from a watch.
Find out if any of the drivers
had any watches and what make.
But it could be any watch maker.
We're at Fossmark, where to now?
Can we stop? I want to smoke.
No stops until we get there.
You need to take a left soon
and then follow the coast.
And then for how long?
-Until the next fjord.
That's four hours away.
There's nothing on the map there.
-No. Wake me when we get there.
This is gonna work out.
My house may be small,
but it's not a barn. Really.
And we can always build.
Why's he taking us thru this wasteland?
-He worked out of Stavanger.
I got a quick brief about the landmarks.
It's a good idea to go on vacation with your family soon.
It'll have to be a lot more than just that.
Perhaps you won't think that way when
you get back from vacation.
I have promised Maja. And I will
speak to Gilsfort once we get home.
You can stay in the business and with the Children's Fund.
What's going on?
What's gonna happen, Robert?
Nothing. Nothing's happening.
How's it going?
-We're driving up the coast.
And Carl?
May I wish him goodnight?
He's fast asleep already. The nanny is
there, while I go back to the office.
I'll power the phone off to save battery.
I'll call if something happens.
Take care of yourself.
You can call me on my cell.
Friday, November 18
10.37 am
day 10
ls election day a celebration for the Prime Minister?
Any election is cause for celebration.
What are the consequences if the girl
is not found? Is she trapped in a tank?
How much further do
they have to go?
Only the kidnapper knows. The parties you
talked to are awaiting further developments.
Why don't I hear anything from Karen?
-Hopefully she's doing well.
Ussing's still there. Let's wait.
-I'm not waiting for Ussing.
Shall I drop it?
You will be allowed to photograph
the Prime Minister.
It's annoying that we vote
at the same place.
It's just a little cozy in here.
A good day to you.
Likewise. Enjoy the day.
It's your last as prime minister.
I'm in the voting booth. I hope
you found out more about the keys.
I'll call later. I still
don't have anything.
Did you go to his friends?
-Yes. I thought I'd try.
He had bought a lock. But he said that
was for the place where he played basketball.
He didn't play basketball.
Have you voted?
-Did you hear anything further?
He's unsure of who to vote for.
Yes, now you can.
-And we don't get a photo?
What are you doing?
You still need to win votes.
Karen has found a place where the key may fit.
Close to where he died.
Postpone all appointments.
What does the kidnapper say?
-It's a green container. No. 67678.
Why can't you find it?
Borch's asking the chief here where we
should be. I'll call you back.
What did he say?
-The container was picked up.
And besides that?
Where's the girl?
If he does that again, we go home.
He won't.
These are the shipments from last night and
this morning, listed by ship and road.
Our container is amongst them.
Where is it?
We have a schedule. It's in your own
best interest to keep it.
He could go to a quieter place, but
this is indeed faster.
Who transported it? Name a name or company, or I'll strike you again.
We must follow the fjord.
Then we go sailing.
Sailing? Where to?
-Back up.
We need a boat.
Sailing? What does he want?
He didn't think the container would be picked up.
I think we're close.
Maja Zeuthen can not reach her ​​husband.
She wants to talk to him.
Make sure that Zeuthen calls home.
And figure out what's in the fjord.
We had business in the fjord.
If you look at his file you'll
know he knows his way around here.
Where else are containers picked up?
-There are some small harbors.
If we look at the end of the fjord,
we'll be late for any other place.
He said that we are safe, believe it.
What's happening there?
Where are you calling for?
-The mother wants to speak to Zeuthen.
Send her to Brix and go
to those watch shops.
That's why I'm calling.
None of the car drivers have been to
a watch specialist. Only Reinhardt.
I saw it on a credit card printout.
The Monday right after the murder of
Louise, Reinhardt bought a new watch.
But he couldn't do it if he was at the hotel.
Are you certain he bought a watch?
The shop owner remembered him.
Where are you sailing to?
And don't hang up again.
Loke identified the spot.
It's an abandoned oil terminal.
Was that hotel data checked thoroughly?
-Why?
Reinhardt bought shortly after the murder
a watch. I want to be sure of his alibi.
There is no doubt.
He came in the afternoon, went to his room,
and checked out the following morning.
But his car was in the child's book.
The deputy prosecutor tampered
with the date in the report.
It must be because of that booklet.
He acknowledged that his
watch broke two years ago.
He couldn't have tampered with
the electronic lock's data.
Here we are.
It takes a little longer in Norway.
They are now in the fjord.
Damn.
What's going on?
We are unfortunately dependent
on the kidnapper.
We are screwed with the other
parties until Emilie is returned.
Tell your brother when he is
drawing up his next ministry list
to put me as Minister of Finance.
I hope no photographers are lurking
about, you don't want to be seen here.
Find a door with a padlock.
We have no feasible option
for a support party!
What are we doing here?
There's no padlocks.
WHERE DOES THE MONEY COME FROM
Government collision course
Okay I see something here.
Reinhard gives Karen Zeeland money.
She shakes hands and thanks him.
Someone's been in here
searching through his things.
Who? The door was locked.
Well someone came to
remove these pictures.
There has to be something
else that explains it all.
There's nothing here but the
conspiracy theories from his head.
He took that stuff seriously,
but it's not why he died.
I'm sorry you got dragged into this.
Karen have everything boxed up.
We'll find a support party.
Ask them how long they want to
wait for good news from Norway.
And the buildings next to the terminal?
We are working on it. What about the
hotel? Nobody saw Reinhardt ...
It's being checked. Are we looking for a
green container?
Is there anything on
the garage or his watch?
We put that line of inquiry on hold.
Hedeby is coming
and Maja Zeuthen is still waiting.
We need to have that alibi retraced.
-I will.
Maja wants to talk to Robert Zeuthen.
Get him on your mobile.
Robert, can you hear me?
We are still looking for her.
I have to hang up now.
I know what you took out of the closet.
I gotta go.
-What do you want it for?
What was that?
What was that just now?
Nothing really.
-We are still looking.
We looked everywhere. It's gone.
He tricked us.
Here he comes.
You promised to give her to me.
-And you said you would punish the killer.
You had a container shipped.
You led us here.
So we didn't find the girl sooner.
Tell me where she is. Come on.
Why would I do that? You don't want
my daughter's murder to be solved.
Why are you letting him go?
I had him.
And the one chance I
had, you took him away.
If you are lucky, there is still
a little time to find her.
But tell me honestly,
how did you do it?
Did what? I don't know
what you're talking about.
So you have no idea.
If he does, he will be punished.
Why should I believe you?
Because I-
Zeuthen, calm down.
Now you tell me where she is!
-Calm down.
Where is she?
I know exactly how you feel.
Zeuthen, put that gun down.
If you do, we find her again.
Think!
Put the gun down.
Put the gun down. Listen to me.
No come on, stay with me.
Why? Why did you do that?
Come on, why?
I had to, I thought...
The Medea.
What did he say? Did he say where Emilie is?
What happened? Is he dead?
How could you have
authorized that trip?
Tell me what's going on.
The kidnapper is dead.
We need people on the Medea.
There's nothing on that ship,
it's going to be scrapped.
If the ship is in port,
the kidnapper could have
used that boat to hide
Emilie Zeuthen there.
Find out if the ship is still there.
Has the girl been found or not?
-I don't know.
I hope we get some good news
before the polls close.
The latest polls. I'm going to coordinate
the dinner while we still have a party.
If I were you, I'd rebuild bridges
with Lebech and the Center Party.
I'm not on my knees yet.
She's calling again. We've worked
so hard, will you take the call?
I don't have the time to do it.
I'll be brief.
We'll support Ussing unless you come
up with something good for us.
We want a greater role, and at least
as many posts as your own ministers.
A strong alliance is in your best interest.
This is just blackmail.
You should have thought of that
before you tossed me aside.
Hello? Kristian?
What did she say?
-Any news of Mogens?
But we need to talk.
-Not now.
Is Kristoffer gone?
Have the IT people look at this.
I'll take care of it.
When we were there I asked
some of the basketball
players if they had seen
anything back then.
I gave them my card.
One of them saw something
because he just called.
He called because he
recognized someone there today.
We have to wait here.
I want to help with the search.
You should wait here.
The ship is still here, we've searched
half of it and she hasn't turned up yet.
She should be there, search the whole ship.
I am, there's nothing here.
She's somewhere she can't be heard.
Maybe the cargo hold, or a cooling room.
We have already looked.
Then check again.
The kidnapper said she could still be
saved, it's probably an unlikely place.
A place he knew where she wouldn't-
Is she there?
She is here, but...
28-1 here. Asbjørn's coming
up but he needs help.
Emilie, mommy's here.
Wake up.
Wake up my sweetheart, wake up.
Maja? What's going on there?
Wake up, sweetie.
She's here. She's alive. She's here.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Thank you, Brix.
Robert knows he broke the law and
he's really sorry about what he did.
I'd like to ask the Norwegian police
to allow him to return by plane.
That's fine.
I'll take care of the formalities.
It just may be him.
We'll go investigate.
The hotel and their lock system.
He went around acting as
the protector of orphans-
He has for years. All over the world. And he still does.
A happy end to the kidnapping case
is good new for the government.
The news of Emilie returning
home is definitely good news.
It's gone reasonably well with her.
I have to say that the police and PET have done a good job.
The rumors of Zeeland pulling its support
for the government have been quashed.
According to exit polls, in the
last few hours massive numbers
of voters have turned out to
vote for the ruling party.
We've achieved a big victory.
Rosa Lebech just called, but now they are
all falling in line and want to talk.
You were in Benjamin's room on the day
he died. You were recognized.
What were you doing there?
Answer me.
Nothing happened.
I was tipped off about those pictures.
They could have been misconstrued.
They could have hurt us.
-What kind of tip?
I explained to him, it might hurt us
should the photos become public.
He threw me out and I prevented the
pictures from being published.
Who asked you to go there?
It was Mogens.
Mogens said PET had discovered
the photos on that server.
That's what they do for us, right?
Mogens wanted me with him when they
started talking, so we kept you out of it.
Have you searched the room?
-No. Nothing more happened.
Did you or Mogens know where he was?
-Mogens.
I would have told you everything,
but Benjamin died the next day.
And then it didn't matter anymore.
You're nothing to me.
Absolutely nothing.
Maybe you should take a
long look at yourself.
I kept my mouth shut
to spare you.
It's not my fault you were
a bad parent.
I haven't failed.
We need to talk.
The IT department took a look at the
USB stick. There are tons of photos.
Benjamin took those pictures of Reinhardt
and me, but they are not interesting.
He followed Reinhardt
after I left him.
Maybe he wanted to find out
who he was. But then he had enough.
But he takes a picture, the importance
of which he does never know.
We need to go over Reinhardt's garage
again, and his old watch. We ...
As long as his alibi stands,
we can't do anything of the sort.
His alibi needs to be reexamined,
he may have been there earlier.
I have a printout from the hotel.
Reinhardt had room 108 and the lock
recorded when he came and went.
You gave me permission to continue
with the case, I'll go to the hotel-
The investigation is closed and management
wants you to start your job with OPA.
The trail is cold and things are different
now that the kidnapper is dead.
We have no evidence. And even if
you're right we can't touch him.
In the eyes of the law
that means he is innocent.
Do you get what I'm saying?
There's nothing I can do.
The man is covered by
Zeeland's team of lawyers.
I can't seem to get my
boss to go to bat for me.
Everyone in my department
considers his alibi water tight.
There's no way to know
if it was Reinhardt.
It might as well have been a car that
is long gone and out of the country.
We've found Emilie Zeuthen. You found her.
That's what this was all about.
I've taken care of the formalities,
thanks again for everything.
I've called for a taxi and we have a
plane waiting at a nearby airport.
You can come with, but
we have to leave now.
You can ride with us.
-Fine.
We'll say goodbye and then go.
We'll have a party soon.
The head of PET had to go to the Justice Ministry.
That should reduce the tension around here.
I'm sorry for getting mad.
You know me.
Is there something I should know?
Only that in six months the chief is leaving.
You'd look good in a uniform.
Royal Prince Hotel, Esbjerg.
I'm calling on behalf of Zeeland. I'm
Niels Reinhardt's secretary.
I want to book a room for him, but
I forgot which one he wants.
That's easy. Mr. Reinhardt always
takes 312, overlooking the sea.
Which dates do you need?
Are you sure it was 312?
I thought he said 108.
Mr. Reinhardt has come here for years and
always asks for room 312. Hold on.
I'm looking in our system. Oddly enough,
a few years ago he stayed in 108.
Why is that weird?
That is a lesser room. We always take
good care of the bosses.
What do you mean by 'bosses'?
-The upper echelon of Zeeland.
Thanks again for your efforts.
No thanks necessary.
You can save your greetings
for headquarters.
The votes are not counted, but I'd
still like you congratulate you, eh?
Do not tell me this is the first
time you've seen this picture.
You knew all along what Zeuthen's
assistant had done it.
You let the deputy prosecutor cover up
the murder and involved PET.
You found out that my son
had taken pictures.
You notified Zeeland,
who erased them from the server.
Kristoffer told me PET told you about the pictures.
What happened to my son?
Well?
Perhaps the minister can explain it better...
-What happened to him?
Answer me!
Intelligence knew were the box was.
We went to search through them, but he
ran out of the house when we arrived.
My people tried to explain what they
were doing there.
But he ran into the backyard
and then along the track.
We tried to call him back,
but he wouldn't listen.
He was beside himself.
He never saw the train.
You killed him.
It was an accident.
It was not my decision to go there.
It is extremely unfortunate...
and sad what happened to your son.
But we had already been cleaning
up his messes for him...
after he had ran around
Jutland in your car.
And that picture is much more important ...
You can explain that to a judge.
Kristian, come on, let's go.
Listen. The economic
crisis was at its worst.
A baseless accusation against a
man who embodies Zeeland ...
we couldn't use it.
Unsubstantiated accusations? This
photo proves that he is the murderer.
That photo proves nothing.
And Zeeland said that making such
accusations wouldn't be forgiven.
Who said that?
I had to make a choice
and I did the right thing.
Reinhardt has an alibi
and the case is closed.
Why go into such trouble for an orphan
girl that nobody will miss?
Let's get going.
We won't make it without Zeeland.
With their support, you won the election
back then, like you will win this one.
We'll first go to the police
and show them the photo.
Then we go back before Mogens can clean up.
We call on the party leadership together
and explain how you weren't involved...
and everything will come to light.
Congratulations on the victory.
With some luck you can
form the government tomorrow.
You should issue warrants for the
Minister and to the PET...
so the whole thing can be
brought to justice.
The photo proves nothing by itself.
What are you talking about?
It was in the best interest of the country.
It was an accident.
You need to hear yourself.
Benjamin had it hard.
We should not stir this up.
That's exactly what they want.
That you swallow their filth because
you won the election.
I'll get a car and then we'll go, okay?
I'm on my way, I'll be there as soon as I can.
How is she?
The doctors examined her and she'll make it.
It'll be nice for the four of us
to go away.
It will certainly be great.
Robert, how great! The management and
board of directors are very happy for you.
Tell me if Reinhardt killed the girl.
On the way home I called our lawyer.
You talked to him when Reinhardt
was still a suspect.
The lawyer said he had no alibi.
Shortly after your conversation
he suddenly has an alibi.
From our own hotel chain.
I understand your reaction.
Did Reinhardt kill the girl?
To be honest, I don't know.
But there is no reason to believe it.
After all, he was your father's assistant.
And we already had enough crises.
Get out.
Pack your stuff and get out
before I throw you on your ass.
You won't.
First, you will find no evidence.
Second, you can't risk a scandal.
It will destroy everything
your family has built.
The same goes for your decision to leave.
Look at the bright side.
You gout your daughter and Maja back.
The government has won the election.
The board supports you.
You can postpone the company's relocation
to a time that suits you.
It's time for Reinhardt to retire.
Spend a long weekend with your family.
Then come Monday we can talk about
the future, shall we?
You should be here. Mark
and Eve are doing so well.
Alright mom.
Are you with Mathias Borch?
Tell him hello, come home soon.
I'll put Mark on.
She's so sweet.
She sleeps a lot of course, but I was
would be okay to stay until-
Of course, of course,
and congratulations.
I forgot to text you pictures.
It's okay.
I'm needed again, we'll talk later.
I'm really looking
forward to seeing her.
Did a little one just arrive?
I spoke to the airport,
the plane is ready.
I'm looking for where I should park.
You must have wondered about the
alibi that appeared yesterday.
Someone at Zeeland has ensured
it seemed like you were in room 108.
That way the electronic lock would
establish your alibi.
You never were in room 108.
You always take room 312.
You killed Louise Hjelby.
And she wasn't the first, was she?
Justice will be served.
I will make sure of it.
I don't think so. Otherwise we
wouldn't be having this conversation.
But I admire your perseverance,
diligence and decency.
These are qualities that
I appreciate... greatly.
I appreciate you have reminded me of those
things. You've taught me a lot.
I'll take them to heart.
But now we must go.
What have you done?
Jump in the car.
Jump in the car, dammit.
Okay. We'll say he tried something.
He went for your gun and then
you had no choice but to...
Goddamn it, Sarah.
He said he did it.
He murdered her.
He did.
Take off your coat and wipe the blood off.
Listen to me.
Nobody expects us until the plane lands.
I'll think of something to say here,
that'll give you a few hours.
You tell the pilot ... Do you hear me?
Tell the pilot to fly you to Reykjavik.
And from Reykjavik go straight
somewhere else.
Some place with lots of people.
You need a security pass to go abroad.
ln Reykjavik you say that your
husband works for PET.
You are visiting a sick aunt, but you
left your passport at home.
That way it tracks as me travelling.
And they can contact me directly.
Also, you should take my
children's health insurance cards.
Take your coat off, dammit!
This is not a good plan.
If you don't make waves, you'll
get by for years.
They trust statements made by PET.
Sarah, for fucks's sake
why did you do it?
If you think he has done this before ...
this was your chance to prove it.
Find something.
Find something and then come back.
You return and then it'll be alright.
Sweetheart. It'll be alright.
I'll let headquarters know
we are leaving.
And when I come back, be gone.
Okay, sweetheart?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org