Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[walking on metal]
[clanking]
[walking faster]
[tape rewinding]
[man] For the record,
state your name and age.
Gert de Jager.
Forty-three years.
[Gert] I want to put on the record
that I'm not doing this
for any time off or anything like that.
I just want to help the girls' parents.
You know.
Find out what happened to them.
[man] Okay. So tell us what happened.
[car rattling]
[Gert] They're gone.
Not just the five or six that you know of.
There's more than 40.
-[car rattling]
-[sobbing]
[Gert] My girlfriend and I…
we kidnapped them, but…
it wasn't for us.
We were acting under instructions.
[man] From whom?
From a National Party cabinet minister.
[man] Which minister?
I can't say.
He'll have me murdered.
[Gert] Even here.
[man] Okay, and the girls?
[girls sobbing]
He had a farm in Brakpan.
[Gert] It's like a lodge.
[sobbing]
[woman] Come on! Get out! Out! Out!
[girl crying]
[woman] Come on, quick-quick!
[blows harshly]
-[woman sighs deeply]
-[girl sobbing]
-[fingers snapping]
-[woman] Let's go.
[woman] Hey!
My goodness…
[Gert] They had this airstrip.
From here, the girls were smuggled
to the Middle East, maybe Iran.
There were sanctions back then
so they were traded for oil.
Kind of like a barter deal.
[girls sobbing]
-[man in Afrikaans] Take them away.
-[man] Go, go, go. Go here.
The thing is,
not all of them were smuggled.
[man] Why's that?
Some were used and…
then killed.
[tape stops]
[footsteps moving slowly]
[girl sobbing]
[girls singing]
[zapping]
[thunder roaring in the distance]
[thunder roaring]
[gun cocks]
[trunk opening]
[agitated breathing]
[gunshot]
[children talking]
[car approaching]
[soldiers yelling]
-[soldier] All right, all right!
-Police! Police! Police!
[distorted voice on the radio]
[cocks gun]
Jode… Jodie!
[soldier talking]
-[gunshots]
-[canister explodes]
[soldier] All clear! All clear!
Ugh!
Freeze! Halt!
Pursuing a suspect on foot, rear window.
[grunts]
[screaming, shouts]
[man talking over the radio]
Fuck.
[man on radio] Check in.
[Jodie] Where are they?
[panting]
[sobbing]
Oh, fuck…
[man over the phone] Get your act
straight! Get your shit together!
I don't want to have
this conversation with you again.
[line disconnects]
[phone ringing]
OLD WOUNDS ARE REOPENED
[knocking]
"Tactical and financial constraints"?
-They had counter-surveillance.
-Should've waited.
If we don't get to them in 48 hours…
-I know.
-Life expectancy…
The resources are
the damned resources, Jodie.
Okay.
So you tell me how do we get to here?
I mean, never mind how they traffic
underage girls overseas
when we don't have what we need
to catch the guys
snatching girls right off the street.
Jodie…
If you don't make busts,
I can't get funding.
No funding, and this whole
operation gets shut down.
Anything?
[woman] Some prints, but no.
[knocking]
I've asked Samuel
to come speak to us today.
He has a case we may be interested in.
Arendse, Murder &amp; Robbery.
White male, 60s,
looks like some kind of ritual killing.
Oupa here is a suspected pedophile.
He used to be on a trafficking watch list.
[Jodie] When?
[man] Twenty, thirty years ago.
Captain, with all due respect…
Jodie, I want you to take this case.
-Sorry?
-Look, just do it.
Thamsanqa, you take over here.
Captain?
I'm sorry, but am I off the operation?
-The Brigadier called me.
-That asshole.
We're not meeting the minimum requirements
-for the victims'--
-Give me what I need.
Listen to me! You're fucking up.
-This is the third bust.
-Give me one more surveillance team.
Take the case and take a break!
That's an order.
[guitar music playing]
[sobbing]
[man] Cause of death
is a gunshot wound to the chest,
resulting in a cardiac arrest
caused by hemorrhage.
Superficial burn on the neck.
Could be a Taser.
And then this.
Had me stumped as well.
Where was the body found?
James and Ethel Gray Park.
But he wasn't killed there, he was moved.
Thanks.
[woman] Another drink?
Sure, why not?
[in Zulu] Brother…
Fun guy.
[trumpet playing]
[vocalizing]
You're great.
[chuckling]
I love this song.
What?
-Mh-hm.
-No.
Don't worry, there are
some white people there.
[laughing] What?
Oh.
[song continues]
[song fading out]
[Samuel] Can you think of anyone
who wanted to hurt your father?
He had his flaws, but…
But he was a good man.
Mrs. Lourens, did you know his name
was on the old National Register
for Sex Offenders?
He was found not guilty.
Who made the allegations?
Mrs. Lourens,
it's easier here than in court.
[Mrs. Lourens] At that time,
he was high up in the National Party.
They had many enemies, as you know.
[Jodie] Excuse me.
Hey.
[in Afrikaans] Are you a police lady?
Mm-hm.
[in Afrikaans] I'm Jodie.
[in Afrikaans] What's your name?
Liezel.
[in Afrikaans] That's a pretty name.
-[in Afrikaans] It's not necessary…
-[in English] Just give me one second.
[in Afrikaans]
I'm sorry about your grandfather.
[Jodie in English] Open the garage.
-[Mrs. Lourens] Why do you want to…
-[in Afrikaans] Open the garage!
[Samuel in Afrikaans] We have a warrant.
[mechanical whirring]
[dramatic percussion builds]
Arendse, get me that ladder.
Holy shit.
[thunder roaring in the distance]
[girl in the video crying]
[sighs]
What do you think?
I think whoever murdered Carel
knew he was into this.
"T.S.C." It's…
Some kind of message.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's just…
This is kind of monstrous
in its own right, you know?
Why don't you check out other crimes
in the same area? Same date.
Thanks.
[quick walking]
[man in Afrikaans] Get inside the house,
quickly! Come on, move it!
[man in Afrikaans]
Quickly. Move, move! Come on!
Come on, come on. Hurry up!
[in Afrikaans] Come on, come on.
[woman in Afrikaans] My goodness, get in!
[man in Afrikaans] Thanks, Gert.
[in Afrikaans] Get in.
[man in Afrikaans]
That one has been used up.
[girl singing slowly]
[woman] Come!
[electronic music playing in the distance]
[overlapping chatter]
[dramatic percussion builds]
[door opening]
[man] Thank you.
[exhales]
[ringing bell]
-Jodie, what are you doing here?
-I have something you need to see.
Personal residences
are strictly off-limits.
Just listen to me for a second.
Get in your car
and go home, get some sleep.
I wouldn't be here if it wasn't important.
Come on.
[Jodie] T.S.C.
I believe it stands
for Tarrynlee Shaw Carter.
[in Setswana] Hey, guys, go to bed,
you know the rules.
Agnes…
His body was found
in James and Ethel Gray Park.
Same place and date that Tarrynlee
was abducted by Gert de Jager.
Gert de Jager…
-De Jager abducted six girls.
-Yeah, I know the history.
This man is a pedophile.
Even his own granddaughter.
Which he recorded.
Wait until your kids are in bed.
Jodie, how much sleep have you had?
George, I want to bring in the operation,
this could be a new line of inquiry.
We barely have the resources
for our current investigations.
Gert de Jager…
Gert de Jager took six girls
who were never found.
Tarrynlee, Frances Hughes,
Jenna Hartley, Olivia Booysen,
-Abigail Viljoen and Yvette Rossouw.
-Twenty years ago.
If the killer is using them
as a scorecard,
there's going to be five more bodies.
-Murder &amp; Robbery's problem.
-I know. But get this:
Shortly after he was arrested,
Gert de Jager confessed on tape.
He fingered a National Party minister,
and the next day he was found
murdered in his cell.
Do you have the tape?
No, it was classified under apartheid,
but I'm going to find it.
Jodie, you're making connections
you simply can't prove.
I need the operation, damn it, George, I--
[sighs]
Jodie, I'm going to suggest
that you go to Health &amp; Wellness
for psychological evaluation.
-It is my assessment…
-Here we go.
-…you're suffering post-traumatic stress.
-Bullshit.
This job gets to all of us.
[softly] It's supposed to get to us,
otherwise what the fuck are we doing?
I'm going to insist
that you take three months off.
[quick punching]
[grunting]
Easy.
-[breathing heavily]
-[ringing tone]
You okay?
[grunting]
Ah!
[panting]
We're done.
[Jodie] Come on!
[woman] Give me your hands.
Give me your hands, Jodie,
and close your eyes.
Take a deep breath in…
and hold for five…
four…
three…
two…
one.
Exhale.
[exhaling]
You know I'm not supposed
to know where you live, right?
Why, are you coming after me?
[chuckles]
You never know.
[woman] Where's this?
[Jodie] Oh, that's…
outreach programs for trafficking victims.
[woman] I love that
you don't distance yourself.
Yeah, well…
They feel like my children.
[Jodie] How are you?
You're asking me how I am.
I never know what you're thinking.
Captain told me.
Three months.
I'm sorry.
I could stay.
I need to be alone.
[thunder roaring]
[gun cocks]
-[shooting]
-[screaming]
[people chattering]
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
[police siren]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Jodie! What are you doing here?
I told her to come.
She needed to see this.
F.H.
Frances Hughes.
Okay.
Follow me.
[girl singing slowly]
Jodie.
[George] What are you thinking?
This is where the killer wants us to be.
What about her?
She works here, but she's not talking.
[woman] Captain, have a look at this.
Waybills.
All from the same shipping
container yard in Durban. And get this:
owned by the Khan brothers.
Salim and Parwaz?
Top of the board.
This one is dated for tomorrow,
it's for a shipment.
Outbound.
I could leave first thing in the morning.
-Without a warrant? Jodie…
-I'll do recon only.
I could tag along.
This is also my investigation.
Okay. But keep it clean.
I'm following a lead to Durban.
I'll see you in a few days.
[man grunting]
[grunting]
[whistling]
[grunts]
[woman] Ntombi!
[girls giggling]
They're checking the waybills.
So what's your deal, Arendse?
My deal?
Yeah, your deal.
Are you profiling me?
I heard you worked undercover,
street gangs in Cape Town…
Apparently they're
into trafficking these days.
So what's your deal, lady?
My deal is right here, right fucking now.
[ship horn blares]
[Jodie] Investigating Officer
Jodie Snyman.
DPCI. Human Trafficking.
I want to know where your containers are.
[man] Where did you get these?
[Jodie] If you cooperate now…
it'll look good for you.
Jodie.
Tell me where this is.
I'd like to see a warrant.
-[Samuel] Jodie…
-We can't just stand around.
Jodie, don't do it.
You don't have to come.
Fuck.
-Are these outbound?
-Excuse me, what are you doing?
I'm opening them up.
[man] Who are you guys?
Investigating Officers, Human Trafficking.
You cannot come in here.
I want to take a look
in these containers, now.
-Are you mad?
-Listen to me. You open them, or I will.
Listen carefully, sir.
One way or the other,
we're looking into these containers.
This is bullshit.
[whistles]
[man] Open this container.
-Why are they empty?
-[man] Redistribution.
Open this one.
Do it!
Open it.
What…
Officer, I assure you I have
the documents for all that.
What is this?
Fuck.
[police siren]
Shit.
[Samuel] It's okay, we're leaving.
Jodie.
Jodie!
[Jodie] We raided the yard.
There was nothing
in the fucking containers. I fucked up.
Jesus, Jodie.
Look, it's fine.
No one's going to say anything.
[Ntombi] Jodie, this could lead to Parwaz.
You realize, even if we did get a warrant,
whatever we found would be inadmissible?
And what if we'd found children?
Young girls? I mean…
There's no way I couldn't have gone
in there. You would have done the same.
Jodie, you're compromising this
investigation, pull your shit together.
[gun cocks]
[gunshots]
[Jodie sighs]
Thanks for sticking up for me today.
How many trafficking convictions
did you get last year?
You don't want to know.
[thunder roaring]
[dramatic percussion builds]
I'm heading up.
Yeah, me too.
Can I get a bottle of pinotage?
Drowning my sorrows.
[quick knocking]
-[girl crying]
-[quick knocking]
[Samuel] Jodie! We've got to go!
Now, Jodie!
[sirens wailing in distance]
[helicopter whirring overhead]
Hawks.
Jenna Hartley.
Excuse me, ma'am?
I think you'll want to see this.
I want every one of these,
from every container.
[man] We're on it.
[thunder rumbling]
Selma, sort this out for me, please.
[George] Jode.
These manifests connect a lot
of different parties to the containers.
We have names, connections, locations.
[George] This is…
This is unbelievable.
I've got a national intervention
task force on standby.
I'm talking multiple arrests,
convictions.
-And the Khan brothers?
-Salim and Parwaz have gone underground.
But we've put a lookout.
We're going to get those bastards.
You mind?
[George] Of course.
I have some
uncomfortable questions to ask.
Only some members of your unit
knew what was going on at this yard.
Is that correct?
What are you trying to say?
It's more than likely
that someone in your operation
was involved in some way or the other.
Seems like this particular person
is just two steps ahead all the time.
Any thoughts?
[people chattering]
[anchor] The community
of the church of Sunderland
was shattered today
when pastor Marius Groenewald
was arrested on charges of child abuse
and selling at-risk children
to traffickers.
This comes
after a startling discovery in Durban,
of children from a nearby township
found in a container marked
for shipping to the Middle East.
[Samuel] Jodie, I like you.
But you have to admit,
the most likely scenario is
that somebody is working from the inside.
[anchor 2] Police have
arrested Tina Moloi,
the principal of the Reformed
Primary School of Kgomotso,
believed to be involved
in the disappearance of several children
who were rescued last week
from a container yard in Durban.
Captain Ntombizonke Bapai.
Can you tell me how long
you have been with the operation?
[Ntombi] Eight months.
[Jodie] Mr. Marais, you're under arrest
for the illegal production
and distribution of pornographic
material involving minors.
Any utterances you make to officers
may be used against you in court.
You have the right to consult an attorney.
[Samuel]
I don't suspect Jodie, not at all.
That woman has got
too much integrity, she's too invested.
I'm only giving you the heads-up
because I have to submit my report.
But the chances of you getting a call
from the Brigadier is more than likely.
[George] I appreciate it.
[Jodie] This is our target.
Salim Khan, 60s, Indian.
[soldiers] Go, go, go!
[anchor 2] Salim Khan was arrested today.
It is alleged he is a senior operator
in an international child
and sex trafficking syndicate,
with his brother, Parwaz Khan,
who is still at large.
Who masterminds
the syndicate is still unknown,
but an investigation by Hawks
is making progress.
Hello.
[thunder roaring]
[grunting]
[in isiZulu] Hey, get out of the way!
[phone ringing]
George?
We have a situation.
My house, ten minutes.
No, just get there.
Shit.
What's going on?
-[Agnes] George!
-[in Setswana] Are you all right?
-Where's your phone?
-[in Sesotho] What's going on?
-Where's Katlego and Naledi?
-In their room.
-Take them to your sister's.
-What's happening?
I need you to trust me, Agnes, please.
Don't ask questions, I can't answer them.
Fuck.
[car engine starting]
-[in English] They got into the operation.
-Bullshit.
-They know where I live, that I have kids!
-Not difficult information to find.
Arendse believes someone
in our operation is aiding the killer.
[Jodie] That's stupid.
Jodie. I was an investigator
for 20 years. Tell me what you know.
[phone ringing]
It's Khan's prosecutor.
Hey.
Fuck.
Yup.
[Jodie] Thanks.
-They're releasing Salim Khan.
-Why?
-We raided his yard without a warrant.
-No, we didn't.
I did.
Jesus, Jodie.
You realize you leave me
no choice whatsoever.
There were children in that yard.
I am going to be calling
for a disciplinary hearing
where I will be pushing
for your dismissal!
If you think you can intimidate me,
you're dead wrong.
-You're helping them, Jodie!
-I'll do whatever it takes!
[huffs]
[car engine starting]
[door opening]
[sobbing]
-Hi.
-Hey.
-Can I get you something?
-I'm fine.
Salim Khan is being released.
I know.
You'll get him.
Or someone else will.
I guess you know George
has started proceedings against me.
You'll fight it.
Let's go for a drive.
Where to?
You'll see.
Jodie…
[thunder roaring]
Jodie, turn this car around.
Jodie, turn the car around.
Ntombi, you need to tell me.
Are you working alone
or with somebody else?
Stop the car.
Look, it's fine.
-I said, stop the car.
-Talk to me.
I love you.
-Ntombi--
-I said, stop the fucking car!
-I'm just trying to understand!
-Stop the car!
Stop the car!
[tires screeching]
Jodie?
[guns cocking]
[groaning]
[gun cocks]
[gunshots]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[heart beating]
Relax, Jodie, you're safe.
Are you all right?
What happened?
Your car rolled.
They're dead.
Who's dead?
The men who hit you.
They were shot and killed.
Did you…
I didn't.
What about Salim Khan?
He was taken.
[George] Jodie…
You need to tell me
what you were doing there.
You're done, Jodie.
[car engine starting]
[quick knocking]
[quick slamming]
Ntombi!
[man] For the record,
state your name and age.
Gert de Jager.
Forty-three years.
[man] Okay. So tell us what happened.
They're gone.
Not just the five or six that you know of.
It's more than 40.
Not just white kids.
I had my maid bring us kids
from the township.
My girlfriend and I,
we kidnapped them, but…
it wasn't for us.
We were acting on their instructions.
[man] From whom?
[Gert]
From a National Party cabinet minister.
[man] Which minister?
VOTE NATIONAL PARTY
[Gert] I can't say.
He'll have me murdered.
Even here.
[man] Okay, and the girls?
He had a farm in Brakpan.
It was like a lodge.
It had this airstrip.
From here, the girls were smuggled
to the Middle East, maybe Iran…
They were traded for oil.
Kind of-- Kind of like a barter deal.
The thing is,
not all of them were smuggled.
[man] Why's that?
[Gert] Some were used.
And killed.
[giggling]
[groaning]
My name is Ntombizonke Bapai.
[men whimpering]
My first name, it means "all girls".
[groaning and struggling]
[faint groaning in the distance]
[gun cocks]
[breathing heavily]
[in Afrikaans] Get the lights.
No, thanks.
Would you care to have a look?
[man in Afrikaans] Start moving, come on.
[Samuel] Don't move!
Investigating Officer Hawks!
Fuck!
[Samuel] I've got back-up on the way.
-[Samuel] Lie down on the ground, now!
-[Jodie] Fuck!
[Samuel] I want those girls off the plane.
[gunshot]
[man in Afrikaans]
What the fuck is going on?
[men in Afrikaans] Come on! Come on!
[gunshots]
[man grunts]
Go, go.
[man in Afrikaans] He's been shot!
[man in Afrikaans] Secure the area!
[gun cocks]
Ntombi.
What-- What are you…
[rapid gunfire]
[tires screeching]
[rugged breathing]
[Ntombi gasping softly]
[Ntombi] I love you too.
No.
No, Ntombi…
Ntombi…
No…
No… No…
[Jodie sobbing]
[girls giggling in the distance]
[gunfire]
Go. Go, go!
[breathing heavily]
[wood creaking]
[dramatic percussion builds]
-[gunshots]
-[body thuds]
[man gasping for air]
Ntombizonke Bapai.
Do you want me to put
a lookout on Jodie Snyman?
How are you today?
[woman] Please remove your glasses.
Have a nice flight.
[calm song playing]
♪ Alone ♪
♪ Listless ♪
♪ Breakfast table
In an otherwise empty room ♪
♪ A young girl ♪
♪Violence ♪
♪ In the center
Of her own attention ♪
♪The mother reads aloud
The child tries to understand it ♪
♪ She tries to make her proud ♪
♪ The shades go down
It's in her head ♪
♪ Painted room ♪
♪ There's something wrong ♪
♪ Don't call me daughter
Not fit to ♪
♪The picture kept will remind me ♪
♪ Don't call me daughter
Not fit to ♪
♪ The picture kept will remind me ♪
♪ Don't call me ♪
♪ She holds the hand
That holds her down ♪
♪ She will rise above ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Don't call me daughter
Not fit to ♪
♪ The picture kept will remind me ♪
♪ Don't call me daughter
Not fit to ♪
♪ The picture kept will remind me ♪
♪ Don't call me daughter ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ Don't call me ♪
♪ The picture kept will remind me ♪
♪ The shades go down ♪
♪ Don't call me ♪
♪ The picture kept will remind me ♪
♪The picture kept will remind me ♪
♪ Don't call me ♪
[ominous music playing]
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-