Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app
Oh!
Dongcheon! Dongcheon! Dongcheon!
Dongcheon! Dongcheon!
You're awake, dumbass?
Hey, are you finally awake?
Get out here and die.
You got your ass beat by a girl
and you blacked out.
I wanna kill myself out of humiliation.
About earlier...
I wanna apologize.
Apologize for what?
It's just a fight.
Hey, man, you wanna hang out now?
Why? So you can get drunk?
Black out and die.
Uh, no.
I thought we could go...
What?
Don't be such a pussy.
You're always saying you want her.
Asshole, do you lost its fucking mind?
Hey.
Don't do anything stupid, man.
You know the boss brought her.
And she won't remember anything though.
You know, I roofied her water earlier.
Such a stingy little shit, bro.
Well, if you really wanna go that far,
I guess I can't refuse.
Yo.
You don't have to come
if you're so scared.
I owe you, Gangjae.
You know, you're the prettiest
little thing around, fucking slut.
Ah, you make me so hard.
I wanna taste you.
Aah.
Ah, promise I won't be too rough.
Hold still.
You need to calm down.
The whole thing will be over soon.
Stay.
Oh! Dirty slut, I can't take it.
DECEASED, YOON DONGHOON
Oh, Jesus!
Oh!
I'm gonna kill you guys.
Fuck!
I swear I'm gonna kill you guys.
It's the fucking bitch...
Shit!
You fucking psycho bitch!
No!
You need to die.
Get over here, bitch.
Gangjae! I'm all fucked up now!
Yeah?
That piece of shit!
Come here.
Where are you going, you dumb slut?
- Gangjae! Stop it! Hey! Gangjae!
- Fucking bitch.
Your face, arms, or legs.
Which one?
I'm only going to mutilate one.
I'm really sorry, sir.
Sir, I made a mistake.
And that's why...
I chose not to kill you.
Which one?
Are you gonna get rid of me?
You said I was useful to have around.
It's most unfortunate.
I assumed this would eventually
happen to her.
That it was something
she had to go through.
Though I didn't know...
it would be you who did it.
Please forgive me, sir.
All I did was push her around a little!
I, myself, brought her here.
You shouldn't have even touched her.
Okay, which one?
No, I'll decide.
Sir, I'm sorry. No. Please. No.
Please, I'm begging you.
DECEASED, YOON DONGHOON
If you're done crying,
please leave.
Because of you,
I've lost one of my best subordinates.
This will be your last chance.
Your very last chance to wise up.
Well, I'm not going anywhere.
When I served Donghoon,
I got to know him very well.
He didn't belong in this line of work.
I can say the same about you.
You should get out now.
It's too late for me to get out.
Sit down.
I used to come here
with Donghoon all the time.
Did your dad teach you to drink?
Drink up.
It hurts?
Uh, no.
You never learned how to say
that you're in pain.
Or maybe no one taught you.
Yeah, there was someone...
but he's dead now.
The whole purpose of living...
could be a search
for when to find a person like that.
A person who can tell that you're in pain
and that life is too hard.
Have you found someone like that?
Yes, I did, but he died.
OCTOPUS STIR-FRY
PORK STIR-FRY
As of today, Yoon Jiwoo is dead.
Do Gangjae has been expelled.
It's punishment for
having murdered that girl.
Oh Hyejin.
From this point on,
you're going to go by this name.
Here's the gun that killed your dad.
The killer left it,
and we recovered it.
So who was it?
This gun is a police issue.
Donghoon's killer is a policeman.
You're gonna find him.
Kill him.
♪ Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa ♪
♪ Oh-whoa-whoa my past look so blurry ♪
♪ Nobody ♪
♪ No one they say ♪
From now on,
your life belongs to the organization.
No matter what happens,
the organization will protect you.
But betray us, and we will kill you.
What do we do now?
We're going upstairs.
What?
We don't know how many are in there.
Hey. Call backup and go to the front.
Where are you...
Who are you?
What?
What's going on?
Which department are you with,
you dumbass?
Whoo!
Money first.
Hey.
I'm not giving you that.
You know what it's worth?
Now, go and call your boss in here.
I gonna see the guy's face
if we're gonna be working together.
It's gonna be an equally shared risk.
Now...
the supply has been running a little low.
Apparently, not for you guys, huh?
Yeah. Forget it. Never mind.
Okay. Fine.
Sit down.
Okay.
Radio her. Tell her it's a sting.
Fuckin'...
right now.
This jackass came here alone
and now he wants to talk in person.
Hyejin.
- I think I can take him down...
- I'm letting you know.
This is a sting operation. Hyejin. Hyejin!
- Freeze where you are, this is the police!
- Are you fucking narc?
- What the hell is she saying?
- Hey, Changoo, get up.
Oh, shit!
- Grab the knife over there!
- Hurry, come on!
Oh, shit.
Stop right there!
What the hell?
Let's go! Don't let them...
Block them right there!
Park Changoo. You're under arrest
for the murder of Lee Sumin.
Goddamn it!
I can walk on my own.
- Hey.
- Shit.
- Stop right there.
- Fuck.
- Hey!
- Fuck! Argh!
- Damnit. Damnit.
- I said I can walk on my own.
- Hey!
- Shit!
So, who the hell are you?
No, who the hell are you?
What?
I'm Sergeant Jeon Pildo from Narcotics.
Oh, shit, you really are a narc!
Corporal Oh from Violent Crimes Unit Two.
Hey, are you okay?
Can you try and get up?
My leg. Aah!
- I think my leg is broken.
- Hey, try and relax.
- Get an ambulance.
- Yeah.
Let's clean all this up.
Hey. Where's Pildo?
He's upstairs.
Do you have any idea what you've done?
Yeah. I think I do.
- I have an idea.
- Well, that's not enough.
You just ruined a sting operation
we've been setting up for six months.
We'll take care of this asshole.
Stop!
- You can't do that.
- I can't...
I can't do that?
You don't know how to talk
to your superiors, huh?
Are you trying to fuck with me?
- He's suspected of murder.
- Hyejin!
It's Captain Lee for you.
- Let's go.
- Aw!
Hey! God!
Yeah.
What?
Understood, sir.
Send him over to us once you're through.
Hey, wait, stop.
- Oh, god.
- Hey!
I don't wanna see you again, huh?
Let's go.
Damn it.
I'll fuckin' walk on my own!
- Argh! Ah!
- Hurry it up.
Damn it.
You son of a bitch!
Mister... Mr. Choi.
I, uh... I, I was wrong, okay?
This will... This will never ever
happen again, huh?
We've worked together...
together for ten years, huh?
Please, sir. I beg you.
Exactly.
So why did you do it
if we worked together for so long?
Don't you know what kind of guy I am?
I, I give you the whole factory
and all the drugs I have.
I...
I must have... have lost...
lost my mind for a minute there.
I, uh...
Please don't do this.
My daughter...
She just started school.
So then I'll make sure
that the funeral runs smoothly.
Mr. Choi.
No. Mr. Choi!
What are you... What...
Mr. Choi! You fucking... Aah!
INCHANG METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
Did you get them checked?
Corporal Oh Hyejin?
Yes, I'm Oh Hyejin, sir.
You know who I am?
I do, sir.
Captain Cha Giho of the Narcotics Bureau.
OFFICER: OPEN RECRUIT
CORPORAL: SPECIAL PROMOTION
FATHER: OH JINYEONG
MOTHER: BAE SUYEON
Why did you do it?
What?
Your evidence was somewhat inconclusive.
So the arrest was uncalled for.
Well, I believe the motive was clear
and he posed a serious flight risk, sir.
Yes, but that's not a valid reason.
Park Changoo has three priors on record.
I'm sure he would have fled
if I told him I was a cop.
So I believe it was valid.
You've applied to this bureau twice.
- Yes.
- Why so eager?
Why do you wanna join this bureau?
Because there's someone I wanna find.
Who's that?
Is it something you can tell me about?
I like punks like you.
You won't survive if you're only here
for the salary or the pension.
Were you waiting for a while?
Hmm.
Here you go.
What's in here?
Chamomile tea.
It's supposed to help with insomnia.
I know you have trouble sleeping.
Why does it taste like makeup?
This won't help me sleep. It's too gross.
How do you like being a cop?
I've been moved to the Narcotics Bureau.
Now, it's starting for real.
If I can find out who the gun belonged to...
and what exactly Cha Giho
had to do with my dad's murder.
Then I...
I'll have more answers.
Then I'll know who killed him.
My dad and I used to talk about
building a beach house and live there.
We'd hang a hammock out front
and we'd fish and swim every day
like people with nothing to do.
'Cause he wanted to live like that.
And I always wonder
if he were still alive now...
would we be able to live like that?
Do you see that warehouse?
Just about ten years ago,
Donghoon saved my life over there.
Everybody was attacking,
trying to take down the organization.
Mujin!
Hey.
You psycho.
Ah, shit.
Hey.
How can I possibly abandon you here?
Come on.
- It hurts, though. It hurts.
- Get up!
Okay, guys.
Smile for the camera.
Will you be okay?
Too old for this.
I'm giving you my dagger.
You kill him as soon as you can.
Trust me.
No matter what happens,
the organization will protect you.
Later, okay?
God, these questions
are fucking pointless.
Hey, motherfucker!
You haven't answered me! Hey!
- Hey! Why are you cursing the man?
- Did you hear? You...
- You're not getting anything that way.
- Did you hear what he just called me?
And he's all shaken up now.
God.
Changoo. Hey.
Who cares about loyalty anymore?
Money is the real boss, right?
Here.
The name's of five big dealers
and your boss, right it down, huh?
Isn't your dad turning 60?
Don't wanna miss the party.
- Write it down.
- But I don't...
Jesus, just forget it.
There's plenty of other assholes
who will talk.
- So get up, you little piece of shit.
- Wait! Hold on! Just hold on!
No.
I really can't just give up our boss.
You little shit.
It's like you're playing hard to get.
You wanna ask me out, huh?
I can't give you names.
I can give you something else, though.
What?
Are you crazy?
There's this candy that's really hot.
Do you know who sell this stuff?
CALL US ANYTIME IF YOU HAVE QUESTIONS
You fucking asshole.
How dare you...
Wait, wait, wait.
Who is it?
Mango.
I'll be right back.
INTERROGATION ROOM
Hey.
Mango is still your contact?
Huh.
Yeah, find out where Mango is.
Hold on. Don't hang up.
NARCOTICS TEAM 1
Why are you here?
You don't let strangers in.
- Park Changoo is still in questioning.
- Yeah, I know that, sir.
- Then why are you here?
- I was just transferred to this bureau.
Asshole.
You fucking narc? Shit.
Shut up. Stop that.
Ah!
Who's this?
Uh, when did you get here?
- Come in. Let's go. Let's go.
- Captain.
But...
- Here. Right this way.
- I'll call you back.
Yes, sir.
What...
Captain. Captain.
So, you just joined our team?
What's going on?
Your partner.
Seriously, sir, I can't work with her.
Junho's leg hasn't even healed yet.
Well, that wasn't her fault.
You just clashed while on the same case.
Exactly. Don't you think
that's a bad sign, though?
You want her for my partner...
Do you want me to carry her on my back?
She seems tenacious and very useful.
She wants to catch someone.
Well, who doesn't?
You keep an eye on her
and see if she'll last here.
Well, I don't think
she'll even last a month, sir.
You look into the candy?
Yeah.
Park Changoo talked to us.
Mango is the one.
So, bring him in.
Okay.
We don't have time. The boat's here.
It's not letting me log on.
Our system is a different one.
I think you need to register.
Why do you wanna log on?
So I can check the status
of the investigation.
Ah...
Status of the investigation.
Status of the investigation is that
a moron wasted six months of work.
I'm truly sorry about that.
I can register you on our system now.
Why even bother? Not like she lasts long.
Well, what would you like me to do now?
I don't know.
No idea what to do with you.
Huh.
He's there?
Got it.
Let's go.
- What?
- Time to get to work.
- Mango.
- Okay.
DEAD BODY OF BAE JUNGOO
CRIME SCENE PHOTOS
SUICIDE NOTE FOUND WITH BODY
MY DEAR WIFE AND DAUGHTER
I'M SORRY FOR LEAVING YOU
Cha Giho here.
I think it's Choi Mujin,
he's gonna make his move soon.
Yamamoto has expressed interest
in striking a deal with us, sir.
How big of a deal?
The first transaction would be 50 billion.
Should I refuse?
It will become a problem
if we can't meet demand.
They just found Mr. Bae.
Hmm.
I'll make a point of going there
next week.
I don't think I've seen
that tumbler before.
- Chamomile tea.
- Uh...
Chamomile tea?
Nice work, Ms. Kang.
Jiwoo just joined the Narcotics Bureau.
This will be very useful.
And you really think you can trust her?
I, myself, don't think
we should trust her.
I trust the power of her desperation.
Jiwoo will serve as our dagger.
If things go south,
we'll have to kill her.
That's correct.
Goddamn it.
I just can't believe this.
God, that was at the worst.
So, the owner of this place
goes by "Mango", okay?
Head in and bring him out.
And what's he charged with?
Huh. No need for Miranda rights
or anything.
Just go in and bring him out.
Go.
Jesus.
Uh, who are you?
I'm here to meet with the owner.
Uh...
Are you like his new girl or something?
Sorry, that's not my thing. Look.
Mango? Where is he?
Not here. Out.
You have to learn to keep your hands
- to yourself.
- Get out...
Hey. Get out.
Pildo. Did the rookie go inside?
Yeah. Mango is gonna run out
holding the drugs.
Get ready to go.
Who's that?
What the hell
is happening here? What is this?
Fuck. What's taking her so long?
How long has it been?
Time to go.
What the...
What...
What the hell did she do? Is he dead?
Pildo. Hey. Pildo. Wait.
Hey, hey. My arm! My arm!
My arm! Shit!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today