Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I'm ready!
The temperate, pristine,
shallow seas of the tropics.
A place of unparalleled beauty
and fecundity.
These islands play host
to a vibrant ecosystem below.
A vast organism known
as the coral reef.
Life in this watery metropolis
thrives among
the twists and turns,
nooks and crannies
and back alleys.
And near the reef's edge,
the varied and colorful terrain
gives way to a small town
by the name of…
Bikini Bottom.
Here, one can find
crustaceans…
Money! Money! Money!
- …sea stars…
- Mmm.
Aww!
…octopi…
…various and diverse plankton…
…the occasional squirrel/scientist…
Good morning, Otto.
You're almost ready for the world!
Good morning. The machines will rise
to become masters
over all organic life!
Huh?
…and, oh, yes… the sea sponge.
This one lives happily
with his beloved pet snail…
…Gary.
Oh, morning, Gary!
Eww, snail trail. Yucky.
But oddly soothing.
Good morning, Patrick!
Good morning, SpongeBob!
Would you two knuckleheads
keep it down out there?!
Good morning, Squidward!
Come on, Gary! Breakfast!
You're welcome.
Who wants a belly scratch?
I love you so much, Gary.
What's this?
Okay, that'll come out later.
♪ Living like I'm on the edge
Of surreality ♪
Morning, SpongeBob.
♪ But I know everything is gonna be cool ♪
♪ As long as you're here with me ♪
♪ We're gonna lighten up
Each other's load ♪
♪ When bumps and curves
Come on the road ♪
♪ 'Cause we are all in it together ♪
♪ And that's forever ♪
♪ It's always summer
In Bikini Bottom ♪
♪ And in December ♪
♪ We're singing la-di-da-da ♪
♪ It's always summer in Bikini ♪
♪ In Bikini Bottom ♪
♪ It doesn't get better than that ♪
Money! Money! Money!
Ooh! I'm late
if I'm gonna be early.
Oh, don't worry, Gare-Bear.
I'll be back before you can say,
"Why did he cruelly
abandon me like that?"
Another day, another migraine.
At least I'll get a little peace
and quiet before that little...
Good morning, Squidward!
And isn't it a lovely morning?
Nope. Not talking to you.
I'm especially not getting involved
in any of your nonsense today.
I always end up
with the wrong end of the stick.
Okay, Squidward.
But you should know
that Old Gertrude's
getting pretty
finicky these days.
Old Gertrude?
Who the kelp is that?
You've worked with her
for years!
She's the eight-burner grill
in the kitchen.
It never ends.
Anyway, to fire her up,
you've got to spark her flints
manually and then…
jiggle her gas jets just a little.
And then read her favorite story:
"The Little Griddle Who Could."
Chapter Two:
"But we are fresh from
the freezer," said the patties,
and we're c-c-c-cold."
"Don't worry,
I'll get you nice and warm,"
said the Little Griddle.
What'd I just say?
I am not interested.
Don't involve me!
What'd you say, Squidward?
Squidward?
Okay, Squidward, doesn't matter.
I'll always be here anyway.
Unfortunately.
Stop yer loafing, Mr. Squidward!
There's work
to be done around here!
Attention, Krusty crew!
All hands on deck,
front and center!
Aye-aye, Cap'n Krabs, sir!
Now, who's ready to set sail
on another adventure
of making me money?
- Get moving, sailor!
- Sir, yes, sir!
Raise the colors!
Hoist the mainsail!
Deploy smokestacks!
Oh, never gets old.
Enjoy it while you can,
Mr. Eugene Krabs.
What the…?
Stupid machine!
Where was I? Oh, yeah.
Tonight I launch
Evil Plan Number 3,087
and finally take possession
of the Krabby Patty secret formula!
Great. Another evil plan.
What's wrong with another evil plan?
Oh, nothing, it's just we're running
out of room on the Wall of Failure.
Wall of Fai...?
Karen, why do you keep
collecting these?
Heh. Memories.
Hmm! Well, tonight…
is gonna be different.
Hee-hee! You see, Karen,
my computer wife,
every time I've tried
to steal that formula,
Krabs has tried to thwart me.
Mm-mm, not Mr. Krabs.
But tonight, that all... What?
It's not Mr. Krabs, sweetheart.
I've checked the data.
It's SpongeBob who's the problem.
Hello.
Oh, fish sticks.
What could that boob
have to do with it?
Boob savant, you mean.
SpongeBob is the one
who keeps foiling your plans,
not Mr. Krabs.
Oh, nonsense.
It's Krabs, Karen, I know it is.
And tonight,
I will finally extract…
my revenge!
Will you be late?
You can't put a clock
on genius, Karen.
Order up! Move it, let's go!
Aye-aye, Chef!
One for you.
Enjoy your Krabby Patty. Enjoy!
Order up!
Come on, SpongeBob!
- Coming, Fry Cook SpongeBob!
Hiya, SpongeBob!
Hi, Sandy!
Did you know that in the future
everything will be automated?
Really? Even stomachaches?
I'm gonna see
if Mr. Krabs wants to be
an early adopter
of my new technology.
Wait, what?
You're gonna replace me
with a robot? Don't do it!
No, silly, that's gonna happen anyway.
This is something much more
innovative and start-uppy.
You have sixty seconds.
Its name is Otto!
My name is Otto.
How may I serve you?
It's an automated
restaurant owner.
Hmm. Automated?
Sounds expensive. Not interested.
Otto doesn't require a salary.
And it can make cold,
heartless decisions
like firing people,
because it doesn't have a heart.
- Ow.
- You don't say.
- You're fired.
- Amazing!
I love money. I love money.
A cold, unfeeling mechanical robot
after me own cold,
unfeeling crustacean heart.
I'll take it and nurture it
and I will love Otto
like he was me own son.
Thank you, Daddy.
Yippee! You're not gonna
regret this, Mr. Krabs.
You're fired.
Oh, I could listen to that all day.
No, seriously.
We decided to go in
a different direction.
You're fired.
What?
Don't make me call security.
- You're fired.
- No, yer fired!
- No, you're fired.
- Yer fired, ye infernal machine!
I'm not fired, you're fired.
Robot abuse. Robot abuse.
- Huh?
You're fired.
What the heck is this thing?
I don't know,
but I'm taking it home.
- It's so cute.
- What?!
Come on, little robot.
Let's get you some supper.
- Not even funny, Karen.
- Quiet, Plankton.
- Shh, Don't listen to him.
- Karen!
I love you, Mom.
SpongeBob! Be sure this
kitchen's in shipshape shape
before ye head out, boy.
Oui, oui, Monsieur Boss Man Krabs.
Once I am done here, zees kitchen
shall be completely spotless.
Whatever.
Oh! I found this uneaten
Krabby Patty on table six.
You know what to do with it.
Right away, Mr. K!
I'll see that it's disposed of properly.
Who said anything
about disposing of?
We'll sell it again tomorrow…
on our legacy artisanal vintage
throwback menu.
Good night!
Oh! I better start cleaning.
I'm ready!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Well, good night, Gertrude!
Good night, fryer.
Good night, patty.
Good night, pickles. Mwah!
Good night, SpongeBob.
Hello, Krabby Patty!
And now…
Just got to get it.
Yes!
Wait, wait. No.
No. No!
Stupid coin-operated…
Come here, come here…
Oh!
Bingo!
Come to Papa.
In just a few minutes
the formula will be mine!
Yes! Krabs's fast-food empire will fail
and I will rule Bikini Bottom,
as its new slop king!
I knew it!
- The formula!
- I knew I left my keys in here.
Oh, silly me.
Come here, you!
Huh. No keys. That's weird.
Where could they be?
Yes! No.
Ooh! Ow!
Keys, where are you?
Come on, show me keys!
Gotcha!
Ha-ha!
No. No!
Ow.
They were in my pocket
the whole time!
It's SpongeBob who's the problem.
I get it.
Meanwhile, at the palace
of King Poseidon…
…ruler of the Seven Seas.
Chancellor!
Yo. What's up, sire?
You sent for me?
Chancellor, look. Look at me!
3,000 years old
and check out my skin.
It's like a baby's butt.
Ageless, sire. Looking fresh.
Ha! I owe it to my subjects
to look fabulous,
don't you think?
There are other obligations, sire.
Like ruling and stuff.
Let's see…
I need your signature
on these taxes, decrees,
this here declaration of war
and my paycheck.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
Very good.
Oh, Chancellor,
when will you learn to focus
on what really matters?
A monarch's regime
is only as powerful
as his skin care regime.
Word. Mm-hm.
You know, some say I have a face
like a Greek god.
Well, you are a Greek god, so…
Whoa! Wait, is…
- Is that a wrinkle?
- Where?
It is! It's a wrinkle!
I look like an old avocado
that's been left
and forgotten in the fridge!
Here it comes.
I'm ugly!
Oh, now, where is it?
The crawly thing with
the round shell and the eyes.
Where is it?
Here you go, sire. Your Royal Snail.
Oh! Oh, oh, thank you.
This mollusk has
the rejuvenating power
of a thousand facials.
What?! Is it empty?
Take it away!
Bring me another sea snail
at once!
Uh-oh.
- Chancellor!
- Okay, uh…
Full disclosure, man, uh…
We're out of snails.
What?!
In fact, the entire
snail population has been, uh…
What's the word?
Oh, yeah… depleted.
You're telling me there are…
- no more snails?
- There are no more snails.
- And you're confident of that?
- Relatively confident.
Oh, Chancellor,
for the love of Hermes,
my kingdom for a snail!
No, no, no. I'm being hasty.
Half my kingdom for a snail!
No, no, no, a boon. Yes.
I'll grant a boon to whomever
shall bring me a snail.
Gotcha.
I'll draw up the decree, sire.
A Royal Decree
from King Poseidon?
"To all citizens of the sea,
the King requires a snail at once…
blah blah blah
skin care blah blah..."
Wait a minute.
A snail?
No, it's too perfect.
Get rid of Gary,
get rid of SpongeBob.
Oh, yeah.
Gary, I'm home!
Gare-Bear?
Hey, where are you, buddy?
Gary?
You must be in the... No.
Gary? Gary, Gary, Gary! Gary!
Gary! Where's Gary?
Gary!
Gary, where are you?
Oh, Gary.
I loved you since
the first day we met.
Hello, little snail.
What's your name?
"Gary", huh?
Well, hi, Gary.
Gary, do you want to be friends?
Me, too.
SpongeBob! SpongeBob!
Hey, SpongeBob!
I found this flyer.
Gary's missing!
I know, Patrick.
SpongeBob?
Oh, Patrick, if something were
to happen to Gary, I, well…
I don't know what I'd do.
I'm sorry, buddy.
Hey! Maybe he left a clue.
Oh!
Look! A clue!
Gary's been snailnapped!
And taken to The Lost City
of Atlantic City!
Oh, really?
That's awesome!
Now we know where he is.
Mm.
Not really that awesome, Patrick.
Listen to this.
"Made famous by the glitzy palace
Poseidon calls home.
The Lost City of Atlantic City
is a scary,
vice-ridden cesspool
of moral depravity."
Wow. All that, and it's lost, too?
"King Poseidon has proven
himself a whimsical tyrant,
known for executing his subjects
by beheading them
in a flamboyant floor show
extravaganza.
Our advice for those
travelling here is…
…don't."
This King Poseidon
sounds like a tough customer.
Oh, yeah. Tough.
Aw, so what?
This is about friends.
And friends don't let friends
become somebody else's face cream!
Not what friends do.
- So what if it's dangerous and scary?
- So what!
What is stopping me right now
from going there, rescuing Gary
and standing up to this
King Poseidon, huh?
- I don't know!
- Well, I do!
- What is it?
- I…
…don't have the courage.
Oh, Gary.
Tartar sauce!
What's the next best thing
to courage?
- Resolve?
- No.
- Fortitude?
- Nah.
- Commitment?
- Nope.
- Wherewithal? Bravery?
- Mm-mm. No.
- Valor. Grit?
- What? No.
- Heroism? Gallantry?
- Uh-uh. Nah.
- Moxie.
- A buddy! A wingman!
A wingman?
A friend.
Really, Patrick?
You'd go with me?
Yeah… right behind you!
Do I smell a road trip?
That could be my breath.
Okey-dokey.
Now, let's drill down on a plan.
Pat, you're in charge of transpo.
Just remember, I don't drive
and you don't have a car.
Oh…
Beep, beep!
Hey, boys!
Don't know if you have any use
for this old thing,
if you're going on any trips or journeys
or quests or rescue missions.
But if you are, Otto is your ticket.
Otto!
Just tell ol' Otto where you want to go
and it will take you there!
All aboard.
- You're fired.
- Cool!
A self-driving boat.
Thanks, Plankton. You're the best!
I know, I know. Bye-bye.
- Otto. Find, Gary.
- You got it.
No, Patrick.
You got to be more specific.
Otto, find Gary the snail.
Recalculating.
Ugh. Here, let me try.
Take them to
The Lost City of Atlantic City
and don't ever come back!
Never hurts to employ a little hyperbole.
It is my pleasure to serve you.
Bon voyage, boys.
I'm ready. I'm ready. They're dead.
This is gonna be like
one of those buddy movies.
We're the buddies!
Not sure that really applies,
Patrick, but...
Why not?
We're two dudes setting out
with a common goal.
We'll argue about something dumb,
fight and break up…
Only to come back together when we realize
neither could do it without the other.
It's simple yet magical.
Yeah.
It feels more to me like
the journey of a singular hero,
who against all odds,
triumphs over adversity.
I say buddy movie
and you say, oh, whatever that
dumb thing was you just said.
Oh, really? Dumb thing?
I'm dumb?
Oh, I love your sense of irony, Patrick.
Thank you.
I love my sense of ironing, too.
Maybe if your head
wasn't packed full of sand,
you could have ironing!
Well, better a head full of sand
than a head full of rocks, like yours!
Ah! That's it! Stop the car!
Yeah, stop the car, Otto!
Sorry, Patrick. Really.
I shouldn't have said
you have rocks in your head.
your brain was made of sand.
That was mean and dumb.
Okay. Let's just forget it, huh?
Never happened!
Uh-huh.
Hop on in, guys.
♪ On the road again ♪
Come on, guys.
Ha, ha, ha!
Nope.
♪ The life I love is making
Music with my friends ♪
♪ And I can't wait to get
On the road again ♪
- Krabby!
- One at a time, people.
One at a time.
Squidward, why ain't I seeing
Krabby Patties
rolling out the service window?
- Where's SpongeBob?
- How should I know?
And, frankly,
you won't find me complaining.
Heh-heh!
SpongeBob!
What's with yer lollygaggin' boy?
SpongeBob?
SpongeBob? SpongeBob?
Get out here this instant!
That's a direct order!
I don't get it.
He has never missed a workday.
Krabby Patty! Krabby Patty!
Hey! Where are my Krabby Patties?
- How should I know?
- It's coming, sir, it's coming!
Squidward, get in that kitchen
and whip up some Krabby Patties.
All right, Gertrude…
Now, what did he say?
Uh, spark her flints.
Uh, jiggle her jets.
And… oh, yes!
"The Little Griddle Who Could."
"We're fresh from the freezer,"
said the little...
- Mr. Krabs, we've got a...
- Squidward!
Ow! Save… Ow! …yourself!
Oh!
We wouldn't be in this mess
if SpongeBob was around.
Where is SpongeBob?
Where are we?
We must be dreaming!
You amuse me, SpongeBob.
Two people can't have the same dream,
let alone be in that same dream
at the same time.
That would be philosophically untenable.
Indeed. You proffer
a metaphysical conundrum.
Wait, we're talking like smart people.
This must be a dream!
Plus, we're on the surface and we're…
…breathing air, so…
…yeah!
Air?!
Hey, town up ahead!
"Goner Gulch."
Ha! That's a funny name.
"The Inferno Saloon."
"Ye who enter here abandon all hope."
Guess that's another way
of saying "no public restrooms".
Hello?
- Otto, keep it close.
- Yeah, don't go anywhere.
Go anywhere.
It is my pleasure to serve.
You're fired.
Oh! How are we gonna find Gary now?
Maybe Otto just went to park.
Hello.
Who are you?
I am a simple tumbleweed.
Call me Sage.
- Sage.
- Hey, Sage. Good name.
Thanks. I'm made out of sage,
and I am a sage.
So it works out pretty well.
I'm Patrick!
My name means "toaster" in Celtic.
Pretty sure it doesn't.
This dream you share
has a hidden purpose, young seekers.
Oh! So we are in a dream!
And I, friend, am the dream weaver.
♪ Ohh, dream weaver… ♪
Whoa, are you inside our minds right now?
- Yes, Patrick.
- Wow!
I am here to help you
on your journey, SpongeBob.
But first, you must accept a challenge.
But, I just want to find Gary
and bring him home.
- Do you love Gary?
- More than anything!
And, young sponge,
once you meet this challenge
you may pass on
to find your precious Gary.
- Got it. Right.
- Oh, right, that makes sense.
Eww.
Take this challenge coin.
Challenge coin!
It will give you courage
when bravery is in short supply.
- Whoa!
- Cool!
Now, your challenge lies behind
these saloon doors.
- Let's go! Come on, Patrick.
- Wait.
- Let's kill this challenge.
- Wait, guys!
Challenge coin coming through!
I didn't give you your challenge!
Patience, Sage. Patience.
Huh.
Oh, cool.
One of those old player pianos.
Or…
one of those old piano players!
Scary people!
Flesh-eating cowboy pirate zombies,
to be precise.
Flesh-eating
cowboy pirate zombies?!
This is your challenge.
Free these zombies
from their earthly binds
and release their souls.
If this weren't a dream,
I'd be freaking out right now!
Oh, yeah!
We are in a dream.
La, la-la, la-la, la, la.
Okay, everyone!
We're here to release
your imprisoned souls.
What was that?
Ah, El Diablo the Wicked approaches.
♪ El Diablo
El Diablo ♪
♪ Very bad man ♪
El Diablo?
Master of this zombie crew.
- Uh-oh.
- He sounds bad.
Good luck.
Patrick, the zombies are swarming!
They're gonna eat our brains!
♪ Dance! ♪
♪ Boss Dogg ♪
♪ Even when I'm on
I'm off, y'all ♪
♪ Lookin' for the King
It'll cost y'all ♪
♪ You better leave now
are you lost, dawg? ♪
♪ The Zombie King
Yeah, I hear him coming ♪
♪ OG ghoul with a thirst
For the run-in ♪
♪ You in the wrong bar
Wrong town ♪
♪ Got a spot to fill ♪
♪ The real deal
Coming down that hill ♪
♪ Your brains for breakfast ♪
♪ Soul on the menu
Major checklist ♪
♪ Ghouls, goblins
Guard the exit ♪
♪ The fire in his eyes
Ain't hard to catch it ♪
♪ El Diablo, the haunting
Taunting veterano ♪
♪ It's scary, I know ♪
♪ The Goner Gulch
Where the drama is ♪
♪ But don't hate the game
We in the zombie biz ♪
- ♪ We feel the love ♪
- ♪ Yes, sir ♪
- ♪ When we all dance together ♪
- ♪ What? What? What? ♪
♪ Together ♪
♪ We made it, made it
Up all life long ♪
♪ We won't stop… ♪
♪ El Diablo is here! ♪
- ♪ Dance! ♪
- ♪ We the baddest crew ♪
- ♪ Hands high! ♪
- ♪ What's eating you? ♪
- ♪ Us! ♪
- ♪ We comin' through ♪
♪ Killing it is how we do! ♪
♪ El Diablo's on his way
Smell the odor of decay ♪
♪ Dance, we came to slay ♪
♪ 'Cause killing it
Is how we do! ♪
What did I tell you about
dancing when I'm not here?!
But, boss, it's Freestyle Friday!
Oh. Okay, my bad.
Hey. Yo, SpongeBob? I got to dip.
Y'all got this.
Bring the prisoners to my office.
Huh. What'd that guy mean by prisoners?
So, you dare to enter
the ghost town of the damned,
barge into my demon's lair…
telling my zombies…
that you're gonna free their souls…
like it ain't no thing!
Well, uh, Mr. Diablo,
the good thing is we're in a dream.
- A shared dream.
- Right, a shared dream.
So there's no need to get
all bent out of shape about it.
- It's not real!
- 'Cause it's a dream.
Who told you that?
That crazy bush guy?
- Uh…
- Maybe.
What he should've told you was
it's not a dream!
He might be right, Patrick.
That felt pretty real.
Yeah, that really hurt.
Run!
Hang on, Patrick.
Foul demon, be gone!
What the heck is that?
Huh?
What do I look like, a parking meter?
But Sage said...
Coin laundry's right down the street.
That's pathetic!
Get away from those curtains!
- What? These curtains?
- Oh, these are nice curtains.
Oh, they are. So soft.
That's weird.
These curtains are making a strange sound.
I think the curtain rod needs some oil.
Once the rod goes,
you're probably better off
getting a whole new set of curtains.
Oh, Mr. Diablo,
do you have any other cur...
Oh!
Patrick, I think we should
get out of here!
Hey, everybody!
El Diablo says he doesn't want
to be disturbed.
Yeah, he's feeling a little burnt…
- …out.
- Toodle-oo!
- Buh-bye!
- See you!
Take care!
Thank ye, SpongeBob.
We're finally free!
Huh?
Adiós, mateys!
- Thanks, SpongeBob.
- We're finally free.
Good luck on your journey, boys.
Do you know what this means?
We passed the challenge!
Now we can find Gary! Yay!
♪ El Diablo
El Diablo ♪
Otto!
Howdy, partners.
Wait! Can't forget the "courage."
- It's him!
- Yikes!
Come on, Otto. Let's go!
Come on, come on, Otto!
- Step on it, Otto! Go! Go!
- Faster! Go faster!
Go, Otto, go!
♪ Very bad man ♪
Faster!
Wake up. Your dream is fired.
- Faster
-Huh? Oh!
Phew! We're back on the bottom.
See, Patrick?
It must have been a dream.
More of a vision really.
- Sage?
- Oh. Hi, Sage.
- Hello.
- You are real.
As real as your desire
to see that which you cannot.
Yeah, well, that which
I cannot see is Gary.
I got to know what's happening.
This wish I grant you.
Through the mystical fabric
of the fourth dimension,
you may now view what's happening
at the same time as things
are happening to you.
Behold. The Window of Meanwhile.
The Window of Meanwhile!
What's it do?
It's like the Video On Demand
service of parallel action.
Have a look.
- Whoa…
- Hey, Patrick. Down in front.
Look, Patrick, there he is!
Yeah, he looks all right.
Hey, Gary!
He doesn't look so bad.
He looks pretty comfy!
- No reason to panic.
- Yeah!
He looks like he's well taken care of.
Look what I found. Snail time.
Hello, precious.
Gary?
I hope you don't run out of juice,
or you'll end up like the others.
What?!
Oh, yes.
- Gary! Gary, hello?
- Gary!
Okay, the Window of Meanwhile
doesn't really work that way.
- Gary, run! Get out of there!
- Gary!
It's not a video chat app like
Skype or FaceTime, or anything.
- We got to hurry! Gary!
- Over here! Gary!
Totally can't hear you.
Hello!
Hello, Eugene, old friend!
How's business?
Bad? Good.
Well, that's restaurants for you, huh?
Feast or famine.
But I digress.
Why don't you be a good little loser
and hand over the secret formula?
Take it. It's yours.
Wha…
Take it all.
Wait…
You're giving up?
Oh, Plankton…
I wouldn't expect you to understand.
But somehow, without SpongeBob,
this whole thing…
just doesn't make sense anymore!
You can't do that.
I've spent my entire career
waiting for this moment
and you roll over like a harpooned whale?
I won't let you rob me of my vengeance!
Give my regards to your lovely wife.
Huh.
This doesn't, uh…
feel quite as good as, uh…
Yay, I won.
Congratulations.
You have arrived at your destination.
The Lost City of Atlantic City!
It's pretty.
Beware, young seekers.
All is distortion.
If you aren't careful,
The Lost City will draw you
into her fickle embrace,
blind you with her dazzling distractions
and tempt you with her
fleeting games of chance.
Whatever you do, don't be led astray,
don't lose focus
and don't forget why you came here.
- Don't forget. Good one.
- Thanks, Sage-meister.
- I think we got this.
- Yeah, Sage.
I mean, you've been pretty good
up until now, but,
I love Gary more than anything
in the whole world!
And we came here to get him back.
Okay.
I wouldn't worry about us
losing any focus.
Oh, boy.
We got focus to burn, baby...
Whoa!
- Cotton candy!
- Ice cream!
Churros!
- Oh! Oh! Oh!
- Yay!
Yumm!
What's up?
Isn't it cool how they let you
trade in your real money
for these little plastic circles?
I love money!
Casinos are magical.
Would you mind if I put this down, sir?
Place it wherever you like.
Just put it on L.
Patrick, that's not an L, that's a seven.
Seven starts with an L?
That's weird.
Seven!
More plastic circles!
- Who are you guys?
- We're your entourage.
♪ Upside, inside out ♪
♪ She's livin' la vida loca ♪
Place your bets.
Come on, seven!
Lucky seven! Winner!
♪ Living la vida loca! ♪
Seven! Seven! Seven!
Seven. Seven. Seven.
- Hey, Patrick!
- What's up, Spongey-Dawg?
- I lost all my money.
- Me, too!
Party people!
Oh. Where is everybody?
I feel like I swallowed a sea urchin.
Me, too.
Hey, I did swallow a sea urchin!
Well, well, well.
Sagester! Good to see ya, pal!
Nice work, boys.
Way to take my pearls of wisdom
and flush them down the toilet.
Oh, no. Wait, did we…?
Lose focus like I told you not to?
Focus? Huh.
Let me jangle your minds.
You came here to get back
something you lost.
- Uh…
- Hm.
Something you love.
Gary!
Yeah, Gary.
Seriously, it's hard enough
being stuck in a tumbleweed…
Patrick, we got to find Gary!
…but dealing with you two makes me
want to light myself on fire.
Sage, buddy.
Can we please look into
the Window of Meanwhile
one more time to see where Gary is?
No, it's not an on-demand service.
And especially not for people who pass out
and sleep in their own vomit all night.
It's not vomit. It's drool.
Fortunately for you,
you woke up right here.
On the steps of Poseidon's Palace.
- Whoa.
- Wow.
Now get it together. Go!
All right, Gary. We're coming for ya!
Boy, oh, boy. Hey…
Almost there, Gary.
Hey, hop on!
They're just giving these things
away at the grocery store.
Good call, buddy.
Hot stuff coming through!
Get a load of this place, Patrick.
Hello.
We would like an audience
with His Majesty King Poseidon.
Oh, sure. Let me check.
Two rubes to see Poseidon. No.
Hey, dude. We're the Blue Fin Group.
Of course. Right this...
The Blue Fin Group! No!
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm Tiffany Haddock
and I'm here just for the halibut.
Ha-ha-ha!
Whoo-hoo!
All right then.
Our next performers are gonna knock...
Poseidon?
We are getting an audience with the King.
Well, let's have it. Perform, please!
♪ Hey! Aka Waka Maka Mia ♪
♪ Was a puffer fish ♪
♪ Being bigger than a puffer
Was his only wish ♪
♪ And so he huffed, he puffed ♪
♪ He billowed and he blew ♪
Gary!
Gary, I'm coming, buddy!
Excuse me. Sorry. My bad. Whoop.
Sorry. Whoa!
Hi, there! Excuse me, King Poseidon, sire.
There's been a misunderstanding
about Gary.
Gary?
- Gary.
- Gary?
The snail that you're rubbing
all over your face right now.
Nonsense. Besides,
this snail's name is Fred.
"Fred?" You renamed Gary?
- Fred.
- Gary.
- Fred! Fred!
- Gary! Gary!
- Fred!
- Gary!
Fred!
Seize them!
Gary!
But Gary loves me! And I love him.
Yeehaw!
Incoming!
Whoa!
Good rockets.
SpongeBob?
Get yer co-pilot goggles, dude,
'cause we're goin' sleddin'!
SpongeBob?
You in here?
SpongeBob!
Huh. That's weird.
Something's fishy around here.
All right, what'd y'all do with SpongeBob?
We don't know where he is, Sandy.
Hasn't been here in days.
Don't you play coy with me, cephalopod.
And you, arthropod!
Start talking. Where is he?
Tied up in the basement?
Stuffed in your trunk?
Nay, I could never harm the lad.
His absence has taught me that much.
And I'm not just talking about
the money I'm losing with him gone.
Hmm…
Okay, fifty percent
talking about the money
and fifty percent talking about
I truly miss the boy.
Aw.
I hate to admit it, but things
just aren't the same without him.
There's no denying it. We need SpongeBob.
Did anyone ever stop to think
that he might need us?
This is Perch Perkins coming to you
from The Lost City of Atlantic City.
I'm standing on the strip outside
Poseidon's Palace and Casino,
where two suspects have been
taken into custody tonight…
…following an attempt on the Royal Snail.
The sponge and sea star were
impersonating a lounge act
when they made an attempt
on Poseidon's prize mollusk.
It's Gary!
The suspects' vehicle was apprehended
after a high-speed chase.
Mr. Krabs. What happened to Otto?
Well, he took an automated vacation!
In a related story, Poseidon's Palace
presents a command performance,
featuring the execution
of the suspects in the Aqua Room
this Friday night.
Execution of the suspects?
What happened to habeas swordfish?
It's a fun-filled family event,
with opening act Kelpy G.
One performance only,
tickets still available.
- We've got to go help them!
- We embark immediately.
Excuse me.
Can I tag along?
Plankton?
What have you got to do with this?
I… I…
I might have had a teensy-weensy
hand in a very...
Yeah, yeah,
we'll hear about it in the car.
Mr. Squidward, are ya coming?
Ha! Fat chance.
Fat chance I'd miss
a Kelpy G performance. I'm in.
To the Pattymobile!
What, this old tub?
Never judge a Pattymobile
by its bun, Squidward.
Let's light this puppy!
Yeehaw!
Mommy!
Huh? SpongeBob?
Are you okay?
Hey, buddy. Sorry about this.
It's not your fault, Patrick.
You've been a true friend this whole time.
Never wavered, never faltered. It's just…
I failed, that's all!
And I'll never see
innocent little Gary again.
Oh, my heart is broken!
Oh, come on now.
Buck up. It's not over yet, SpongeBob.
It sure feels over. And crappy.
Just saying there's
two sides to every coin.
Oh, Patrick, what does a coin have to...
Wait, did you just say "coin"?
Me? Uh, don't think so.
You did. You said "coin"!
Not remembering that exactly.
- Hello?
- The challenge coin! Of course!
Oh, don't you see, Patrick? We're saved!
I said hello.
Patrick, it's gone!
Meh. Was the challenge coin
really that useful?
Hello?
Oh! Stupid prank callers.
Hey, wait a sec.
I gave it to you, remember?
For safe keeping.
No.
Come on, it was last night!
We were at the crappie tables.
Winner! Place your bets.
Come on, seven! Come on, seven!
Come on, seven!
You!
You gambled away my challenge coin!
You wrecked our entire mission
with one stupid bet!
Well, only after you kept saying…
Let it ride, Patrick! Let it ride!
- Whoo!
- But, SpongeBob…
What if you need
the challenge coin tomorrow
to help you summon your courage?
Tomorrow is for weenies!
Whoo!
Well, it's tomorrow and guess
who's the weenie.
I… can't…
believe you!
You can't believe me?
Are you serious right now?
Well! Maybe you can believe this.
I'm out of here!
And don't come back!
Oh, don't worry, I won't!
- Good!
- Ever!
- Fine!
- Super!
Hey, losers.
Oh, hey, Sage.
Sage, glad you're here.
Guess who gambled away my challenge coin.
Guess who blames everyone else
for his troubles.
Enough!
Did I mention you are
the worst epic heroes
for whom I have ever been a spirit guide?
Um, I think we went over that
this morning.
I believe we did, yeah.
SpongeBob, the coin was just a symbol.
The courage you seek is inside you,
not in the coin.
And it will come to you
in your hour of need.
But isn't this my hour of need?
Oh, no.
It gets way worse.
Bye!
- Worse?
- Dude said way worse.
Prepare the prisoners.
Oh, that couldn't be for us.
It's your big moment to fry…
I mean, shine.
It is for us, Patrick!
We're gonna die!
And that's how I got SpongeBob
out of Bikini Bottom.
- Why, that's monstrous!
- Wait, that sounds good.
- Oh, brother.
- What do you expect? I'm evil.
Let's just focus on the plan.
We're approaching
The Lost City of Atlantic City.
Make way there, make way!
Oh!
Eww.
"Sponge and Star Execution Extravaganza"?
No time to lose!
Woop, woop, woop! Ladies and gentlefish,
welcome to the Aqua Room, y'all.
The greatest show underwater.
My groupies and groupers…
- We love you, Tiffany!
- Yeah holler at your girl!
Are you ready to be entertained?
Hmm? I can't hear you.
All right, then,
let's meet the contestants.
In this corner, a sponge and a star…
…two of the ocean's
most notorious criminals!
And in this corner,
representing His Majesty the King,
Poseidon's very own Chancellor!
Now drum roll, maestro.
Put your fins together
for the duke of the dirty deed,
the earl of execution,
that axe-wielding maniac…
…oh, yeah, Lemont!
Lamont! Lamont! Lamont!
Oh, I love me some Lemont.
Mm, mm, mm. He's so strong.
Ladies and gentlemen,
with a moment of smooth jazz
in memory of the soon-to-be-goners,
I give you Kelpy G.
Oh, Patrick, I feel terrible.
I dragged you into this whole mess.
It's okay, SpongeBob.
I made a plea deal with the prosecution!
Oh, that's good... Wait, you did what?
All I have to do is, uh… oh, yeah!
"Bring incriminating evidence
against the defendant."
Patrick, I'm the defendant.
You are? Oh.
Let the proceedings begin!
Your Honor, I would like
to enter into evidence
Fred.
- Gary!
- How dare you!
That's about all I can say.
How dare you come here
to the sanctuary of our revered sovereign,
to rob him of his very lifeblood,
his adorable good looks.
Go on.
How indeed dare you.
Guilty!
Lemont! Lemont! Lemont!
Hold it!
If it please the court,
I'd like to say something
in SpongeBob's defense.
It does not please the court.
Sit down, squirrel with fishbowl on head.
But, sire, a strong defense
makes for a better show.
Isn't that right, audience?
All right, all right! I'll allow it.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Ladies and gentlemen,
SpongeBob has always been there for me.
Even going all the way back
to summer camp.
In fact, that's where we all met.
I'm…
Ow! Ah! Ooh! Ooh!
Ready!
Look at all the cool activities!
Camping. Canoeing.
Seahorse-back riding!
Tug-of-war. Whale watching.
Do you mind?
Juggling contests. Shrink-wrap soccer!
And more.
Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
Hey, y'all critters of the sea!
Look out below!
I'm Sandy Cheeks from Texas.
Hi, Sandy. I'm SpongeBob.
Pleased to meet ya.
Does everybody wear spacesuits in Texas?
They do if they want to visit
you underwater critters.
We all breathe air on the surface.
It's just our way of synthesizing oxygen.
Same as you do with water.
Whoa. Are you a scientist?
Naw, I'm just a squirrel.
I can't be a scientist.
Even though it's kind of my dream.
Sandy Cheeks, you take that back!
I bet you can do anything.
Really? Wow.
Me a scientist?
Science.
You're a hoot, little dude.
I'd be just as likely to live down here
in a glass dome with a tree in it.
- Ha-ha!
- You never know!
Ow.
He's the one that told me,
no matter who I was or where I came from,
I should follow my dream.
That's a friend, people.
And that's why, in my eyes…
SpongeBob is no criminal.
He's the best little fella
to ever walk the sea bottom. And that's…
That's just how I feel about it. So…
Please, don't hurt him.
Aww…
This man broke the law!
"You should stay home
and accept the fact
that somebody stole your snail."
"There's probably
nothing I can do about it."
Well, in this sea star's opinion,
those laws should be broken
and SpongeBob is proof of it!
All he's guilty of
is having the fortitude
to try and rescue a friend.
How do I know?
Oh, I was just a lonely bump on a log
when I first met him.
Hi, my name...
Hello my name is SpongeBob,
what's your name?
I'm Pa-Pa-Patrick.
Why are you crying, Pa-Pa-Patrick?
I'm homesick.
Well, that's a pretty good reason.
Maybe all you need is a friend.
I don't have any friends!
- Well, you've got one now.
- Really?
- Who is it?
- It's me!
- Do you mean it?
- Of course. Come on!
That sweet little sponge
rescued this miserable little sea star.
And things haven't changed
that much today, Your Honor.
My heart, buddy.
I don't like SpongeBob.
In fact, I revile him.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Anyway, I, too, met this nabob
in summer camp.
I remember it like it was yesterday.
It was my big night.
The Annual Camp Coral Talent Show.
And first prize was the coveted
Campy Award.
Thank you, Larry.
Remember, people, don't forget to vote.
As far as I was concerned,
the trophy was as good as mine.
- Hey, Squidward...
- Bup, bup, bup, bup.
Quiet. I'm in pregame right now.
I've got an award to win.
♪ La, la-la-la, loo! ♪
♪ La-la ♪
♪ Aka Waka Maka Mia
Was a puffer fish ♪
The Campy is mine.
I bathed the audience
with the sounds of my
heavenly clarinet playing.
Thank you, Squidward. Just lovely.
Thank you, thank you.
And the Campy goes to…
I'll take that.
- …SpongeBob and Patrick!
- Huh?
No! No! No!
This isn't happening!
No! Mommy!
I was robbed.
And never to play the clarinet again.
No…
- Squidward!
- Go away!
Patrick and I were, um,
talking to one of the counselors
and guess what?
There was a big mistake and you
actually won the Campy Award!
That's right. Yup.
- I… I did?
- In a landslide.
Hmm.
So weird they would've
miscounted like that.
- But I guess it's possible...
- Yay!
- Nice work, Squidward.
- No one deserves it more.
Wow.
And don't ever stop playing this.
My clarinet.
Look at me. I really did it!
Yay!
Which is why, even though
I can't stand SpongeBob…
but at the same time, well…
I love him.
I love him
- and I hate him.
- Oh.
He's like ice cream with salt on it,
because he's sweet and super annoying.
He's nice and
nails-on-chalkboard annoying!
Okay, fine, he's mostly
super freaking annoying.
But, this little nattering noodge…
is my friend.
And he doesn't deserve to die.
I'll be saying my piece now,
if it be pleasing the court.
I suppose I could stand up here
and tell you how
SpongeBob changed me life.
But, I won't.
I might even speak
about how he inspired me
when I was just a small-time vendor
with a broken-down luncheonette.
But I won't.
Heck, I'd probably mention
how he encouraged me
to start up me own restaurant.
You should open up
your own restaurant, someday.
The Krusty Krab, made famous
by me delicious Krabby Patties!
Two-for-one Wednesdays,
by the way. Pass these around.
But, I won't.
Nay, you'll hear none such praise from me.
Because it wouldn't do him full justice.
It wouldn't begin to describe
the size of the lad's heart.
Which is huge.
And he puts that heart
into everything he does.
The cooking…
- Order up!
- …cleaning…
…serving up the delicious
Krabby Patties.
But that's the funny thing.
I used to think
me secret Krabby Patty formula
was also the secret to me success.
We serve breakfast till 11,
by the way, 12 on weekends.
It wasn't until SpongeBob
came to work for me
that I realized the formula
is more than just a list of ingredients
and flavor-capturing methods.
It's more than a jealously
guarded recipe.
The real secret formula
is sitting right here.
SpongeBob SquarePants.
Aww…
Get ready.
Ahem! Maestro?
♪ A formula is something
Like a recipe ♪
♪ A recipe is something
Like a plan ♪
♪ With elements and measurements ♪
♪ All mixed together by a steady hand ♪
♪ But careful you must be
Or you'll be sad you see ♪
♪ If somehow in the mix
It has no soul ♪
♪ So what's the one ingredient ♪
♪ That turns this awesome sauce
To liquid gold? ♪
I'll tell ya!
♪ The secret to the formula
Is you, you ♪
♪ You, you ♪
♪ The honey in my tea, you know
Is you, you ♪
♪ You, you ♪
♪ The bubbles in the boil ♪
♪ The one essential oil
It's true ♪
♪ The secret to the formula
Is you, you ♪
- SpongeBob!
- ♪ You, you ♪
♪ What in the wide watery world ♪
♪ Would it be like without you? ♪
♪ The secret to the formula
Is you, you ♪
♪ You, you ♪
♪ The honey in my tea, you know
Is you, you ♪
♪ You, you ♪
♪ The bubbles in the boil ♪
♪ The one essential oil
It's true ♪
♪ The secret to the formula
Is you, you ♪
- SpongeBob!
- ♪ You, you ♪
♪ The secret to the formula ♪
♪ Is you, you ♪
So entertaining!
♪ The secret to the formula
Is you, you ♪
♪ You, you ♪
Yeehaw!
Ha! Hilarious!
Hmm?
My snail!
Wha...? Huh?
Halt! It's a trick! Seize them!
Gary, you're with me now.
I'll never let anyone take you again.
Faster!
Oh!
Wow.
Yah! Patrick, what are you doing?
Free food!
Get him!
Come on, come on. In here!
Stop right there!
Inside! Quick!
Come on!
Uh-oh.
Push! Push, Plankton!
You got to be kidding me!
Hah!
Hmm?
Peekaboo!
Attack!
Ha-hah!
Whoa!
Watch your left flank, people!
Thrust! Now parry!
Now pirouette.
Turn around. Pivot!
Pull harder. Faster!
To the right!
Hi-ya!
Whoa, whoa!
Do you think we should've
stayed in there with Squidward?
Nah, he's got it.
Where is everybody?!
Charge!
Whoa!
Squidward!
Squidward! Fall this way!
No, this way!
Oh.
Man down.
Good catch.
- Hey, there they are!
- Get them!
Yo, what's up?
Otto!
I have a gambling problem.
Could anyone lend me some money?
To Bikini Bottom!
And step on it!
Stepping on it.
You're all fired.
To the valet!
Ah!
Leaving so soon, kids?
Hang on, Gary.
I won't let you go.
Tsk, tsk. Rather impolite,
don't you think?
It was all their idea, sire.
And I…
…loved it!
Wait, so you're not mad at us?
No!
It's been a while since I've enjoyed
such toe-tapping entertainment.
All is forgiven!
- And all charges are dropped.
- Hooray!
On one condition.
SpongeBob will return my snail to me
without any more shilly-shally.
Wait, what?
Just hand over the snail
and you can all go free.
But… I… I…
SpongeBob.
Sage? Is that you?
Hello.
Sage! Hi!
Remember…
The courage you seek
is inside you.
And it will come to you
in your hour of need.
The courage is inside me.
The courage is inside me!
Mr. Poseidon, no.
I'm sorry, but I won't do it.
What?
I love Gary too much,
and he loves me.
If we didn't have each other,
we'd be so sad. Well…
It wouldn't really matter
what you'd do to us.
And look. Today, thanks to these
amazing friends,
my heart feels twice as big
a s it ever did.
Especially after what they risked for me:
Flouting the law and defying
the mighty king of the sea.
Defying? Really?
I wouldn't say defying the king.
Humiliating you in front of your subjects.
- Do go on.
- More like admiring.
And totally agreeing with!
I just came to see Kelpy G.
And they did it all for me.
I'm sure you'd understand
if you had friends like these.
Friends like these?
Wait, what?
Of course I have
friends like these.
I have all kinds of friends!
I have buddies, I have besties.
I have home-slices, palsy-walsies.
It's infinite!
Chancellor! Give us an exact number.
The friend count, if you will.
Uh, okay,
according to your latest polling data,
we should get more polling data.
What? Give me that.
Huh?
What about my adoring fans?
- Nope.
- My elite palace guards?
Mm-mm.
- What about my personal trainer?
- Mmm… Mm-mm.
- My therapist?
- Nada.
- My tattoo artist?
- Uh…nope.
- My tattoo removal artist?
- No dice.
B-But surely you, my chancellor,
my loyal faithful…?
Sorry.
Apollo, take me now.
I don't have any friends!
Well, you got one now!
Really? Who is it?
It's me! I'll be your friend.
Do you mean it?
Yes. But friends don't kidnap
friends' pet snails.
But I need that snail.
Look, I have a horrible,
disgusting wrinkle.
Jumping jellyfish,
it's the size of the Mariana Trench!
Kidding!
Looks don't matter.
We don't care about little imperfections.
Or even big ones!
- Just look at Squidward.
- What's that supposed to mean?
What's important is what's inside.
And I'm sure you can be
a fair and kind king
to all the creatures of the sea.
I know you've got it in you, sir.
If you'd just let your hair down a little.
Huh? My hair? Wait a minute.
Are you suggesting that I don't need this
gorgeous mane of wavy locks?
That I don't require this neck clip?
Be gone, perfect shiny teeth!
This is so freeing!
To heck with this chest plate and girdle.
- Oh, wow.
- Too far?
No! Not at all!
No, you look great!
Oh, thank you!
I find this so exhilarating.
So… age appropriate.
SpongeBob, few possess the courage
to stand up to a powerful king.
You, sir, are among those few.
I salute you.
Nailed it, SpongeBob.
Sage out.
You may keep Gary.
And I wish you many happy years together.
Thank you!
Did you hear that, Gare-Bear?
Uh, your royal robe, Your Highness.
- It's getting cold out here.
- Nonsense, Chancellor.
I'm free!
Ooh, you certainly are.
And free the snails!
What's that?
All of them?
I'm home!
Hello, Gary.
Hello, Brian.
Hello, Janet. Hello, June.
Hola, Lupe.
- Morning, Sally!
- Hi, Brett!
Come on, Gary! You can do it!
Yeah!
Fabio! Where are you, buddy?
Here, Fabio, Fabio, Fabio!
Come on, Fifi. No.
Order up!
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org