Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Another bonus!
The islamic Republic now has
3,000 centrifuges,
2,700 more than those known
of up to present day,
and enough, say experts,
to make an atomic bomb within a year.
The president of Iran denies this
and once again insists
that they are only for enriching uranium
for peaceful purposes.
Give me a dash of anisette.
Anisette?
Yeah, a dash. To kill the taste.
Fuck you to hell and back!
What brand?
Doesn't matter, what you've got.
Anis del mono.
We're out of mono.
None left.
Some change.
And give me another.
And expect violence from
young anti-system protesters.
Which have invariably accompanied
the latest summits.
Although border controls
have been tightened,
around a thousand
of violent protesters
are in the city.
Now for the sports news.
- Good evening.
- Good evening, David.
We begin with information
from the teams in the capital.
- Fucking turn that down.
- Madrid lost.
Fuck 'em.
Sir, that's 34 Euros.
- We've got to close up.
- One last one.
Boss, we should've closed up
half an hour ago.
You should go home and rest.
Fuck you both.
Come and get me, you bastards.
Come and get me,
if you've got the balls.
We're closed.
You've got the music on.
There you go. Closed.
The girls have already gone.
You're still here.
Colombian, right?
Spanish.
Get me a rum and coke, honey.
She's not getting anything.
We're closed.
What do you bet?
Get me that drink, cutie.
I'm telling you to leave.
The easy way.
See? I am getting that drink.
Now get me that rum and coke.
Good evening.
Excuse me, but they have to be
strict about the hours.
You understand, don't you?
Ingrid, get the inspector a drink.
And one for me too.
Scotch.
Neat.
It's a shame you've come so late.
We've got some stunning girls.
You must come one evening.
On the house, of course.
Ingrid, get the inspector
another drink.
Don't worry, my friend.
We all have bad days.
Can you put me through
to Hugo anglada's room?
He's not in?
Can you tell me
the room number, please?
Thank you.
Yes, Ana.
I'm in a traffic jam.
What?
Where's that?
One shot in the back.
Two in this one.
In the shoulder and the head,
point blank to finish the job.
He's got a broken nose.
Maybe pushed into
the bar first, there's blood.
This one was shot
at very close range.
Sorry.
What's this?
Three dead by gunshot.
No papers.
For now, we've only found
papers for the woman.
And no shells.
What's that smell?
These places smell like that, ma'am.
Take a look outside,
see if the car turns up.
- The disc, do we have it?
- No. It was taken away.
I saw a camera at the entrance
to the industrial estate.
It hasn't worked for three years.
We've found another.
Verénica Garcia.
She turned up in valencia.
She's been arrested
for setting fire to a car.
Right, the destinations
for back-up at the summit.
You and rubio, you're on watch
at the German embassy.
- You know I can't run.
- That's why.
Alvaro, you and herrera
take the odd numbers.
Marta and Lorenzo,
all doorways from 2 to 12.
Check the residents,
windows, the usual.
You two,
watch on the Italian embassy.
This time, you're calling the family.
- Where are you going?
- I'll call you later.
Yes, that's me.
You told the inspector
you saw a man.
I was surprised to see someone
at that hour, so I looked at him.
He was your height.
He wore a black leather jacket
and had long hair. He got into a car.
A dark man.
Can you confirm that
it was 5:15 A.M.?
Yes, ma'am.
I always get to work then.
Did you notice the car?
That man scared me,
and I hurried along.
Are you sure
you didn't see anyone else?
I'm sure, ma'am. Just that man.
Thanks a lot.
Your testimony
will be of great use to us.
- Can 1 go?
- You can go. Thanks very much.
Thank you.
It's a citroén xantia.
The model's a few years old.
I had the family model.
Pedro vargas cartagena,
alias "the old man", age 59.
Colombian, from Cali.
He's been in Spain since 2003.
Married to
Maria Fernanda olmedo Sanchez.
The club is in her name.
He was involved in
a cocaine-trafficking case in 2004.
The other body is still unidentified.
We're crossing prints with interpol.
Ballistics says all the shots
are from the same gun, a 38.
- Have any mobile phones turned up?
- No.
Talk to his wife.
Everyone's got a mobile.
She's to give us the number.
Ana, prepare a warrant
for the phone company.
What's the time?
8:20.
It's time to go home.
Hey!
What's up?
Have you seen rachid?
Who?
I don't know you.
I don't know you either.
I'm looking for rachid.
He hasn't been round here
for a while.
Is he still with Celia?
I don't know.
Go ask her.
Can we go?
Hello, Celia.
Fuck! You gave me a fright!
What do you want?
I saw you dancing
and thought you might
let me have a drink.
That's what I've got.
- No rum?
- No.
Where's rachid?
Rachid... where is he?
In the wardrobe.
You don't mind, do you?
Is it coke?
Horse.
You want to chase the dragon?
No.
Is he still in business
with the Colombians?
I don't know,
and I don't want to know.
But if you find him,
tell him I'm throwing his shit
in the trash.
Call him.
That's an old number.
I don't have his current one.
You still haven't told me
why you're after him.
I miss him.
Are you still with
that dark-haired honey?
Nobody wants me.
I feel so sorry for you.
Colombian. Wanted for murder
in Holland, France and Italy.
We don't know which identity
he was working under.
We're looking for all three.
Around 300,000 Euros.
Thanks, Ana.
300,000 Euros, here...? No, huh?
No.
In the end I had to talk
to the blonde's mother.
I'm fucking sick of
swallowing all the shit.
What, did you choose
the biggest loser in the department?
Go fuck yourself.
Go on, complain, kid. I would.
Maybe you'll get me kicked off
at long fucking last.
What time do we get relieved?
We've got seven hours to go.
Route 21, metropolitan police.
Three buses on fire
in the university district.
They appear to be gathering there.
Fuck the world.
Since when do you
listen to "pachanga"?
What's this shit?
You're not doing blow?
You and Mr. vargas were partners?
We did some business in the past.
Pedro was a friend of my dad.
And now? What was your link
to Mr. vargas lately?
More personal than anything else.
Like family.
Have they identified
the other victims?
Where were you on the night
of Sunday march 7th?
In Rome.
I'm expanding my food business.
In which hotel?
The excelsior.
Was Mr. vargas linked to
cocaine trafficking?
People always think that Colombian
and trafficker are the same thing.
Answer the question.
Was he linked to cocaine trafficking?
I don't know,
but I don't think so.
Do you know if Mr. vargas
had any personal enemies?
He didn't have any enemies.
Don Pedro was a good guy.
Was Mr. vargas into any other
business besides club ladies?
Maybe. I can't tell you for sure.
- Were you partners in club ladies?
- No. I'm into import-export.
Foods, mostly.
The hotel trade, normal stuff.
You're also the owner of
some nightclubs, sala machuca,
and club cartagena.
What kind of places are they?
Dance halls.
Latin atmosphere.
Meeting spots, and for parties.
They're not brothels.
That's not my business.
In 2004 you and Mr. vargas
were involved in
an investigation into
the traffic of narcotics.
Cocaine, isn't that right?
We had nothing to do with that.
That was dropped, ma'am.
There was nothing in it.
Yes. This is Ana.
Yes, leiva.
I'll tell her right now.
If you intend to leave the country
in the next few days,
advise this office beforehand.
Leiva.
Hi, raman, it's leiva.
What's up?
Like everybody else,
don't you complain.
We've got a car, in the car park.
Do me a favor
and check out a passenger list.
Take this down:
Rome-Madrid flight.
October 3rd, one of yours.
Number 1951.
51, yes. At 5:15 P.M.
Yes. Send me a fax to chamartin.
To the hotel, yes.
Thanks.
Did you get the GPS?
No.
Do you recall if
it turned up at the club?
No, no GPS turned up.
- What about upstairs?
- No.
Request the tapes for
the last 72 hours, the whole hotel.
Inspector leiva?
- Your fax arrived.
- Thanks.
Ana, get me the narcotics bureau.
Ask for cerdan.
You're losing form.
Those are just targets.
As the date of
the g-20 summit approaches,
pressure increases from
the ant-globalization groups.
In the university district,
throughout the day,
violent confrontations have ensued.
But we must also report
another kind of violence in Madrid.
Two of the victims of
club ladies massacre
in the early hours of yesterday
have been identified.
A Colombian man
and a naturalized Spanish woman.
Antonio, get on home.
You're pretty far gone.
Come on.
First theories indicate
a possible payback
between mafias
in the white slave trade.
What's up, honey?
What can I get you?
Nothing, thanks.
We're going. See you tomorrow!
- See you!
- See you tomorrow.
Rum and coke, romero.
Havana, right?
Are you Santos Trinidad, sir?
Yes...
I'm vazquez's son. José vazquez,
I don't know if you remember.
Sure.
- How is he?
- Fine.
He's going to be happy
when I tell him I saw you.
My father speaks highly of you.
He tells a load of stories.
I'm getting ready
to join the group too.
That's great, lad.
It's a fucker
what happened to you.
Hey, don't tell your father
you saw me.
I'll be outside for five minutes.
- Are you judge chacon?
- Yes.
I'm cerdan.
Sorry to make you come here.
With this summit,
we're all out of place.
Yesterday, I spent all day
at the airport.
Don't worry.
Do you know this man?
Yes. Yes.
Andrés David hurtado,
a killer with the Colombian mafias.
He was in the farc guerillas.
Quite a guy.
He's involved in
the club ladies thing.
- Do you think he did it?
- No. He's one of the victims.
Right. Well, one less.
You investigated the case
on Pedro vargas
and Augusto lora
in 2004, didn't you?
Yes.
You did an excellent job.
What I don't understand
is why the case was dropped.
The prosecution appeal came
on a Friday,
but a civil servant forgot to lodge it.
By Monday, it had expired.
That's what happened.
What can I tell you?
I imagine you're still
investigating these people.
No, no.
After that, lora took over
and took greater precautions.
They reduced the shipments,
they changed their transport
and distribution channels.
They stopped working
with the galicians...
Roger.
Roger. Two minutes.
Excuse me.
They left the galicians and switched
to the north African hashish mafias.
For some time, most of the cocaine
has come into Spain via Africa.
We're a colander.
From here it goes all over Europe.
Primarily to Italy.
Who are they're working with now?
Sorry. The investigation went to
the head unit, foreign intelligence.
Why is that?
You should talk to them.
They thought the north africans
had links to radical islamic activity.
Just before being murdered,
at 3:50 and 4:05 in the morning,
according to the phone records,
Pedro vargas made two calls,
both to a number
at a company you own.
I assure you,
he didn't speak to me.
How many phones
do we have in the company?
Some 25. I don't know.
I'd like to know if this is
an interrogation
or a private conversation.
It's a conversation.
We can do that, can't we?
Yes, what we're having is a...
Conversation.
Those calls are nothing unusual.
It's normal for us at that hour.
He could've called for information,
an order, anything, it's normal.
Do you know a man called
andrés David hurtado?
No.
Are you sure?
Maybe under another name...?
No.
He's the man that turned up dead
in the club with Pedro vargas.
I don't know him.
Last October 3rd
you two flew
from Rome to Madrid.
Excuse me, Mr. lora.
Give me a second, flavio.
I don't know. Maybe.
I go to Rome quite often.
Yes, we're aware of that.
I you'll allow me...
Business is booming, huh?
Sorry, inspector.
You were telling us
about that plane.
Yes.
You two were travelling
in seats 2A and 2b.
The dead man,
andrés David hurtado,
that man you don't know,
was on the same flight,
exactly three rows behind you.
So?
There's no reason Mr. lora
would know the other passengers.
Of course.
I'm sorry, inspector,
but we're not going
down this road anymore.
And I'm thinking of complaining
to judge chacon.
If you wish to question
my client again, show me a warrant.
Mr. lora,
you want to convince us
that vargas was "Heidi's granddad".
But he was iced along with
a killer who's wanted all over.
I think some fucker has started
a war against your business.
And you know who it is.
I also think that
if you're not helping us,
there's some reason for it.
Have a drink at the bar, inspector.
On the house.
Thanks.
Santos.
Hello, leiva.
- What are you doing here?
- Nothing. Looking for a girl.
Sure, you're in missing persons now.
Santiago told me.
- How are you handling it?
- Fine, slow, another life.
Good.
What's it been?
Three years since I saw you?
Or more.
- You're still the same.
- You do what you can.
Nice to see you, Santos.
Santos...
- Did you know Ortega died?
- Yeah. I heard.
Well, leiva...
Take care of yourself.
Fuck you, leiva.
What can I get you?
Coffee.
With a dash of anisette.
Anis del mono.
Sorry, we don't have that.
Just coffee then.
Your coffee.
Right... we have the details
on that license plate,
but it isn't a 4-wheel-drive,
it's a mini, registered in la corufa
to a Carmen ciller Castro,
a teacher, 40 years old.
Anything else?
Nothing else.
What is it?
No.
Tell him what the fuck you want,
but I don't know when I'll be there.
Listen, I'll call you later.
What did he say?
Where the hell is he?
- What's wrong with Santos?
- It's valencia.
The third call about Santos.
What do I tell them?
Put it through to me.
Come into my office.
Yes.
Excuse me, ma'am.
He's just arrived.
Show him in.
Come in.
Inspector mérida,
head unit, foreign intelligence.
Good morning.
I'm very grateful.
I know you're busy these days.
I won't keep you long.
I know you handled a narcotics file
linking Pedro vargas
and Augusto lora
to African hashish networks.
Correct.
Why?
Why what?
Why did foreign intelligence
take charge of a narcotics file?
Well...
I recall that one of our informants
told us about a connection
between these Colombians
and a Moroccan group
headed by someone close to
radical jihadist cells.
Terrorists.
Excuse me.
Do you believe that vargas'
and lora's link to this group
is still going on?
Maybe, but we're not aware of it.
You don't know.
No.
Our objective was
the group leader, ceuti.
He moved to Barcelona
and we lost his trail.
We dropped that line of enquiry.
What about the rest of the group?
Who?
The rest of this ceuti's group.
Do they still work
with the Colombians?
I suppose the case
went back to narcotics.
You suppose,
or did it go back to narcotics?
Do you recall the first name
of this ceuti?
I'd have to look it up.
Would you mind calling
and finding out right now?
I also want to speak
to your informant,
the one who told you about
the contacts between these people.
That's more delicate, ma'am.
You should speak
to the commissioner directly.
The file hasn't reached me yet,
commissioner.
It hasn't? One moment.
This is ontiveros.
What's going on with the ceuti file?
Tell him to call me when he gets in.
- Thank you.
- Anyway, mérida told you everything.
We got lucky with ceuti at first.
At first.
Trouble is, these people move around
quite a lot and unpredictably.
That's what happened with him.
One day he went to Barcelona
and we lost the trail.
Later he was located in Afghanistan
and latest reports place him in Yemen.
Why didn't you arrest him before?
Well...
We never work on just one option,
we take several directions
and ceuti was only one possibility.
When we lost him in Barcelona,
we assumed he'd left the country
and we gave up that Avenue.
But ceuti's people were still
bringing cocaine to the Colombians.
That's why the case
went back to narcotics.
Narcotics has no knowledge of it.
Then let them look again.
It has to be there.
Incredible. What's wrong?
Don't you talk to each other?
What's up, champ?
Rachid,
let me introduce judge chacon.
She's interested in finding out
who Augusto lora is in business with.
What do you do?
I'm in public relations,
stripper and model.
I've been in various TV series
playing a Moroccan hash trafficker.
With the permission
of the commissioner.
You did 6 months
for attempted robbery.
Yes, ma'am. A mistake.
Do you know Mr. lora personally?
Sure, we're good buddies.
He's got a couple of nice dancehalls.
How did you know ceuti?
He's a bad dude, that ceuti.
He controlled all the hash
in malasana.
He was violent, overbearing.
A bad dude.
Then he went nuts about religion.
Did you put ceuti in touch
with Mr. lora?
Lora wanted to change things,
meet other people,
and I introduced them.
We supervised that operation.
Who does lora work with now?
No fucking idea.
Sorry.
I mean, I don't know.
There are a lot of north africans
in Madrid.
I'm getting out of all this.
I want to lead a good life.
Right, commissioner?
Thanks very much.
- Is that it?
- Yes. For now, that's it.
You can eat that
on the way, can't you?
Sure, champ.
Delighted, ma'am.
Sorry he wasn't more help.
That's alright, don't worry.
Ma'am...
Let me tell you,
we do a good job,
believe me.
We have nine possible active cells
under surveillance at present.
But these people move around,
and for us to nail them down,
to locate them, is very hard.
In my opinion,
your Colombian massacre
is the work of professionals
hired by Latin mafias.
These people don't usually
work like this,
especially jihadist radicals,
they're in another war.
Ceuti is not your man.
Still, if you think it's necessary
to go down that road,
bear in mind that to avoid
confusion and misunderstanding,
we should be kept up to speed.
You understand, don't you?
Of course.
And I hope it's reciprocal.
Make sure you send me
that file, please.
Yes?
Excuse me, does a José Luis
Garcia Garcia live here?
Yes. Is something wrong?
Just a formality.
I wanted to ask you some questions
about a place you own.
An apartment on 6 litos St.
Come in.
This man is with the police.
He's asking about
Paloma's apartment.
My husband.
Go ahead.
I work in missing persons.
We're looking for a girl
and in the course of investigation,
this address came up:
6 litos St.
The electricity bill
is still in your name.
That apartment was ours, yes.
We left it to our daughter
when she got married.
- Does she live there?
- No.
She and her husband
have been in London for two years.
Is this your daughter?
Yes, that's Paloma.
Her husband is an arab?
Spanish, from ceuta,
from a good family.
He taught arabic in lavapiés.
That's where they met.
- He was a very nice boy.
- Until they got married.
Now my daughter dresses like that.
Do you recall the address
in lavapiés? Where he taught?
There may be a card somewhere.
I'll go look.
Do you have any children?
Yes.
Then you'll understand.
All my life I taught her to be free,
to not bow down to anyone.
You know what she said
when she decided to get married?
That she was freely giving up
everything for this man.
Here it is.
Tangier cultural association.
- You can't see his face here either.
- Hold on.
This is 15 minutes before.
He doesn't look Colombian.
- The report on the prints.
- Thanks.
Tangier cultural association
- What is it?
- I want to talk to rachid.
And no stories this time
or I'll slap you around.
You're such a pest about rachid!
I know he's in Madrid. Find him.
Hi, Vanessa, it's Celia.
I'm fine.
I need rachid's number,
the one he's using now.
Easy as pie.
Final year of computer engineering.
Good student, ordered life,
discreet, no visitors.
Looks like he's gone.
He hasn't been around for 3 days.
- Since Monday.
I assume that's for me.
- Hey there, ontiveros.
- Leiva.
Does he ring a bell?
His prints are on bills
in vargas' safe.
Very young. He must be new.
- Has he got a record?
- No.
He got his Spanish passport
two years ago.
Leiva.
Find out if the other residents
recognize him or have seen him,
ceuti isn't in Spain, ma'am.
He's married to a girl from Madrid?
Yes, of course.
Couldn't you have
told me this before?
Get in, I'll take you.
Do you know her?
- No idea.
- Are you sure?
It's important I find her, rachid.
Good family, classy girl, you know.
Never seen her before.
I'm told she lost the plot
with one of your kind.
With this guy.
That's you. You know him, right?
That's ceuti,
he doesn't care about women.
This is an old photo.
We used to play football.
We'd meet up sometimes. Where?
- In restaurants, at his place...
- The apartment on litos St.?
Apartment?
I know nothing about that.
He lived in the country then.
But it's impossible he got involved
with that girl. Impossible.
Besides, he's not in Madrid.
Oh, no? Where is he?
How should I know?
He left Spain.
And the place where you met?
I don't remember.
It was a long time ago.
Give me your mobile.
Concentrate, rachid.
You'll have to jog that memory.
Two years?
Yes, more or less.
Has something happened
to my daughter?
Not as far as we know.
Take it easy.
We're interested in your son-in-law.
This is him, isn't it?
Yes.
Do you known this man?
No.
Do you have the phone number
of your daughter in London?
She has no phone.
She always calls from a phone shop.
You don't know if your son-in-law
might've come back to Madrid?
No.
My husband and I already told
that other policeman.
Sorry, who are you talking about?
What policeman?
He was looking for a missing girl.
He came at lunchtime.
Do you remember his name?
No. I don't think he said it.
I think it's this way.
We already came this way, rachid.
Then it's the other way.
You're looking to
get smacked around.
Are you sure?
You stay here.
I told you he wasn't here.
You're still working
for ontiveros, right?
I work for a lot of people, boss.
It's bad to work for
so many people, rachid.
You get my drift?
Sure, champ.
Last night, I went to see lora
and ran into a fellow cop.
Santos Trinidad.
He's in missing persons.
We graduated the same year.
I'd swear that's him.
- Have you spoken to him?
- No.
I've only told you.
What does it mean?
What's his link to the Colombians?
He was in special operations.
San raimundo cross,
police gold order of merit...
What's he doing in missing persons?
He was posted to our embassy
in Colombia.
Hi, honey.
No, you give him dinner.
I'm going to be late.
Put him on.
Hi, honey, how are you?
No, mom can't...
Oh, really?
That's great!
Well, be good.
Big kiss, darling.
What time is it in Colombia?
Rum and coke.
Another bonus!
- Some peanuts?
- No.
I'll settle up.
A winner!
Another bonus!
Rock 'n' roll.
You fucking smart-ass.
Son of a bitch.
Go, go!
- Do we leave this behind?
- No! Pack it all up!
Everything's ready for the official
inauguration of the g-20 summit,
to take place today in Madrid
at the palacio de congresos
it will be presided over
by king Juan Carlos and queen Sofia.
Blasco?
Hello. I'm leiva.
It's a bit early. Sorry.
That's okay.
White coffee.
How long have you been
with Santos?
A year and a half.
- And how is it?
- Fine. Fine.
What's up with Santos?
What are you on now?
Keeping watch on the summit.
The other day I ran into him
and he said
you were looking for a young girl.
Well, several.
What did you do on Monday?
Monday... routine surveillance.
- And Santos was with you, of course.
- Of course.
Between 1 and 2 P.M.?
I guess so, yes.
You guess.
Come on, lad...
Was he with you or not?
Why don't you talk to him?
Because I'd rather talk to you first.
I've got a subpoena for Santos.
This is serious.
Answer me.
Was he with you between
1 and 2 P.M. on Monday?
No.
- You've got your mobile switched off.
- What are you doing here?
Fix yourself up.
They're expecting us at the station.
What for?
Tell that to the judge.
- You use a revolver, don't you?
- Yes.
Would you accept
a voluntary ballistics test?
What's this about, leiva?
Come on, hurry up.
Shower and put on something clean.
- Chacon?
- Yes, that's me. Come in.
Sit down, please.
Can I find out why
I've been subpoenaed?
It's just some questions,
but if you think you need
a lawyer present...
I don't think there's any need.
- Are you alright?
- Yes.
You had a brilliant start.
First of your graduating year,
various distinctions...
What happened later?
Why did you leave
special operations?
The time had come to do it.
Right.
In recent years
you've had a lot of days off
- and some psychiatric treatment.
- Psychological.
- Are you still being treated?
- No.
I also see here that you've had
some problems with alcohol.
Last Sunday, march 7th,
were you drinking?
No.
- What were you doing?
- I was at home.
- Can someone corroborate that?
- I live alone.
Did you go to sala machuca
two days ago?
Yes. What for?
I was looking for a missing girl.
In the course of an investigation
out of my bureau, I told leiva that.
Do you know this man?
No.
And this one?
That one I do, yes.
Did you visit the parents
of his wife?
Yes, in the course of
the investigation.
This is him.
The photo was among
the girl's things.
A friend of hers said
he was seen with him.
I know this guy.
His name's rachid
and he's one of our informants.
In fact, I went to
sala machuca to see him.
And what did he tell you?
Nothing. I didn't find him.
In 1997 you killed someone.
In the line of duty.
They gave me a medal.
And in 2003, you seriously wounded
a fellow officer.
You two were posted to
the Spanish embassy in Colombia.
Can you tell me
what happened there?
It should say it there.
Answer the question, please.
During an operation, my gun jammed.
When I unjammed it, it went off.
Your partner became a paraplegic.
He died. Two years ago.
Are any of the investigations
in your current department
linked to Pedro vargas
or Augusto lora?
No. Not that I know of.
Who are they?
Do you know Hugo anglada?
Maybe you know him
by his real name,
andrés David hurtado.
No. I don't know him.
You said that during an operation
your gun went off.
What kind of operation exactly?
A stakeout.
Is it normal to have to use
your gun on a stakeout?
We're not allowed to talk about
operations we took part in, ma'am.
According to the Colombian police,
in 2003, on the same day
you state that
your gun went off accidentally,
there was a shoot-out in vallaito,
a slum outside of Cali.
In this shoot-out,
two top members of a drug cartel died.
At first, the Colombian police thought
these two events were connected.
They suspected that your partner,
Luis Maria Sanchez najera,
had links with members of that cartel.
Luis was a good cop.
All can tell you
is in the official embassy report.
My gun went off.
In the early hours
of Monday, march 8th,
were you in the chamartin hotel?
No.
On that date,
this person entered the hotel,
searched Mr. hurtado's room,
then went to the parking lot
and searched his car.
Someone thinks they recognize you
in this photo.
That's not me.
- It isn't you?
- No.
I see you've fired your gun recently.
I like to practise.
You may take your weapon.
I don't get how this character
can still be in the police.
Are you going to charge him?
No. Not for the moment.
With a negative ballistics report,
I can't.
Got any pills left?
The ones elephants take
for a toothache.
I'm sorry, Santos.
Relax, kid.
I'd have done the same thing.
Where are you going?
I'm fucking off.
Exit for benidorm,
dock 28.
Exit for los alcazares,
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org