_
What is it you think happened?
Someone killed this girl,
made a big show of it...
left a painting
of the crime scene
on one of your old churches.
You're obsessive.
You're obsessive, too,
just not about the job.
Are you gonna go home
with this guy?
Really none of your business.
Stop!
You know if it's true?
I didn't hear anything.
What have you been
doing, Marty?
I found another girl.
She was positive for
meth and LSD.
You ever think maybe
he tried to push things
where he wanted them to go?
Hey, we caught a break
in the case, boss.
I thought you were
handing that off.
She had a boyfriend
you know about?
Reggie.
Reggie Ledoux.
Reggie Ledoux skipped
parole 8 months ago.
He's busted in connection
to a narcotics lab
used to make meth and LSD,
did two years at Avoyelles,
and guess who his cellmate was
the last 4 months.
Charlie Lange.
What Dori do?
Dori's dead.
I need an all-state APB
on one Reginald Ledoux.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
♪ from the dusty May sun ♪
♪ her looming shadow grows ♪
♪ hidden in the branches ♪
♪ of the poison creosote ♪
♪ she twines her spines up slowly ♪
♪ towards the boiling sun ♪
♪ and when I touched her skin ♪
♪ my fingers ran with blood ♪
♪ when the last light warms the rocks ♪
♪ and the rattlesnakes unfold ♪
♪ the mountain cats will come ♪
♪ to drag away your bones ♪
♪ and rise with me forever ♪
♪ across the silent sand ♪
♪ and the stars will be your eyes ♪
♪ and the wind will be my hands ♪
True Detective - 1x04
"Who Goes There"
What you doing?
You fucked with us, Charlie.
I did not, sir.
Reggie Ledoux.
Hey, I don't even want
to know that freak, man.
Y'all ain't asked
nothin' about Reggie.
Fuck, man, my--
my wife just died--
Ex-wife!
You had Reggie Ledoux
take her out,
didn't you?
- No.
- Hmm?
- What are you talking about, man?
Reggie? Put her out there
with them antlers on? I--
You have Reggie do it?
- What are you talking about?
- Hmm?
Reggie Ledoux did this?
Reggie Ledoux?
Reggie motherfuckin'
Ledoux did this?!
Fuck, man! Shit!
Let me out, man!
Let me out!
Fuck, man!
Hey, Charlie?
We're not gonna give you the Oscar
no matter how hard you try.
Oh, fuck you, man.
You don't know me.
You don't know
what I been through.
And what are you talking
about? You talk to me!
Ledoux knew about her, right?
You talk about her to him?
Yeah, man-- yeah, the way
you do sharing a house.
Yeah, you talk pussy,
talk scores.
That's what you do.
Showed him pictures
of her, hmm?
Yeah, I guess so, yeah.
I had some she give me
when I first went down,
stuff for me to look at.
You know, like Polaroids.
He was a big guy--
a lot bigger than you.
Do you tell me you
didn't get along?
Nah, I mean, I did, most part.
You've got to,
you're sharing a house,
like I'm saying.
I mean, he gets you high, man, but he's creep.
I ain't want to know him.
Tell me about Ledoux.
How is he creep?
He's a cook, you know,
like a chemist?
He used to, uh, make shit
out of kitchen stuff--
cook down cleansers
and whatnot.
Used tater skins and fry grease
to make high-test sour mash.
He got mad knowledge for that shit,
but, like, I don't know, man,
he talk like a short-eyes,
like something.
How you mean? He wouldn't
talk that shit up in here.
No, man, he didn't. Like,
me and him at night,
blasted up on one of his mixes.
I mean, he could
brew some shit up
put you up out your head, man.
That's a big deal in here.
I mean, fuck, man, it's a
big deal out there, too.
So, uh, what kind
of shit was he talking?
He said that there's
this place down south
where all these rich men
go to, uh, devil-worship.
He said that, uh...
they-- they sacrifice
kids and whatnot.
Women and children
all got--
all got murdered there,
and, um,
something about someplace
called Carcosa
and the Yellow King.
He said there's all these, like,
old stones out in the woods,
people go to, like, worship.
He said, uh...
He said there's just so much
good killin' down there.
Reggie got this
brand on his back,
like in a spiral?
He says that's their sign.
What the fuck ever,
you understand?
I don't listen
to the man, but he's big,
so I don't tell him to
shut the fuck up, neither!
You remember any buddies
he ever talked about?
So we checked the records here,
and he hadn't ever
had any visitors.
We both know Tyro Weems.
Tyrone like to tell you
where he's at.
Look, man, Reggie's
crazy, like, for real.
Had to be tough,
living with somebody
spouting insane shit
in your ear all day long.
You gonna give me something
for what I told you just now?
Parole board nod.
Fair's fair.
Hey. Hey!
You think 'cause I talked
to him about Dori that...
I might have got her killed?
You probably had
something to do with it.
I don't think you should have
shown him those pictures.
Do you?
We need to find
this Tyrone Weems,
see what he knows about Ledoux.
Yeah.
Ahem.
You didn't have to tell
him it was his fault.
Guy was already low.
Yeah, he asked
about his end first.
Parole board.
So?
So fuck him.
You're funny, Marty--
the shit you get soft about.
I wanted every member
of that family that I could find.
Turns out...
there weren't any.
You know how weird
that is in Louisiana?
A cousin, what was it,
Dewall, was
not on paper except
for a, uh, trucker's license.
Ledoux had turned into a ghost
from the time he skipped
parole check.
Tell me, young studs,
what would you do
when you hit a wall like that?
Responding to the complaint,
I approached the house.
Seeing that the screen door
was broken and the inner door...
ajar, I-- I felt that entrance
complied with standard
procedure.
Upon entering
the domicile, I noticed
what appeared to be marijuana
and a white powder
on the coffee table.
Hey, Martin.
We don't have to talk, Lisa.
The hell we don't.
You don't get to do what
you did to me last week.
Look, I'm sorry. I was
hurt and real drunk.
Talk to me now.
Okay. Ah, I wish you
a great life
and good luck with
your new friend.
You philandering
fucking asshole.
Hey, look.
There is no pageant
to perform, okay, and
your disappointment
is irrelevant.
You don't get to act
like that, Marty,
or like this.
The fact is it's nice
to know you got him,
and I don't want to have
this conversation with you.
You need to respect me, Marty.
This is respect.
Rust figured a connection with
an earlier death, suspicious--
Rianne Olivier.
Led us to the DB's old
boyfriend, Reginald Ledoux, 35.
Statch rape charge
against a 12-year-old,
acquitted for lack of testimony.
Did a bit for manufacturing
meth and LSD,
which fits the tox screen
for Lange.
His old cellmate
was Lange's ex-husband.
He showed him some
cheesecake pictures of her.
Uh, from what we
know about him,
the way he talked,
he sounds like he's
real good for it.
No line on any of his people.
Swamp folk, dug in
off the grid.
We are tracking
a KA, Tyrone Weems.
He's in the sheets
that we passed out.
Any questions?
I didn't think so.
Let's get to work.
Are you Theresa Weems,
Tyrone Weems' mom?
Tyrone ain't been around
in a while.
You know, a few months.
We got in a fight 'cause
he sold my microwave.
And what about his friends?
You know where they hang out?
I don't know, he dated
this girl Kelsey
for a little while.
Kelsey, when's the
last time you saw Tyrone?
Months.
We've been broke up.
I don't ever hear from him.
I don't want to.
I heard he got
Shawnda Miller pregnant.
So do you have his
address, phone number?
Look. I really wish I could
help you, but I can't.
I have to get back to work.
Hey.
You know that gal back there?
She got a man, manager?
Hey, do I got to pull my badge?
Hey, we run clean here.
How you gonna run
when you're shut down
6 months for
a grand jury inquiry?
Why are you making me
say this shit, man?
Do you know her old man?
Yeah, he came around,
collecting from her.
Boss kicked him out for trying
to sell christie, the girls.
That was about a month ago.
Look familiar?
- Yeah, that's him.
- He ever pick her up?
Yeah.
Went to work on Tyro
Weems, known associates, family.
Had a little leeway
with Quesada
now that we had our suspect.
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
Goddamn it!
- Lisa?
- How does it feel?
I told you you can't
treat people like this.
Listen, I just need to know
exactly what you told her.
You think it's okay
what you do?
All of you think it's okay
to treat your wives
the way you do,
to treat women the way--
fucking liars and bullies,
and this is what you get!
This is what you get!
I have children.
You blew up my life,
you fucking whore!
What did you just call me?!
What did you just call me, you fucking
wet-noodle, whiskey-dick faggot fuck?!
I will skull-fuck you,
you bitch!
Hello, Jake?
- Jake, is this you?
- Marty?
- Is Maggie there?
- That's none of your goddamn business.
Jake, I know she's there,
I know she's there,
so just put her
on the phone,
would you, please?
Leave her alone,
you fuckin' asshole.
- Jake, I--
- You're not hearing me.
- I don't know what she told you.
- Leave her alone.
And I know we haven't
always seen eye to eye--
- You're goddamn right, we haven't
seen eye to eye. - Just please,
- put her on the phone
for me. Just please-- - No, no.
You are no damn good, Marty,
she deserves better,
and don't call here again.
Jake.
How many exes you guys have?
I mean, that's what
I'm talking about.
Did I make some mistakes?
Yes.
You know the detective's curse?
Solution was right under my nose, but I
was paying attention to the wrong clues?
- See you later.
- Bye, hon.
Fuck.
Reggie Ledoux.
Where is he? Now.
That's what this is about? Yo,
man, why didn't you say so?
Where the fuck is he?
I-- I heard
he still cook.
I heard he stopped selling
after he did his bit,
that he only cook
for one client now.
Who?
Some bike gang.
They buy all his product.
Bulk order, no mess.
I heard this
at the clubs is all.
Reggie don't
distribute no more.
Which bike club?
Iron Heroes or some shit.
Iron-- Iron Crusaders.
I don't keep up
with them gearheads.
Iron Crusaders?
You sure?
Yup. Them ones.
What I heard, Reggie cook
their loads and that's all.
Close your eyes and
count to a hundred,
if you can.
Go.
1... 2...
- Louder.
- 3!
4... 5...
Listen I-- I talked to Weems and, uh,
the dude is cooking for some
motorcycle gang out of Texas.
Iron Crusaders.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
but-- Iron-- Iron Crusaders?
You're sure he said
Iron Crusaders?
I'm sure he said
Iron Crusaders.
So we'll, uh,
we'll chase that
tomorrow, yeah?
- What are you doing right now?
- Right now I'm busy.
And, as I recall, I...
I had to take
some personal time,
see my dad.
I mean, this is like,
what, 17 years ago?
Yeah, you'll have to understand
if my memory hasn't
sharpened in the interim.
Ahem.
Fran, stay by the phone.
I will.
Maggie, can I talk to
you for just a second?
No. I'm working graveyard.
Girls are with my mom and dad.
It's all in the note, Marty.
Okay, will you give me
a chance to--
She came to my home.
Our daughters saw her.
You lying fuck.
You stupid, lying fuck.
Jesus Christ.
Listen to me, Mags.
I meant everything I said the
other night, every word.
- I-- I stopped.
- Oh, my God.
You think your betrayal's
removed by its interruption?
She was disgusting.
You're disgusting.
- You can't fix this.
- Listen to me. God, listen--
- Get your hands off me.
- Okay.
I-- I've been--
I've been a mess.
Rattled. My...
Just...
my dad dying--
- Oh, my God. That was a year ago.
- And drinking and--
I don't give a shit about
your goddamn feelings.
You need to get out of our
lives, Marty, me and the girls'.
- Read the note. It's all there and you
can't come home. - You don't mean that.
- Yes. Yes, I do.
- You don't mean that.
Listen, I...
You are not gonna break up
my fuckin' family, okay?
- Get out of here right now!
- No.
Excuse me.
You all right, Maggie?
Sir, I suggest you leave.
Everything's fine, Doc.
I'm State Police.
I appreciate that, but are you
here in that capacity now,
as-- as law enforcement?
You don't want to do this.
Get your hands
off me, goddamn it,
and call your
commanding officer.
- You're making a scene, Marty!
- No!
There is no scene, unless
Mall Patrol here makes one.
I am calmly discussing
a private matter
with my wife!
Private in a pretty public way, man.
Easy, easy.
- This is none of your fuckin' business.
- No, no.
It's none of my business,
but we got to work.
You hear me, Marty?
I got a line on Ledoux.
I got it right fuckin' now.
I need you to come in,
leave this shit till later.
I love you, honey,
and I ain't givin' up.
Come on.
We can get to Ledoux.
Marty, it's gonna be dirty.
I just need her
to give me another shot.
If I could just get
another shot--
Listen, can I
tell you something?
Yeah.
This is none of my business.
I don't want to hear it.
All right. I'm sorry.
You total shit.
You know, this is part
on you, you know?
You can't just slide
into my life,
creating tensions,
judging me--
What, I make you tap some bimbo,
looks like a young Maggie?
I make you flaunt that shit?
Fuck, that night
at the Longhorn,
you were so obvious,
man, checking her out,
and she looked crazy enough
to have followed you there.
With all the dick swagger you
roll, you can't spot crazy pussy?
I fucked up.
I just...
I like something wild.
I always did.
I just...
it feels like it--
it smoothes out the other
parts of my life most of--
Listen, Marty, one more time.
It's none of my fuckin' business.
Ah, fuck.
Look, we got a job to do.
Off-book. That's the only
play I can think of.
I-- I got to straighten out things
with the family. I got to fix it.
That bike club.
I know 'em.
I had deals with 'em when
I was working narco.
We can get to that
motherfucker Ledoux.
So, enough with this
self-improvement,
penance,
hand-wringing shit.
Let's go to work.
Do you think you're...
Fuck!
Hell of a bedside manner
you got, Rust.
Ah, you know being stupid's
different than callin' in sick,
and this is a bar,
not a fuckin' bedside.
Friend in need.
Every time I think
you hit a ceiling,
you just keep raising the bar.
You are like the Michael Jordan
of being a son of a bitch.
Let's go. Come on. Really
gonna love this jacket I got.
Holy shit.
You visit a lot of gun shows?
Ah, it's just some stuff I kept in
case some work came back on me.
These boys Ledoux deals to,
they're out of east Texas.
I worked 'em when I
was DEA task force.
They know you're 5-0?
No.
I wasn't sure,
so I checked with
my old handler.
As far as my cover goes,
I took 3 slugs
in a DEA shootout
in Port Houston.
Anybody that gives a
shit figures I'm dead.
Major said
the task force used
to call you Crash.
I'm gonna have to take
some personal time
on this, Marty,
a couple of weeks.
Got to get out there and
get seen, drop some lines.
I mean, badges ain't gonna
get us near these people,
so the plan is
we make 'em an offer...
we get a line
on their supplier,
confirm it's Ledoux,
bring him in.
And then, once we're out there,
all right, it's just
you and me on this.
I don't like that.
What happens, they clock
you're not you?
Mmm.
No, I can't do what I need
to do if we got watchdogs.
Besides, like you said,
Quesada'd pull me.
The stakes ain't
that high anyway.
I get found, I take
a bullet to the head.
This cartel I worked
on the border,
they, uh, they had
this routine.
They'd duct-tape you to a chair
that was bolted to the floor,
use a couple rolls,
make sure you couldn't
budge a fuckin' inch.
And they'd cut
around your face,
grip your scalp, yank down,
rip your face off.
Hmm.
And they'd put a mirror
in front of you
so you could get
a good look at yourself.
And they'd cut your dick
and your balls off...
shove 'em down your throat
until you bled and choked out,
while you were watching.
So...
as far as high stakes go,
bullet to the head?
It ain't that.
Hey.
You sure you want to do this?
Not exactly.
Realize you got
a upstairs here, right?
What is that?
Ink and cayenne.
Irritates the skin,
looks contused.
How long they have you out
there, working the corridor?
Almost 4 years.
4? What the hell?
UCs ain't supposed to
do more than 11 months.
Yeah, but I-- I'd
fucked up on the job,
and to make it better,
they went with me.
That's a long time,
being like that.
I need a good story to move
fast, and I think I got one.
All we need now is
some good coke.
Where you gonna get that?
Don't worry about it.
So you got a suspect,
and you take a leave
of absence?
Yup.
Like I said, to see my pops.
Had leukemia.
Favre. Ahem. I get the
evidence key from you?
Yeah. Heard you
were taking time.
- Thank you.
- Leaving tonight.
- Sign the log.
- Yep.
You supposed to see
both eyes in this one?
They really should have
a better system for this.
We looked at your
old partner's history.
And coincidences
keep mounting, Detective.
Oh, coincidences like what?
Well, I don't know if it would
qualify as coincidence, but,
near as we could tell, his
pops never had leukemia.
- No hospital records of that.
- Fact, nobody in that town in Alaska's
seen Travis Cohle
in more than 30 years.
That it?
You still angry
at him, your pops?
No.
He's dead.
You were, though.
I mean, why you two
didn't talk.
We never really liked
each other.
There's a difference.
He was in 'Nam.
Met my mother on leave
in Galveston.
Time he came back, I was two.
She dumped me on him,
then she hauled ass,
and he and I moved to Alaska.
He was a survivalist,
I guess you'd call it.
Had some very fucking
strange ideas.
Oh, there's nothing like
the night sky out there, though.
But I couldn't handle
the cold, so...
I headed back to south Texas
'cause all I could remember
was at least it never got cold.
My old man always made like
I let him down that way.
Said I had no loyalty.
A clean break is best now,
while they're still young.
Look, that's none
of my business.
I mean, but I do need him
to watch my back on this.
This is how you all get warped.
You always short-change
the wrong things.
Short-change?
Mm-hmm.
What else?
He wanted me to pass
a tide of apologies
of which I'll skip...
and he wants to see the girls,
if you can make time for it.
Kids are the only thing
that matter, Maggie.
They're the only reason for
this whole man-woman drama.
I'm sorry.
What are you
suggesting, exactly?
Just that people fuck up.
We age.
Men, women-- it's not
supposed to work
except to make kids.
So, if you can imagine
Marty's behavior
as an expression
of weakness, pain,
you'd see that it's
not about you.
So, end of the day, you
duck under rationalization,
same as any of them.
You must have been
a great husband.
People have been seeing me
around for about a week.
Guy I used to run with, he
wants to meet me tonight.
Now, if I can get him
alone, we snatch him up,
work him over,
maybe get to Ledoux.
Okay.
- All right?
- Great.
Listen--
Phone's fully charged. And
remember, it's real simple.
Green-- answers,
red-- hangs up.
- All right.
- I'm the only one that's gonna be calling.
- Yeah.
- And keep it charged.
Listen, uh, how was she?
What'd she say?
She was better. I could
see her softening.
She didn't use the "D" word.
My odds, I could see you two back
together within a couple months.
That your honest read?
That's my honest read, Marty.
Look, I don't know
how this guy I'm meeting
tonight feels about me.
- Okay?
- What does that mean?
It means, if you lose track of me
tonight, keep this fucker handy
and be listening to
Beaumont police channels.
- Yeah.
- You got it?
Yeah.
You got it?
I got it. Are you
gonna be all right?
Yeah.
Crash, here for Ginger.
Well, after Houston,
I got to a doc in Eagle Pass,
then a coyote got me
across the border.
Past two years, I been
working security
for a group in San Miguel.
Feds never ID'd me,
you know, so I figured,
hell, two years pass,
things chill down,
it's cool for me to come
back, stick my head up.
That'll be tough, man...
thinkin' you been dead
this whole time.
I look dead, motherfucker?
I'm lookin' to get with you.
You or Miles.
Miles ain't gonna want
to see you, Crash.
- Oh, I think he might.
- Well, yeah.
Then I'd say
I don't think
you want to see Miles.
Man, I ain't here to start
a thing, all right?
Boys I been running
with in Mexico,
there could be a hell of
a deal for both sides,
fuckin' money to be made.
Real money.
What kind of money?
Goddamn Rust.
What the fuck?
My boys are looking
to trade, all right?
Coke for meth.
What you got there?
Ahem.
- This one's just for you.
- Just for me?
Uh-huh.
What'd you cut it with?
Oh, you'll see.
You'll dig it.
After all I meant to you, huh?
Now, who exactly
are these guys?
Uh, they, uh...
ex-Mex Army.
They got a Colombian connection.
They need meth for
the maquiladoras.
Yeah, they could
cook it themselves,
but then the cartels
would take notice,
and that ain't what
they're lookin' for.
Hmm.
Here.
Taste that, homie.
That ain't no
fuck-around shit.
Goddamn.
Whew.
You keep it.
I've got bulldozers' worth of
that shit where I came from.
The thing is...
we got one cook.
Does all our work,
exclusive-like.
He's real specific about that.
Now, what's this worth to you,
Crash, me selling Miles on this?
Well, I'd go you one
better, brother.
We don't take that shit
to Miles at all.
You and me work the supplier,
the cut's whatever the
fuck we want it to be.
Now, now, that's
tricky shit, bro,
and I don't know you
like I used to.
Yeah, I don't know you
like I used to, either.
That's why the fuck I'm here.
Well, let me tell you
why I came, Crash.
I need something
from you, tonight.
I had a 4-man team
for a big grab,
lost one to smokies.
I came looking to replace him,
if you're still
a bad-ass.
I don't do A&R, man,
no fuckin' bank jobs.
It ain't nothin' like that.
I need a good soldier.
Now, you do this with us,
we talk about
puttin' you with my man.
Look.
I don't ride cowboy
no more, Ginger.
- Oh.
- I don't do this small-time shit
like this thing you're
talking about, all right?
What, you get neutered
down south, huh?
I embrace the outlaw life.
Now, you dress the part still.
That just an act?
When in Rome, brother,
but I do clean up
real fuckin' pretty.
Motherfucker,
I need a gunslinger.
Now, you ain't too timid,
get on this shit with me.
Then we can talk
about doin' business.
Where?
My place.
Down the bayou.
All right.
I got my truck.
It'll be safe here.
Members only.
I'm just lookin' for a friend.
Hey. What the fuck?
Look, look, look,
my buddy's not here.
- You ain't listening!
- I'm his sponsor, and
I'm worried that he might
have started drinking again.
You better worry that we
don't pull your head off
and shit down your neck!
He's been 20 years sober.
Just give me one second.
What the hell!
- I'm leaving, sir.
- A guy can just come in here and say,
"Lookin' for a fuckin' friend"?!
Ought to worry more
about your balls, faggot!
Get the fuck outta here!
I'm leaving.
Jesus Christ.
Run, motherfucker!
That's good.
Son of a bitch, man!
- Fuck is that?
- That there?
- That's Tigger the nigger.
- Name's Tiger Thomas.
Dealer in them Hoston Projects.
You know them?
That's like them bungalowed,
flat-like joints, right?
Yeah.
They keep a stash house there.
I'll get you, you fucking dicks!
Hey, why don't you shut
the fuck up, nigger?
Fuck you!
So you all gonna
take a stash house
in coon country, huh, 4 guys?
Well, how big's the projects,
man, like square block-wise?
Get the gear, mates.
Wait till you see this.
You're gonna love it.
Oh, you're going in
as cops, huh?
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
You know where
the stash house is?
Tiger's gonna take us there.
Well, you got an exit plan?
Hmm?
Timetable?
The real cops come,
then what, huh?
I mean, you say you're going
in the one fuckin' car?
Uh-huh.
Far as I remember, man,
the place is blocked in.
That is one way in,
one way out.
It could be fuckin'
Mogadishu, man.
We hit trouble,
you're just gonna
fuck it in the ass.
You scoop out the soft brains
inside the skull.
Well, so you have
thought it out.
My bad.
I come through
for you on this tonight,
I got to know you're
gonna hook me up,
'cause I got a real job I
was supposed to be doing.
Hmm?
You got my word. You back
me on this, I'll back you.
Fuck it. Let's go.
Up and at 'em, eggplant.
Motherfuckers.
- Fuck you!
- Come on.
I'll kill you, motherfuckers!
Y'all are dead!
406 reported on Fullington Street...
Air 3, Dispatch.
Go ahead, Air 3.
Over Zone 6, Hoston Projects.
Pretty quiet, possible 507s.
Everything's Code 4.
Copy that.
10-4, Air 3.
Man, you got two ways
of lookin' at it, Tiger.
You can die and lose your shit,
or you could live,
go make some more shit.
- What's up? - Y'all get back
in your house, now. Police.
Sheriff's Department! Get
back in your house. Do it.
There's nothin' to see here.
Sorry son of a bitch.
- Fuck out of here and start going...
- Fucker, start moving.
Tiger, man, yo.
What's up, man? What's this?
- Yo! Fuck! Lamar!
- Sheriff's Department.
- Lamar!
- Freeze, motherfucker.
Come on...
Aah!
Get up there, big boy.
Get on the door.
- Tell them that it's safe.
- Lamar.
- Get the fuck off me!
- Come open the door, Lamar.
- Tell them who you are.
- Fuckin' door, man. It's Tiger.
Get up here. Get back!
Police!
Fuck!
Everybody down, now!
Sheriffs!
Hands behind your head!
Shut up!
Get the fuck down!
Don't move.
Get in the tub.
Listen, listen.
You lay down.
Don't you move.
Got no shit!
Let me outta here!
Shut your fuckin' mouth!
Look on the left.
It's right there.
No, no, no, no. Ginger, no.
Don't touch it.
- It's in there.
- You open it, motherfucker.
- Get that gun out of my face.
- I'll put something else
in your face,
you don't shut up.
Get your fuckin' ass
over there! Start movin'!
Come on!
Ginger.
You motherfucker!
Get that shit off of there!
- Come on! Hurry your ass up!
- Fuck.
- Fuck you!
- Watch your fucking mouth.
All right, 30 seconds,
in and out.
30 seconds, in and out, Ginger.
Get that safe open.
Watch it, watch it. I'll
nuke you, motherfucker.
Keep your fuckin' mouth shut.
I'm gonna fire on you,
motherfucker.
Get the fuck off my dawg!
- Fuck!
- Easy, easy.
Just get in and get
the fuck out, Ginger.
It's Christmastime, Crash!
- We got this shit!
- Easy.
Fuck that fake-ass po-po!
Stay calm. Get it, Ginger.
Get the fuck out of here.
Ginger, man, they're
gathering out there--
Aah!
Come on, Ginger!
- They're animals out there, man.
- Easy, easy.
Easy, motherfucker.
Easy. Easy.
Ginger, let's fuckin' go!
- You sorry-ass motherfucker!
- Easy.
I told your cracker ass!
You're dead!
Don't fucking
fire! Do not--
Goddamn it.
Lamar!
Ginger! Ginger!
Stop fuckin' around!
Fuck!
- What the fuck!
- Ginger!
I fuckin' knew it!
Aah!
Wish I could have done this from
the start, you fucking moron!
Oh, fuck! What the fuck
are you doin', man?
Shut the fuck up.
Motherfucker!
Hey!
Freeze. Who else
is in the house?
- Nobody.
- Okay. Get in the bathroom.
In the bathroom.
Lay down.
Marty, okay.
I need you to meet me
at Amelia Street
between 18th and 19th
in 90 seconds.
You got it?
Amelia!
18th and 19th!
90 seconds, motherfucker!
Ooh, one right there!
- Aah!
- Here comes another one!
Aah!
Get your ass up!
Come on!
Aah!
Ginger.
You stupid mother--
The neighborhood--
Come on, man!
Police behind us, man!
Come on.
Keep going, man!
Come on! Hurry up, man!
Put the weapon down!
You motherfucker!
I'll get you!
You'll get yours, fuckin'
Crash, you motherfucker.
You'll get-- aah!
Come out
with your hands raised!
Get down on your knees!
Quick, hide. Here.
Oh!
Oh, shit!
Hey!
Go!
Go, go, go!
What the fuck happened?
Remember that meth contact now?
You rat motherfucker!
You're gonna give me
the location for Ledoux,
I'm gonna let you
slide, Ginger.
Bullshit.
What the fuck you think
I want with you, huh?
Oh, goddamn.
I am so done talking
to you like a man.
Go, go, go.
We have multiple gunshots.
217, multiple suspects...
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org