Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ the war was lost ♪
♪ the treaty signed ♪
♪ I was not caught ♪
♪ I crossed the line ♪
♪ though many tried ♪
♪ I live among you ♪
♪ well disguised ♪
♪ I had to leave ♪
♪ my life behind ♪
♪ I dug some graves ♪
♪ you'll never find ♪
♪ the story's told ♪
♪ with facts and lies ♪
♪ I have a name ♪
♪ but never mind ♪
♪ never mind ♪
♪ I had to leave
my life behind ♪
♪ the story's told ♪
♪ with facts and lies ♪
♪ you own the world,
so never mind ♪
♪ this was your heart,
this swarm of flies ♪
♪ this was once your mouth,
this bowl of lies ♪
♪ you serve them well,
I'm not surprised ♪
♪ you're of their kin,
you're of their kind ♪
♪ the war was lost ♪
♪ the treaty signed ♪
♪ I was not caught ♪
♪ I crossed the line ♪
♪ though many tried ♪
♪ I live among you ♪
♪ well disguised ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
♪ some say love ♪
♪ it is a river ♪
♪ and that it drowns
the tender reed ♪
♪ and some say love ♪
♪ it's like a razor ♪
♪ and that it leaves
your soul to bleed ♪
♪ some say love ♪
♪ it is a hunger ♪
♪ an endless,
aching need... ♪
You got your father's hands.
♪ I say love ♪
♪ it is a flower... ♪
My father made me nervous.
Maybe you were already nervous.
Maybe you lacked grit.
♪ it's the heart... ♪
I see you...
running through the trees.
You're small.
The trees are like giants.
Men are chasing you.
I'm right here.
You step out of the trees.
You ain't that fast.
Oh, son...
they kill you.
They shoot you to pieces.
♪ who cannot seem to give ♪
♪ and the soul... ♪
Where is this?
I don't know.
You were here first.
♪ when the night ♪
♪ has been too lonely ♪
♪ and the road ♪
♪ has been too long ♪
♪ and you think ♪
♪ that love is only ♪
♪ for the lucky ♪
♪ and the strong ♪
♪ just remember ♪
♪ in the winter ♪
♪ far beneath ♪
♪ the bitter snow ♪
♪ lies the seed ♪
♪ that with the sun's love ♪
♪ in the spring ♪
♪ becomes the rose ♪
"Monstrous Mike's
Morning Mash-Up" moves on
with a little Zevon
to get you all the way up.
Pissed myself.
What the fuck, man?
I'm commanding officer
of this detail.
You call me you got something.
Well, I got shot.
That's something.
I found our murder scene.
That's something else.
You don't enter a scene
without your partner-- me.
I didn't know it was a scene.
I walk in, next thing
somebody shotgunned me.
- Twice.
- Then how are you still--
Rubber buckshot.
It's just impact.
Riot shells.
You know, like--
like cops use.
You all right?
Couple of cracked ribs.
Took one in the sternum,
so my heart aches.
And how did you
find this place?
Prost tip through a CI.
Said Caspere
took her here once.
All right.
Well, get cleared by a doctor.
See if you can
bring in the hooker.
Fuck, it smells like piss.
Burris is already inside.
So I'll go ahead
and take the day, Xena?
Everything goes through
Vinci PD Special Homicide Task Force.
What are you doing
with my scene, Lieutenant?
Securing it.
One of my men gets shot,
you better believe I'm on site.
It's all yours.
Soundproofing.
Christ.
It ain't working.
Look, this--
God damn it.
Is it the place?
This never happened to me
in my fucking life.
Maybe we could get
a room nearby.
Take our time.
I ain't got the time.
This is important, Frank.
No shit.
You don't think I know that?
There is no part of my life not overwrought
with live-or-die importance.
I take a shit,
there's a gun to my head
saying, "Make it a good one.
Don't fuck up."
Baby, just relax.
This whole thing is unnatural.
Don't feel right.
We talked about this.
A lot.
It's unnatural.
They already said I'm fine.
What does that mean?
What I said.
This. This.
Phenomenal motility,
the doc said.
God forgive me for misreading
what subtle clues
you embed for me
in your limp dick,
which is as wishy-washy
as your fucking mood.
So what if it's hard for us?
Like I'm your
fucking incubator.
Suck your own dick.
Bungalow was a business lease
through the Catalast Group.
Same place leased his car.
Utilities paid by Porpoise LLC,
which was Caspere's company.
And he had
a landline here, too.
Printed out the phone record.
If we don't get anything today,
I want you on working girls.
Put those looks to use.
Sure.
So I could not mention it,
but you're an adult.
All right.
That actress--
If you're asking me
if I did what she said,
then I'm gonna get out
of the fucking car.
Well, I was gonna ask
if you thought the exposure
would interfere
with doing fieldwork.
I seriously doubt it.
You should sue her
when it's over.
Chick's loaded.
Is that a fucking
e-cigarette?
You can't talk on the phone?
I'm trying to stay
off the phone.
What?
What do you got?
Who else knew about that spot?
Caspere's place?
You walked me
into something, Frank.
What are you on about?
Wow.
That's some luck on you.
Fuck.
Where's the girl
who gave up the place?
Caspere bought whores.
She was one of Danny Santos'.
My crew don't pimp.
Well, then maybe
she had a boyfriend.
You know,
set Caspere up for him.
Or maybe Caspere
was into so much dirt,
there's no telling
which side the ax came from,
because let me tell you,
there was some fucked-up psychology at work
in that place before
it was a murder scene.
Now, are you gonna tell me
what Caspere was doing with you
or do I wait to walk
into another dark room,
this time with real bullets?
There's a certain
stridency at work here.
I'm gonna put it off
to you getting blasted.
Oh, frankly, I'm apoplectic.
I'm feeling a little
apoplectic myself.
What's with the water?
Booze tends to take the edge off.
I want to stay angry.
Caspere had a lot
of my money in play.
Real estate.
Property adjacent
to the rail line.
How long did you know him?
Started working with him
the last few years.
He was here when we moved
out of the city.
They stole a hidden camera
after they shot me.
Hard drive.
Boggles the mind what might be on it.
Like I said,
I'm gonna put off the stridency.
Well, you do that, Frank.
Is Ray hurt?
What happened?
Somebody murdered him.
The mayor of Vinci
lives in Bel-Air?
Are you Betty Chessani?
We're state police, ma'am.
Veronica Chessani.
I'm Betty's stepmother.
Mrs. Chessani, do you mind if we ask
you a few questions?
Did you know Ben Caspere,
the Vinci city manager?
Only a little.
A dinner party I meet him once.
You guys have
a party last night?
No.
Is medicine for my eyes.
Hello.
Do you remember Mr. Caspere
and your husband
ever talking late at night?
No, I don't think.
Have you talked to Austin?
He say okay
for you coming here?
- Sure.
- Oh.
We're checking
because Mr. Caspere
kept an apartment in the city
and his phone records
show a lot of phone calls
coming to this house.
1:00, 2:00 AM.
I-- I don't--
I don't know.
I don't pay attention.
Is upstairs line.
Business.
So how long have you been
married to Mr. Chessani?
Mayor Chessani.
Never mister,
he says.
For a year.
And how'd you guys meet?
A party.
Hey.
Everything all right?
And stay down there, you dumb bitch.
I tell you to keep
these whores from my house.
Yo, Ronnie,
who the fuck these people?
State police.
Cover yourself.
Got a warrant?
Why you hurt me like this, huh?
Yo, why don't you
chug a pot of coffee?
Take a Xanax
and chill your ass.
Bodine on his way down.
I called him.
People ain't happy
with y'all goose-stepping up in here.
You knew Ben Caspere?
Nah, some old guy
who worked with my pops.
No! No! No!
Who left door open?
Where'd you pick up
that accent?
Accent?
You racist woman.
Mm-mm.
I admit, it's a total put-on.
Different roles
for different jobs.
I have a lot of friends.
And what is it you do?
Specialty events.
I am an organizer.
What kind of events?
All kinds.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
y'all best to
get stepping 'fore my man Bodine
come in here with a lawyer,
chew your asses out.
You ain't got no jurisdiction
coming in here.
Burst capillaries,
cholesterol terrible,
your liver is redlining.
Can I ask how much you
drink in an average week?
All I can.
Drugs?
A few.
And I'll just go out
on a limb here
and guess that your diet
isn't particularly healthy.
Well, this,
you know, had me
thinking about, uh...
changing some things.
Well, it's certainly possible
to live with unhealthy habits,
but it helps if you don't
have every one under the sun.
Am I cleared?
I'd take a couple days,
but, yeah, you're cleared.
Burris says to clear
you at any rate.
Great.
All right, see you.
Can I ask you something,
Mr. Velcoro?
Do you want to live?
What are you doing here?
Vertical mall.
What do you need, Frank?
Gratitude, for starters.
Frank, you know I'm grateful.
I've told you.
Gratitude you can count.
Frank, what I pulled together
to take your shares back,
no one else would have
paid what I did.
And I'm grateful
with the rail corridor stuff.
It's great.
Thank you.
How many times do you expect
to be paid for the same thing?
Every month.
25% of your net.
I-- I already paid you.
Come on, man.
You moved on.
Things change.
If they change for me,
they can change for you.
Things are good right now.
That's good.
Maybe one day the Teamsters,
your electrical workers,
they get a problem
with this site.
Probity Loan that
loaned you that money
that lets you buy
into this gravy train,
they're gonna
call back the note
and you'll need a friend,
which is what I'm offering you.
How's Mary and the boys?
She stood by you, huh?
You like the schools
in Tarzana?
I want weekend deliveries.
And those electrician fucks,
they're charging me for five
guys when three will do.
There you go.
One hand in the other.
First of the month, Bart.
I'm not going anywhere.
He had a safe-deposit box
at a Bel-Air security firm.
Articles of incorporation
for a couple LLCs.
These corporations he had
formed within the last year.
We're looking into
asset listings now.
Good. They can use that
to follow his money.
No closer on a suspect?
Velcoro didn't see
who shot him?
Said they were masked.
You think he could
have staged that?
I mean, at the end of the day,
he just got banged up some.
Can't imagine why he would.
There was something else
in that box, too.
Blue diamonds.
We'll follow up
on the corporate holdings
and the prostitution
connections
while the lab processes
the apartment.
Caspere seems deep
with Catalast.
Nothing much public on them.
Own a lot of land.
Gotten close to Velcoro?
- My impression?
- Mm.
- Straight up?
Guy's a burnout.
Bitch comes into my house,
no warrant, no nothing,
harasses my wife, my children.
The mayor is very upset.
What did you find, Ray?
A murder scene in an
apartment in West Hollywood.
This private development group
Catalast rented it for Caspere.
And?
Oh, same kinds of weirdness
we found at his other place.
You know, his fetish shit.
And there was a spot where a
camera and a hard drive had been,
but the guy
that shot me took it.
And you didn't get
a look at him?
No. As soon as I turned,
I just saw the blast.
What about the cunt?
Bezzerides. She ask any
questions about the department?
No, not really.
Velcoro's dirty.
I want him.
I thought I was clear on that.
We got a crooked
Vinci cop we can leverage.
All the better.
He's a man, for Christ's sake.
Yeah, so what?
I'm not saying fuck him, but maybe
let him think you might fuck him.
Detective Bezzerides
isn't IA or UC.
She's tasked with a murder.
Sure. Sure.
And I'm not putting
this in a memo,
but Velcoro is worth a bonus.
I can see working
a promotion for you.
State attorney subpoenaed
our time sheets.
- Hmm.
- What's your next move on Caspere?
- Well--
- I want her badge.
I want her hick
sheriff boss's badge.
This state thing is gonna
get cleared up soon enough.
They're gonna come out
owing me and that--
that cunt is walking the plank.
Look, the camera taken means
there was something on it.
Maybe the killing,
maybe footage of the killer.
But he was traveling up and down
the state doing land deals.
Well, that's smoke and no fire.
Land deals aren't
gonna bring this in.
But keep working the hooker
angle and get it wrapped
before state makes this
part of their probe.
Clear?
Um...
Bezzerides is running
the case, sir.
Bezzerides is gonna be
running a yogurt stand.
So steer her
to something concrete.
I like a pimp for this.
Look, you want the truth?
Maybe this is a good
excuse to take me off.
You know?
I mean, she don't trust me.
And I ain't ever
exactly been Columbo.
What the fuck does that mean?
This is your best man?
You're on it, Ray, period.
How's the, uh, probe looking?
We'll work it out.
Yeah.
They treating you all right?
Like a cheerleader
on an oil rig.
Oh, shit.
Hey, thought your phone
was busted.
- I heard you were up here.
I thought I'd stop by. - Okay, yeah.
I've just-- I've been
working down south.
No, yeah, I know.
I know.
I just thought maybe
we could go grab a bite.
Ahem.
I can come down,
you know, since you're not
answering my phone calls.
Yeah, Steve, look,
you're a decent guy, but--
- Wait, wait, wait. Come on.
- This has run its course.
Okay?
No big deal.
You didn't do anything.
But you and I,
there's just not much there.
There's not much there?
Well, you could have fooled me.
You know, you fucking
started this.
Don't push this somewhere ugly.
Just be a little
mature about it.
- Have some dignity.
- Dignity?
You're a real suck 'em
and leave 'em type, huh?
You talk to me like that again,
you're gonna need a little
baggie to carry your teeth home.
- Mama's boy.
- What?
Stop. Stop. Get the fuck
out of my squad room.
All right.
You know, you got serious
problems, Detective.
I'm whittling them down.
- Wow.
- Yeah?
- Nice.
- You got something to say?
Nothing at all.
Ah!
You could just drink
from the bottle.
Drink out the bottle,
you got a problem.
You know that last shit you
gave me kept me up all night.
Thought I could
hear your mother.
Well, not that.
It's indica.
The smell of burning flesh.
Your own.
Well, then talk! What did
you do with the stuff?
Now wait a minute, fellas.
Louis is okay.
I had a dream
about you.
I can't ever
remember my dreams.
Barely sleep anyway.
Where's your badge?
Well, it's...
You shouldn't do that.
Whatever you saw on the news
or whatever pissed you off,
you'll wake up one day
and you'll miss it.
I won't miss it.
There ain't no PD anymore.
Well, if you're gonna throw
it away, I'll take it.
I'll give it to Chad.
Pull. Have you got any
friends with push like that?
You been eating?
Nah, I don't get hungry.
Well, that grass
will give you an appetite.
Put you to sleep, too.
Mm.
How's your boy?
He's all right.
It's hard being a kid.
We don't see each other
as much as we'd like.
Pop, the guys in Vinci, you
knew Kevin Burris a little.
Holloway the chief?
Holloway's a good man.
Hard charger.
Old school.
Worked them tough beats
under Gates.
Back when you could
actually do police work.
Yeah, Burris, too.
Why'd he leave?
Set up shop in Vinci?
'Cause he's fucking smart.
Then after the riots and OJ,
we just couldn't
do the job right.
So he said so long
to those cunts
and, phew...
headed on out of town.
I should have been
looking ahead.
Wouldn't have
no half pension now.
Anyways, I hadn't
seen you in a while.
Yeah.
I figured you needed
your medicine.
Look at that shit.
Kirk Douglas.
No country for white men, boy.
I guess I'll take off, then.
I don't get it.
We'll be in Vegas for a few days.
I have other business.
Gives me time to confer
with my people.
We can talk next week.
A month ago it sounded
like we were a done deal.
We've been over this, Frank.
I don't make
these decisions myself.
And Caspere?
My thinking is this is somehow
connected to you getting cold feet.
Sure.
We're not stupid.
What you had sewn up,
the stitching's frayed, Frank.
This is too big
to walk away from.
I don't ask permission.
I wasn't talking about you.
You leaving?
Bon fucking voyage.
All right, Frank.
Fucking Commie Jew fuck.
Where's Blake?
I messaged him.
And Stan--
why isn't he here?
Shouldn't
a reasonable man infer
from Osip's arrival
and departure
and fucking failure
to make good on our terms
as being connected
not just to Caspere,
but prefiguring Caspere?
In a causal sense.
I'm saying...
do you think Osip
could have done Caspere?
Not my department.
But if you're asking me
is he that kind of guy,
he looks half anaconda
and half great white.
So I saw that paper, bro.
Thought I'd check up on you.
Got you downrange, huh?
It's bullshit.
I'm half working
this thing for state.
Supposed to see me through.
So?
So fuck no, I didn't.
Yeah, well,
I didn't think you did.
So you been going to meetings?
I went the first year.
I mean, if you want
to get over something,
maybe sitting around
and remembering it
in every detail
ain't the right way.
Yeah, well, the thing of it is
some of that knowledge
they spill makes sense.
Stuff about the past,
not denying it...
letting it be a part of you.
Yeah.
You working?
Yeah, just some things
here and there.
Mm, I got on with
the electricians union.
- Mm, great.
- Still a low man.
You ever miss it?
Yeah.
You know, I keep thinking
about the village.
Outside Al Awjar.
The valley.
Nice people, man.
Mountains.
We ain't soldiers anymore, man.
I remember thinking
I could have just stayed there.
Just forget finding the squad.
I mean...
I think, like,
that was like the--
it was the last time
shit felt right for me, bro.
You mean combat.
Would you ever go back to it?
I don't think so.
Didn't think I'd stay on
as long as I did.
And then it was hard to see
coming home, you know?
That's not what I mean.
You know
what I'm talking about.
Them three days.
- I think about you, man.
- Stop it.
Why? What if I don't
want to forget, huh?
Dude, you should go.
- I'm out.
- Hey, look.
Don't pretend, all right?
Don't pre--
Hey, hey, hey.
You see that?
Fuck you, asshole.
Woodrugh, I'm sorry, man.
I didn't mean for that.
I'm sorry, man.
I'm drunk.
I am drunk.
I'm sorry.
City traffic cams came back.
Ventura picked this one up
1:00 AM night of the murder.
Caddy pulling onto PCH
from the 33.
Car's registered to a film
transportation department.
That flick
they're shooting here?
Got it in one.
You're back.
Yeah, not for lack of trying.
Caspere arranged
our tax incentives.
Only way you can film
anything in California now.
Threw him a coproducer credit.
We're real sorry to
hear what happened.
Cut!
- Was he around here much?
- No.
I mean, he came by--
we were in prep,
helped out with PD, zoning.
That producer credit
come with a paycheck?
Back end, yeah.
What about that car?
The Caddy?
Went missing
one morning last week.
We filed it stolen
with sheriff's.
Put in the insurance
papers yesterday.
I'll bring you
to our transpo head.
Yeah, Monday
morning it was gone.
Lock on the gate was bolt cut.
Sheriff's took a report.
Any personnel missing?
No, nothing unusual.
We had a driver quit the week
before due to family issues.
I never knew the Caspere guy.
I need names and addresses of
everyone in your department.
Sure. Yeah.
Cut.
Fuck it.
Check the gate.
Let's move.
Hey, what's this thing about?
About two tons of shit.
Some collapse of
civilization revenge flick.
Ought to make it a silent picture
the way the guy does his lines.
- That's your job?
- Yeah, set photographer.
It's the best use
of my time so far.
You ever--
you ever seen this guy around?
Yeah, I've seen him.
Some city guy.
Wants to brush shoulders
with the industry, I guess.
Heard he partied with
our director once or twice.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, Daisun was going on
about some party they went to.
Well-attended, he said.
I mean pussy.
Like, wall to wall.
I guess being the set photographer
don't rate an invite.
Yeah, it was just like
a dinner, drinks thing.
Lots of suits,
potential investors.
What about girls?
Yeah, girls were there.
They are over half
the population.
Were there any hookers
at this party?
I really wouldn't
know that, ma'am.
- Hmm.
- Where was it?
Somewhere up above Ventura.
I really don't remember.
Tell you the truth, I drink.
So it makes
my recollection unreliable.
Jack, get everyone up
for a rehearsal.
I'll be there in a sec.
Burning dollars.
Yeah.
I still work for the
city manager's office.
With Mr. Caspere--
with what happened,
they sent me down to collect
copies of the tax agreements.
Why? Something
wrong with them?
I don't think so.
They're just trying to get all
the city's paperwork in order.
With the state's inquiry.
All right.
Thank you.
The fuck have you been?
You take off on me now?
Just with my lady.
- My-- my phone died.
- Your fucking phone died?
Am I a goddamn teenage girl?
Frank, Stan.
What about him?
He's dead.
Couple of our Mexicans
found him, boss.
What is this, huh?
Who the fuck would have
something against Stan?
Don't make any fucking sense.
What is he to anybody?
Too much coming
right after Caspere.
No shit.
Who, huh?
Who the fuck's coming after me?
Huh? Who?
Get Santos, Fregredo,
Constantine,
anybody that works
on our property
or what used to be
our property now tonight!
Santos' place.
What are you thinking?
Just fucking do what I tell ya.
Pack him up.
He deserves better than this.
How you guys doing?
You ever see this guy around?
Mm-mm.
You ever see this guy?
♪ oh, there are killers ♪
♪ oh, in this town ♪
♪ oh, oh, killer, killers ♪
♪ with all their killer plans ♪
♪ a war is ♪
♪ on the horizon... ♪
You guys ever see
this guy around?
Look, I'm not vice.
I don't give a shit
who fucks who here.
No?
I've seen him before.
Where?
Never dated him, I mean,
but he'd been around
a few times.
I was working.
Good with faces.
Where was this?
Couple times, this club
a couple blocks down.
Lux Infinitum.
You been there?
No.
Is it big with hookers?
Big with all sorts.
But, yeah, they got
some prime time in there.
It's one of them
circuit clubs, you know?
Trade runs through.
Some European.
That pussy is expensive, so...
yeah, you got party people,
but also suits and whatnot.
All right.
Thanks.
They're not gonna talk to you.
They probably wouldn't
even let you in.
This angsty cop drama
you're rolling.
You like models, I guess?
Yeah, started building
them with my kid.
Then I just started
doing them without him.
Thanks.
Shit.
Just a minute.
Hey.
Look, Ray, I, uh--
I just wanted
to see about Chad.
Yeah, I don't want to
repeat that conversation.
I don't want to do that.
I think you've got
worse trouble.
State police officers
came to see us.
Investigators, two of them.
Wanted to know about you.
Wanted to know what?
If I ever saw extra cash
you couldn't account for.
If I had ever known you
to be violent.
If I, uh...
ever knew or suspected
you took retribution on
the man who attacked me.
It's 10,000.
For what?
To not contest the custody.
We just-- we just want to
do what's best for Chad.
You think you can buy my son?
No, it's for...
it's to just go, Ray.
It's an alternative.
Go somewhere.
Before we can't turn back.
Whatever happens,
those questions,
a custody battle,
it's not gonna
be easy for Chad.
So don't start it.
The way those two
investigators sounded,
it's a matter of time, Ray.
You put that envelope away.
I'm gonna pretend like you never
really thought I'd take it.
I didn't.
But I hoped I might be wrong.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we should
get back to work.
Yeah, he liked it here.
One of them older guys,
never left the bar,
just wait for the girl
to walk up.
Thank you.
You know anyone
he ever left with?
Uh, a few of the girls
here for sure,
but I wouldn't try
talking to them.
You'd just get them
into trouble.
- He like boys?
- More like he likes to watch.
Had me and this girl
go at it while he sat in the corner.
You do girls.
In a pinch.
With the right medication.
Who's this girl?
Fuck.
Her name's Tascha.
She's one of them Euro tricks.
Hasn't been around lately.
One of those elite bitches,
worked those private parties.
What kind of parties?
I just heard about them.
Expensive, private, rich men.
Maybe she found a sugar daddy.
Doubles.
You know, Frank,
I don't know what this is,
but, look, I don't
run things like that.
I mean, shit, who does anymore?
Mexicans?
Russians?
That's a good
question-- who?
Who has something to gain
by trying to fuck with me?
You think it was someone here?
What's in it?
What he means is
what you got worth
taking anymore, Frank?
My associate.
His name's Ben Caspere.
He was into that sweet
Eastern Bloc pussy
you all run between clubs.
So some of you might have
girls that know him.
Daniel here did.
And what I need you
to do now for me
is put the word out.
Any john you rob,
any flea, any tick
crawls across your carpet,
you ask them about Ben Caspere.
You find out
who wants what's mine.
Frankie, I think
you got us confused
with them bitches upstairs.
Appreciate our past dealings,
but you're the one
that left all that behind.
This ain't your club no more.
Those days done been over.
You're straight, right?
Why don't you call a cop?
Stay where you fuckin' are.
Yeah, I know.
You put them crazy eyes on
and everybody's supposed
to shit their pants.
Thing is, you ain't
that thing no more
what you used to was.
He speak for all of you?
I'm speaking for me.
Yeah, you're tall,
but you're really little,
and you're old.
Yo, this meeting is over.
Y'all motherfuckers
get out of my place.
Will you talk this much
when I rip your
fuckin' lip off?
All right, Frankie.
You wanna squab?
You can keep your rings on.
Won't matter to me.
All right.
No!
I've always hated
these fucking things.
What kind of way is that
to greet the world?
Ah! Ah!
We heard you quit your job as
a driver a couple weeks back.
Yes, he took care of me.
I was sick.
And he couldn't take
the sitting all day.
He's a good boy.
You live here with her?
Only sometimes.
I got a place with friends.
A car was stolen
from where you work.
He wouldn't do it.
He ain't been in trouble
since he was a little boy.
Yo, yo, all's I did
was quit my job.
Got a lumbar problem.
Is that the fucking car?
Hey!
Hey, hold on!
Don't move!
Police!
Fuck.
Get outta here!
Ugh! Oh!
Stop, motherfucker!
Fuck!
Oh! You're gonna
burn it all!
Son of a bitch.
Ah! God damn it!
Oh, fuck!
My fucking ribs.
That was him.
That was fucking him.
Fuck.
Thank you.
You wanna thank me,
tell me what state has on me.
I don't know.
I waited for you.
What happened?
We should make up.
I thought...
I stayed up.
Do you wanna talk?
Maybe tomorrow.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ in time you find
your way to release ♪
♪ and then it goes away again ♪
♪ what had been the strongest
force against you ♪
♪ becomes your only friend ♪
♪ you can't help but laugh ♪
♪ and I own your soul ♪
♪ a shadow unwanted
by any on earth ♪
♪ most of us rejoice
at your awful crying ♪
♪ we live to force you
to regret your own birth ♪
♪ the balance of love
is shifting ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org