There's an Oxford in your world,
too? Has it got scholars?
Maybe I can find one who can
tell me about Dust.
People are going to be looking
for me. Bad people, the police.
You mustn't draw attention to us.
Charles. Lizzie.
If you ever want to know more about
these artefacts...
Well, they came to the lab.
She's followed Asriel, she's
followed him through that window.
You're a scholar?
Believe it or not, I am, yeah.
I need you to tell me about
the particles you study.
There's a knife in a tower,
surrounded by angels.
The legends are true. This knife,
the boy will lead us to it.
Your parents exchanged letters.
For some reason, the police think
that they're important.
You were right, he came to us.
I have concerned myself with a man
named Stanislaus Grumman.
People say he knows the whereabouts
of some kind of object
that gives magical protection.
I thought I might find this item for
her and get her that protection.
If I don't find out about Dust,
Roger's death will be for nothing.
We study something called
dark matter. That's Dust.
I found the scholar!
She's called Mary Malone and she's
got an engine that can see Dust,
and she's going to make it talk.
It says you have something
important to do.
The Magisterium in my world want to
destroy Dust.
They think Dust is evil.
I think what they do is evil.
Did it really say my dad was alive?
You can trust me.
I'm leaving.
Are you going to find Asriel?
I'm in search of something
infinitely more valuable.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
SERAFINA: Witches of Lake Enara,
hear me.
We are facing devastation on
a scale not seen in centuries.
The Magisterium will pay for
their crimes,
but we cannot lose sight
of the great war ahead.
The prophecy states that life in all
of the worlds depends on the child.
She is more important
now than ever.
We must find Lyra
before anyone else does.
PAN: We're not really
doing this, are we?
I promised Mary I would,
and I think that machine
has more to tell us.
But the alethiometer was clear.
We need to help Will
find his father.
First, we need to find out more
about Dust. For Roger.
If it's such a good idea... Sh!
WHISPERS: ..then why
are we creeping?
We need to stay with Will.
It's too dangerous
for Will in Oxford.
The police are looking for him.
But the alethiometer
said that we should...
Lyra, are we sure about this?
It's fine, there's no-one around.
Lee Scoresby...
..I call ye and declare ye now.
Return!
Return.
Return...
WIND WHISTLES
Lee, we're moving.
The wind is a-whistling!
Lee, wake up!
That's weird.
We weren't heading for Yenisei.
Looks like the kind of place
a famous explorer might wind up.
You said that about
the last three towns.
We're on our way, Mr Grumman.
FLAMES ROAR
REPORTER: John Parry, what will you
be taking with you from home?
JOHN: If I could,
I'd take everything from home.
But I can't do that,
so a toy car of my son's.
ELAINE: This world is broken.
It takes extraordinary people
to fix it.
JOHN: Sorry, Will.
ELAINE: Like your dad. Like you.
JOHN: Truly epic letters.
ELAINE: Like you...
Take up his mantle.
JOHN: My darling Elaine.
We've finally arrived.
We're stuck 140 miles
south of the island...
Dearest Elaine.
I'm lying awake here,
thinking of you.
It's nearly summer solstice...
..22nd of August.
Such agony to leave you behind.
Do send more news of our boy.
Lyra! Are you awake?
We need to talk to
the alethiometer again.
My dad's alive.
We can find him.
Lyra?
What did you tell Lyra?
Let's see if we can make this work.
Oh, come on, you did better
than that for Lyra.
Hello.
I'm DI Walters.
I'm interested in a visitor
you had yesterday.
PAN: How much longer
am I going to be in this bag?
Mary!
SOFTLY: You have to go.
Why are we whispering?
There's a policeman in my office
asking questions about you.
He knows you came to see me
yesterday.
How does he know? I have no idea.
Lyra, are you in trouble?
Do you need help?
Sorry to keep you waiting,
I was just...
Can you both step into
the office, please?
What a wonderful moustache.
We heard there was a child
running unsupervised
around St Peter's College.
What's your name?
Lizzie. What's yours?
I'm Inspector Walters, Lizzie,
and I've got a few questions,
if that's OK with you.
Of course.
Where are you from?
I'm from London.
But you're staying in Oxford.
I am.
With whom?
With some people. Friends.
What's their address?
I don't know exactly,
but I can find it out for you,
if you want.
Is this really necessary?
Shouldn't we wait for
the girl's parents?
Do you go to school?
Yes, sometimes.
But you're not at school today.
Well, it's the holidays.
I really don't think
this is appropriate.
And you've come to see
Dr Malone today because...?
I'm interested in her work.
Lizzie is welcome here any time.
Do you understand her work?
Some of it.
Is Will staying with you?
Yes, he is. He's...
Where is he...
..Lyra?
Sorry, could I speak to you
over here, please?
I really think that
the girl's guardian... No! No!
MARY GASPS
Stop her!
PORTER: No running!
Help me, Pan!
PAN: Take a left, Lyra,
just down here.
DI WALTERS: Student suspect...
PAN: This way!
PAN: I can't see him.
Maybe we lost him.
Lizzie, isn't it? From the museum.
You look lost. Can I give you
a lift somewhere?
No.
Are you sure?
Hey!
Actually, yes.
Where to?
Summertown.
SEAT BELT WARNING BEEPS
Seat belt.
It's on the right-hand side,
pull it across you.
Did you find anything more about
those skulls you were looking at?
I found it fascinating.
I asked about them after we spoke.
BUCKLE CLICKS
BEEPING STOPS
Are you OK?
Um, yeah, it's just...
I...
I can't be late, my mum will worry.
I'm sure she will.
BELT CONTINUES TO
LOCK AS SHE TUGS
I-I think I know where I am now,
you can just drop me off
wherever you like.
I'd rather take you home,
save anyone worrying about you.
It's fine, honestly,
just let me out.
Just let me out!
Please, Mr Latrom, let me out.
SEAT BELT UNBUCKLES
DOOR LOCK BEEPS
Lizzie!
Your bag.
Thank you.
Until next time.
SHE PANTS NERVOUSLY
PAN CHIRPS
It's gone. What?
WAIT!
He's stolen the alethiometer.
He was nothing but a thief!
You know, I've got
a good feeling about this one.
It was getting dark about this time.
I still had the club in this hand,
and I was thinking about
what he'd just said...
..and he said it again.
To which, I said to him...
You want to guess what I said?
I can't imagine.
I said...
.."No."
That's it? Mm-hm.
Well, that is some story
you got there.
Actually, now that we're friends,
maybe you could help me out.
You heard of
a Stanislaus Grumman?
Mm.
Strange man.
Lean, tough,
curious about everything...
You know where he is?
You know, he was a geologist
or an archaeologist.
Some say he became a shaman
and went to live way off
in the wilderness
with some folk up the Yenisei.
That's interesting.
But the last I heard, he died.
He died?
A trader told me Grumman
got his leg caught in a trap -
cut it right to the bone.
We had a man in here last week
said Grumman survived that trap.
Well, that's great news.
He tell you anything else?
He worked at the observatory
for a while,
up the mountain,
not far from here.
Maybe try up there.
Thank you.
OK, if I've got this right,
you should be able to make words
and I should be able to hear them.
It's just a simple question
that needs a simple answer.
Is Lyra safe?
One word - yes or no.
SHE TYPES
Lyra?
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
What are you after?
You know, maybe I can help.
I know this place backwards.
Who's that in the tower? No-one.
There's definitely someone up there.
It'll be a ghost or something,
I don't know.
Wouldn't surprise me
if it's haunted. It's a person.
It can't be.
There's no way in and no way out.
What's it for, then?
The Torre degli Angeli?
It belongs to the Guild.
The Guild?
No-one knows much about
them, really,
but my brother says
they're this group of men
who know important stuff
like philosophy, alchemy...
Cowards, mind you -
they ran away when
the Spectres came,
just like all the other grown-ups,
and now only the children
are left here.
They get your parents?
The Spectres?
No. You're lucky.
Got mine.
Right in front of me.
Ate the life out of 'em.
I'm sorry.
Makes you nervous,
being on your own.
It does.
I'd best be off.
You need a plan.
You're almost a grown-up,
and you know what that means.
Won't be long before
the Spectres are after you.
I'm not scared.
That's because
you've never seen them at work.
STEADY BEEPING
Is Lyra safe?
ANGRILY: Right, then.
Maybe I'm going mad.
Still no sign of the girl. Sorry?
She got away, apparently, the kid.
Oh, right.
Well, I'll be sure to keep
an eye out, of course.
Night, George.
BEEPING INTENSIFIES
SCRATCHY INTERFERENCE
HE PANTS
Hello, sir!
Close the door, please.
What brings you to the observatory,
Mr Scoresby?
I've just got a couple of questions,
if you don't mind.
Wow, this is something.
It is.
Even better when the fog lifts.
Well, I'll bet.
Can't do anything about that?
No, you can't control the weather.
It's a powerful force.
Don't I know it.
You work here alone?
Yes. The others...
It's just me.
Dr Haley, could I ask you about
a Dr Stanislaus Grumman?
An Englishman, despite the name.
I understand he worked here
some years ago.
What do you want with Dr Grumman?
Uh... You wouldn't happen to know
where he is now, do you?
Somewhere up the Yenisei river.
Why do you want to know?
So he is alive?
Dr Stanislaus Grumman...
..is a heretic.
I didn't know that.
Well, you've been most helpful.
We'd better get going -
the weather being what it is.
"By their fruits shall ye know them.
"By their questions
shall ye see the serpent
"gnawing at their heart."
GROWLS
Amen.
You have a good day.
Well, that was weird.
Yenisei river, though, that's...
GUNSHOTS
Ah!
Dr Haley...
Damn fool, why did you do that?!
Don't.
Let me help you.
Dr Grumman is an enemy
of the Magisterium.
And so are you.
He didn't give us a choice.
You didn't shoot to kill.
We need to go.
Is there any place left
that the damn Magisterium...
..hasn't infiltrated?!
Let's get out of here.
AGGRESSIVE BARKING
DOORBELL RINGS
Hi!
Oh! Oh, hi. Hi.
You forgot, didn't you?
No, I would never forget
my favourite niece and nephew
coming to visit.
I just got home, actually.
We haven't had our snack today.
Yeah, I felt faint
in the car.
Well, that is shocking.
Let me see what I have - I haven't
been shopping for a few days.
Oh, there you are.
Yes!
Mine says "muesli" on it.
With chocolate!
It's really bad for you, I promise.
Why are you always reading my mail?
There has to be some way of finding
out what's going on in your life.
You look knackered.
I'm not knackered.
I'm just frustrated. I'm on
the cusp of a massive breakthrough,
and they're going to kick us
out of the lab in a few days.
When was the last time
you did something you enjoyed?
Ah!
What's going to happen if
you take some time out from work?
A break could lead to that
breakthrough, couldn't it?
BIRDS CHATTER
Now, what will we do? I told you
we shouldn't have come back.
What are you doing
just going off like that?
What happened? What's wrong?
I've lost it.
Lost what?
The alethiometer - someone took it.
But we need it. Without that,
we'll never find my dad.
I know!
And that's not everything.
What?
When I went to see the scholar...
..the police were
there asking about you.
They must've spotted us yesterday.
We need to go back to Cittagazze.
Now! No, we can't leave
without the alethiometer.
We can't do anything without it.
Do you have any idea
who took it, then?
There was this man I met
at the museum.
He gave me a lift.
Wait, Lyra, the card.
Yes! He gave me his card.
Charles Latrom. That's his address.
Let's go round there,
see what he says.
SIRENS
The police'll be looking for us
both now -
we have to hide
until it's dark. Come on.
SCREECHES
GRUNTING
SNIFFS
Hold back, I know that bird.
Serafina Pekkala sends good wishes
to the bear-king.
I send them back.
But if it's help you're after,
I cannot give it.
I see the mountains are melting.
The seals have depleted -
my bears will starve.
Asriel's hole in the sky
has damaged too much.
I am not here on Serafina's behalf,
but for Lyra Silvertongue.
GRUNTS
The Magisterium are making hell
for the witches,
but all Serafina cares about
is finding the girl.
There is a prophecy that says
she is to bring the end of destiny,
to return our free will,
not in this world, but far beyond.
Does Lyra know of this?
She must do it in ignorance.
If she's told what she must do,
it will all fail.
GROWLS
So Lyra's a toy for your future,
set on a course she can't change.
It is for all our futures.
We are all subject to the Fates.
I couldn't follow her
up the mountain,
but, later, I returned...
..and saw traces in the snow.
She followed Asriel through.
Thank you.
The Magisterium,
how do they target you?
They have destroyed our homes,
killed our people,
but we will find our own justice
for that.
INDISTINCT SPEECH
Yes, ma'am.
DOG BARKS
Apologies for the unscheduled stop,
ma'am.
We've secured a room for you
and we'll resume our journey
as soon as conditions improve.
For your sake, I hope that we do.
Room 17, left at the top
of the stairs.
Second outsider we've had in today.
Really?
We had an aeronaut in earlier,
and I've just heard
he's been arrested.
METALLIC CLANGING
Who are you
and what do you want?
Is that how you greet visitors?
Did you bring food? No.
Then, who are you
and what do you want?
You are not endearing yourself
to me, Mr Scoresby.
Madam, I've done nothing wrong.
I don't know where you think
I've deviated,
but I happen to think
the Magisterium
is one of the finest organisations
around,
and I will happily make
any sort of pledge to prove it.
Whatever you want, name it.
So, can I go now?
Hmm.
What does the name
Lyra Belacqua mean to you?
Let me think. Gee, I don't know.
What does it mean to you?
SHE LAUGHS
This is serious.
Your life depends on it.
Oh, is she any relation
to Asriel Belacqua?
Cos I've always been a fan of his.
Often thought one day
I'd meet that man,
shake his hand and ask him
how he did it all.
You know exactly who I am,
don't you?
And I know who you are.
I don't think we've been
properly introduced.
Lee Scoresby.
The famous aeronaut.
HE GROANS
Where is Lyra?
Can't help you there.
Well, that's interesting
because the last time I saw her,
she was flying off
from my station in your balloon.
I ain't never going to tell you
where to find that little girl
because my life is worth one-tenth
of hers. Indeed, it is.
But you do misunderstand me,
Mr Scoresby.
SHE SIGHS
I'm her mother.
So? So she needs me.
No, she doesn't.
There are things that
she just doesn't understand.
See, I think there are things
that you don't understand.
The worth of a life would be one.
Didn't you shoot a man dead
this morning?
Do you have children, Mr Scoresby?
No. Then, how can
you possibly understand
what it feels like?
I need...
..to find her.
You love her.
Of course I do.
It's not enough, though, is it?
Love.
It doesn't mean you won't hurt her,
doesn't mean she's safe with you.
It doesn't work that way.
Just tell me where she is.
I can't...
..because I do love her.
And I swore I'd keep her safe.
She's safe with me. The woman
who turns children into ghosts?
I don't think so.
SHE SNORTS
SCREECHES
HE GROANS
Yeah, I've got very few skills
in life...
..almost nothing to offer
the world, if I'm honest...
..but I did find out at a young age
I'm good with pain.
This one time, my father hit me
so hard with his shoe,
my leg swelled up.
I couldn't sit. I couldn't stand.
I couldn't do anything.
He says to me, "Don't you even
think about running away."
Run away?
I couldn't reach down
to put on my shoes.
FEIGNING SYMPATHY: Mm.
HE GROANS
Yeah.
He'd humiliate me until
I'd said enough sorries
to make up for whatever thing
he decided that day
would justify his temper.
You know?
You do know, don't you?
You know...because you had parents
just like mine, of course you did.
Of course you did.
SHE SCOFFS
You know nothing about me.
Yeah, and I believed it.
I believed him, I believed I was
nothing, believed I deserved it.
I was almost grateful for it
when it came.
Ever feel that? Grateful?
You did, didn't you?
I know what it's like
to feel hurt like yours.
But, right now, I feel more alive
than I have in years
because of her.
She's given me hope.
SCREECHES
I will rip out every nail
and I will break every bone...
And it won't break me,
and you know it won't,
because it wouldn't
break you either.
You can threaten me, torture me...
..but I will never tell you
where Lyra is.
Because my life
is worth one-tenth of hers.
SCREECHES
It's been a long time since
you've talked about him.
I know.
You did good.
SHE BREATHES ANXIOUSLY
WARBLES COMFORTINGLY
TRILLS SOFTLY
Paddington...
Paddington? Paddington!
LIFT DINGS
Psst! Mr Brown, in here.
What are you doing?
We need to get into that archive.
Sorry. Sorry.
Paddington, please don't
take this the wrong way,
but are you certain
there was an explorer?
You didn't just find a hat
and make up some...?
What?
WHISPERS: Just sit down.
Why are you looking at me like that?
This should be a safe place
to hide for a while.
Is it me, or is it hot in here?
Why do I feel so...? Uncomfortable?
Mm. Flushed?
Mm. Queasy?
Mm.
It's called a hard stare.
My aunt taught me to do them when
people had forgotten their manners.
Give me strength.
Mr Brown, you can trust me.
There really was an explorer.
If we can find him,
I know he'll give me a home.
A proper home.
What is this?
It's popcorn. It's disgusting!
It tastes like wood shavings.
Then stop eating it!
I'm trying.
Do you take anything seriously?
Is that why you came looking for me?
You thought I was messing around?
Just because I'm not sat
in a corner crying
doesn't mean I don't
take things seriously.
I lost my best friend.
He was killed by my father.
And I think about him
every single day and I miss him.
I want to talk to him.
I want to tell him I'm sorry
because it's my fault he died.
AUDIENCE MEMBER: Sh!
I came looking for you because
I was worried about you.
HER BREATHING ACCELERATES
SHE EXHALES DEEPLY
SCREECHES
HISSES
You stole them from the guard.
Thank you!
There's a prophecy.
About Lyra.
Witches speak of it,
and it means people will be looking
for her, and not all of them good.
So you mustn't trust anyone.
I'm searching for Lyra myself,
but if you find her...
..please...
..keep her safe.
I will.
I promise.
Resurrection comes
in the strangest of forms.
Do you think you can stand?
I hope so.
How are we going to find Grumman?
Head up the Yenisei river,
see if we can find him up there.
GRUNTING
Are we getting the balloon back? No.
It's exactly what they'll expect.
We can't fly out of here.
So, what do we do?
If we can get ourselves a boat,
we should be on the water by dawn.
GUARDS SHOUT
Find Grumman and his item
of protection,
then find Lyra
before her mother does.
Now.
DOG BARKS AND GROWLS
INSISTENT BARKING
OK...
SHE EXHALES
WHISPERS
ENGINE WHIRS SOFTLY
BEEPING INTENSIFIES
SCRATCHY INTERFERENCE
"To the mind that is still...
"..the whole universe surrenders."
SHE SIGHS
This is it.
Come on.
You ready?
Lizzie?
What a pleasant surprise.
You'd better come in.
ALARM PASSCODE BEEPS
It's nice to see you again so soon.
Take a seat.
You haven't introduced me
to your friend, Lizzie.
This is...
..Mark.
What can I do for you, Lizzie...
..and Mark?
Lizzie thinks she left something
of hers in your car earlier.
We've come to ask for it back.
I take it you mean this.
That's mine! Yours?
I think you'll find it's mine.
I'm a collector. You're a thief.
So let me call the police
and they can settle this.
No!
No?
Not in your best interest, William.
Or yours, Lyra.
SHE GASPS
You still don't recognise me.
You're not as astute...
..as your mother.
The party in London.
Now she remembers.
You don't even know
what you've stolen.
Lyra, stop.
You're just going to stick it on
a shelf, so give it back.
Can't do that.
Give it back! Lyra!
Sit down before I call the police.
I was going to give you
a chance...to earn it back.
Get me the object that I want...
..and I'll return
the alethiometer to you.
What is it that you want?
I'm aware you found a doorway...
..that leads to another world.
A crossroads world.
The man that made that doorway...
..has a knife.
I think he's hiding in the tower,
the one with the carved angels
around it.
Torre degli Angeli.
Bring the knife to me...
..and I'll give you what you want.
We'll do it.
Good.
We'll get your knife.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org