What have you found, Lyra?
This is about the human
and his daemon, Pan.
MOANING
We believe that there is an
organisation that is capturing
children and taking them north.
We're going to get him back.
Lyra? We're more likely to find
Roger with them than on our own.
They want to get their children
back - we can trust them.
It worked.
She can read the alethiometer.
She will be more valuable to us
than any soldier we have.
Set a course for Trollesund.
Colonel John Parry. He travelled
from my world to yours.
He left a wife and a child.
This is Kaisa, daemon
of Serafina Pekkala.
Where are they now?
Four days northeast of here.
They call it The Station,
the witches call it Bolvangar.
Iorek Byrnison, we wish
to offer you employment.
I know the people you are seeking,
the child cutters.
HE HUFFS
Lee Scoresby - aeronaut for hire.
We need you, and the bear.
You need the bear and I'm secondary.
An armoured bear is nothing
without his armour.
The Magisterium have it hidden.
HE ROARS
These people need our help,
Iorek. Let's go give it.
Welcome aboard, Lee Scoresby.
This house, this family,
they're connected to someone
I desperately need to find.
Watch them and report back to me.
Witches hear the immortal whispers
of those who pass between
the worlds.
They speak of a child
who is destined to bring
the end of destiny.
If told what she must do,
she will fail.
But she won't walk alone.
There is a boy
whose fate is bound with hers.
Together, they will change
everything.
Careful in the back there, Tony!
I am.
We need those weapons.
Guard them well.
I am! Mr Scoresby,
you're not walking?
Three reasons.
One - I struggle terribly
with bunions.
Two - someone's got to protect
this balloon.
I can protect your balloon.
Protection requires
a certain expertise.
I've got expertise.
You got some, kid,
I'll give you that.
Number three - why walk
when you can ride?
Then why aren't you
in your balloon now?
Saving it for when it's needed.
Wouldn't it be useful to have
a view of what's ahead?
We have.
And a witch's daemon is a better
eye in the sky than I'll ever be.
KAISA SCREECHES
Mr Scoresby? Call me Lee.
We're going to win
this one, aren't we?
We're going to get those
children back.
Well, if I was a betting
man, I'd say no.
And I am a betting man.
But I can tell from your face
you want me to say yes,
so...yes.
You're not an easy man to
like. You know that, Lee?
So people tell me.
He comes home every lunchtime?
Every day.
And he looks after her full-time?
Seems so.
And none of the authorities
were involved?
No social services right now,
as far as I can see.
So no-one checks up on them?
Hmm.
There he is.
Right on time.
He seems like a good kid.
Lyra. You asked to see me?
Your bear? You were right.
We needed him.
He looks magnificent, doesn't he?
I wanted to consult your
symbol reader.
I want to know more about how
they're defending this place
- Bolvangar.
COGS CLICK
WHIRRING
Tartars.
A company of Tartars, Lord Faa,
guard The Station.
They have fences all around it.
60 men with rifles and bigger guns.
WHIRRING
It's trying to tell me
something else.
It's trying to warn me of something.
I suspect it's trying to warn
you of everything.
We're walking into a blood
battle here.
But we're ready.
Heave to, lads!
If you think that's bad, wait
till we hit the snow and ice!
The alethiometer told me...
I was asking about Bolvangar...
Hello, Lyra. Yes, hello.
..and it told me about
the next valley -
there's a village with
something horrible in it
and folks are troubled by a...
Yes?
..a ghost, I think.
Or something. It's connected to
our task, but I don't know how.
I think I need to go to it.
No.
I'll go alone.
So you want me to let you go
off on your own
to look for some horrible ghost?
We need to get to Bolvangar
to rescue our children.
Have you forgotten how much
you are hunted? By my mother?
Mmm.
I can't be afraid of my mother
for the rest of my life.
You taught me that.
All right.
I'll give you some other reasons.
We need you.
It's two days' walk to Bolvangar.
Anything could befall us.
Your skills with the
alethiometer keeps us safe.
The alethiometer says I need to go.
Well, Ma Costa's down there, mm-hm?
Do you want to go and tell
her that her son has to wait
because you went off on a whim?
It's not a whim.
I trust it.
I don't know why, but I need to go.
We can't let you go, Lyra.
This is too important.
I'm sorry.
MUFFLED CHATTER
Do you trust me?
Are you eating with us?
There's somewhere else I need to go.
A fishing settlement.
The alethiometer says I must go.
Farder Coram won't let me.
He give you a reason why?
Because they want to carry on
to Bolvangar
cos they need to get Billy back.
And Roger.
Tony, look after the food.
I'll burn it.
I don't care.
What do you say is in this village?
I'm not sure, but it might be
some sort of ghost, I think.
Something awful has happened there.
Why is this ghost important?
I don't know, but it might
be a vital clue.
It might help me find
Roger and Billy.
You're asking me to trust you
over... No. No, I'm not.
I'm asking you to trust this.
Well, you ask a lot.
I need to think.
SCHOOL BELL RINGS
Wait!
LAUGHTER
Freak.
HE SNICKERS
CAR DOOR SHUTS
Elaine?
Elaine, isn't it? Charles Latrom.
I don't know who you are.
Oh, you must.
John and I were in Glasgow together.
Must be 20 years?
I was lieutenant then.
I probably look unrecognisably old.
You haven't aged a day.
John's friend?
I was in Oxford for work.
Thought I'd pop by
on the off-chance.
I can't believe it.
It's been too long.
John isn't home, is he?
John died.
Died?
Well, that's terrible news.
When?
13 years ago.
I should have been told.
I mean...
I'm sorry.
It was a long time ago.
I have to go.
How?
Their expedition was lost in Alaska.
They never found their bodies
in the storm, but he...
He didn't come home.
If I can ever be
of any use to you...
Here's my number.
I'm sorry.
He was a good man.
OK, boys, go easy this time.
Now, box.
Gloves up, stay tight.
HE GRUNTS
Good, Will. That's right.
Good, good.
Stay in the centre.
HE GRUNTS
Keep it tight.
One, two, three.
Good. Quick, up, Will.
HE GRUNTS
One, two, three.
VOICE ECHOES AND THRUMS
William!
DOOR SLAMS
Will!
William.
HE SNICKERS
William!
I know, I shouldn't have come.
Your mum's here to save you,
William.
I had a visitor and I...
I got... I didn't I didn't know
where else to go.
She had a visitor?
From outer space?
No, no, I just, I just wanted
to see you.
Why don't you sit down here,
Mrs Parry? Come on, come on.
Sit down. Just there.
There you go. It's OK.
I don't mean to cause any trouble.
I'll go. I'll go.
BULLY CHUCKLES
She comes, she goes.
Beep, beep.
Your mum's mental, Parry.
HE GRUNTS
Oi!
Break! Oi, break!
Don't...! I said get up.
Break!
What the hell was that?
The both of you!
He fouled me first. Towel off!
We're done today.
Go after her.
Mum, Mum, Mum.
I'm sorry. I am sorry.
That was wrong. I know
you don't like that.
I didn't want to come, but I had to.
Come back inside, Mum.
I was going to the shop to get eggs
and they were following...
They weren't following you.
There was a man and he was
asking about your dad.
Sure.
What are we doing now?
UNDER BREATH: Eight, nine, ten...
Come back inside, Mum.
I need to get my stuff.
Mum? I'm just... Mum? Mum. Mum.
Hey. Come back inside.
Yeah?
OK.
Will.
Is she OK?
She's just having a bad spell
at the moment.
They pass.
Look, I know what people think...
Your mum needs you to not
care what people think.
But if she needs care, Will, proper
care, or if you need proper care...
She's just a bit unsettled.
We're not at risk.
Well, my door's always open.
I know things aren't... We're fine.
I hope that's right.
FOOTSTEPS RECEDING
Come on, Mum.
Let's get you home.
You'll give yourself a headache,
staring like that.
I'm looking for my father.
Maybe once we save Roger,
we can go save my father, too.
She is wise to look for him
up there.
Kaisa, is he right?
Is there a city in the lights?
He believes so and the Magisterium
thinks he intends to use Dust
in some way in order to make
a bridge between this world
and the world beyond the Aurora.
Is that why they imprisoned him?
At the Magisterium's behest,
the bears are keeping him captive.
But King Iofer is scheming and
duplicitous and allows your father
to continue his research
under house arrest.
Do you know what I'm looking
for in this fishing settlement?
No, but I know you're
right to look into it.
You must trust your instincts, Lyra.
Where are they going, do you think?
Your guess is as good as mine
on that one.
You better talk to John Faa
in the morning.
WHOOSHING
Serafina?
You haven't changed since
the day I left you.
You don't look so different.
Right.
Coram, I am 300 years or more.
You aren't so old I can't see
the man inside.
I didn't know you'd want to see me.
I didn't want to see you.
You went to our Consul.
You started... I had no choice.
We need your help, Serafina.
Look at us.
We are walking into a battle
poorly manned and prepared for.
They will be ready for us.
But you will fight them anyway.
They are stealing our children.
You've found your fight
since last I saw you.
Our son was taken by disease.
These are being taken by other human
beings and they must be stopped.
And even if I am too weak to fight
them, I am duty-bound to try.
The Magisterium?
Yes. While it may be madness to
confront them, we cannot stand by.
That said, Asriel
cannot claim sanity.
He looks for multiple worlds when
he should concentrate on this one.
He is right to search.
He is?
Witches have known of the other
worlds for thousands of years.
We are as close as a heartbeat...
..but we cannot touch...
..or see or hear
these other worlds...
..except in the Northern Lights.
And why there?
Because the charged particles
in the Aurora
make the matter of this world thin.
It is a time when
anything can happen.
Anything?
Not that.
Not him.
I must leave now.
I have much to discuss
with my sister witches.
Will I see you again?
Kaisa will continue
to lead you there.
What he sees, I see.
Where I can help, I will.
But Asriel is bringing a great war
and the Magisterium know it.
Even the witches aren't
as united as we once were.
There has never been a moment...
..when I have not thought of you.
Of him.
Goodbye, Coram.
HE SOBS
You're sure that symbol reader
isn't playing the fool with you?
It never does, Lord Faa.
I don't think it could.
You call me Lord Faa when you want
something and John Faa
when you don't, you know that?
No, Lord Faa?
HE CHUCKLES
Iorek Byrnison.
You're willing to do
as this child bids?
If you can spare me.
I can't.
But she's insistent and I trust it.
You are to take her
where she wishes to go.
HE GRUMBLES
I'm commanding you now, Lyra.
Do you understand?
Yes, Lord Faa.
You go search for whatever it is
and when you find it,
you come and find us.
I want you back in the safety
of the camp before tomorrow night.
Thank you, Lord Faa.
I won't let you down.
I wasn't going to miss this.
Iorek's first ride.
HE HUFFS
I'm not heavy.
I'm not a horse.
LEE LAUGHS AND HE GROWLS
But, kid, promise me that
this alethiometer thingy
isn't lying to you.
It doesn't lie.
I trust it, too.
Ghosts, I heard - you're going
to find a ghost?
Think so. Is that a sensible
thing to do, look for ghosts?
I've never heard Lee Scoresby talk
about being sensible before.
Ha-ha.
I will bring her back.
Hold tight.
I won't be gentle.
Now, you two be good
to each other, OK?
Careful.
SHE GIGGLES
MUFFLED TV IN BACKGROUND
CLINKING
FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING
You're just like him.
Your father.
CAT MEOWS
You've told me that before.
I don't think it's true.
I love you.
I love you so much.
You know that, don't you?
And I hate being like this.
That man this morning set me off.
I love you too, Mum.
And you're not to say that.
Now eat. You need to eat.
You cook like him as well.
I don't remember his cooking.
Oh, he didn't need much
to rustle up a genuine feast.
It's an omelette, Mum.
No feast. And you're
kind like he is.
You've got his temper.
He always... He always wanted
to protect the vulnerable.
And he went out into the world
and found a way to do it.
And you're going to follow him.
Take up his mantle.
His mantle?
What does that mean?
He wasn't done.
He had more battles to fight.
What battles?
You don't see? This world is broken.
It takes extraordinary people
to fix it.
Extraordinary people,
like your dad, like you.
I'm not extraordinary.
Something is different.
What?
The rug's been moved.
There's marks on the carpet.
Someone's been in here.
Have you been keeping up
with your meds?
You're not yourself.
They have, Will. They have.
Just sit down and eat, please.
Mum, calm down.
You were eating.
HE SIGHS
LID SHUTS
SHE SIGHS
They have been in here.
You might not be able to tell,
but trust me, they have.
What's in the folder, Mum?
I can't... It's not right.
What's in the folder?
WHISPERING: It's not for you.
These are not for you.
Tell me what's in that folder, Mum.
You're scaring me.
Letters...
..from your father.
They're important.
His letters?
You never said anything... No.
No.
You shouldn't...
I have to keep you safe.
Safe? You're not ready. Not yet.
CLANGING
Just...
..ignore me.
It's nothing. It's nothing.
WIND WHISTLES
Do you have food?
Ma Costa packed me bread and eggs.
HE GRUMBLES
It's cold and you're warm.
I meant no rudeness.
You can keep warm.
HE MUNCHES
Do you never get
lonely without a daemon?
Bears are made to be solitary.
Solitary?
What about Svalbard bears?
Aren't there thousands of them?
HE GROWLS
I didn't mean to offend you.
HE GRUNTS
I was just curious, you see.
They have my father prisoner there.
He is imprisoned at Svalbard?
I am not a Svalbard bear.
Oh, I thought you was.
They said you were.
I was a Svalbard bear
of wealth and rank -
a prince, but I broke the rules
and I was sent away.
What did you do?
I killed another bear.
Who did you kill?
That is not the important question.
And what is the important question?
Why did I kill?
Bears should not kill
other bears, Lyra.
But I did.
I was not of right mind.
For such a crime, I was rightfully
stripped of all rank and title.
I was exiled and Iofur Raknison
has become king.
If your father is a prisoner
of the Svalbard bears,
he will not escape.
He'll find a way out.
One blow will crush a seal's skull,
or break a man's back
or tear off a limb.
And we can bite.
He'll trick them.
Trick them?
Bears see tricks and deceit
as plain as arms and legs.
We can see in a way
humans have forgotten.
You cannot trick a bear.
You don't know my father.
He tricked me into believing
that he was my uncle
and that my mother and father
were dead
and then he didn't tell me
who my real mother was.
And then one time when they were
trying to poison him, he...
HE GROANS
But you are not a bear.
You're wrong.
Some part of me
is definitely bear.
You'll see.
Mum?
FLOORBOARD CREAKS
I've been thinking.
You can read them
if you like - the letters.
You might need them.
Soon.
No.
No, they're to you.
I was just looking for you
to say goodnight.
That's the place I saw.
You're not scared, are you?
Not yet, but when I am,
I shall master the fear.
There is worse to come, then.
HE GROWLS
Something is wrong here.
Where is everybody?
HE GROWLS
That's the place.
PAN: Lyra.
Do you know what you are doing?
No.
But I hope I'm doing the
right thing all the same.
PAN WHIMPERS
Whatever you're seeking,
it's in there.
Shall I go with you?
I'll go alone.
Wait here and keep watch.
PAN WHIMPERS
Pan, you're making me nervous.
Don't let Iorek see me nervous.
HE WHIMPERS
When I am frightened...
..I shall master my fear.
When I am frightened,
I shall master my fear.
Don't stay here.
Oh, Lyra, go now.
Turn back.
Pan, don't.
Please.
We have to trust the alethiometer.
HE WHINES
When I am frightened,
I shall master the fear.
I shall master my fear.
HESITANTLY: When I am frightened,
One.
Two.
Lyra? Is that who I think it is?
Three.
Billy.
How long has he been here?
Where did he come from?
And where is his daemon?
He's got no daemon.
No, Lyra, keep away.
Billy, where's Ratter?
I know we should help him,
but I'm scared.
Come on.
Come on, Billy Costa.
Your ma's been waiting for you.
Let me take you to her.
IOREK GRUMBLES
BIRD SCREECHES
Billy! Is that my Billy?
Come on, son.
Where's Ratter? Where's his daemon?
Is that my Billy?
Billy, where's Ratter?
SHE MOANS
Maggie, let me help you.
Take him inside. Get him warm.
SHE SOBS
Best leave them to it.
Trust me when I tell you that
they love you, but this...
..they won't want you there for.
He was... He was...without
his daemon. Like a ghost.
MA SOBS
The alethiometer was right.
It was like...
..like he wasn't there.
Like he couldn't even hear me.
This must be what they do.
This is what they take.
It's horrible.
It's worse than anything.
Why would they take
someone's daemon?
It's about control, isn't it?
Because if you can remove someone's
soul, you can do anything.
IOREK GROWLS
Yeah, our furry friend here doesn't
deal too well with emotion.
Never has. He'll be
back at first light.
Hey, you did a brave thing, kid.
A good thing.
I am proud of you.
You trusted your instincts.
You found Billy.
Come on.
What they done to him, Ma?
Why did they take Ratter?
What'll it do?
HE SNIFFLES
We can't help that now.
Billy, it's your ma.
Do you want to look at me?
# Hush, little one, just breathe
# Feel the light in you
and the light in me
# Settle now, be still
# My love holds you
on the eternal wheel
# Hush, little one, just breathe
# The mighty stars
await your majesty
# Hush, little one, just be
# Feel the light in you
and the light in me. #
SHE SNIFFLES
It's all right.
We'll be all right.
You can go to Ratter.
SHE SOBS
SHE CRIES
Billy.
CAT MEOWS
CAT PURRS
LOCK CLICKS
SHE SOBS
Whatever this is,
I hope it's important.
Are you still watching the house?
Of course.
Good.
You're right to be.
Why?
I've hacked the wife's bank
and I found a money trail.
What kind of money trail?
Parry set up an account
two weeks before he left
which pays a small amount into
his wife's account every month.
How much money?
Substance, basically nothing.
The money's not important.
The important thing is,
is that it still pays out now.
That however much he put in there,
he knew that he was paying out
for a marathon
and not a sprint.
He knew it was possible that he
was going away for a long time.
That man had been on over 20
expeditions before
and served in countless war zones.
And this... This was the moment that
he thought he needed to make sure
his family had long-term support.
Go on. He knew about the window.
Or something like the window.
And he wanted to make sure his
family were being looked after.
But if he knew about
the window before, then...
There's probably answers
in that house.
A paper trail.
Find that and you might just find
out where and how he crosses.
I like this mouse hunt.
It's fun.
Lyra.
He died.
He must been wandering around
for days - frozen, exhausted.
Can I see him?
Of course you can.
Now we know what terrible wickedness
these people are capable of.
Now we can see our duty
plainer than ever.
We have to fight.
We have to kill.
FIRE CRACKLES
SHE SOBS
SHE CONTINUES SOBBING
THEY HUM
# Dear son
# Your soul never leaves you
# God does never leave you
# Dear son
# You are God's son
# Your soul never leaves you
# My son
# You are God's son. #
FIRE CRACKLES
INDISTINCT WHISPERS
THEY GASP
WATER SPLASHES
DAEMON SQUEAKS
PAN: Lyra, I heard
something outside.
SHE PANTS
THEY SPEAK IN THEIR LANGUAGE
DOG BARKS
THEY SHOUT INDISTINCTLY
SHOUTING IN DISTANCE
THEY CONVERSE IN THEIR LANGUAGE
DOOR SHUTS
HE SPEAKS IN HIS LANGUAGE
SHE REPLIES IN HER LANGUAGE
SHE ASKS A QUESTION IN HER LANGUAGE
Do you have a name?
Lizzie.
Brooks.
Lizzie, eh?
And you have a...
Is that a ferret daemon?
PAN SQUEAKS
And there we are.
She was young enough after all.
Good.
SHE SPEAKS IN HER LANGUAGE
SHE GRUNTS
Ah! You can come with me.
Sister Clara, could you take...
Sorry, I've forgotten.
Lizzie. ..and see to her?
Certainly, Doctor.
Come with me, dear.
She looks on the verge of change,
don't you think?
Yes, Doctor.
She's category A. Prep her
for immediate treatment.
Now you can take everything off.
We'll take a quick little look,
see you're all nice and healthy
and then we'll get you
some nice, clean clothes.
Who did you come here with, Lizzie?
My father.
We were bringing some
new Danish smokeleaf.
We were trading it for furs.
Everything?
Everything.
I see it, too.
It's like the one Billy was wearing.
This is it, Pan.
This is Bolvangar.
What happens to the children
that leave this place?
Where do they go?
To a place for more grown-up
children, of course.
So, they don't die?
You don't cut their daemons away?
This is just pain we're causing
and the Magisterium will recognise
and celebrate us
for the job we've done here.
Sticking out is
the only way we're getting out
and I'm not staying here.
This place is guarded by wolves
and Tartars. You can't pass them.
You've got a wasteland of ice.
Trust nobody in this place.
Every boundary in
experimental theology
requires the sacrifice
of the few for the many.
BUZZING
This will change the world.
We get this right, and we
will truly free generations
from tyranny of sin.
Get her inside.