During the initial Warring States Period,
China was divided into Scores of States.
Warlords scrambled for territories.
Society was in turmoil.
7 states reigned supreme: Qin, Chu, Han,
Zhao, Wei, Qi, Yan.
A century later,
smaller states were being annexed.
Han and Zhao were conquered by Qin.
In 227 BC,
Wei troops were sent to attack Liang
but were ambushed at Phoenix Hill.
A bloodbath ensued.
Both armies were annihilated.
3000 soldiers died.
Sanlang.
You’re less fortunate than me.
General.
Who are you?
l’m a Liang soldier!
A big road passes through my house.
My house is below Liang Shan
with five mou of rich soil.
How marvelous!
Five mou of soil! What should I grow?
You know,
when I was little, I caught a wild boar.
My father set it free.
Do you know why?
It was pregnant.
Are you pregnant?
You know what? You’re my captive.
No fatal wounds
though much blood has been lost.
This salve
for knife wounds is a family formula.
I rarely use it on strangers.
Does it hurt?
Now, it’s going to hurt more.
Young man, don’t be such a wimp.
You know what? You will live for me!
Stop cursing.
My father said:
Scratch when it itches,
smile when you’re dismal.
How marvelous!
General.
Colonel Yu.
Yes.
Stay down.
Why are we here?
To pursue and kill Liang soldiers.
How many have you killed?
Speak up.
One.
My army must fight with all its might.
The Liang troops are fierce and impregnable.
They are ready to die for their land.
I wish General remember I saved you.
What’s the military
discipline against deserters?
General, our troops were wiped out last night.
How could you say that
they all be wiped out when l’m still here?
We were ambushed last night.
Are you the mole?
You are so ruthless.
He saved you and you killed him.
What are you doing?
He was right.
Your troops were wiped out already.
Kill me.
I don’t kill captive.
If you beg me now,
I might even let you go.
Kill me.
You really want to die?
l’ll help you.
What a pity.
There’s no time for me to defeat Liang.
Haha. You want to die?
Even if you want to die, I won’t let you.
Prince Wen, the job is done.
He said
it’s an honor only to die on battlefield.
You’re a deserter.
No, l’m a soldier, who just played dead!
My father said
it’s not shameful to fear death.
To die in vain is shameful.
That pitiful solider Sanlang.
I let him play dead but he wouldn’t listen.
How much am I worth?
There’s no harm telling you.
Five mou of good soil
for a live captive of a General.
Five mou!
I have a piece ofjade tied to my waist.
How much is this rotten stone worth?
lt’s worth a lot of money.
Thank you for your gift, General.
I don’t believe you.
He’s one of ours. He’s still alive.
We were ambushed.
Anybody here?
Waiter! I want meat and wine.
Is that how big shots speak?
Insolent! Take him out and chop his head off!
There’s nothing to eat here.
Have mercy, General.
2000 Liang archers and foot soldiers
ambushed against 1000 of our best soldiers.
Both sides were annihilated.
This is the sword I gave him.
Where is he?
l’m sure l’ll find him.
Wu.
If he’s still alive.
Everywhere is at war now.
Where can you flee?
Have you heard of the Magic Tree?
The Magic Tree in Phoenix Hill
is said to be potent.
He’s your captive?
He’s my lucky star.
Be patient. We’ll be there soon.
How many more days?
Two.
Little man.
Don’t force me.
Don’t push me too far.
Give me wine.
No.
Wine.
Have you fought a lot of battles, General?
A lot. l’m a seasoned warrior.
Untie me.
You must have killed many men?
Even more so.
I fought 8 soldiers on my own yesterday.
Take me along, General.
l’ll be you captive too.
Oh, good.
I learned singing before.
I can sing while General drinks.
There is a lone fox at that dam over the Qi.
What if he’s still alive?
Remember. He’s dead already.
My heart is sad; that man has no garment.
There is a lone fox
at that deep ford of the Qi.
My heart is sad; that man has no girdle.
There is a lone fox by the side of the Qi.
My heart is sad; that man has no clothes.
Why?
You killed many men, General?
l’m not a general.
Maybe it’s you who killed my family.
I was sold to be a songstress
to entertain people like you.
Maybe l’ve served General before.
I wasn’t going to give you the drink.
Stop fighting.
Open up! l’m a Liang soldier!
I have Wei General...
Stop.
Who is he?
The Wei General.
It’s him. l’m sure.
This head was really the Wei General’s.
Give him the reward.
Wait.
Who killed him?
I did.
You managed to kill him?
Must be a deserter.
He’s cut a corpse’s head to fool you.
Execute him.
l’m innocent.
Where’s the horse?
You either kill me or release me.
Or l’ll kill you once I have the chance.
Kill... Kill... Kill.
l’m just a farmer.
I don’t kill and I don’t want to kill.
If you keep pushing me,
I still might not kill you
Can’t believe I was duped by a woman.
I gave her food but she drugged me.
You cheated her. She cheated you. That’s fair.
That woman should have beaten you up instead.
It’s no good wearing this.
What did the woman whisper to you?
Little man.
Who’s stronger, he or I?
He’s a born warrior.
Am I really inferior to him?
You’re softhearted. He’s stern.
To be the King,
you should learn from him.
l’ll lead a search around Liang.
You should head back, Your Highness
I won’t go back until I find him.
You know what?
l’ve waited twenty years.
No more wars
and a farm to till.
The cart is gone. This was hacked off.
No need to play dead. You can’t fool me.
The big road is too conspicuous.
We better take the small path.
l’ve never taken the small path.
Don’t worry. I have my father’s map.
Liang wine is too strong.
A small path also passes through my house.
Guard! Guard!
My father said
it’s good luck to step on bear shit.
Ambush!
I know.
What’s in the cart?
Nothing.
Seize it.
Wait, who are you?
A General.
Really?
Beat him.
Oh, no!
Stop beating him
Sorry.
Please stop beating him. I beg you.
Keep him alive. Take all the stuff.
What do you have?
Just a broken cart.
Revenge.
Shut up.
Who is he?
He.
He’s my son.
l’m not his son.
You unfilial thing.
He’s mad. He insisted on going to war.
I tied him up to take him back to our farm.
You till the land.
Our fields were destroyed by you soldiers.
l’m the boss here. Take the cart.
You want to die? What do you want it for?
To make a sickle.
A sickle? Do you have a farm?
Let’s go.
Such fools.
He doesn’t know
the most precious thing is you.
Your son?
l’ll be filial to you?
Come. Tie me up!
Tilling the land!
Don’t move. Hold your breath.
You want to strangle me?
I just saved your life.
Shameless
I haven’t touch you yet.
My father was right. I stepped on good luck.
How marvelous!
I beg you, please spare our lives.
Don’t move.
I can let him die or I can let him live.
I have the prerogative.
One mou for beans. One mou for gourds.
Two mou for beans. Two mou for paddy.
No, let’s say three mou for beans.
What should I plant in five mou of land?
I can give you 1000 mou of land.
1000 mou is too much.
I can’t even handle one more mou.
Paddy or beans, which is better?
Rice. I like rice. Rice.
Stupid. Rice is paddy. Paddy is rice.
Are you very tired?
Are you comfortable?
l’m not tired right now.
l’ll be busy with five mou of land.
Right, I should buy a cow.
Better two. One male, one female.
The male plows the field.
The female gives milk.
Let’s see how you’ll bring me back to Liang.
Right, I don’t know how to milk cows.
I better marry a woman who can milk cows.
My eldest brother was the best in fighting.
He was killed on battlefield.
My second brother was the most honest.
He also died on battlefield.
l’m the only one left behind.
General, do you have brothers?
lt’s better not to have one.
What’s going on?
I really can’t find them.
Phoenix Hill is huge. How do I know he...
He’s tied up?
His father tied him up, said he’s mad.
I thought both father and son were mad.
l’m leaving!
Revenge!
lt’s not easy to rescue you from me.
l’ve been in the war for years.
l’ve never seen such a pretty arrow. Have you?
I have. It belongs to my enemies.
You people... Fry in your own fat!
You know what?
They want to catch you to kill you.
I captured you so that you can live.
Your father was right.
It’s shameful to die in vain.
l’ll go with you.
So even General is afraid to die.
I just want to die honorably.
This side or that side?
If we manage to reach Liang,
I can surrender to the King of Liang
on condition that you’ll be executed.
Stop lying. No one can lie to me.
Except that woman.
You have lots of women?
Tell me, what’s your type?
Slutty or learned?
I prefer someone honest.
A learned one is fine.
She can teach me to read.
You don’t have a woman?
What did that woman really tell you?
l’ll tell you when we reach Liang.
You. Go check downhill.
You go back
the same path and check thoroughly.
Who are they?
Nomad bandits from Loufan. Quite well behaved.
Go greet them.
They don’t understand my tongue.
These people are loyal but truculent.
Don’t mess with them.
Hurry up. You should be less exhausted.
Birds have their nests.
Phoenixes are homeless.
My father used to talk about birds and fowls.
A phoenix without hair
is worse than a pheasant.
You’re pretty good at casting stones.
That’s how my brothers
and I used to hit pheasants.
How you knew we’d set up camp by Phoenix Hill?
How could I know?
Anyway, we’ve been in ambush for two days.
Indeed there was a mole.
Or we couldn’t have been ambushed.
The soldiers I trained were formidable.
They could have taken down Liang easily.
Bullshit.
You think we Liang soldiers are sissies?
Anyway,
soldiers like you are a disgrace to Liang.
Come. Let’s see how formidable you are.
A general versus a deserter?
lt’s Liang versus Wei. Very fair.
Fair? Then don’t touch my wound.
Good. This is even more fairer.
You’re already dead.
You’re dead too. We’re both annihilated.
Shameless!
The war is over. Wei has won.
We’re constantly at war.
Men are forcibly enlisted everywhere.
He’s hitting him, he’s hitting him back.
It’s not worth watching.
Liang has won! Liang has won!
You call that fair?
lt’s a war. What’s fair or unfair?
We’ll have meat to eat soon. Eat this first.
Too dirty for you?
That’s fine.
General,
what do you eat when you’re not at war?
The tastiest meat is a gorilla’s lips.
The tastiest fish is the caviar
from Eastern Sea.
No wonder you went to wars. You ate too much.
Aren’t you illiterate?
My father only taught me these two words.
They are simple to write.
These two words are not simple at all.
Why don’t you follow me back to Wei?
I can give you an official position.
I forgot to tell you.
The reward for capturing an enemy general live
is land, cash,
and exemption from military service.
Exemption from military service for life.
Only tilling land. No need to go to war.
There’s always a victor in a war.
Only when the victor has unified the world
will there be true peace,
so little men
like you can lead a regular life.
You know what?
If you hadn’t gone to war with us,
I could have been living this life right now.
You really don’t want to eat?
To be honest, l’m actually rather hungry.
Here comes the meat.
Oh.
The meat has arrived.
l’ll light the fire for you.
You’re pregnant. I can’t eat you.
My father has said that.
Scram! Scram!
Someone’s coming. Hurry up!
No sweat, only one horse.
A Liang soldier?
Brother!
Asshole!
You, go check the bush.
Liang troops.
On your knees.
A Liang solider
only kneels before a Liang general.
What’s the situation?
Are you a scout from Liang?
Yes.
You?
Me too.
What are you scouting for?
I went to the front at Phoenix Hill.
The whole army...
The whole army was wiped out. Right.
Why did you take the small path?
You’re already covering the big road.
The small path is just as fast and convenient.
Quite fast.
I don’t know him.
What? He fell and hit his head.
He is confused.
I didn’t fall. I did fell.
No matter what, I don’t know you.
What?
What’s the situation?
During a war, we don’t kill the scouts.
Is this your sword?
Yes.
How come you have a Liang general’s sword.
I found it.
You’re not a scout.
l’m not.
Where’s the Wei general?
I don’t know.
You dare to say you don’t know?
I know! I know!
I captured your general.
You’re quite capable.
l’m not capable.
Where’s he?
He fled.
Fled? That proves you’re useless.
No, I hid him.
Take us to him.
He really fled.
You’re toying with me.
Don’t come near. Don’t come near.
Don’t come near.
You guys don’t come near.
If I die, you won’t know anything.
What do you want?
I want a reward.
I can give you a reward.
What a disgrace to Liang soldiers!
One of you is redundant now.
What’s the situation?
Mount the horse and chase.
Get ready!
Sorry.
Wu.
Stop!
Let them pass.
He’s still alive, right?
How marvelous!
What’s so marvelous? Just a general.
Perhaps l’ll capture a king later.
Did I disgrace Liang?
Come.
Come get me.
l’m still alive. Never imagined, right?
Your plot
has killed 1000 of my Wei soldiers.
Their ghosts will not forgive you.
And you.
You pathetic little man.
You timid deserter.
A big road passes through your house.
You’ll be going home empty-handed.
Where are you from?
Where is your home?
After I win the war,
I should start building the ship.
That’s right.
I shall set sail under the moonlight
and tour around the world.
The King said,
if we draw 10,000 dragons on the ship,
the phoenix will be drawn to come.
Once you become King, you can have anything.
In order to become King,
I must cut my previous ties with him.
Time to go to bed, Your Highness.
My father said
a sparrow could become a phoenix.
How marvelous!
Why did you lie to me?
I even beat you.
Kill me, General.
l’m not a general. l’m just a soldier.
What’s the difference? You’re all killers.
Have you got lost?
You really think
the Magic Tree is potent.
l’m just a little woman.
I have a map here.
It can help you find the Magic Tree.
There is more hill paths. Take the horse too.
Take this back.
Hungry? l’m hungry too.
Have to find something to eat.
With five mou of good soil.
Five mou of good soil! What should I grow?
lt’s your fault.
Stop bickering.
To convince all warlords
and become famous scholars, you still lack...
What?
Patience.
Sir, where’s the way to Wei?
Over there.
Wei should start forming strategic alliances.
There!
Liang’s dangerous geography can be our shield
while Chu can protect our back.
Let’s see where you can run.
You can settle down here.
I have to go home too.
Stay alive for me.
How marvelous!
A big road passes through my house.
My house is below Liang Shan
where the soil is rich.
Marvelous?
Marvelous.
Easy, easy.
Should have strangled you at the inn.
If the bear hadn’t saved you,
you would have died.
Hands off. Do you understand?
Snatching us to build a tomb.
Build a tomb?
l’m sure they want to bury us in there.
Sacrificial burial.
How far is Liang from here?
If you take the river from our village,
it’s one day.
Which village are you from?
Three-Foot Hole Village.
You still want to turn me in for a reward?
Sure. You’re my captive.
Hey! l’m not your captive.
l’m his captive!
Take a horse in exchange for him.
Be careful, Your Highness.
Get ready!
How to untie this?
I was about to ask you.
Wu.
I have an idea.
What idea can you have?
Remember, we’re a team now.
Right, my father said,
Inside a wok, eagles or chicks are just meat.
True.
Help me.
It’s not a very good idea.
It’s a good idea.
Come.
Wu
Yes.
You finally use a real sword on me.
You’re no longer my master. Sorry.
It’s a pity. You’re my best pupil.
Come. Up here.
Buffalo, run faster.
Your Highness, hurry up.
Here.
There. Here... there...
You know what?
It wasn’t my intention to save you.
The buffalo just ran amuck.
You think the buffalo was too strong
or the wall was too weak?
At any rate, thank you.
How marvelous! How marvelous!
What’s inside your belt?
lt’s a secret.
Let me tell you a secret before we split.
You know why they want to catch me?
I don’t want to know.
You big shots have complicated affairs.
Since I met you,
everything’s become complicated.
Little man.
You’re still my captive.
Let’s see where you can run.
You’ve delayed a big event of mine.
You’re my big event.
Come. l’m your land.
Yes, five mou of land.
And cash.
You’re right. Lots of cash.
Stop.
Why?
I ask you to stop.
I don’t believe you.
I told you.
The sapling is not strong enough.
Don’t grab me.
What else can I grab?
Let go of your hand. l’ll help you later.
You think l’ll believe you?
Look.
Wu.
Your Highness.
Why?
He’s still alive.
It’s destiny. He’s over there.
Let’s go back to Wei first.
No, you don’t know what l’m thinking!
I really admire you.
Tie it. You tie it.
Let’s first see what place this is.
See what place it is.
Where are we?
No use! We will die here.
A big road passes through my house.
My house is below Liang Shan
where the soil is rich!
Are you mad?
How marvelous! My father said,
As long as you’re alive, it’s marvelous.
Do I have to be the King of Wei?
lt’d be better for Wei if you’re the King.
Are you persuading me to kill him?
We have reached a path of no return.
In that case, how can we let him die
with dignity?
What are you thinking?
Canola flowers.
I can grow some canola flowers.
Why?
Why what?
Why are we in such a place?
I could’ve defeated
all warlords to unify the world.
Then l’d build a huge tomb.
Tons of men
would be buried inside with my treasures.
And now l’m dying here anonymously.
l’d use some of the money to open a pharmacy.
To be honest,
your medicine is quite effective.
l’ll make you in charge of the court pharmacy.
You know?
We could’ve been friends in peacetime.
Perhaps.
If you can survive this,
promise me one thing.
After all, I saved your life.
Tell me.
Never invade Liang.
Not a stone is to be
taken within at least 10 years.
So cunning. It’s a deal!
You also have to promise me one thing.
Say it.
If you can survive this,
you tell your general
that I died on battlefield.
Tell him I died on battlefield
without disgracing Wei.
Though we were wiped out,
our flag is still hoisted.
Don’t lie to me, you little man.
It’s marvelous to be a little man.
Stop dreaming.
Father, l’m alive again.
Thank you, Heaven!
I remember.
You know what? This is Three-Foot Hole.
There’s a village nearby. l’ll find a boat.
It takes only half a day on the river.
To where?
Nonsense. To Liang.
Don’t try to flee.
You can go nowhere without me.
Hurry up.
Hide.
Hide what?
Help me up.
Little Brother.
Little Brother? He’s your little brother?
You must have had a hard time pursuing me,
for such a long way?
Crown Prince.
Crown Prince?
Who are you mourning?
The King our father.
Before my expedition,
he’s only very ill. It’s you.
It’s destiny.
You only waged wars to please the King.
If I hadn’t angered him
over a Wei- Liang alliance,
I could’ve been the Crown Prince too.
You staged an ambush
so l’d die on battlefield.
Because of your sibling rivalry,
2000 Liang soldiers died as a result.
You’re not worthy to talk to me.
It’s you who are not worthy to talk to me.
Leave him out of this.
Thank you. But he’s your enemy.
He wants me to live. You want me to die.
Come. Kill me with the bow I gave you.
You can go back and be King of Wei.
You’re softhearted after all.
This is your sword.
Kill him or he’ll kill you.
Only one of you can be King of Wei.
I don’t get it.
Why does one of them have to die?
None of your business.
You people are making things more complicated.
I said none of your business.
I get it.
That baldpate is trying to make trouble.
l’ll shut up.
They are here for them. We can leave first.
I disappointed you.
Follow your conscience, Master.
Let’s hide.
General.
Watch your back.
Mind you own business.
What a pity.
How comes there’s not a single rock?
Don’t come near.
Or l’ll hit your other eye too.
Stop fighting.
It’s me you want to kill
Between the two of us,
one of us has to live.
You don’t understand what l’m saying, right?
You understand it now?
That is what I really want to do.
Little Brother.
Brother, am I dying with dignity?
That big ship.
We won’t be able to go together.
Give me a hand.
Help me bury him.
Stop dawdling.
We have half a day of boat trip, General.
No, Crown Prince.
Your Wei wine is not strong enough.
I know what you’re thinking.
I too know what you want to say.
How marvelous! We are still alive.
Honestly, seeing you and your brother
reminded me of my brothers.
They were good soldiers too.
In fact, I wanted to be a good soldier too.
All three of us
were forced to enlist together.
The first expedition took three years.
When we got back,
our village had been burnt to the ground.
We had no home.
Before my father died, he told us,
our family has been patriotic enough,
but when will this war ever end?
He said, listen, my children,
one of you three brothers must survive
in order to carry on our family’s name.
Now l’m the only one left behind.
Capturing you is my luck, my only luck.
Looks like l’m not in luck.
Don’t ask.
The other day she said to me:
Retribution!
Little woman!
Peace
You know what? Liang is just round the corner.
Friendship between Wei and Liang.
Perhaps my brother was right.
If the King of Liang won’t kill me,
perhaps I can still talk about alliance.
Perhaps... Perhaps...
Perhaps it’s too late.
Perhaps.
Liang is always bustling with activities.
Your secret.
l’ve underestimated you.
You really manage to drag me to Liang.
Am I your captive or enemy?
Neither. Scram!
Hurry up, before I change my mind.
Why?
You and your brother, one of whom must live.
You better keep your word.
What?
Within ten years...
Not a single stone is to be taken. Of course.
I forgot to tell you.
The piece ofjade you took is really valuable.
You can exchange it for your land and money.
I found it.
Perhaps that’s not my destiny.
Back to nothing. How marvelous!
Run.
Let him surrender.
Liang has been conquered.
Kneel down and surrender.
Liang has been conquered?
How can Liang be conquered?
Liang did not surrender.
We Qin have exterminated it.
Your whole army was annihilated.
Kneel down and we’ll spare your life.
The whole army was annihilated?
Liang has been conquered?
I really have nothing left.
Put down the flag.
A big road.
Your army has been annihilated.
Not annihilated.
Passes through your house.
Put down your sword.
There’s still me.
Come.
My house is below Liang Shan.
with five mou of rich soil.
Five mou of soil! What should I grow?
Father, I cannot carry on our family’s name.
A big river passes through my house.
With a wife and a son. And a big tiled house.
With chicks and geese, cows and sheep.
With beans, paddy and rape flowers.
I have not disgraced the name of Liang.
Liang was conquered by Qin.
The "General" returned to Wei
and was crowned King.
He started to renounce
all military expeditions.
In face of the Qin invasion,
King of Wei surrendered without resistance.
Soldiers and civilians
were able to enjoy peace.
Several years later,
Qin continued to defeat all warlords.
In 221 B.C., Qin unified China.