-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
I remember damage...
Then escape.
Then adrift
in a stranger's galaxy
for a long time.
But I'm safe now.
I found it again...
- My home.
It's been a week.
Can you stop worrying
about David?
You should be more worried.
He was so sad
about his wife.
I wonder what happened to him.
What did he say
his wife's name was, again?
Rose.
By any other name.
There probably was no "Rose."
I know that.
Well, so what if people
make up who they are?
It's what you all do
all the time.
- All of who? Actors?
- Pre-Pans.
What did he say to you
when you were alone with him?
Why do you care so much?
Well, I care,
because if something happens
to you, it's my fault.
The world's still a very
dangerous fucking place, Alex.
Cartwheel.
Just... don't talk
to strangers!
Welcome to the fork
in the road,
the beautiful
Petoskey Station!
I finished reading it!
It's inspired.
Inspired!
- Really.
- What is it?
Wendy adapted "Hamlet."
Takes place
in Portland, Oregon.
Told in the vernacular
of '90s indie rock.
- It's wild.
- All right.
Circle the wagons.
Four watch points.
Swap every four hours.
That's our route.
Learn to love it, Dan.
We don't go off-wheel.
Why is Pingtree crossed off?
That way's Pingtree.
Golf course where a bunch
of professors live now.
Gil, our second founding
member, he retired there.
And that way's Nuevo Santiago.
Whew, they love music.
We used to split up
every year.
Actors went that way,
and musicians went that way,
and we'd rally here afterwards
and all head to Traverse City.
So why don't we
do that anymore?
Gil had a second-marriage
thing going on at Pingtree.
Some professor named Katrina.
Conductor found out,
like, three years now,
and she shot Gil.
She killed our director?
We don't go to Pingtree.
Stranger.
- Stranger.
Hi! Hello! Hello.
- No danger.
- I finally caught you!
No danger.
I'm very much looking forward
to your next performance...
tomorrow.
Dieter,
here's a suspicious man
I didn't bother to tell you
about from the other day.
Perhaps this is
the perfect time
to invite you once more
into the Museum
of Civilization.
To the east.
It's only a week away, and
I will personally guide you.
Personally guide you.
We're fans of yours,
Ms. Larson.
I listen to it all the time.
- How?
- Uh...
Well, we will not be coming
to your town,
but I will be taking this.
Thank you.
I used to be on NPR.
Well, um...
perhaps I'll... I'll try you
again in Nuevo Santiago.
The answer's
still gonna be no!
Third... third time is a charm!
Remember what you love.
We don't leave the wheel.
- "Beware the Prophet.
- If you see this man,
"cover your ears
and run for your lives.
"Beware the terrible prophet
in these parts
and the cult of the children
who follow him."
Oh, fuck.
That should clear it up.
Okay.
He asked me
what it was like
to be the only Post-Pan
in the troupe.
I said I didn't think
about it that way,
but he said that I should...
That Post-Pans were special...
the first human generation
to be rid from trauma...
and that the survivors
were the only liars left.
That's what
the Undersea thought.
It's from "Station Eleven."
- Maybe he read it.
- No.
There's only one copy,
and I hid it.
Huh.
It's at Pingtree...
in Gil's office.
- We should go tonight.
- Just us.
Check on Gil and...
and make sure everyone's okay.
I'll talk to Sarah.
Let's unload.
♪ You don't move me ♪
♪ Like you did once before ♪
♪ Don't care for you anymore ♪
- Ready? Are you ready?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Are you ready?
- Go. Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, there you go.
- Oh! Fuck!
What's wrong with you?
You're so bad at cards.
We should do this more,
though, for real.
I mean, it's not like
we have lives or anything.
Yeah,
but you've been writing.
Don't attempt
to score "Hamlet."
It will kill you.
"The winds of chaos,"
as my mama used to say.
I saw you...
onstage.
Something had you...
just for a second.
What happened?
Tell me.
Is this what you were playing
when I met you?
I was attempting
to play that.
You can't play
"La campanella" on the keytar.
That's not the reason
I can't play it.
I still fantasize, though...
About that harlot being forced
to hear me play it for Gil.
- Maybe we should go back.
- No!
Fuck her,
and fuck him.
I did hear something,
actually, um...
At St. Deb's.
I don't know.
It might have been a rumor.
What?
That Katrina died, actually.
What? How?
Pneumonia.
Although...
I don't know.
You know what?
It was secondhand.
And I don't know if...
Everyone!
Oh, Sarah.
Listen up!
We're splitting the troupe.
The actors and I are going
back to Pingtree.
The rest of you,
take the wagons
and go on to Nuevo Santiago.
We just make up the rules
as we go.
Why?
Hey.
Now the road's open,
maybe we can
go scavenging again.
We don't need anything.
How about a new book?
I like this one.
Why, though?
Really, I mean,
I played the main guy,
and I still don't even know.
Is it actually any good,
or is it just
what was in your backpack?
Read me a line.
"To the monsters,
we're the monsters."
What does that mean?
You murdered
Big Daddy's entire family.
Murdered?
The wolves think you're scary
like you think they're scary.
- We're the same.
- Hmm.
We're not the same.
- I don't know.
- Everything looks safe.
Everything looks normal.
Still the fake minefield.
No sign of the Prophet.
I should have seen
what he was doing.
No, it's hard
to see dangerous people.
You knew it, though.
Yeah, I knew it,
but I was dangerous
when I was little.
And people really
put their guard down
when you play vulnerable.
I mean, the leg,
the dead wife.
What's the situation?
We're not sure.
Does that sign say
"minefield"?
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
- There used to be a minefield.
Why are there mines
on a golf course?
- Just out of curiosity.
- Oh, back in Year One,
- And what are Red Bs?
- Red Bandanas.
A bunch of militias
of crystal meth morons.
Called them Kevins
back in Virginia.
I thought this place
was all, like, nice people,
college professors
and the old director.
Not all of them.
There's still some pockets
in the woods.
- Yeah.
- To the east.
And you know
Vlad was a Red Bandana, right?
Really.
You could ask him.
There!
- Oh.
- It's Gil.
- Hey!
- Gil!
- Yeah!
- Hey!
- Gil!
Stop moving!
- We put the mines back in.
- What's he saying?
Gil, it's us
from the Traveling Symphony!
- Stop!
- There's mines!
- Who is that?
- It's Katrina.
My God, I hate Katrina.
Stop moving!
We put the mines back in!
Well, hello to you, too!
You're already in the middle
of the minefield!
It starts back there
at the fucking green!
Oh, my God.
You are surrounded!
Hello, Sarah.
- Stay still.
- Okay.
So do you know
where they are?
Uh, well, we just sort of
scattered them everywhere
out here.
What happened?
Why did you put the mines
back in?
'Cause he fucking
took everything!
The Prophet!
The cult came here last fall,
and they...
They stole your children!
- No!
- No, Allie!
- Don't move!
Stay there!
Oh, my God.
- I'm sorry, Gil. Gil.
- It's okay.
- Gil, I'm scared.
- I mean, they're your kids.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- It's all right.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
Okay. Did anyone see
where she stepped?
- Kind of a straight line.
- Oh, my God.
No?
Okay. I think...
Sarah...
we could really use your light
and life more than ever now.
Good!
- It's an even year!
- What comedy are you doing?
"Hamlet."
Well, we said
we'd never do "Hamlet."
Well, that was back when we
made decisions together, so...
I see.
So what are you planning
for score?
- "Tubthumping"?
- Gil!
We all just almost died.
Could you not be an asshole
for a second?
- Sorry.
- You're not an asshole.
- Hi, Kirsten.
- Welcome back.
- Hi.
- Don't talk to him.
What did he do, though,
specifically?
Why did you let him in?
One day, a man and a boy
appear at our front door.
They're on a journey.
They are traveling
for the first time.
He even has crutches.
I mean, anyone who would be
disarmed by that story
in Year Twenty...
There's something
about him, though...
The Prophet.
You've met him?
We both did,
uh, at St. Deborah's last week.
Yeah, we talked to him.
I'm not saying I trusted him.
The opposite.
It was like he knew
I knew he was pretending.
- It was a game.
- To me, he just felt honest.
Most Pre-Pans don't.
Maybe if you're young enough,
he can be compelling.
But he's not innocent
or kind.
Anyway,
we gave them some food
and sent them on their way.
And he comes back
the very next day.
No crutches.
Different name,
different story, different kid.
And we ask him why.
And he just smiles
and nods
and says,
"There's no before.
The survivors are the problem."
That psychopath
stole my grandkids.
We let them have a campfire.
He told a ghost story,
and two weeks later,
the only four children
of Pingtree were gone.
Penelope, Michael,
Brett Olson, Annie.
What was the story?
I don't know.
Would have
basic thinking skills.
Enough, Sarah!
We need your joy right now.
Okay, let's... let's talk
about the play.
Now, honestly,
"Hamlet" is easily
the most overrated play
of all time,
and, yes, I'm including
"August Osage County."
I love that play.
Oh, of course you do, Dieter.
- I'm not a great actor.
- I know that, Gil.
Well, we all know that,
Dieter.
I know that.
What's embarrassing
is that you don't know
you're a bad director.
You're not missed.
I knew this would just become
a resentment festival.
Is there an expression
of basic joy?
- It's fine. We do this.
- This is what we do.
Golf with weapons?
The weapons
were already here.
Doesn't that sound a little
close-minded to you people?
Do you know what I think
is close-minded?
Performing Shakespeare
without updating it.
Oh, that's one of the reasons
that you left, wasn't it, Gil?
It's one of the reasons, yes.
You don't like risk.
We're artists.
Everything is dangerous.
We have completely
deconstructed "Hamlet"
this season.
It's set in Poland.
- Portland.
- Whatever.
What?
Wendy is our writer.
Alex is the lead.
Hey, that's awesome.
Wow.
Well, this sounds interesting.
- Is this your first lead?
- Mm-hmm.
- Congratulations.
- That's great.
Afterwards, maybe I'll play
a little on that baby grand.
We should go rehearse, right?
I'm looking forward to this.
Hardly finished here.
Dan! Now!
Thank you so much.
Dinner was wonderful.
Wait, what's a camcorder?
A camera that takes videos.
But phones make videos.
I'm not saying that.
- You are gonna say it.
- I'm not saying that.
- I'm the writer.
- I'm the actor.
Wen, I'm sorry,
this just doesn't feel
like the same play.
- It's not holding me.
- It makes sense, you guys.
This is actually...
It's so powerful, Wen.
Hamlet's the same.
He doesn't see that
Ophelia's faking everything.
He's obsessed
with his own emotions.
No, that's Ophelia.
- Forget it.
- This is gonna work.
Come on!
Let's put it on its feet.
You heard Gil.
They need us right now.
They need our light
and our life.
Come on, come on!
Oh, yes, it is gonna work.
- Hey.
- Sorry.
Is she directing now, too?
Just... just be
more positive, okay?
It's your job to help,
no matter what,
even if you're not a lead.
Right.
Wen.
- Just try. Just once.
- Okay.
Where's my book?
- I don't know.
- Side pocket?
What did you do?
Did you take it?
Hi.
What are you doing here
behind my desk?
I was just looking
at your big book of...
I was thinking
of adding the word "great."
"The Great Book
of Joy and Despair."
Mm.
Fuck books.
You wanna putt?
I have balls.
Uh, I'm good.
I don't know why I leave
that thing out there anyway.
Never try to write
an oral history of the world
after it ends.
We miss you,
for what it's worth.
I mean, the actors,
'cause we have no director.
And Dieter's wrong.
You were really good at it.
Yes.
Gil, can I ask you something?
Is this what you thought
it would be?
Like, living off the wheel?
Oh, retirement.
Ah, not really.
No, no.
"Our revels are now ended.
"Yea, all which it inherit...
Shall dissolve.
"We are such stuff
as dreams are made on,
a little life
rounded with a sleep."
Come back.
Leave with us.
What? You can.
Katrina just lost everything.
So did everyone,
20 years ago.
You sound like him,
you know?
The Prophet.
"There's no before," right?
I'm just saying
you should come home...
if that's what you want.
This is what I want.
"Station Eleven"
is the story
of a stranger named
Dr. Eleven,
who we first meet
floating unconscious in space
and who then gets stuck aboard
a broken space station.
Captain Lonegan is in charge,
but he has no crew
and is locked
inside the bridge
and just drinks scotch
and talks about the past.
And spilled
half an ocean
into the workstations
of the crew.
This drowned every grown-up.
The survivors are kids
called the Undersea.
They want to go home
and build a future Earth
by using time travel.
Dr. Eleven talks to both sides
and doesn't care
- what happens or what they do.
- Hey, Jee.
He scares everyone.
You still scared
of the dark?
Yeah.
It's gonna get cold.
Hey, Luli.
- Hi.
Nice to meet you, Kiki.
What did the Prophet say
to you?
What was so amazing?
I wanna know. Really.
He asked me
to leave the Symphony.
And I said yes...
Because that's
how I felt that day.
And then
after the bonfire,
I went to go meet him,
and he didn't show.
Well, thank God.
- I didn't wanna be with him.
- You get that, right?
I wanted to be the lead,
just once.
Well, I'm glad you get to.
It's weird that you do that.
It's weird that I do what?
Take weapons to a play.
Not to me, it's not.
We all bow to you!
You're wonderful!
I love you, Ophelia.
Can't you see that?
No, you can't.
You're fake.
My love is real.
You're just inside of it.
- I knit you out of it.
- Hi.
My entire family lived
and died before we met.
That's true of everyone here.
Fuck you, Hamlet.
Brava! Bravo!
It was inventive,
it was unlike anything
I've ever seen, and she,
Alexandra, my God...
Absolutely wonderful.
You did bring us new life.
Well, we've been too scared
to be out here
since he came.
The Traveling Symphony
isn't afraid of anything.
- We're artists.
- We are terrified.
Well...
you don't seem to be.
Sometimes I think we should
be out there looking for them.
Well, maybe they'll just
come back on their own.
- Sorry.
- Really important play thing.
Come on, girl. This way.
The way they held you
when you said it,
and there's just something
about being Hamlet, you know,
and just, like,
devouring people.
You were really great, Allie.
I should say that more often,
but you were.
- Come ride with me.
- We'll celebrate!
- Come, come, come. Come on!
- No. No, no, no, no, no.
- Come on. Come on.
- Stop.
- We'll ride the minefield.
- There's no before.
Hey!
Don't say that.
That guy's a psychopath.
He probably does the same thing
in every town he goes through.
No. That's you...
all of you.
Oh, you never deviate.
Rules. Routines.
"We never split the troupe.
We never go off-wheel."
"Ah, wow! Hooray!
They're here.
"It's... it's the...
"The terrified carnival
of trauma!
It's the Traveling Symphony!"
Hey! Just... stop it.
The Traveling Symphony
raised you.
- Watch your mouth.
- I'm going for a ride.
- No!
- No?
- You are not going!
- God damn it!
- Why not?
- Because he's still out there!
He didn't die
when I stabbed him!
Yes, I tried to protect you
at the bonfire, Alex!
That's why he didn't
meet up with you.
You're welcome.
- Why are you so mad at me?
- I'm not...
Whatever happens to you
is my fault.
I haven't made a single
choice for myself
since I met you.
I was just supposed
to walk you.
You made us leave Frank's.
Yeah, but we waited too long.
We stayed
for your fucking play.
Why are you being like this?
Because you can't just say
you felt like leaving
the Traveling Symphony one day.
No.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I'll just be downstairs.
- Don't worry.
- It's still in the Ziploc.
Alex, it's getting dark.
Just make sure
everyone comes inside.
Okay.
- Found this onstage.
- On the ground.
I never liked this recording.
Why not?
I recorded it two months
before my father passed away.
That's all I think about
every time I play it.
The whole thing just dies
when you try to capture it.
It's like it happened,
and then it ended,
and then,
that's it.
What's wrong?
Well, I moved
into a country club.
You did do that.
Yes, I did.
- These people respect you.
- Yeah.
Katrina there loves you.
I never treated you
very well.
Yes, you did.
You wrote a brand-new
fucking symphony every year.
You actually got better
after the world ended.
So what?
You heard me.
You organized me.
Sarah...
You do know
that I love everything
we made together.
I feel the same way.
But I didn't leave.
- Alex, you can't.
- There are mines out there.
- Alex!
- Alex.
You're in our room.
Hi.
What are you wearing?
What is that?
Is that a mine?
They're beacons
for the Prophet.
Oh.
Well, maybe you can show me.
Your friends are
gonna start to disappear.
First, Alex.
The Conductor maybe?
Who knows?
Penelope?
I'm not Penelope.
Okay.
He's wearing a bomb!
Stop!
You know,
I seem to remember
a little girl
who loved miniature golf.
She loved it.
Gil, the kids have bombs!
Do you wanna try?
Show me.
Stop! No, no, no.
Gil, he's got a bomb!
- You came back.
- Gil!
- There is no...
- There is no before.
- Captain's log.
- Star date 2817.6.
Starship "Enterprise"
diverted the schedule
for the purpose
of a confirmed discovery
by Dr. Thomas Leighton.
An extraordinary
new synthetic flu,
which would totally end
the threat of famine.
You mean to tell me,
you called me
three light-years
off my course
just to accuse an actor
of being bogus?
Jeevan!
- Jeevan!
- Guys!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today