There is some evidence to suggest
that Hayley was strangled.
DCI Stuart,
Hayley was a friend of mine.
I was supposed to be doing
a cleaning job,
Hayley did the job for me.
It was in a holiday rental.
I'd forgotten
that's who we let it to.
He does that quiz show on the BBC.
James Hollis.
Just give me ten minutes,
I'm not feeling 100%.
Dad, this is not about the past.
Or, at least, not the past
you're talking about.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
Tim, it's your word against hers.
I pretended to go out.
I just heard him go for her.
I don't believe
I ever lost my temper.
I'd really appreciate
having somebody here.
They took money
I had for a deposit on a flat.
I do think you should consider
opening a bank account.
No. No. No. No. No bank accounts.
I would feel very lucky to be able
to help you grow stronger.
There'll be money
in the joint account tomorrow.
Mr Carr sold my father a cash ISA.
We want to cancel it.
I can't see any paperwork here.
Mr Hollis, we wondered
if you had five minutes, please,
to help us with a case
we're investigating.
I will need my lawyer present.
Els, it's Dad again.
They've come about her.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Oh, shit!
Oh, you...
Dad!
- Dad!
- Yes?
Morning.
- Blimey! Are you all right?
- You left a pan on.
Me? No.
Yeah, I walked in
and it was burning.
Is that your porridge?
This was off when I left.
Right. Well, I've, like,
literally just walked in.
So.
Well, it's still under warranty.
I'll get in touch with the company.
I'm sorry. If I knew anything,
I'd tell you, Mr Hollis.
- You know I would.
- I do. But if you do hear anything,
tell him I need to speak to him.
Tell him it's really urgent.
And, so, in the end,
the case really came down to
one person's word against another's.
And in this instance,
we feel bound to consider Dr Finch's
many years' exemplary practice
and his reputation
as a hard-working, generous
and trustworthy GP.
And as such, we find
we do not uphold the complaint.
I heard him. He might sit there now
looking like butter wouldn't melt,
but he's got another side to him.
Yeah, you look embarrassed, mate.
You should, 'cause you're a disgrace!
Gov.
Yep?
- He's here.
'Peter, its Mark Harper.
'Kate and I can find no record
of any paperwork
'relating to an ISA
in the name of Salthouse
'and I need to know today
how a three-grand cheque from him
'has been cashed. So,
'you really need to call me.'
There.
OK,
I'm going to change
all of your settings
so that only your friends
can comment.
What does it make them feel
when they say those things?
I doubt very much
they feel anything at all, Mum.
'Cause they're messed up.
And that, that isn't about Dad
or about you or Hayley.
It's about them.
It's just a mirror people hold up
to themselves to shout at.
I wanted, if I may,
to ask you about a house you rented
in Middenham, in December 1999,
which I believe,
was an eight-bedroom house.
Yes, I can't remember specifically
but, yes, it was big.
- There were a bunch of us.
- Three other families?
Yes, although,
for the first few days,
there were only me and three mates.
Our wives and kids
joined us on New Year's Eve.
Right.
It was primarily a golfing break.
Mm, OK.
And what were their names,
please, the men?
Tim Finch.
Chris Lowe.
Pete Carr.
- And are they all still around?
- Yep.
Still friends?
Yes, we were at school together,
so it's a long connection.
And the families, can you
give me details of those people?
Tim was there
with his first wife Derran
and their two little girls.
Pete was single at that time,
so on his own.
And Chris Lowe was with his first
wife Laura and their little girl.
And your wife?
Yes, my wife Mel
and our little boy Eliot.
- Are you two still together?
- No.
- I remarried a few years ago.
- Oh.
So, this is a photo of Hayley Reid.
Do you recognise her?
Yes.
- And is that just from the papers?
- Sorry, where is this heading?
We're just trying to corroborate
evidence from another witness,
who thinks Hayley might have cleaned
the house you rented.
- I have no recollection of that.
- You never saw her there?
No.
I mean, we were out most days,
but, hey, this story was huge
and her photo was all over the TV.
So, if she had cleaned our house
and any of us had have seen her,
- then I think someone would have
mentioned something.    - Absolutely.
When did you return to London,
Mr Hollis?
When the rental ended,
which would be
perhaps
around the second or third.
- And you drove back up
with your wife and child?   - Yes.
How did they got down there
on the 31st?
Train. I picked them up
from a nearby station.
OK. And this is the last question.
What did you all get up to
on the Millennium evening?
Well, as I remember, we,
we had a meal in the house,
all together.
Then, I think the...
the children stayed up a bit,
till about nine or ten.
I think the adults watched a movie
and then all went to bed
after Big Ben.
- Is that all of you?
- As I recall, yes.
And then no-one went out again
for the rest of the night?
No.
OK.
That's it.
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much for your time.
Sorry.
- You said you guys met at school.
- Yes.
- Where was that,
the school you went to?   - Finchley.
Right. And you all
- lived round that area?
- Within a couple of miles, yes.
OK, thanks again.
Well, I think we want
to know more about four guys
who grew up
half a mile from her grave.
I think we do.
Hollis, you wanker.
Shit!
And this sort of sized garden
is very unusual
for a flat in this part of the city.
It's also west-facing, so...
Anyway, have a natter
and I'll be outside if you need me.
Thank you.
He's never had a garden
with grass before.
You like it.
I think it's perfect.
What?
There's a "but" coming.
But,
if we're going to be
properly together,
I need to know who you are, Chris.
Who I am?
How does someone like you,
so brilliant, so lovely,
end up like you have?
How does that happen?
So we had two key leads
that I believed
were potentially significant,
but were never resolved.
St Matthew's C of E,
which was burgled at some
point that New Year's Eve,
with about five grand's worth
of 18-century silverware
taken from a locked cupboard
in the vestry.
Blood smears were retrieved on
some smashed glass into the vestry,
but there were no matches
with anyone on our database.
The church
is about halfway between The Swan
and Hayley's parents'
original house.
And one possible theory was that
she saw something after
she left work,
she went to investigate and
ran into the burglar or burglars.
Certainly, I believe
it's worth following up again.
And then a black car,
which was seen driving
very erratically on the road
between The Swan and her house
at approximately 12:25,
maybe 15 minutes after we know
she left the pub.
No reg or make,
but the witness thought
it was a black four-door saloon
with a tow bar.
Oh, and it's worth mentioning that
the weather was very bad that night, with
heavy rain
from about 11 o'clock onwards
and very poor visibility.
That's it.
So John will be available
for the rest of the day,
and then on the phone,
at any point, for any questions.
But given what he's just told us,
I suggest DNA swabs should be taken
from any suspects we speak to.
Thank you again, John.
That was very useful.
So,
specific points of action.
Fran, can you double-check
all these timelines, please,
for Hayley's movements
on the night of her disappearance
- and the week before?
- Boss.
- Murray, you take the witness
who saw this car.   - Yup.
And, Jake, obviously,
the body was found in London
and, given that new development,
- it's worth having another chat
with Adrian Mullery, I think.  - Gov.
And following this morning's
interview with James Hollis,
myself and DI Khan
will certainly be speaking
to the other three male
occupants of The Spinney.
OK, that's it. Thank you, everyone.
That was great. Thank you again.
- Yeah.
- No problem.
So are you heading back down
tonight or?
No. No, no, my kids
live with their mum in town,
so I'm going to stick around, spend
some time with them for a few days.
- Right. How old are they?
- 21 and 20.
Ah, same as mine. Boys or?
Two boys.
Jinx.
Hm!
Anyway, I better go
and check into the hotel, so...
- Go for it. And we will
speak soon, I hope.  - Yeah, absolutely.
John. Thanks for that.
That was great.
Listen, if you're at
a loose end any evening,
there's always a few of us
at The Enterprise,
if you fancy a drink.
It's just opposite.
Yeah, great. Cheers.
- I might take you up on that.
- Good.
- All right, see you.
- See you.
- Cheers.
- Ah.
- You're welcome.
- Yeah.
- Hello.
- Hola, gordo conejo.
- Hola, muy gordo conejo.
- How you doing?
- Yeah, all good. You?
Yeah, very well. I've just been
in Manchester on a work thing,
driving back to Sussex now with Caz.
- Oh, right. Give her my love.
- I will.
But listen, very quickly,
I presume you've seen the news
about the Hayley Reid case.
- Yeah, I did. It's very sad.
- Oh, wasn't it?
Anyway, the police are obviously
doing a general trawl
for potential new witnesses.
And they spoke to me this morning
about the house we rented.
Right.
- Apparently they think
she may have been our cleaner.   - Wow!
I said I couldn't recall us
having a cleaner
and I certainly think one of us
would have noticed
- if it had have been her, given
the amount of coverage.   - Indeed.
Anyway, the long and short is
they're probably going to want to
speak to the whole gang of us, so,
I just thought
that I ought to let you know.
Yeah, no worries.
Obviously,
they're looking for people
who may have seen something
that only now seems relevant.
But I told them we all
stayed in the house that night,
eating with our families, so...
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
I'll give Pete a bell and maybe
you could give Chris the heads up?
Sure.
And I've e-mailed some dates
for our meet-up.
Oh, yeah, I saw. Item...?
- I can do any of those.
- Excellent!
Speak soon, mate.
Yeah, cheers, Jamie.
Jamie sends his love.
How is he?
Oh, he's very well.
He's just trying to arrange
a get-together.
The four amigos.
That'll be nice.
Yeah, it will.
It's been too long. Much too long.
Of course I remember.
I was meant to have bought
the puddings and I forgot,
so I legged it to the corner shop
and bought a load of Cornettos,
which your ex
wasn't too happy about.
Anyway, I just wanted to check that
you remembered it the same as I did.
So, we're all ready for the 22nd.
Chris has replied now so I'll book
a table and send you all a link.
Just one quick thing
before you go, Jamie.
Actually, I'm literally
just heading into a meeting, mate.
Yeah, yeah, I'll be ten seconds.
Jamie, I need a massive favour.
I was married for
12 years
and I had, have, I have a daughter,
Maya,
who I last saw 17 years ago.
My marriage ended early 2000.
And because of some issues
that I had at the time,
my wife Laura,
she felt it was damaging for Maya
to be around that.
And I'd run up some debts.
So I went from living in
a nice house in Notting Hill to
a one-bedroom flat in Acton
and then a hostel and
and then the streets.
How long were you homeless?
On and off for seven years.
Oh, Chris.
I'm so sorry.
And you had no friends
who could have helped you?
Yeah. Yeah. I had friends who would
have been desperate to help me.
Yeah, but you have to want
to be helped. And I didn't.
I hated myself. I thought I deserved
everything that happened to me.
And your marriage,
he issues you mention?
OK, so,
as you know,
I have bipolar disorder,
which was undiagnosed at the time,
and so it was unmedicated,
which meant that,
you know, my behaviour
was challenging.
And as soon as I started
costing my company money,
it was inevitable
I'd be asked to step down.
And that was
just not what she had married,
an unemployed man
who had mental health issues.
So she asked me to leave.
And I did.
And then, 18 months later,
she married a hedge fund manager,
who bought her a house
in Holland Park, so.
And then, in 2012,
Maya wrote to tell me that
Laura had died from breast cancer
and to ask that I stay away
from the funeral.
I thought about writing back,
and saying that I was better now,
that I was a different person,
and I am.
But I think there comes a time
when you have to accept
how things have turned out.
That life can sometimes
simply be unfair.
And to keep resisting that,
it takes so much energy, Mila,
energy that you need for the future.
Love?
In here.
Hey, Pete.
Hello, Mark.
What a lovely lady your missus is.
I was just about to call you.
You're punching above your weight
there, buddy.
Three grand,
and my apologies.
I was stressed about some deals
and screwed up the paperwork.
I accidentally paid Salthouse's
cheque into my personal account.
But,
there it is,
all there.
You know what we used to call
blokes like Pete, Maria?
Filth.
Failed in London, tried Hong-Kong.
Bit of a Wild West out there,
wasn't it, mate?
Attracted a very distinct
sort of person.
I see you, buddy.
Lovely to meet you, Maria.
I'll let myself out.
I'm sorry about that.
I need a shower.
This isn't working, Pete.
You and me.
I'm sorry, but
this just isn't what I thought
I was buying.
It'll get better, babes.
Trust me.
I've got some really good business
coming in.
Oh, I forgot to say, I've got
a couple of guests arriving.
Can you show them in, please, Liz?
Yes.
Thanks.
Adrian.
Have you got five minutes?
Well, obviously I recognise her,
but I don't recall ever seeing her
at the house at any point.
As Jamie said,
if we had have seen her, we would
have discussed it at the time.
- It was a huge story.
- Absolutely.
So,
Mr Hollis, he told us
that the four of you had gone down
- on your own, at first, to play golf.
- Yes.
And then your wife Derran
and your girls arrived on the 31st.
Yes.
And how old were they, the kids?
Claire would have been eight
and Emma just turned ten.
I'm sorry,
just to go back on one thing.
New Year's, the kids
would have gone to bed at...?
Nine, ten, maybe.
- And no-one went out after that?
- Nope.
What car where you driving
back then, Dr Finch?
I had my Audi in '99,
I think. An A4.
Sorry, was that the saloon or...?
No, the Estate. We needed
the space for holidays and stuff,
to save faffing around with a
top box or a trailer or any of that.
And what colour was it?
Silver.
And your wife and kids,
they went down by train?
With Jamie's wife and son.
- And everybody headed back to London
on the 2nd?   - Yes.
Did you all live in London then?
All except Pete.
He lived in Hong Kong.
And your marriage to Derran,
that ended when?
What relevance has
when my marriage ended to anything?
Sorry. If any question
makes you feel uncomfortable,
you don't have to answer.
- We separated in 2001.
- OK.
And do you remember when Mr Hollis
and his wife separated?
Same year, I think. Or maybe 2000.
And Chris Lowe and his wife?
Yeah, roughly the same time.
And are you still in contact
with Derran,
if we wanted to speak with her?
I haven't seen Derran
for many years,
but I can get a number from my kids,
if you need it.
That would be very helpful,
thank you.
Oh, I should just say that
she's had a number of issues
over the last couple of decades,
depression, anxiety and so,
I'm not entirely sure
you'll find her
the most reliable of narrators.
OK.
Well, thank you for that.
And then, one last thing,
and, I should say,
do feel free to say no.
But in order to help
eliminate you from our enquiries,
how would you feel about
giving us a DNA swab?
Yes, of course. No problem.
So, if nobody went out after ten,
then it can't be them.
I mean, we know Hayley
was seen alive at 12:10, so...
Yeah, I think you're right.
And if we're spinning our wheels
on these guys,
I don't want to waste any more time.
Let's take the last two separately.
Hi, Dad, it's me.
Look, I'm really sorry,
I'm going to be a bit late.
Please call me.
How many times
have you been here before, Jamie?
It'll be fine.
You know,
the longer this goes on,
the more his problems
consume him.
The more you look at the paths we
took, the choices we made, I made,
and think -
was it then?
Was it that choice or
that choice
that messed everything up?
Was it then
that I ruined my child's life?
Call me.
Sometimes, I just...
- Hi.
- Hello.
Gemma left some school books
at mine, I brought them round.
- And then she wanted
to show me her room.  - Right.
- Lovely place, though.
- Thank you.
Anyway, I need to shoot off.
- Nice to see you.
- And you.
Bye, girls.
- Bye.
Yeah, well, you see, I'm from the
clip-round-the-ear-hole generation.
- I think he'd still like to,
to be honest.   - Oh, dear.
- And do you have children?
- No!
Never had the
urge to be a mother.
- Wow. Smart move.
- Tell me about it.
They take so much from you,
don't they?
- Not sure I'd see it quite like.
- Just, I'm too selfish, I think.
- Yeah?
- Liked my career too much.
I think, if you are going to have
children, you need to be around.
- Whoops.
- Well, yes. I mean,
an evening like tonight,
it's fine you letting us down but,
how did you cope
when that was your kids,
turning up two hours late
for supper?
Oh, we muddled through.
Anyway, Dad tells me
you're off to Venice at the weekend.
- I know. You should tell him
to stop spoiling me.   - I should.
And first class, too.
Venice?
Right. Yeah.
Funny. Very funny.
Actually that's not quite
what I said.
OK.
I have it here, you said you
saw her leave just after midnight.
No, I said she would have left
just after her shift ended
at midnight.
I never said I actually saw her.
Right.
Guy Halford, the manager,
he's the one who actually saw her.
Sorry. And so what was
the last time you saw her?
Just before 11.
I was working through till three and
I took a half-hour break then.
When Guy came back,
he put me in the bar
and I just presumed that Hayley
was finishing up in the restaurant.
And Guy Halford,
does he still live in Middenham?
- Hi.
I'm looking for Christopher Lowe.
Hello.
Go on.
Stay there. Stay.
- Mr Carr?
- Yeah.
DI Sunny Khan.
Have you got five minutes?
No, I'm...
Sorry.
OK.
Absolutely sure?
- Yeah.
- You know who she is, though?
Yeah. Of course, yeah.
I mean, I never saw her
in that house.
- Are you OK, Mr Lowe?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I just...
I don't cope with stress very well.
- Would you prefer to have
someone with you?   - No. No.
- No, I'm fine, fine for now.
- OK.
So we're just asking everyone
we speak to
a number of general questions
to help us with our enquiries.
So, can you tell me
what car you were driving that week?
I didn't take a car.
I went down with Tim.
And then, did you and your family
travel back with him or...?
My wife drove down
with our daughter and
we went back in her car.
Right.
So what car was she driving?
She would have been
driving the Maserati.
Right.
You know what?
I think I did see her at the house.
Right. Are you sure?
Yeah. Just one time, but,
she's got a distinctive face,
I guess.
- I think that was her.
- OK.
Was that on your own or...?
I'd come back
from a round early.
I was still a bit jet-lagged, so
I went back to the house for a kip.
When I walked in,
she was there, hoovering.
I said hello and asked if there
was anything else she could do,
'cause of the noise.
What day would that have been?
Oh.
I'd have to check a calendar.
Do you know when it was rented from?
Yeah.
Monday the 27th.
Monday. Well, we arrived
in the evening, I remember that.
I think we just chilled
the next day,
had a couple of bevvies
in the local
and played our first round
the day after.
So, I'm thinking the Wednesday.
Just to go back to
the conversation with her,
- was it just about the hoovering,
was it?   - Yeah.
When I woke up, the other lads
were back and she'd gone.
And you didn't discuss this
with the others?
Discuss what?
That this girl,
who later went missing, had been
in the house you all rented.
No.
I mean, I drove back to London
on the 2nd
and then flew out to Hong Kong
first thing the next day, so...
This was a big story?
It was huge. It was in all
the national newspapers for weeks.
Right, well, I had no idea
about that.
And her photo being on the front
pages the last couple of days.
Work's been crazy. I haven't
had time to look at the papers.
I'm sorry, but the first I've ever
heard of this girl is now.
I suppose one of us
would have cooked
and then all of us,
with kids, I mean,
would have eaten together.
And that was a pleasant evening?
- Yeah.
- Everyone had a nice time?
Yeah, we had a nice time.
Why do you ask that?
Well, just
because Christmas and New Year
can be quite stressful, can't it?
And I understand your marriage
broke down not long after.
What has that got to do
with anything?
Well, I wondered
if that was in any way,
connected to something
that happened on this break.
You know, I think I do,
I do need someone with me.
Mm. And I can arrange that,
of course, but
can you answer that question,
please?
Because I'm aware that, of
the three of you that were married,
all of you were separated
within the year.
No, that was ...
nothing to do with anything
that happened on that break.
So.
Sure.
Who's that?
That's my girlfriend and her son.
I want to stop now, please.
One more thing.
Lastly, we're asking everyone
that we speak to
how they'd feel about
providing a DNA swab.
Entirely voluntary of course.
How would you feel about that?
Not a problem.
Good. Won't take a minute.
Mr Mullery, DC Jake Collier.
Have you got five minutes
for a quick chat, sir?
Now, you'll have my home address,
but you decided to come here
because you thought what?
That I'd be embarrassed
and gratefully duck into some
car so no-one saw?
I just want to ask
a few quick questions, sir.
So a couple of hours ago,
the head suggested
that maybe I should take some leave.
Some of the parents have been
uncomfortable with the situation.
And, of course, I could refuse
because she has no legal right.
But do you know what?
I have spent the past 18 years
telling people
that I wasn't even charged,
that not one single piece
of evidence
could ever be found
to incriminate me,
that the lead detective retired
just before a misconduct case
could be brought against him.
So I am knackered
and I'll take the paid break,
thank you very much.
But what it also means
is that I am not remotely
fucking embarrassed, mate.
I am not remotely
embarrassed to stand here
and tell you loudly,
no, I will not talk to you.
I will not sit in a car or a room
or anywhere with you,
voluntarily, ever.
And if you want to arrest me,
be my guest.
But I'll not say
another fucking word to you,
not even, "No comment"
because I think the police are scum.
I think you lie.
I think you break the law.
I think you take bribes
and you sell stories.
But worse than that,
most unforgivable of all,
I think you're thick.
I think your ranks are made up
of dim-witted mediocrity
who joined the force
because they wanted power
but they're too stupid
to get employed anywhere else.
So shame on you
for the way you treated me,
for letting Hayley down
so catastrophically.
And shame on you, DC Jake Collier,
for becoming a police officer.
And how sure did he seem?
Pretty sure.
It was an instinctive reaction.
I don't think he was recognising her
from the newspapers.
So this definitively places her
in the house,
- possibly with all four men, before
the wives and kids arrived?   - Yeah.
What was he like otherwise?
Odd.
An odd mixture.
I mean, I guess you've got to ask,
why would he be telling me
that he saw Hayley in the house
if he had something to hide?
But?
But when I asked him
if he'd give a DNA swab,
he slightly looked like
he'd just shat himself.
What's his background?
Lived and worked in Hong Kong
for 25 years.
Only married for the first time
six years ago.
No previous convictions,
at least not here.
And ah!
Drove down to Middenham
on a motorbike.
Do we have a response
from James Hollis about his car yet?
I'll chase that.
How was your man?
So.
He lives in a camper van.
Oh.
I'd say he's definitely had
some mental health issues,
looks like he hasn't got
a pot to piss in.
Except, in 1999,
he was CEO of DDM Lowe,
his own advertising agency.
And this is a guy who got
a double first from Cambridge,
was basically a bit of a genius
through his life,
lived in a five million quid house
in Notting Hill.
Wow. When did he leave?
Early 2000.
"To pursue new challenges."
What, like,
how to live in a car park?
DCI Stuart.
Hello, I'm just returning your call.
It's Mel Hollis here.
I'm James Hollis' ex-wife.
Ah, Mrs Hollis.
Yeah, thanks for returning my call.
No, it wasn't a pleasant evening.
What it was,
was a train wreck.
In what way?
Look the meal was fine.
We ate, we cleared up,
the kids were knackered,
it'd been a long day getting there,
so they went to bed about 9:30,
which was good,
that they were in bed, I mean,
because they didn't have to see
Chris go completely nuts,
- for want of a better word.
- How do you mean?
Out of the blue,
he just started ranting about
his life,
his marriage, his friends,
how it all meant nothing,
how everything was an illusion.
- It was quiet terrifying.
- Wow, yeah, I can imagine.
And so, what did people do?
Well, I mean, we all tried
to calm him down, obviously,
particularly Laura his wife.
But he was flailing his arms
and shouting and,
to be honest,
we were all quite relieved
when he then just
suddenly walked out.
- Of the house?
- Mm-hm.
- And went where?
- I don't know.
Had he been drinking?
Well, he'd had a few.
We'd all had a few.
It was New Year's Eve.
Anything else?
Someone might have bought some coke.
I don't know,
maybe he'd had a bit of that.
OK.
So who was taking coke?
Not me.
Not any of the women, actually.
Tim Finch?
Definitely not, no.
He never did that.
Pete, no, he was more of a drinker.
James, yes.
In fact, I think it was him
that probably bought it.
When Chris went out of the house,
- what time would that have been?
- I don't know.
- Just after ten, I guess.
- And did anyone go after him?
Yeah, after a minute or two,
James and Tim.
- Did they catch up with him?
- No.
No, Chris came back on his own
about an hour and a half later.
He was absolutely drenched.
I mean, it was raining hard
at this point
and his clothes
were covered with mud
and he went straight upstairs
to bed.
- No explanation, no apology, nothing.
- Right.
Where was Pete Carr at this point?
Pete had been out
since right after the meal,
- trying his luck at the pub.
- Trying his luck?
The ladies.
He got back just after midnight.
- On his own?
- Mm-hm.
And pissed.
- And your husband and Dr Finch?
- The same.
No, they got back
just before midnight.
Just in time for Auld Lang Syne,
bless.
Were they separate or together?
I can't remember.
And what happened then?
The guys went to bed,
the women stayed up
- and talked about
our car crash marriages.   - OK.
This is really important,
Ms Hollis, so,
I want you to think
very carefully, please.
Did you see anyone go out again
after that?
No.
No-one went out again after that.
You sound very certain.
Firstly, I sat up talking
to Laura and Derran
till about three o'clock
in the morning, and then,
I wasn't going to sleep with James
that night, so I slept on the sofa.
Except, I didn't, really.
Sleep, I mean.
So that meant I would have seen
if anyone had gone out.
And they didn't.
Right.
Fuck.
The last sighting of her was after
they were all back in the house.
- So she could be lying.
- Yep.
Or mistaken. Maybe she did sleep
and one of them came down
at four or five or whatever
and then went out.
Except, if one of them came down
at four or five,
went out then and killed her,
where...
where was Hayley between leaving
the pub at 12:10 and four or five?
- No, that feels wrong.
- Yeah, maybe.
But not as wrong as all four men
having clearly lied to us
through their teeth.
There is that.
I need a drink.
Yeah, it was about ten past,
maybe quarter past midnight,
- enough time to change, anyway.
- For the party?   - Yeah.
'Cause she went as Madonna,
the"Desperately Seeking Susan" one.
You know, the slap and the hair
and everything.
It was an '80s theme, I think.
- Sorry, just a sec.
- Sure.
This is from Hayley's diary.
"I hate the '80s, I hate
fancy dress, so am going as ME!!
"They should be so lucky.
Lucky, lucky, lucky!!"
Maybe she changed her mind.
Were there any other female staff
going to the party
who would have been the same age,
same build as Hayley?
Hey.
Hey, Fran, what's up?
There was another employee,
same build, same colouring,
same hair as Hayley,
who's just confirmed to me
that she went as Madonna
and she left around 12:10.
So you think the manager
saw her leaving, not Hayley?
I think it has to be
a very strong possibility.
Which means the last confirmed
sighting of Hayley was way earlier.
At 11, after which she could
easily have bunked off work early.
OK, this is brilliant work, Fran.
Let's talk first thing tomorrow.
- Goodnight, boss.
- You heard that?
So she could actually
have left the pub earlier.
At 11.
Which means we now have four men,
variously pissed,
drugged up
and possibly mentally unstable,
out somewhere in Middenham,
at exactly the same time as Hayley.
Corrected by DB
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org