WORKMEN SHOUT
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app
Whoa, whoa!
Sahid! Sahid!
SPEAKS OWN LANGUAGE
♪ All we do is hide away
♪ All we do is,
all we do is hide away
♪ All we do is lie and wait
♪ All we do is,
all we do is lie and wait
♪ I've been upside down
♪ I don't wanna be
the right way round
♪ Can't find paradise
on the ground. ♪
CLOCK TICKS
SHE SIGHS
MALE VOICE OVER RADIO:
'Viking, North Utsire -
'variable four,
becoming south-easterly 5-7.
'Showers...'
Well, if I had to choose,
then I'd say...
I'd say chef's table at KFC?
No, what worries me
is you think I'm joking!
All right, I gotta go. She's here.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
We could do that, but, erm...
Tell you what,
why don't you come to mine?
The girls would love to meet you.
Seven's perfect.
Yeah, I'll text you
the full address.
OK. Yeah, I love you too.
I am so sorry.
Ah, it's not a problem.
Woke up stupid early again, then
fell asleep in my kitchen chair.
You tried valerian?
No, I can't do sleeping pills.
They zonk me out for the next day.
No, no, no - these are herbal.
No, you're absolutely normal
by 11 the next day, easy.
Right. Although they do stink
like rotting fish.
Well, they sound marvellous!
So, what do you think it is, then...
that's waking you up?
No idea.
Hey, Jake!
Morning, boss.
What we got?
They're laying new
drainage channels down here,
been doing it the last three months,
and then last night,
one of the workmen,
who happens to have trained
as a doctor in Basra, dug up this...
which he suspected was a section
of a human hip bone.
Dr Balcombe came out early doors,
confirmed it was human,
which is when they called for us.
SHE SIGHS
Oké, let's have a look.
I'm sure you think I'm being daft.
There's absolutely nothing
to be embarrassed about, Harry.
Nothing at all.
As you might imagine,
death is a pretty constant part
of my daily life,
and if I've learned anything
in the last 35 years,
it's that grief takes
every form imaginable.
Hm. For some,
it passes quite quickly.
For others, it can last many years.
Neither is right or wrong,
they're both just... how it is.
You were with Wendy for 63 years.
She was a part of you.
So, to still miss her
after just two...
Well, it's the... blink of an eye.
So, please, never be embarrassed
about wanting to talk about her
with me.
In fact,
I want you to talk about her.
I miss her, too.
Is the position significant?
What, that it's archaeological,
you mean? Yeah.
Not really, no.
Most cultures buried their dead
in a variety of positions -
Romans, Saxons, early medieval...
It could be any of those.
But your instinct is
that it is archaeological?
Well, I have no evidence of that,
it's just...
on balance, for obvious reasons,
I think it's more likely than not.
Why?
Well, because of where it is.
Who buries a body in the
central reservation of the M1?
Someone who doesn't want it found?
I guess, I just...
So how much is remaining?
About 60%, I think.
I'll know more when I get her back.
Right, so you think it's female?
I think, from the pelvis shape.
Again, I can confirm that
when I get everything out.
No clothing fragments?
Not found any yet, no.
It would appear we just have bones.
FLOORBOARD CREAKS
Bye, Jack.
Do you have records for what it was
before? What the land was used for?
Yeah. Yeah, no, I can hold.
Highways Agency.
Just seeing if they can tell us
what the land was used for
before construction of the motorway.
Did you know that Edgware Road
was built on Watling Street?
Old Roman road, did you know that?
I didn't.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, yeah, I'm here.
DIALLING TONE
'Hi, love.'
Hi, Dad. Everything OK?
Er, yeah, why?
No, no, just...
'you weren't home last night.'
I-I'm at Jen's.
'I told you.'
Did you?
I told you yesterday at breakfast
I was staying at hers.
Sorry, my mistake.
'Anyway, it's... it's no problem.'
I'll see you tonight?
Yeah, I'll see you later. Yeah.
'OK, great.'
Or, you know, stay out,
it's not a problem.
Oh... Thanks!
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't mean...
I gotta go. Lots of love, bye!
Actually would be quite smart,
don't you think?
What would?
If you killed someone, burying
them in a central reservation.
Smart? Yeah, if you were
a construction worker,
lanes were already closed
for repairs...
Even if you weren't
a construction worker, just...
hiring a van,
getting a hi-vis jacket,
three in the morning,
put up some bollards...
Then start digging a grave
in the middle of a motorway?
I mean, it'd take balls, give you
that, but... who's gonna stop you?
Who's gonna think, "Oh, I bet
he's not a construction worker.
"I bet he's... burying a body."
You know, the fishy smell's
really not that bad -
I think you should try them.
Yeah, all right!
SHE CHUCKLES
Oh, hi!
Hi there, how are you?
DOG BARKS
Oh, we're up, are we, young man?
Oh, super dog! Super, super dog!
You've decided to get up, have you?
Here's breakfast.
Today's the day big day, super dog,
when everything changes.
Yes, my Frankie,
today's the big day!
So it is female, and from the teeth,
I can tell you she's young -
early 20s, oldest. OK.
Most importantly,
you were right, DCI Stuart -
these remains
are not archaeological.
Do you see that? The bone suffered
a compound fracture at some point
and was fixed with a surgical plate.
So, plates have been used commonly
for about a hundred years,
but if it's titanium -
given the lack of corrosion,
my guess is that it is - then...
this is no more than 50,
60 years old, tops.
HE SIGHS
Find the need, sell the want.
Sell the want.
I'm not sure if I'm going to
sign anything today, Mr Carr.
And I completely understand that,
Mr Salthouse.
And tell me, is it the amount
that's worrying you?
Well...
Is it too much?
Well, possibly, but also...
So, what do you think
you could afford?
Well, as I say, it's not just the...
8,000? If you feel ten's too much,
how about eight?
You see, eight is still...
Seven, then?
I suppose...
I suppose I might be prepared
to invest... three.
Three.
Perhaps. Perhaps three.
Three's not enough.
I'm sorry?
Three's fine,
and I can do you the same terms
for three, so we're all set.
Right, well...
I'll get my cheque book, then.
It's here somewhere...
Just sign and date it, Mr Salthouse.
I've got a stamp.
So, first up, yes, it's titanium.
So, 60 years old, oldest?
Give or take.
And then, there's this...
which I'm guessing is some sort of
manufacturer's mark?
You ever seen that before?
Nope, and I've seen hundreds
of these.
But plates do usually have
a manufacturer's mark on them?
No, usually,
they have serial numbers indented.
For all of them? Yes.
So...?
So, I'm guessing this is foreign.
So she could've come from anywhere.
Do EU ones have serial numbers?
I think so.
At least from when the country
joined, but you'd have to check.
She could be British, gone abroad
and had the plate fitted there.
That's also a possibility. OK.
Can't you determine...
race or ethnicity from a skull?
To a degree.
It's not an exact science.
I mean, there are certainly
general characteristics
of Asian skulls versus African
versus European, etcetera,
but they suggest a likelihood
of origin, no more than that.
OK, can you do that for us?
Mm. And age-wise,
you said early 20s...
Would you be able to narrow it down
any more than that?
We'll be doing an
ossification test -
cartilage turns to bone
at a very specific age.
That should narrow it down
considerably.
Who might be best-placed to
recognise who the manufacturer is?
I'd start with the orthopaedics
departments of large city hospitals.
Given the amount of foreign-born
NHS employees we have, there's...
got to be a good chance you'll
come across a surgeon who's inserted
a plate with that mark on it.
Mm-hm.
Well, that's it for this week.
Join us same time next week
for the first of the semis.
It's goodbye from our teams...
ALL: Goodbye!
..and it's goodbye from me. Goodbye.
FUNKY THEME MUSIC PLAYS
CHEERING
LAUGHTER
And would you mind signing a copy
of your book, please, Mr Hollis?
No, of course not. So, erm,
is that to "Karen" or "Kaz", or...?
Actually, if you could just put it,
er, "To Nan."
"Nan"?! Oh, dear, oh, dear!
At least it used to be, "To Mum."
Am I that ancient now?
I'm gonna have to steal you away,
I'm afraid, James.
OK, sorry, guys, she's the boss,
but, listen...
erm, I hope you all enjoyed
yourselves today, and seriously,
well done, all of you.
You're a sight smarter than I was
when I was your age.
OK, cheers, guys. Safe journey. Bye!
Ta-ta!
Oh, of course, yeah!
They're so lovely...
So, couple of messages
from the production office.
Your friend Pete rang,
something about a dinner?
OK, thank you.
And then your wife has rung twice,
needs you to call her. Amy?
Yeah. Right, thanks, Kelly.
Recording again in 20 minutes.
All right.
Start with the hospitals...
OK. I might stick a photo
of that mark on Twitter as well.
Yeah, good, cos if we can identify
the origin of the plate,
possibly narrow down a time window,
that's gonna be key.
You want to look at
missing persons yet? Er...
SHE SIGHS
Well, until we know
what country it was made in
and the likely ethnicity of the
victim, no, I can't see the point.
Hiya.
Where've you been?
I've left half a dozen messages.
In recording. What's up?
It's Eliot...
'I'm sure it's nothing
to worry about, '
but apparently his flatmate hasn't
seen him for a couple of days.
Who rang you?
Melissa.
Oh, so she rings you before
she rings me now, does she?
Only because you'd end up
screaming at each other.
I'm still his dad, Amy.
She should ring me.
Has she spoken to him, the flatmate?
Ed. Yes, briefly.
She said she's going to finish work
early and get there about four.
What work? She's been writing
the same shit novel for ten years!
Erm... can you call her?
I'm about to start again.
'Tell her I'll meet her there.'
Sure.
And, Jamie, it'll be fine.
'He'll be fine.' Yeah.
'Call me when you've seen Mel,
yeah?'
Sure.
Hey, Chris. Hiya.
Nice to see you. How are you?
Oh, I'm good. I'm good, thanks.
How are you?
Ah, you know, not too shabby.
Glad you dropped in, actually -
sold two more pieces at the weekend.
Oh! Oh, OK!
Got a bit of space for
a couple more, if you have any?
Yeah, I'm working on something...
maybe beginning of next week?
Perfect.
Rob, I-I need some of my money.
Er, yes, not a problem.
Erm, how much?
4,000, please.
OK, fine.
Sorry, you mean now?
Yeah. Right!
Well, I have to go to the bank,
obviously. Can you wait ten minutes?
Uh-huh, yeah.
So...
..that's quite a lot of money,
Chris,
and I'm very happy to get it
for you, of course,
but you're absolutely sure
you need all of this?
I am, yeah.
Have you got somewhere safe
to keep it?
Yeah.
Erm, well...
do you wanna wait outside,
or maybe you could hold the fort...?
No, no, I'll wait out there.
No problem.
You're over-thinking it, love.
So you read it as him hiding,
I read it as he was just busy,
you know,
preparing his dad's lunch,
changing his bed sheets or whatever.
So why didn't he come out
when I said goodbye?
He probably just didn't hear you.
Mm.
Tim, sweetheart...
..I promise you,
no-one in this town believes a word
of these allegations.
They know you,
and they know Alison Pinion.
They certainly know Alison has
a grudge against this practice.
As your rep says, the case won't
even get to the next stage.
So, please,
just try and forget about it, hm?
Let's just have a lovely evening
tonight with your girls.
Come on.
DRAMATIC MUSIC
SWELLS OVER SPEECH
INAUDIBLE
Ah, these are Greek letters...
erm, intertwined.
You see that...
You see there,
that is an A and the X is a C.
Stands for "Angelis and Christos".
They're a Cypriot firm,
based in Nicosia. Right.
They do all sorts of surgical stuff.
Do you know if they're
still in operation?
Er, I think so. I think
they only started in the '80s.
And certainly, they were still
in operation when I worked there...
couple of years ago?
DCI Stuart, it's Leanne Balcombe.
So, I just spoke to Dr Balcombe...
and her tests suggest
that the skull is European,
which narrows things down a bit.
So we now know that the plate
is made by a Greek company,
Angelis and Christos,
based in Cyprus.
Now, they didn't start
operating until 1984,
so that's as old
as the plate can be.
But I've sent them some photos
and the MD's gonna come back to me,
see if he can help us
narrow the dates down a bit.
But, er, in the meantime,
we can now also tell you...
..Dr Balcombe did various tests
on the major bones and teeth.
And she was able to determine,
with, actually,
a pretty good deal of certainty,
that these remains are actually
those of a young female...
..between the ages of 13 and 15.
So, this is not an adult,
it's not even a young adult.
This is the body of a child.
So, as of now,
we have a window of 34 years,
and as soon as we hear back
from A&C,
we start searching for all
missing children of that age.
We're gonna start with the UK,
but if we have to,
we'll liaise with Interpol
and roll this out across Europe,
because not many children
of that age go missing
without leaving people behind.
And...
..somewhere,
there surely must be parents...
who have lived in a world
of almost unimaginable pain...
..for many, many years.
Let's give them their child back.
Don't apologise - your English
is better than my Greek.
'Anyway, what we can tell you
is that in 2004,
'when we joined the EU,
in line with EU regulations,
'we started using serial numbers
on all our plates,
'so it has to predate that.'
Well, that is already
extremely useful.
'And the logo, we didn't start
using that until '95.'
'95?
Right, so... that has to have been
made in this nine-year period?
'Oh, absolutely.'
Right. Thank you.
'So, what time
do you think you'll be back?'
Not late, six-ish.
Thought I might take the boys
to the beach if it stays dry.
Yeah, they'd love that.
'No problem.'
Oh, and by the way, the boiler's
turned itself off again.
Right, remember,
just press the reset button, then...
Yeah, I know.
I did it eight times
before it fired up.
'It's broken, Pete.'
I'll look at it later. Back at six.
Yeah, OK.
Mum!
Oh, OK!
When a man goes into a shop, Pete,
to ask for a quarter-inch drill bit,
he doesn't really want
a quarter-inch drill bit, does he?
Doesn't he?
What he actually wants...
is a quarter-inch hole.
I'm sorry, Mark, I've got absolutely
no idea what you're talking about.
You've asked me for new leads,
but what you actually want
is to be making more money, right?
Of course.
Which I can't give you.
I couldn't give you
a quarter-inch hole...
..and I can't make you
a better salesman.
So she was found in the UK,
and I think it's fair to assume
she's more likely to be British.
Yeah.
And if she is British...
..why might she have had
an operation in Cyprus?
Cos she was on holiday?
With her family.
And according to the insurance rep
I just spoke to,
most families on holiday in Cyprus,
they go to Paphos.
So we make contact
with this hospital,
see what records
they have from then.
Meanwhile, get the team
to start an outstanding review
of UK miss pers of, say,
12 to 16-year-old girls
between '95 and 2004.
Yeah, I'll get them onto it. Mm.
Hey, Pete, I got your message.
Sorry I'm being rubbish,
but work's mad now.
So, yeah, let's put in a date
for a meet-up.
Why don't I call Tim
and you do Chris?
I miss you, big man.
Lots of love.
How's he been the last few weeks?
How's his... mood been,
would you say?
I dunno, he's just seemed...
really stressed.
Stressed? Yeah.
Stressed by what?
Dunno.
Stressed by watching back-to-back
Family Guy all day long? James...
Stressed by having to choose exactly
how he'll fuck my life up this week?
What d'you think?
I'm just trying to help, mate.
To be honest, it's not my problem.
For what it's worth,
having a father like you...
would stress the fuck out of anyone.
Does it ever get tiring,
being so angry all the time?
Does it get tiring
being such a smug tit?
Sorry.
HE SIGHS
You'd think 20 years of this,
of wondering every time
he goes off on one
if this is the time
he'll wind up in a canal,
would inure you to the fear,
but it just seems to make it worse.
For us both.
I'll do the pubs,
you do the dealers.
SIGHS
OFFICE CHATTER
Hello, um, do you speak English?
Brilliant, brilliant.
Yeah, wonder if you can
help me with something...
MAN: Eight.
GROUP: Eight.
Friday. Friday.
Saturday. Saturday.
Sunday...
Can I use the phone in the office?
I can never get signal in here.
Yeah, yeah, no problem. Thanks.
But he's, he's OK now?
Yeah. I got him back to sleep
at about five,
and then he slept in till midday.
Oh, and... was it about his dad?
'No, he rarely dreams about
his dad.'
He was too little to remember,
really. No, it's...
pretty much always the gas.
'I'm so sorry.'
Listen, it's much better
than it used to be.
'This was the first time in months.'
Would you like me to come round?
I could do some painting with him?
I think he'd love that.
How about... tomorrow, after school?
Yeah, well, OK. Four-ish?
'Perfect.'
Oh, OK. Er, well, you...
'..send him my love.'
I will.
'And I'll, I'll see you tomorrow.'
Bye.
GULLS CALL
PETE: Come on,
see if you can tackle me!
You're just running away,
miles away...
Here we go!
Oh, looking dangerous now.
It's looking dangerous.
Can we save...? Oh!
Ohh!
Here we go.
Go and get that!
And have you started pronouncing
your words stupidly yet?
'Only when I eat...
AMERICAN PRONUNCIATION: ...oreg-ano.'
AMERICAN ACCENT: On your ris-o-tto?
'New York's actually pretty like
London. It's just... cooler.'
Yeah, well, don't get too attached,
cos you're not moving there.
'Oh, am I not?'
Sorry, needed here, I'm afraid.
'Right, you see, I didn't realise
I had no say in this decision.'
THEY LAUGH
'How's Grandad?'
Yeah, all good.
'He there?'
Er... no, no,
because he's out with Jenny tonight.
'Wo-o-ow! Wow!
That's quite a thing, isn't it?
'How long have they been goin' out?'
Er, well, dunno. A while.
FEMALE VOICE: 'Adam! Adam!'
'Yeah, I'm coming.'
Six months, maybe?
'Just gimme a sec.
'Mum, look, I gotta go.'
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you go.
'I'll call you next week, yeah?
I love you.'
And do some bloody work, cos
that is why you're there, remem...?
PHONE RINGS
Hiya. 'Er, boss...'
Yeah, yeah, sorry to disturb you.
LAUGHTER IN BACKGROUND
'No, no problem.'
The Paphos hospital just emailed me.
'They lost all of their
pre-2008 records in a fire
'a couple of years ago.'
Shit.
'Yeah, irritating.'
Obviously, I'll try the other
hospitals in the morning, but...
'for now,
we're back to a nine-year window.'
OK, well,
thanks for letting me know.
SIGHS
'Sounds like it's going well...'
You're doing great.
'Sunny?'
Yes, boss - sorry.
Er, it is, very. I'll let you go.
'Have a great evening.'
And you. Night.
'Night.'
MICROWAVE DINGS
I know you feel she can be tricky,
but... can't you just reach out?
She's your mum.
And there were very good reasons
you got divorced, Dad.
Can we not turn this into another
Mum slag fest, please?
I completely agree.
She's a lovely lady who did
extremely well to put up with me
for as long as she did.
Maybe we can do a trip up there
for her birthday?
Not a chance. I'm driving 300 miles
to the middle of nowhere to...
OK, fine, forget about it.
Let's talk about something else.
Let's talk about why we're here...
Here's to you both.
Happy anniversary!
And a huge well done to you, Carol,
for tolerating the old bastard
for ten years. To Dad and Carol.
Thank you.
Thanks, guys.
Excuse me...
Just wanted to say, Dr Finch,
for what it's worth,
nobody I know believes a word of it.
This is corked.
Is it?
Right, sorry about that,
let me just...
No, no. You don't need to smell it.
I smelt it. It's corked.
I'll bring you another bottle.
Anything?
No.
Looked everywhere, no sign.
HE SIGHS
So, we very much hoped the Cyprus
hospitals could've given us a name
that we would find here,
but they haven't.
Which means now
we have two options -
checking each file
against dental records,
which will be very, very slow...
or we make contact with each of
the families of these missing girls
and ask them if their daughter
ever broke her arm on holiday.
Now, if we find one who did,
and it was in Cyprus,
chances are we've found her.
In the end, I think this is
the least worst option.
But it's gonna be hard.
The best most of these families
will have hoped for, for many years,
will simply have been
finding a body to bury.
And for all but one of them -
that's if we're lucky -
we're gonna offer them
that little glimmer of hope,
only to snatch it away
seconds later.
So we tread gently, please.
We tread very gently.
I'm so sorry to trouble you -
my name is DC Fran Lingley,
I'm calling from Bishop Street
Police Station in London.
...And I'm part of a team
investigating the discovery
of human remains in Hendon,
North London.
And I wanted, if I may, to ask you
a question in connection with the
disappearance of your daughter,
Annabelle.
Yeah, I'm very sorry to hear that,
Mr Mason.
So, who might still be alive
that I could talk to,
who would know if your sister
ever broke her wrist?
I completely understand,
and I really wish I could've
given you some answers.
Is there someone who can be there
with you, Jackie?
And I can tell you we can eliminate
Michaela from our list.
OK, thank you. Take care. Goodbye.
They're my oldest friends, Maria.
It's one night.
We stay in a Travelodge,
we eat in a pub!
And I can't afford to buy the kids
new shoes.
Josh, Will, downstairs now, please!
CHILDREN GIGGLE UPSTAIRS
But, fine.
Things will get easier, I promise.
I've got some really good business
coming in in the next few weeks.
What? When have you not had
some really good business
about to come through, Pete?
I think the day I met you,
you were about to buy the club
we were drinking in.
Yeah, then the world
went to hell in a handcart.
I mean, I'll take the
blame for a lot of things,
but not the global financial crash!
We're gonna be late.
Look...
buy the kids whatever shoes
they need.
There'll be money in the
joint account tomorrow.
At the end of the day, Tim,
it's your word against hers.
And given what we know about her...
He saying he's at Smudge's,
apparently.
Right, so...
I don't know Smudge.
Where does he live?
Panford House, number 22.
I hope he's OK, Mr Hollis.
Thank you.
You look after yourself, Steven.
No, I'm sorry, if Jasmine never
sustained an injury like that,
then it really can't be her,
I'm afraid.
No, you cry away, Robin,
and I'm so sorry
we can't give you any more
positive news.
And you're her sister, did you say?
'Yeah.'
And how sure are you, Jessica,
that she broke her wrist?
'100%. I remember the cast,
what I wrote on it.'
OK, do you remember how she did it?
She slipped by the swimming pool.
By the swimming pool? So this was
a swimming pool at home, or...?
We were on holiday.
What year would this have been?
Erm... mid-'90s, maybe?
Do you remember where
you were on holiday?
'We were only little, so I'd have to
check with my mum, but, erm...'
I think it was Cyprus?
OK, Jessica, I think we're gonna
have to come and see you,
but in the meantime,
is your mother...?
She lives five minutes away.
Could you ask her about Cyprus for
me, and also ask if she remembers
if Hayley had a surgical plate
fitted following a fracture?
'No problem.' Can you do that now
and get back to us?
Yeah, sure.
'Do you really think it's her?'
Jessica, I...
Obviously, I can't say for sure,
but...
..I think it's certainly
very possible, yes.
I'll call you straight back.
Anyone remember
the Hayley Reid case?
She was on her way to a party,
wasn't she?
Mm. From a shift at a pub.
New Year's Eve.
Millennium, 1999.
Awful. She just... disappeared.
What was the name of the guy
they thought did it?
Mullins, was it? Mullery.
Adrian Mullery was the boyfriend.
We were exactly the same age.
Yeah, I remember my mum
wouldn't let me get a Saturday job
when that happened.
Yeah, I remember her.
Brown stripes,
and there are the trees.
I think you have a gifted child.
He has a real talent.
Well, you bring it out in him,
so thank you.
It gives him such pleasure.
Jamila, I wan...
I wanted to ask you something.
I wanted to ask you...
do you think that
you would ever consider...
..marrying me?
I'm sorry?
I know, yeah, this has probably
come as a bit of a shock...
And I know I'm not what people
would consider "a catch",
but I'm earning good money now
with my paintings,
and I've saved up enough
to put down a deposit on a flat
to rent for us all.
I just...
In the last couple of years,
we've got to know each other
really well, and, erm, months ago...
..I realised that
I was in love with you.
Just... watching you do
ordinary things.
And, yes,
I should've said something sooner,
I should've mentioned it,
but I was so scared.
I was so scared that you wouldn't...
you know.
And I just wanna make things better
for you, Jamila.
For you and for Asif.
And for me, for me, obviously,
for me, because the idea of me
being with you both
and us being a family...
..that'd make me happy.
Wow!
I'm a bit... shocked.
I mean in a good way, but...
You don't have to say anything.
You know, h-have a think about it
and then we can talk soon.
Maybe tomorrow, at the centre...?
Yes, right. And, erm...
..thank you.
I nearly forgot...
I bought you this.
See you tomorrow.
So the complaint against you,
Dr Finch,
is that on the 27th of April 2017,
while on a house call to
Maureen Anne Avery, since deceased,
and seemingly unaware that
her daughter, the complainant,
Alison Pinion, was in the house,
you verbally abused
and threatened Mrs Avery.
Specifically, that you called her
a "tiresome old bitch",
and that you then told her you'd
"half a mind to stick her
full of morphine,
"and give us all a fucking break".
DOORBELL RINGS
CHATTER FROM RADIO
IN BACKGROUND
Mum?!
Mum?
FOOTSTEPS THUD ON STAIRS
Wake up, Mum.
Jess...
Jessie, what is it?
When Hayley broke her arm that time
when we were on holiday,
did she have a plate fitted?
What?
I think we were in Cyprus.
Did she have a plate fitted?
Why?
Did she?
Yes.
It was a compound fracture.
She had it done
at the local hospital.
Why?
You're gonna have to get up, Mum.
The police are gonna be
coming down from London.
They think they've found her.
They think they've found Hayley.
APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS
Eliot?
Hey, Els, how you doing?
Hi, Dad.
GULLS CALL
Eliot!
My client's mother, Mrs Avery,
was diagnosed with dementia
over seven years ago.
As you can imagine...
Oh, shit!
BREATHES HEAVILY
JESSICA:
Yes, she had a plate fitted,
and it was in Cyprus.
It's her.
SHE SOBS
WAILS
Subtitles by TVT
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app