♪♪
You have a call
with the PBA chief at 1:00,
you have a briefing
with TARU at 3:00 p.m.,
and an intelligence meeting
directly after.
Bad news.
How do you know?
I just know. Gimme.
An off-duty cop,
Officer Kevin Olivet,
shot and killed
a 32-year-old female
at a pharmacy
on East 96th Street
at approximately 600 hours.
The victim was unarmed...
No knife, no gun...
And the press
is swarming.
Why did the officer use
deadly force?
The victim was shoplifting,
and when the officer tried to
intervene, it became physical.
So shot
in the commission of a crime?
Victim have a record?
Assault, four counts
of robbery dating back
to 2013, possession
with intent to sell,
and aggravated harassment.
Our new mayor isn't going
to like this.
What does a public
advocate know about governing?
They know how it's gonna play
to the eight and a half million
of us who aren't cops.
Oh, so we're gonna alienate
35,000 of us who are cops?
It was a police action.
- Yes.
- And police actions...
Don't have
a political component.
But maybe we can be a little
more measured in our response.
We will handle this one
exactly the way we always have.
Do I need
to remind you that your
ex-husband is not very reliable?
Jack is a lot
of things,
but he would never
stand me up.
And he's not answering my calls,
and he always answers.
Look, Erin, I know what
you're up to, okay,
and no amount of busywork is
gonna keep my mind off of Linda.
That's not
what I'm doing.
Of course it's
what you're doing.
It's what the entire
family's doing.
I know
you don't like Jack, but...
What would make you think
I don't like... jackass?
Something isn't right.
- Well, did you call his assistant?
- Yeah.
She's not answering, either.
This his office?
Yeah.
Jack!
Oh, my God. Jack?
Call 911.
When I rode with Welch,
I drove.
That was then,
this is now.
He liked that I drove.
And you could always go
back to riding with him.
Why? You want to go back
to riding with Patimkin?
I didn't say that.
Because you missed me.
I didn't say
that, either.
Didn't have to.
12-David, welcome back.
We have a 10-54, an OD
on West 23rd Street
and West Side Highway.
12-David responding.
And it's good
to be back, Central.
♪ ♪
- Did you call 911?
- Yeah, it was me. I called.
Please, my girlfriend...
She needs help.
All right, let's go.
Step aside. Excuse me.
Step back.
Police.
Coming through.
Right behind you.
Police.
Step aside.
Jamie, I got this.
Stay here.
Hey, sweetheart, what's
your name? What's your name?
Everyone, back up.
♪ ♪
Is this her?
- What's your girlfriend's name?
- It's Taylor.
Hey, Taylor, can you hear me?
Taylor, what'd you take? Hey!
Come on.
Hey, kill the music!
Shut the music off!
Shut it off!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Eddie, call it in.
Central, 12-David. 10-85.
Requesting additional units
at this location.
And put a rush on that bus!
♪♪
*BLUE BLOODS*
Season 08  Episode 01
Title: "Cutting Losses "
MAN (over P.A.):
Code red. Code red. Code red.
No, no, no, no,
I need you to stop, folks.
Can't go any further.
We'll come and get you
as soon as we know anything.
You okay?
Okay, who...?
Who would want to kill Jack?
Look, it's Jack.
The list of possible suspects is
endless.
I mean, he's been a prosecutor
and a defense attorney.
He deals with a
lot of bad people.
Okay, so where do we start?
We don't start anywhere.
Erin, I already told you...
I'm putting in my papers.
No, but-but after
you close this.
No,
Erin, not after I close this.
The person
who closes this is gonna be
an unbiased homicide detective
who catches the case.
No, Danny.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Good afternoon.
The NYPD officer involved,
Kevin Olivet,
has been a member of
this department for four years.
I think it is worth noting
two points...
That in those four years,
he has served
with an unblemished record,
and until yesterday,
without a single incident
of discharging his firearm
in the line of that service.
That being said,
there are protocols in place
for investigating every
- officer-involved shooting.
- I would like to say something.
Madam Mayor.
Welcome.
Carlton, what the
hell are you doing...?
Not my idea.
Please.
Thank you, Commissioner.
As leaders, we have an
accountability to the protocols,
but we also must
be accountable
to the laws of common sense.
An unarmed woman
was shot to death
for allegedly shoplifting.
That calls for a common sense
investigation, as well.
- And I intend to see that through.
- Mayor Dutton,
- are you suggesting that Officer...?
- Is it true that...?
Please sit down.
Okay.
What the hell was that?
That was your mayor
weighing in...
Not on police business.
Not at a department press
conference at One Police Plaza.
This is my house.
Get used to sharing.
Get some respect
for this institution.
Your definition
of police business
is both out of date
and out of bounds.
- City Hall doesn't write that book.
- When a woman
is executed for shop...
I'd be careful of my choice
of words if I were you.
- Semantics?
- She assaulted a police officer.
She has a criminal history.
Her criminal history has nothing
to do with this case.
You don't get
to decide that, Madam Mayor.
Then let's just see Officer
Olivet's disciplinary record.
Release that.
No.
Yes.
You have to make things equal.
They are not equal,
Madam Mayor,
because she is a criminal and
he isn't.
Are you telling me
that you won't do it?
That's exactly
what I'm telling you.
Then you're fired.
You still haven't answered
my question.
You had so many, I lost track.
Why do you really want
to hang up your shield?
Why does everybody care
whether I put
my papers in or not?
Because, for years, being a cop
has defined who you are,
and you're good at it,
and you love it.
I don't love it anymore.
And because you need
to retire because
it's what you really want,
and not as a reaction
to what's happened
these past few months.
Come on, what difference
does it make?
It'll make a difference
to your family.
I know you blame yourself
for the house,
but it was just that.
The house.
You guys were the ones
that made it a home.
Isn't that what Linda said
to you when it burned down?
It didn't burn down.
It was torched.
It wasn't your fault.
It was my fault!
Don't you get it?!
The house was my fault,
the fire was my fault,
and Linda was my fault!
Where you going?
We still have a lot
to talk about.
You have too many questions.
Hey! Hey, you!
Where'd you go?
We told you to
remain at the scene.
Look, I just got to go
check on my girlfriend.
No, no, no. Come back here.
We need to talk to you.
What'd she take?
Look, I don't really know, okay?
You don't know what drugs
your girlfriend took?
I'm not sure.
Six kids OD'd last night.
And right now the parents of
those kids are getting visits
from police officers, telling
them that their kid is dead.
There was a guy
walking around with pills,
asking if anyone wanted Molly.
Next thing, kids were
dropping like flies.
A guy?
What did he look like?
It was so dark, I...
Give me a break, you didn't
get a name or a description?
- He uses the nickname "Ice."
- Uses?
- You know this guy?
- No.
All right, let's
see some ID.
Look, you're not gonna tell
my mom about this, right?
Let me see some ID.
His appointment book
is full of clients
and court dates.
Yeah.
His last appointment
was at 5:00.
Hey, I already told you we're
not working the case, okay?
We're gonna hand it off
to Homicide, so just stop.
- I know.
- Okay, then.
According to this,
Jack was meeting
a Dr. W. here.
Baez.
Detectives.
Are you
Jack Boyle's assistant?
Maria Cuesta.
I'm Detective Baez.
Where were you
when Jack was attacked?
He sent me to court
to file a motion.
And who was this
Dr. W. at 5:00?
Dr. Weber.
Hold on. You're talking
about the same Dr. Weber
that Jack represented
against Erin?
Yup.
How'd that meeting go?
He came to ask Mr. Boyle
to represent him.
Again?
In what case?
I don't know.
Because Mr. Boyle said
he would never
represent him on any case.
All right.
If we need anything else,
we'll let you know.
So where's this homicide
detective who caught the case?
I guess you're looking at him.
Really, Jack?
Our wedding photo?
I need to remind you that
Nicky is graduating this year
and you need to be there.
And when she gets married,
that's your job
to walk her down the aisle.
You got that?
You've got to pull
through, Jack.
You owe that to her.
You hear me?
Ms. Reagan?
We got the results back.
Your husband needs surgery.
Ex-h... Ex-husband.
Uh, when?
Immediately. He's got
internal bleeding,
a ruptured spleen.
We're prepping
the O.R. right now.
We'll need your consent.
W... My...
Uh, I don't understand.
You're the one listed
as his next of kin.
We need to do this ASAP
or he's not gonna make it.
I'll send in a nurse with the
consent forms for you to sign.
I remember the day
you got this.
First time I ever met
a sitting president.
- Had a lot of people cross this floor.
- Yeah.
Bill Clinton
was my personal favorite.
I want you both to know
I've secured positions for you
within the department.
Sid, you'll be the new C.O.
of Manhattan North, and,
Baker...
this department can always use
a decorated detective.
I'd rather be here.
Me, too.
Well, you'll have to
take that up with my successor.
Chapter one, point ten
of the city charter:
"While so acting
temporarily as mayor,
"the public advocate
shall not exercise
"any power of appointment to
or removal from office
"or any power
lawfully delegated
by the mayor."
She can't fire you.
I'm aware of that.
Are you kidding?
That's great.
Thing is...
my new boss wants me gone.
It doesn't matter
what she wants.
It's what you want.
You think I should
just barricade in here
because of some fine print
in the city charter?
Boss, are you telling us
you got no more fight
left in you?
Oh, that's not gonna work, Sid.
What, you can't
- take a challenge?
- And I'm not
ten years old and you are not
Sister Mary Damien
screaming at me
from the sidelines.
All right, you're your age now,
and you're the PC
and they're stringing up a noose
for one of your men.
- You're just gonna let them?
- Please.
- Shaming me's not gonna work, either.
- I would like
to say something.
As a woman.
That is the biggest
load of crap
that I have
ever heard.
You're just gonna
let this broad
push you out the door?
This broad happens to be
mayor of New York City.
So what?
That's all you've got...
"I don't think
the mayor likes me"?!
Who the hell do you think
you're talking to here?!
I'm sorry to
keep you waiting.
- Lieutenant Simon Kinnear.
- Narcotics.
Please, have a seat.
This about the overdoses
at the party?
Six kids died at that
party last night because
some punk drug dealer
decided to mix
a lethal amount of
fentanyl in the capsules.
What's that
got to do with us?
Well, when you responded to the
club, you got some information
from a kid whose girlfriend
went into arrest.
Ryan Young.
We flipped him.
He's willing to
make an introduction
to the drug dealer who sold the
drugs. Goes by the name of Ice.
That's great.
Yeah. But he will
only work with you.
You interested?
- To get a drug dealer off the streets?
- Hell yeah.
- Good.
- Have to make it look
a little less suspicious.
You need a girlfriend.
Guess that's where
I come in?
I've always wanted
to be arm candy.
Now, we want you
to make a buy.
Young... will meet you
inside the club
and introduce you
to Bryce Medero,
aka Ice.
What happens
if we get into trouble?
If things get
out of hand,
you'll use an agreed-upon
safe word to alert us.
How about
"get us the hell out of here"?
Yeah, would that work?
Apparently Weber wanted
to retain Jack's services again.
You know what that was about?
After I lost the case
against Weber,
I took a magnifying glass
to his life.
Apparently... another one
of his girlfriends
disappeared five years ago.
Body was never found.
So I reopened that case.
And he wanted Jack
to represent him,
Jack said no.
Which may have set Weber off.
All I know is Jack was anxious
to talk about something.
Does Weber have an alibi for
the day this girl disappeared?
He says he put her on a train to
Manhattan, never saw her again.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Without a body
it's hard to convict.
Well, what do you think?
Were you able to get a subpoena
for his phone records
or something?
Based on what?
Based on the fact
that he's already
confessed to one murder.
That has no bearing
on this case.
Oh, come on.
Mom! Quick!
What? What happened?
No, Dad's awake.
- Hi.
- Oh.
How you feeling?
Like I've gone through
a wood chipper.
Well, it proves you
got thick skin, Jack.
Mom and Uncle Danny
are the ones that found you
and got you to the hospital.
Did you get a look
at their face,
remember their voice, anything?
All I remember is someone...
h-hitting me in the head
from behind.
I love you, Dad.
I'm so happy
you woke up.
Why don't you tell me
how you see the problem?
You do realize
you're taking advice
from a murderer, right?
Might want to save
yourself some money
and save yourself, possibly,
by getting the hell out of here
as quick as you can.
Detective...
I'm just saying.
Is this absolutely necessary?
Well, I didn't want
to embarrass you in front
of your, uh, patient there.
Did you stab Jack Boyle?
What did you and Jack
fight about?
I-I would love to help you
but, unfortunately,
I think that's covered
under attorney-client privilege.
Where were you yesterday
at 11:00 a.m.?
Where were you May 28?
What did you just say?
Danny! Danny.
Walk away! Just walk away!
Are you sure you don't
want me to unpack that?
No, thank you.
Should I put it away, then?
It's fine where it is.
May I ask what's in it?
The cash, the weapons,
the secret tapes.
Abigail...
I'm tired.
The kind of tired
you can't sleep off.
Commissioner.
Officer Olivet
is here to see you.
You knew about this?
Let's have him.
Kevin.
Welcome to the 14th floor.
Commissioner.
It looks like it's a slow day
in the office.
The gang's all here.
So why don't we
- move to the couch?
- .Please.
Well, I'd hoped
to be coming here
for a different reason.
I think I've got some idea
what you're going through,
and I'm sorry.
I saw the press conference.
Thank you for trying.
This particular commissioner
sees that as part of his job.
To alienate the new mayor?
To stand up for his officers.
To be the voice of
its men and women.
Listen, how you holding up?
Considering the papers
are saying
that I killed
a defenseless woman,
that I'm a murderer?
Well, you'd do well not to pay
any attention to the press.
Tell that to my
five-year-old.
When there's a police shooting,
the first 24 hours
are always a free-for-all.
But it's the PC's job
to be a real champion
for the guys in blue.
Without that, there'd
be a lot more cops
dropping out of the department.
I'm walking the beat
with a target on my back.
The truth is gonna come out.
The press can be brutal,
for sure,
but that's what we're here for.
To make sure you get your say.
To know that you've got someone
at the top watching your back.
I'm resigning.
Don't pull your pin.
Clear your name.
And,
please, there's nothing
that you're gonna say
that's going to change my mind.
Your partner
had to physically come
between you and Dr. Weber.
Yeah, well, that's because the
guy is a cold-blooded killer
- who's walking around free.
- Eh.
But that's not what set you off.
What set you off
was when he mentioned May 28.
- Hey. No.
- The day that...
No, I can't do this, okay?
You can't do what?
You can't talk about it?
- I just said I can't!
- Can't what?!
I can't do this without my wife.
Okay?
I think you can.
I know what it's like
to lose the love of your life.
I lost mine ten years ago.
Well, what does that mean?
That you're supposed to shed
some light on it for me?
Teach me how to cope?
Unfortunately, I...
I don't have a...
a magic formula.
I still miss her.
But I'm able
to live my life.
And that's what
everyone wants for you.
Linda's death wasn't your fault.
I know.
So whose fault was it?
No one's.
Really?
'Cause, see,
if I hadn't been working late
and she hadn't changed her shift
because of me,
because of my job...
Just as she had done
a dozen times before that.
She was doing
her job.
She died doing what she loved.
What you would have done.
I should've stopped her.
No, Danny, she...
Danny, she died in a helicopter
crash airlifting her patient.
I should've been home more, Doc.
You know?
I wasn't.
You've been coming
here for months,
and you have never uttered
the words that she's gone,
that she's dead,
she's never coming back.
It's not healthy,
Danny, and you know it.
What about Sean and Jack?
Hmm?
You want them to live in
anger and denial because...
because you can't get over it?
I just don't know how.
Very small steps.
And if I can't?
If you can't,
you lean on your family.
Linda's the one
I always lean on.
♪♪ Dance music playing...
(indistinct chatter)
♪♪
Hey, Jamie.
Remember Eddie?
Hey.
This is Bryce.
This is Jamie.
He's a friend of mine.
He's cool.
Hey.
I've never seen you here.
I've never seen you either.
He just wants to score
some Molly.
He looks like a cop.
That's funny. I was thinking
you look like a criminal.
Give him a toss.
What?
You have a problem with that?
I think we should
take our business
someplace else.
I think you're a little jumpy.
And I think you've seen
Scarface one too many times.
They're clean.
Lucky you.
Hey, I thought you said
your guy was cool.
Chill out. How much
you looking to score?
Enough for a little party
for two.
Oh, my God. Eddie?
Ohhh, man. Long time.
I-I-I'm busy right now.
God, I haven't seen you
since college. You look great.
Hey, who is this guy?
Listen, I'd-I'd love
to catch up.
Maybe we can go and have
a drink together.
Why don't you take a hike.
Yeah, this is
really not a good time.
Never is a good time.
All right?
Doing business here or what?
Yeah.
Four will cost you... $200.
Enjoy.
Oh, we will.
All right,
police. Nobody move!
Hands where we can see 'em!
Autopsy showed cocaine
and amphetamines in the victim.
That's good news
for Olivet's defense.
Unfortunately, it
came after the media
had beaten him
up pretty good.
He resigned.
Oh, you didn't tell me
he resigned.
Collateral damage.
Things'll get better.
I'm on my third mayor, Pop.
I think I'm used up.
I don't think we need
two of us sitting here
worrying about Danny.
Is he back yet?
Came in the front door
and went straight upstairs.
No dinner,
no chitchat,
no nothing.
He should be down here
with his boys.
Of all my kids,
I think he's the most like me.
When we lost Mary,
you checked out completely.
I was stuck in quicksand.
I remember.
You know what got me out?
Work?
Purpose?
My kids became my purpose.
What are you doing?
I got Judge Barton
to sign a subpoena
for Weber's phone and computer.
Based on what?
Well, based on the fact
that Weber's
a person of interest in his
ex-girlfriend's disappearance.
This was signed
at 2:00 a.m.
Yeah. Judge Barton, you know,
he likes to play bridge
until all hours of the night.
Oh, and he also does have
a taste for good Scotch.
How much did that
set you back?
You don't want to know.
So, what have you got?
Well, seems Weber didn't have
his cell phone turned on
the morning Jack was stabbed, so
I couldn't track him that way.
- But he does have a ZipPoint.
- A ZipPoint?
Yeah, it's to help you find
your car if it was stolen
or if you can't remember
where you parked.
Kind of like a mini GPS.
The ZipPoint puts his vehicle
at the scene.
It's still not
enough to arrest.
No, it's not enough to arrest,
but it is enough
to get a warrant
for Weber's house.
Which is exactly what
we're gonna do.
Upstairs,
downstairs, nothing.
We're just not looking
in the right places.
Or he didn't leave any evidence.
Let's keep looking.
Trap door? Are you kidding me?
Okay.
Let's take a look.
What do you think this is?
I think maybe he forgot
to take out the trash.
Hello.
Afternoon,
Commissioner.
The mayor said
you can go right in.
Commissioner Reagan,
thank you for coming.
"Frank" will do fine.
Close the door, have a seat.
I read the autopsy report.
- Mm.
- She was
clearly under the influence.
To put it mildly.
Well, how would you put it?
Officer Olivet was trying
to reason with someone
who had snorted enough jet fuel
to win the ninth race
at Belmont.
I'm not going to pressure
the DA's office
to pursue any criminal charges
against Officer Olivet.
There's something
you should know
about police officers.
- Oh, I think I know...
- Hold on.
Okay.
They know what people
are capable of
in ways that most,
thankfully, do not.
They have seen firsthand
the cigarette burns
on an infant's back
or the black eyes
and the sideways jaw
on an 80-year-old
rape victim.
And they assume the worst.
And they take that on
so that good people
can go about their lives
and think generously
about their fellow man.
They provide that luxury.
You say that as if it's a fact.
It is to me.
And a hard-earned one.
And whoever is in my office,
he or she,
if they're any good,
is gonna feel the same way.
My job is to advocate
for the people.
And if that calls
for an investigation
into your department
or any of your officers,
it's not personal.
It's going to happen.
Because of your rush
to judgment,
this city has lost
a good police officer
as surely and as finally
as if he were killed
in the line of duty.
I didn't ask you here to argue
the-the finer points
of the shooting.
I called you in here
to apologize.
As it turns out,
I can't fire you.
Really?
I didn't know that.
I guess I could just resign.
Your polling numbers are higher
than any mayor's in memory.
Oh, don't pay any attention
to those.
Why do you say that?
They don't poll the folks
who we put behind bars.
But I'm kind of like one of
those last century buildings
you fought to save when you were
on the landmark commission.
How's that?
Oh, people walk by me every day
and I look like an anachronism
against all the glass and steel,
but tear me down...
all of a sudden, I'm beloved.
That's it? We're done?
I am.
Do you want to stay on the job?
Only if I'm wanted.
Madam Mayor.
Good day.
Maggie.
You found our body.
Yep. Crime scene has it.
You'll be able
to put him away.
Thank you.
How is Jack?
He's gonna make it.
Somehow I feel guilty
about that.
- Don't.
- You were right.
I asked you to work this case
so you were too busy
to even think about Linda.
Yeah.
Wasn't too hard to figure
that one out.
Trouble is, all I do
is think about Linda, anyway.
Maybe you should
think about
what Linda would say if you told
her you were gonna quit.
I know what she'd say.
She'd be ecstatic.
No, she wouldn't.
You would have
driven her insane at home.
What are you gonna do?
You suck at fishing,
you hate golf.
What you're good at is the job.
The job doesn't need me anymore.
Well, maybe you need the job.
Will you just think about it?
Yeah.
And if you ever need
a shoulder to cry on...
Call Jamie?
Exactly.
Come on, Danny.
Just take a minute, man.
No. You said you were
gonna drop me off.
It's one little stop.
Yeah, well, I don't feel
like socializing.
Come on. It's Pop's friend,
Mrs. Ginty, all right?
She hasn't seen us since
we were kids. I promised.
Great. Then we'll send her
a picture.
Get out of the car now.
Surprise!
Hey.
What's going on?
- Wait till you see the game room.
- The what?
It's not a game room,
it's a man cave.
- What is this?
- This is your new home.
Only a five-minute
walk from school.
We rented it for you.
With an option to buy
if you decide
you like living here.
There's even a real backyard.
- Come on, let's eat.
- I'm starving.
We'll give you
the full tour after.
Danny.
Everything you need's
right here.
Why are y'all looking at me?
I don't know what to say.
Okay.
I did read an obit a while back.
When you reach a certain age,
you do that sort of thing.
And someone said,
"We are all just passing time.
And occupy our chair
very briefly."
The time we had with Linda
was a gift.
And we are all the better
that she occupied her chair...
so well.
Some say
we have more than
our share of loss.
But I see God's light
in this family every day.
And though I may not
understand it,
I trust in His plan for us all.
When Mary died...
When I lost my wife...
I was a mess.
And it was my kids...
Joe, Erin,
Jamie,
and Danny, who...
even though they
had lost their mom...
always made sure,
each in their own way,
to be there for me.
I'm not sure
what a shrink would say
about that.
But it was appreciated.
Boys, I'd like you to say grace.
Actually, um,
I'd like to say it.
Bless us, oh, Lord.
These Thy gifts,
which we are about to receive
from Thy bounty,
through Christ our Lord.
Amen.
♪♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org