♪ I’m goin’ down to South Park,
gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ Goin’ down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"Howdy, Neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can’t unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm!
Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Yes, sir -- If you're looking
to move out of the city,
I think your family
would love South Park.
You can get four times
the house here
that you can get in the city.
A cortado?
Is that like a coffee?
Yeah, we --
we have a coffee shop here. Yes.
We're up in the mountains
about an hour from Denver...
Do you think you could drive out
from the city this weekend
and I could show you
some properties?
Oh, you have a Tesla?
Oh, how nice.
South Park -- yeah, it's
a charming country village.
If you're able
to work from home,
I think you'll really love it
out here...
LaCroix?
The sparkling Mineral Water?
Yes, I do believe we have that
in our stores here...
We're seeing a massive influx
of city people
moving out here to the country.
And the truth is we just don't
have enough real estate agents
to keep up with all the demand.
Well, I don't have
much experience,
but I thought
I'd give real estate a try.
Mrs. Cartman,
being a real estate agent
takes a lot of intellect
and a lot of raw talent.
You have to get
your picture taken.
Get people to like the picture
and go,
"Oh, I'd like to hang out
with that person."
And then act like
you like those people
when you show them houses.
Well, I do believe I'm good with
people, and the truth is...
I need to do this for my son.
Our...rent is going up
because of all the new people
moving into town --
and I don't think
I can afford it anymore.
Well, then, I'm going to give
you a shot, Mrs. Cartman.
For your little boy.
God dammit...
Oh, you piece of shit!
Hello, sweetie!
Mom! Where the hell
have you been?!
I've been home from school
for like 45 minutes!
I'm sorry, honey,
mommy had some errands.
I didn't have anything to eat
except Nutella.
I was about to call
Child Services!
Honey...
Mommy has some big news.
What.
I...got a job, Eric.
I'm your job.
Oh, honey --
It's going to be good.
Mommy is just going
to be working a few days a week
and you can be a big boy
and take care of yourself.
No.
Eric, this has to happen.
We can't afford
to live in this house
unless I make more money,
and this job pays really well.
Wha-- What job
could you possibly have?
You don't know how
to do anything.
I'm a real estate agent.
A what?
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
Hey, Butters,
I need your help.
Well -- Well, sure, Eric!
What's goin' on?!
Butters,
I have some shocking news...
My mom got a job.
Oh...Oh, and you're worried
that maybe now
your mom won't always be there
to take care of you?
What? No.
My mom got a job.
My mom is dumb as shit
and somebody is paying her
to do something.
Have you ever heard of
a real estate agent, Butters?
Well, not really.
Yeah, well, neither had I.
So I looked it up on a bunch
of those shows and stuff.
You don't do anything.
You just look nice
and hug people
and then when someone buys
or sells a house, you make
money.
Wow! Well, that sounds like
a good deal!
It's more than a good deal,
Butters,
it's *bleep* legal theft.
If my mom can be
a real estate agent,
then literally
anyone in the world can.
We've got
all these people moving
from the cities into our town,
I can probably be a millionaire
in just a few days time.
Wow wee!
Now, whatever you do,
don't tell anybody.
If anyone else finds out
about this,
they'll all want to be
real estate agents, too.
You've always been great
at taking pictures, Butters.
I won't forget this
when I'm rich.
Gosh, thanks, Eric!
Okay, Liane...
You've got this.
You can do this.
Bottled water. Bottled water.
Bottled water.
Hello there! I believe I spoke
with you on the phone?
I'm Liane Cartman
with South Park Realtors!
Uh-huh...Uh-huh...
Well, this is the house
I was telling you about.
It just came on the market.
It's a 2,300 square foot
mid colonial home.
Detached garage.
Pilates?
Excuse me?
Pilates.
Is there a gym
my wife can do Pilates?
Oh, you're about five minutes
from the local gym.
Pilates. Bottled Water?
Oh! Um, you have such
a lovely family!
It must have been a big drive
from the city?
Tesla. We have a Tesla.
Wi-Fi! Wi-Fi!
Is there Wi-Fi?
No Wi-Fi. Bottled water.
Well, come on in,
let me show you around!
Okay, this is a three bedroom
house with bathrooms.
Front yard and back yard.
Eric...
what are you doing?
Oh, I just got some clients here
looking to relocate.
These people are from the city.
Uh, cortado.
Bottled water.
Wi-Fi. Pilates.
Uh, excuse me one moment.
Eric!
What are you up to?
I got a job
as a real estate agent, mom.
You are not
a real estate agent --
Neither are you --
Now just march
right back home
and I will see you
when I am done with work!
Mom,
real estate is an open market.
You're not the only one
who gets to take advantage
of all the city people.
Cortado?
Cortado!
Oh, bottled water?
Wi-Fi!
Metal bottled water!
Eric,
this house is being represented
by South Park Realtors.
You don't get to just walk in
and show it!
Oh! Ok! That's fine!
I have tons of friends
in South Park!
I'll get my own listings!
Mayor: People...
this is the most exciting time
in the history of South Park...
As you know, there are people
from all over the country
leaving the cities and coming
to small, rural towns like ours.
It's truly incredible
for all of us.
With this new surge of people
from urban areas,
we're seeing more town money
from sales taxes,
more profit
in our local businesses --
My bakery has seen
a 20% increase in sales.
Oh, I just love
all these city people moving in!
That's right. It's great to have
chitty people.
These chitty people come
with their fancy chitty clothes
and their big chitty cars.
You know,
and these chitty people
have a chitty way
of doing things
that will expose us all
to their chitty ideas.
Yeah, and they've got city money
and city lifestyles!
Chitty money,
chitty lifestyles.
And they'll move here
and bring their chitty families.
And their cultured, chitty kids
will hang out with our kids
and expose them
to their chitty ways.
I've always dreamed
of South Park
becoming more than a little
hick town.
And these city people
bring with them...a new hope.
Here's to the future,
everyone!
All: The future!
Okay, so this is a three bedroom
two and a half bath --
Come on in, everybody!
Wi-Fi?
-Wha-- Wha-- Wha-- Wha?
-LaCroix.
You got about 2,300 square feet
and there is
a finished basement.
Oat milk. Oat milk.
Detached garage --
stairs head up to the master,
which is an en suite,
if I remember correctly.
Let's get on back
to the kitchen...
Cortado?
You've got a nice, big kitchen,
pretty, new appliances.
Door in the back
gets you out to the garage.
Excuse me,
what are you doing?
Just showing them your house.
Come on, let's check out
the second floor --
Our house isn't for sale!
Hey!
Nice, big bathroom
for the two rooms up here.
Tweek's grandma
is staying in one of the rooms,
which serves as an office space
when she's not here.
And then we are back down
to the spacious living room!
Will you please
get out of our house.
Yeah,
we're just about done.
Well,
what do you guys think?
MacBook, Tesla.
I'm sorry, I didn't get that...
My son left his MacBook
in the Tesla.
Oh, sure,
well, let's head on out now.
We can take a look
at Jimmy's house.
It doesn't have
such sucky furniture.
Let me talk to these guys
and see if we can come up
with a number.
I think I can get you
4 million for this place.
$4 million? Really?
I'll be in touch.
Told you
our furniture sucked!
Hey -- Hey, John,
I got some bad news --
We just lost another client
to South Park Realty Group.
What?!
We're losing people like crazy.
These guys are ruthless.
Who is this
South Park Realty Group?
Has anyone heard of them!?
It appears to be
mostly one agent.
A-A pretty young guy --
Can't have been in the business
that long --
Oh, my God...
That's a pretty
damn good picture.
How'd he get
that kind of depth of field?
I don't know he's gotta be using
some kind of soft filter --
nothing I've ever seen.
Alright, everyone!
Looks like we've got
some competition!
If anyone thinks they can take
our clients,
they've got another thing
coming.
Everyone get up.
We're gonna retake our pictures!
All: Awww!
No, no, no,
we're getting our butts kicked,
and we need to show this kid
what we can do!
Come on, Chris!
You gotta look really welcoming!
Ugh. I'm trying--
Come on,
arch your back more!
I'm, ugh,
arched as far as I can...
Come on, Chris,
you wanna lose another sale?!
Arch your back more!!
I-I got it --
That's good, we got it --
Get in here, Carol!
Got it! Ok, next!
Hey, guys, it’s Eric
from South Park Realty Group.
Are you dreaming of moving out
of the city
and into
the beautiful countryside?
I want you to check out
Clyde’s house.
This is a 2,300 square foot
mid colonial home --
detached garage -- now listing
for just $3.5 million.
Let’s check it out.
♪
This house is so spacious.
I think my cameraman Butters
can attest to this.
Isn’t this nice, Butters?
Butters:
Yeah, it’s real roomy!
Just look at these amenities.
♪
These giant, glass double doors
lead to the unfinished backyard.
Plenty of room here for a pool
or a horse stable.
This is just one of the amazing
properties we have
at South Park Realty Group.
We’ve got other great listings,
like --
And my personal favorite,
Kyle’s house.
Get out of that sewage drain
you call a city
and start living the country
life you’ve always wanted.
South Park Realty Group.
Get out of the city
and into beautiful South Park.
Uh, Liane,
you got a call, line 2.
Sounds like a broker
interested in 4600 Highgate.
Ooh! Okay.
Hi! This is Liane
with South Park Realtors.
How’s it going?
This is Eric Cartman
with South Park Realty Group.
Eric, stop it.
Well, I’m standing here
with some clients
who want to make a deal
on this Highgate place.
They wanna offer $175,000.
You are going to get me fired,
Eric.
And then we are going to lose
our home.
$175,000 is a great number --
$25,000 below asking,
but you know
you’re never gonna get $200,000.
Don’t worry, these deals
are always like this.
I am doing this job for us!
So we can have a roof
over our heads!
The HVAC all needs to be redone
and you know it.
I am not talking about this
anymore!
Okay, that’s fine mom, why don’t
you go to *bleep* hell?!
It always gets like this
with agents.
Don’t worry,
she’ll call back, watch.
South Park Realty Group,
this is Eric.
You are in so much trouble,
young man.
Okay, okay...
$180,000, but that’s as high
as I can do.
We got it.
It just isn’t fair...
We retook all our pictures,
and what does
South Park Really Group do?
They go and make a video.
And just like that,
they take all our customers.
I think maybe real estate
just isn’t the same anymore.
Maybe we gotta start making
fancy videos to keep up.
Excuse me, there’s all these
City People moving into town --
and I think I’d like to sell
my property.
-R-Really?
-That’s great!
-Hey, hey, sir --
-We can sell your house!
Move! Move! Get! Get!
That’s a very smart idea!
It’s definitely
a sellers’ market right now!
It’s good you came
to South Park Realtors.
What kind of house is it?
♪
Once in a lifetime,
a property comes up for sale
that is so unique,
it defies words.
We know that good houses
are getting hard to come by
in South Park...
and that’s why we are so excited
to bring you this exceptional
new property.
♪
This is the historic
Aspen Park Hot Dog.
200 square feet of pure luxury.
Let’s check it out.
♪
You want to move out of the city
and enjoy the laid back
country life?
It’s all here.
Find out more about
this dream home today
at South Park Realtors.
Man: LaCroix? LaCroix?
-Wi-Fi?
-LaCroix?
Huh...
people.
Oh, no, there’s way too many
people!
Go on! Go, go, shoo!
Go on!
people!
People...
We have a giant problem.
There are now so many
city people
looking for houses
in South Park...
that it could destroy
our rebounding economy.
Uh...How so?
I thought city people
were good for our economy.
They are,
but Mr. Kim has a theory,
and I think you all better
listen to him.
Mr. Kim.
What’s the one thing
people hate most?
people.
people wanna get out
of the city.
If too many come here...
chitty
people
gonna leave.
We can’t let that happen.
Not when things are finally
starting to turn around!
So then we have to find a way
to stop this.
It’s the damn
real estate agents!
They’re the ones
who are going overboard.
They only care about
their commissions!
Yes, we have to tell
the realtors to cool their jets!
Realtors don’t care
about anything but money.
We have to show them who’s
really in charge of this town...
Jimbo -- go to your gun store
and get the necessary supplies.
I’m declaring open season...
on real estate agents.
Cortado?
Cortado.
Oat milk?
Bottled Water...
Metal Bottle Water.
LaCroix?
LaCroix!
Metal bottle water?
Edamame. Edamame.
Cartman:
Welcome, Home Buyers!
I'm Eric
with South Park Realty Group.
We hope you're enjoying
the provided food and beverages.
LaCroix!
Yes, that's right!
You know,
here at South Park Realty Group,
we've had
some amazing listings --
Craig's house,
Jimmy's house --
but I think you'll all agree
that what we have for you today
is a whole nother level.
I present to you...
Tolkien's house!
♪♪
-Baw?
-Wha-- Wha-- Wha-- Wha -- Wha?
These owners have just moved out
to a farm,
and we're listing this house
at just under $50 million.
Yes! Go on in!
Check it out!
Make me an offer!
-Pilates?
You are in big trouble,
young man!
This is my listing, mom!
I have had it with you!
Come here right now!
This is my listing, mom!
Eric!
What the hell?
Over here...
What happened here?
They're too smart for us.
South Park Realty Group.
We tried to keep up --
took our pictures again --
ahghg!
My spine is broken.
Well, it serves you right for
what you're doing to our town!
You're driving
all the city people away!
Not us...
South Park Realty Group...
they upset the natural balance.
Real estate agents
don't really do anything.
If they start doing stuff,
then the whole housing market
goes crazy.
Where is South Park Realty Group
located?!
They're showing a house...
The Tolkien house...
You have to stop them.
Ahg! Help!
Somebody call
Child Protective Services!
Eric, you're only making it
worse!
I am not doing
a co-brokering deal, mom,
it's not gonna happen.
This isn't about that, Eric,
and you know it!
You're upset.
You're upset because you don't
want your mom to have a job!
That isn't true.
It is true!
You're scared and you're jealous
that a job will take
my attention away from you!
You just want to offer
the sellers a lower commission
to list this house and it's not
going to work, mom!
It's ok to be scared, Eric.
I know that I'm the only family
you have,
but you're making everything
worse for us!
I see one!
There's a real estate agent
right there!
There's a big one
and a little, fat one!
Eric, you need to stop this
right now.
When I close this deal, mom,
I'm gonna be the richest kid
in town!
It's doesn't work that way,
Eric!
You aren't going to make
any money --
you're just driving up
the market
and none of your deals
will make it through escrow!
Well, we'll just see in 30 days,
won't we?!
Except for some of my deals,
which have a 45 day
contingency period!
Fine, Eric.
Will you stop all this
if I quit my job?!
And you won't get
any other job?
No.
And your only job will be me?
And you'll be home
when I get back from school
and have my mid afternoon meal
all ready on the table?
Yes, Eric...
Yes..
Hold yer fire!
Come on out,
ya damn real estate agents!
Don't shoot!
I am not a real estate agent!
I am quitting as of right now.
And South Park Realty Group
is no more.
We did it...
We *bleep* did it!
♪♪
Head Realtor: Real Estate
is a delicate balance.
It has to be left
to the professionals.
There's a great migration
happening all over America.
And if we do it right...
Everyone ends up in a home...
that they can afford.
I think it's cool
we live in a hot dog.
We have everything
we need here.
We've got running water,
a couch to sleep on.
And most important,
we have each other.
Weak...
I live in a hot dog.
♪♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today