♪ I'm goin' down to South Park,
gonna have myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking day or night ♪
♪ People spouting,
"Howdy, Neighbor!" ♪
♪ Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind ♪
♪ Mrph rmhmhm rm!
Mrph rmhmhm rm! ♪
♪ Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine ♪
Watch Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
As farmers
and cultivators of marijuana,
we have a responsibility
to society...
I know we all respect
the crop here,
and we seek each day
to better understand
the nuances and legitimacy
of its uses.
Let's go weed! Wew!
But we growers must face
a harsh reality...
Since the legalization of
marijuana, communities of color,
black and brown Coloradans,
those most affected
by the racist war on drugs,
have now been locked out of the
wealth creation of the industry.
Luckily, the public is starting
to understand this unfairness...
And many people are now talking
of boycotting cannabis growers
who are only white owned.
Boycotting what?
Wait... What?
We are seeing a healthy
and dramatic spike in consumers
who demand that their marijuana
be grown
by those who understand
the fight for social equity.
Ugh ahhug...
The bottom line is this...
A completely white owned
weed business these days...
just isn't going to survive.
Guys... I wanna have kind of
a tough talk with you.
We don't really have
any black friends,
we don't reach out
to the black community.
Shelley you never bring
any black dudes over.
I mean, Stan, your three
best friends are all white.
There's only one black kid
in my whole class.
Yes, that kid Token.
How come you never hang out
with him?
I do hang out with him.
In a group maybe
but I don't recall
just you and Token
ever doing anything.
I've never seen Token
here at the farm
just like the two of you guys.
Why not?
I... I don't know.
Randy, stop, we're not racists.
We'd like to think that
wouldn't we?
But... actions speak louder
than words, gang.
I guess...
I guess I just want you
to think about it.
Uh hey Token.
Oh hey Stan.
Uh listen, I uh...
How're ya doin?
Fine.
Um... You think your family would
wanna come over for dinner?
Out at our farm?
It's kind of far isn't it?
Yeah but...
Look, Token, I think maybe you
and I should hang out more.
What are you talking about?
I mean we never just hang out,
you and me.
Hey we never hang out
just you and me either, Stan!
Shut up, Butters.
Look, just will you please
just see
if your family
will come over for dinner?
It would mean a lot.
Okay, there we go.
That is a farm fresh hemp salad
sourced locally here at Tegridy!
Alright, come on, everybody,
dig in.
Thank you so much
for having us over.
This is really nice.
We've never been
to a marijuana farm before.
Well, you know, with our boys
starting to become so close...
We thought we better get
the families together!
If they're friends
then we need to be friends! Huh?
Do you mind if I post this?
Check out our friends!
Randy... I hope you didn't invite
us here because we're black.
W-What are you talking about?
It's just that
the past year or so
a lot of people have been
inviting us over to dinner
and then taking pictures of us
to show everyone on Instagram.
Oh, that's so lame.
No, we really just wanted
to get to know you guys better
since Stan is friends
with Token.
You know...
Just out of curiosity...
Why did you guys name him that?
What do you mean?
Well... I mean, it's just
kind of an odd name, isn't it?
Like, some people might think
you guys naming your son that
isn't very cool.
People have a problem
with Tolkien's name?
Well, I mean other people
just think it's a little...
I mean, come on, I mean, I'm...
I'm not calling you guys racist,
but...
Why did you name your son that?
My husband has always been
a huge fan
of "Lord of The Rings"
and "The Hobbit."
I wanted to name my son
after my favorite author.
But she didn't want
to name our son J.R.R.,
so we just named him Tolkien.
His name is Tolkien?
Yes, you know
his name is Tolkien.
- I thought your name was Token.
- My name is Tolkien.
Sorry, I don't think
it's that weird.
J.R.R. Tolkien is one of
the most prolific,
influential writers of our time.
Holy shit,
that's what his name means?
What did you think
his name meant?
Would you like to see how we
grow and process our weed?
You see,
it's all about refinement.
Here at Tegridy,
we believe the best weed
is untouched from the earth...
So we distill it down
to its basic essence.
Over there
are our clean out vats
and up here we have
our first stage drying racks.
Oh, real quick!
It all takes about six days
from the field to a jar
that we can sell.
So... What do you think?
It's... uh, very involved.
Yeah. It takes a lot.
You know...
I just had a crazy idea...
Our boys are best friends now...
Why don't you come work
for Tegridy?
Randy, I have a job.
I'm a very successful
co-executive
of a financial consulting firm.
Oh my gosh... I was just saying
we could really use
a co-executive
of financial consulting!
Look, I...
Would it be okay if...
If I sent you
some of our receipts
and you could help us
financial consult?
That's what we do...
Sure.
Oh, my God, this is amazing.
Here's to the start
of something wonderful.
Would you like some free weed?
No.
Hey, Stan.
Dude... My head is reeling,
you're not gonna believe this.
Not gonna believe what?
Token's name isn't Token.
It's Tolkien.
Yeah, I know it's Tolkien.
No, no, no, no.
He's named after the guy
who wrote "The Hobbit"
and stuff!
Yeah, I know.
J.R.R. Tolkien.
What did you think it was?
You knew it was Tolkien
like the writer.
Everyone knew it was Tolkien.
No, no, no!
No, no, no, no!
I distinctly remember Cartman
wearing a shirt
where he spelled it T-o-k-e-n.
Yeah, dude,
cuz Cartman's a fuckin' moron.
Wha... Hold on a second!
Whatsup, dog.
Dude, Cartman, did you know
that Tolkien is named
after J.R.R. Tolkien?
Well, yeah, I just figured.
Then why did you spell it Token
without the "L" or the "I"?!
J.R.R. Tolkien has an "L" in it?
That's gay.
Who did you think Tolkien
was named after?
Stan? You out here?
Uh, yeah,
hang on a second Tol-kien,
just taking a shit.
Oh, okay, sorry.
Oh, my God...
I suck...
This is your mornin' commute,
South Park.
Looks like we have a bit
of slowing heading into town.
There's like a truck
and a couple cars...
maybe take ya
a couple minutes there.
Also, if you're heading
out of town on the main road
there's a... there's, like,
a car there, too.
What the fuck?
Now let's look at the weather.
Weather's looking like
we're gonna have a little bit
of snow.
And the, uh... the...
What the hell are you doing?
Taking shit tons
of Tegridy orders.
Sales are going nuts right now.
No... why is my face
on a billboard?!
Because we work together.
You said you just needed someone
to help with accounting!
Yes, but then...
You got promoted!
I was gonna surprise you.
Don't you see how lucrative
this can be?
I mean, we make a pretty damn
good team in the weed business.
I mean, we are Ben and Jerry...
We're Ben and Jerry.
You're Jerry, and I'm Ben.
I thought I was Jerry.
No, you're a towel.
Oh, that's even better.
I told you before
that I'm not interested
in the marijuana business.
I don't believe in drinking
or doing drugs.
Doing dru... Do you remember
when Bilbo first set out
with the dwarves to fight Smaug.
What's the first thing
they all did?
They partied their asses off.
♪ Chip the glasses,
click the plates ♪
♪ That's what Bilbo Baggins
hates ♪
And then they certainly had an
adventure together, didn't they?
Filled with...
lucrative treasure.
You really think we could make
a lot of money together?
Ben and Jerry, my man.
Ben and fuckin' Jerry.
Hey-hey!
Stan the man!
How ya doing, buddy?
Okay, I guess...
The nurse said you came here
by yourself. No parents?
I... kinda wanted to talk about
something in private.
Oh, okay, pal...
What is it?
I think...
I might be horribly racist.
Well, kiddo...
You don't normally go
to a doctor's office
for feeling racist,
but tell me what happened.
So... there's this kid
at my school and... he's black.
And his parents named him
after the guy
that wrote "Lord of the Rings."
Uh-huh, Tolkien.
Great name.
Yeah... well I-I thought
his name was Token.
Like... Like a black kid
that's just there
so that... like...
there's a black kid.
Uh huh... and how long
have you thought that?
The whole time!
I've thought that
the whole time.
Wow...
Fuck you.
Huh?
You really thought
a couple of black people
had a child and named him Token?
Why would anyone
name a black kid Token?
You're a piece of shit.
No, I was just try...
You were just going along
with the dominant culture
of the white paradigm,
that's what you were just...
Get out of my office,
you make me sick!
I'm sorry!
I don't know what's wrong
with some people.
I wonder if anyone else thought
that this kid's name was Token?
Hmm? Anybody?
Anyone else just assume
his name was Token?
Because that's disgusting,
and you are the problem.
Doctor?
I thought I told you
to get out of my office
because you seriously
make me sick...
I'm gonna shit my fucking pants
right now.
Doctor, please,
I don't want to be like this!
I'll do anything,
just tell me what to do.
Oh, you wanna change?
Then I suggest you start
doing a lot of reading.
Okay.
What should I read?
And I suggest
that when you're reading...
You do it from the perspective
of a black person!
The knight Pigwiggen rides
on a frisky earwig,
and sends his love, Queen Mab,
a bracelet of emmets' eyes,
making an assignation...
Old Tom Bombadil
was a merry fellow.
Bright blue his jacket was,
and his boots was yellow...
It is told
that in their beginning,
the dwarves was made by Aule
in the darkness of Middle-Earth.
♪ Black puppy and white puppy ♪
♪ Play together
in the backyard ♪
♪ Why can't we? ♪
♪ Getting rough
with a brand new chew toy ♪
♪ Oh, boy ♪
♪ Let's all get along ♪
♪ We all know that puppies
are the same wherever you go ♪
♪ There are good puppies... ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
♪ ...and bad puppies ♪
♪ When one of them
chews a shoe... ♪
As the owners of Tegridy farms,
you are accused of plagiarizing
a song
for your marijuana company.
How do you plead?
Not guilty, your honor.
The complaint says
that you asked for the rights
to the song "Ebony and Ivory,"
but when you were turned down
by Paul McCartney,
you copied the song
into something similar.
Not true, your honor.
I've never even heard
Paul McCartney's version.
"Black Puppy White Puppy"
is a song I wrote by myself
on my piano keyboard.
♪ Black puppy, white puppy ♪
♪ Playing in the back yard,
why can't we? ♪
♪ Black puppy, white puppy,
playing in the back... ♪
Guys... Lately I've been doing
a lot of soul searching.
I've had to ask myself
hard questions,
because for a long time now,
I've misinterpreted
some amazing writing.
I've done a lot of reading...
And I've learned why Sauron
built the black gate of Mordor
across the pass
of Cirith Gorgor,
which led into
the enclosed plain of Udun.
I've learned
that the Mouth of Sauron
was once a man,
who commanded the orc armies
of Gorgoroth
and dismissed Aragorn's claim
as King.
I think Stan's lost his marbles.
I firmly believe that everyone
would benefit
from the school making required
reading of these books.
Because if we don't fully know
about Tolkien,
then we can make some terrible,
offensive mistakes.
In fact... did you guys know
that our friend Tolkien,
who goes to school here,
is named after J.R.R. Tolkien?
Yup!
Yeah, I knew that.
Why else would his name
be Tolkien
if it wasn't for the guy
that wrote the books?
My point is,
we need to petition the school
to make Tolkien
required reading.
To better understand
our classmate.
I think maybe
we all haven't done enough
to make sure that Tolkien
doesn't feel isolated
and left out.
Guys?
Can I come in now?
Not yet, Token.
Just another couple minutes.
W-What are you guys
talking about?
Just a couple minutes, bro.
♪ Black puppy bitch,
black, black puppy bitch ♪
♪ White puppy bitch,
black, white puppy bitch ♪
♪ Black puppy bitch,
white, black puppy bitch ♪
Hey, guys, I've got something
really exciting to show you!
Ohhhh buzzkill...
I had this awesome idea
last night...
and I couldn't even sleep
I thought it was so cool...
Oh, okay, what is it?
We do an entire line of cannabis
based on all the different races
of Middle Earth!
We do seven different strains in
all, representing the dwarves,
the elves, even the uruk hai!
Uh, yeah... no.
Everyone will think we're dorks!
Randy, you seem not to care very
much about any of my ideas.
Well, you're just... You know,
you're just not the idea guy.
I don't seem to be
the anything guy.
I thought we were Ben and Jerry.
Alright, look, I'm gonna tell
you the truth about ice cream...
Jerry actually doesn't do shit.
Ben does it all,
everyone knows that.
Well, I don't want
to just be here
like some kind of token
black person.
Oh, come on, I'm sorry.
No, I totally get now
why you want me around,
and I'm not gonna do it.
He doesn't even really sound
like a black guy, you know that?
Alright, everyone, listen up!
We have a special announcement
today.
One of our fourth grade students
says he's done a lot of work
and has grown as a person.
And he'd like to share
his journey with you.
Please welcome Stan Marsh.
Sup guys. You know, I've done
a lot of reading lately.
And I'd like to announce
that the school has allowed me
to declare today J.R.R. Tolkien
appreciation day.
These books go so much deeper
than the Hollywood movies.
And we see
its influences everywhere
in our modern culture.
In fact, how many of you knew
that our classmate Tolkien
was named after J.R.R. Tolkien?
But you don't know
that "Lord of the Rings"
was an analogy for World War II,
did you?!
And I'll bet you didn't know
that there was originally
19 Rings of Power
that were forged by Celebrimbor!
So there's much
we need to understand.
And so I would like to bring up
the man himself.
Come on up here. Tolkien!
Come on!
I actually don't like
"Lord of the Rings"
and I don't like "The Hobbit."
Just cause my dad's into that
stuff doesn't mean that I am.
I've always hated
that my name is Tolkien,
but I didn't really have
a choice, did I?
So please, whatever you do,
just don't draw
any more attention to my name.
I can't stand any of it.
It's a bunch of nerdy,
jive-ass dragon shit.
Stanley,
are you feeling any better?
Nope.
Not any better, mom.
Well... Your friend Tolkien
came over to see you.
He's downstairs.
Tolkien is... here?
Hey, Tol-kien.
Oh, hey, Stan.
What are you doing here?
Stan... Are you ok?
You've just been acting
kind of strange
the last few days.
Yeah, I'm good. I'm...
No... I'm not...
Tolkien... I have something
I have to tell you.
Okay.
This whole time.
I thought your name was Token.
Like the token black person.
Wow...
Yeah.
Why would my parents
name me something
that means
the only black person?
I don't know.
So I understand if you don't
wanna be around me anymore.
Well, it's not like
I really have a choice.
That's why I'm here.
My parents just bought the farm
across the street.
- What?!
- Yeah, out of the blue,
My dad was just like,
"We're going into
the farming business!"
And we all just picked up
and moved.
Oh, my God, this is great!
Mom! Dad!
Guess what?!
Tolkien's Family bought the farm
across the street!
We're neighbors!
Oh, that's great!
Yeah that's really cool, boys...
Wait, wha-a-a-a-t?!
What the hell's going on?
Oh, hey, Randy.
What'dya think of the new place?
Credigree Weed?!
How stupid is that?!
Credigree isn't even a word!
Oh, hello...
We'd like to buy a little weed.
It's our anniversary!
Well, there's really good weed
across the street!
Tegridy weed?
Yeah, we're just...
We're looking for something
with a little more...
street cred.
Yeah, a little more cred!
Well, ya'll came
to the right business,
cuz this shit is hard.
Oh, oh! He didn't even talk
like that before!
This guy is a total phony!
Now just come across the street,
and I'll show you some real nice
weed made with Tegridy.
These people
don't even belong here.
Wow, bro... you're a racist
piece of shit.
Can we see
what you've got, please?
Hell, yeah,
we got all kinds a shit...
Lemme give you a sample
of my Rivendell Elvish Magic...
They stole it!
They stole my idea!
- Who did?
- Those dickheads across the street!
They took everything I learned
about using black culture
to make a bigger profit
and they're doing it themselves!
Get this little prick
outta my house!
- Dad!
- Get him outta here, he's a spy!
Hey fuck face!
I don't want your kid
over at my house, you got that?!
Hey, man, what's your problem?
You want a war?
Well, you got one!
Game on, asshole!
Game on, muthafucker.
Everyone back in the house.
Come on, let's go.
But dad... Shut up!
The story of young
Stan Marsh might seem incredible,
but the fact is many people
suffer from unconscious biases.
If you or someone you know
might have also thought
the name Tolkien
didn't come from J.R.R. Tolkien,
then please call...
Because you
are the fucking problem.
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org
The Best UK, India and US IPTV channels
WWW.ALLIN1BOX.CO.UK