♪ He's just ♪
♪ A stereotype ♪
♪ He drinks his age in pints ♪
♪ He has girls every night ♪
♪ But he doesn't really exist ♪
(A SUDDEN SILENCE)
MELON: It was the moment
I clapped eyes on her.
You know, like they say,
it was like a wave crashing.
I caught myself just looking at her.
I couldn't stop.
I knew her age.
I knew it was wrong.
13.
And I was disgusted in myself.
I did everything I could to stop it.
Tried not to be anywhere she was, pretty much.
No contact.
We have to do this.
Two years, I tried to do that.
I kept it to myself.
I buried it.
And then, out of the blue,
she just came out of nowhere.
Up at the activity centre. Greig Tower.
A joint youth club weekender.
I couldn't help but see her.
I had to... I was running
two of the courses.
I tried not to look at her the way I wanted to.
Once, maybe. I swear to God, no more.
And then... Then she's just
come out of nowhere.
You know, on a hike up a hill, of all places.
She was 15 by then.
And she's just stood in front of me
and saying she knows what she wants.
I told her till I was blue in
the face that it was wrong.
You know, it was just a crush
at best and nothing...
nothing good would come of it.
And I swear, I kept telling her and I told her
and I told her, I swear.
I swear to God, Nelly, I told her.
But you couldn't help yourself, could you?
I couldn't.
CLAIRE: I didn't expect...
I mean, I know you have to.
That's the point.
You're so much like her. You are.
It felt like they'd found Jody.
I'm so sorry.
It's OK.
That's partly why we wanted you
to meet Lorraine beforehand.
Not to get caught out on the day.
- Thank you for doing this.
- I hope it helps.
Thank you, Lorraine.
With these reconstructions,
our aim is to jog people's memories...
commuters, members of the public, anyone.
(CLAIRE EXHALES)
Claire...
As I was saying, our aim
is to jog people's memories...
commuters, members of the public, anyone...
many of whom won't remember
what they did or didn't witness on the day.
(SHE SOBS)
You're on a list says kids
should give you a swerve, Melon.
That was my dad, not Mel.
He wouldn't have it that I
hadn't been taken advantage of.
Tried to get me to say...
Mel had had me when he hadn't.
Barely kissed or owt at all.
Just my dad wouldn't hear it.
Got Melon buried.
No, no, I was a youth worker.
You know, it was a position of responsibility.
He never broke the law, ever.
I did 18 months and I had
to go on a registry for that.
It's been me and him every day since.
Liverpool first, then down here.
Piss off now. We don't
want you here. Get out.
- Sit yourself back down.
- You gonna stab me if I don't?
Sit her back down!
You're in here without being asked!
And you've got a knife on us!
The knife's only here so that you two
will see how seriously I'm taking myself,
that I'm here for what I'm here for,
whichever way I've got to get it fucking done.
- Sit yourself down!
- Please, sit down.
I want my phone.
I'll fuck you up if you won't go on your own!
- Nelly, don't.
- Give me that phone.
Bernie, give him the phone.
Give me the phone and sit the fuck down.
- Nelly, watch the knife.
- Sit down.
Perfect stranger, throwing
myself around her like a fool.
Oh, Jesus.
It just feels like he's taken her again,
like Jody's gone all over again.
I hate this.
We've got five, or a bit more, floating,
spread over most months.
Never more than ten, nowhere near 50.
I checked.
BJ said to ask you where it's
from, so where's it from, Barry?
All over.
A few places. I scrambled
together what I could.
- I'm doing everything I can.
- I'm not saying you're not.
Can I see it?
See it? See what?
The cash, the cheque, whatever, however you've...
I hate this, I hate that it's eating me alive,
and whatever it's doing to me,
I can see what it's doing to you
and I just...
Look, I want to be sure.
You think I'd say I have 50K?
- That I'd go on TV saying...
- I think, because you do,
- because you've been...
- When I haven't.
What, you think that's what I'm playing at?
(KEYPAD BLEEPING)
Where's it from?
I told you, it's from all over.
You can tell me. Tell what you
did to get cash like that.
I am telling you.
I will tell you what it was for
once we have Jody back,
OK? Just, please...
There was a night...
This was a good few months back.
Doors closed on us at The Palm, it was a lock-in.
It's when Stacey's dad was over.
You, me. There were a couple of others.
We were laughing loud and
talking shit for shit's sake.
Do you remember? We were at it, hard.
It was... I dunno,
it was my birthday, or whose?
I wasn't there, Nelly, so I don't know.
What, you don't know when my birthday is, Melon?
Mum's name, then.
You know that.
Aye, Glenda. Glenda,
but I swear this wasn't me.
My favourite singer.
Who?
It's a toss-up between
Mick Hucknall and Jeffrey Osborne.
You think now's the best time
to try and be fucking funny?
I don't, no.
There's just that one song
you like by Jeffrey Osborne.
He's a computer geezer.
You're a computer expert.
That's how you make your living.
- It just wasn't me.
- You know 'em inside out.
I mean, you know 'em well enough
to make out you're me on one of 'em
or you know 'em well enough,
I dunno, to use against my kid?
No, he's not done that!
- Just tell me where Jody is!
- I don't know.
The things...
The things you know,
things I would have told you...
Things he wrote to her.
I mean, that time I met Jody for the first time.
- I didn't write anything.
- The pub.
Where was the pub, Melon?
The posh, by-the-river boozer.
I would have said Rotherhithe.
Rotherhithe!
- Not to me. No, not to me...
- To you.
And The Cat's Whiskers, there.
- Cat's Whiskers!
- I don't know.
The club on the Streatham High Road,
I would have told you that's where I took Claire.
- Can you just go, please?
- So tell me where Jody is.
I don't know. I swear, I don't know.
If I fucking stabbed her in
the knee, would you know then?
- Let go of me.
- Tell me where she is!
I don't know!
All that time, hearing me out,
getting me to go on about Claire and Jody.
- Don't tell me this wasn't you!
- It wasn't me, Nelly.
That's how you did it. Nights like that.
Nights like that night we went straight through
and out the other side with Stacey's dad.
- I've never met Stacey's dad.
- Don't you try that with me.
You were sat across from her.
You were sat across from us all night.
I remember he came from Greece
but we weren't introduced.
I swear to God it wasn't me. Ask Stace!
- I'll cut her fucking kneecap!
- Nelly, please!
- Why?
- Please, Nelly. It wasn't me.
- Then fucking who?
- It wasn't me!
Fucking who if it wasn't you?
You fit! It has to be you! It has to!
Cos if it's not you, then...
If it's...
Fuck.
How am I on eight when she's on 13?
- What's it matter?
- When did that happen?
- It says it there.
- I'm better than you
- and not nearly as mashed.
- They having a go again, babes?
They are, Stace, yeah.
Is that cos of how mashed you are?
(LAUGHTER)
Just checking in about tomorrow.
Oh, yeah, we'll be there
for when the train gets in.
Er... there should be about 20 of us.
You're darlings, thank you.
You all right?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Thanks for printing all them fliers, Linda.
It's not for him, Stace.
It's for you, yeah?
Either way, much appreciated.
Gav.
Stace.
You all right, Melon?
He is, yeah, Goz.
Your Gill still after that record, the 69 years?
Er... nah. Nursery got
in the way of that.
Good day.
- How do you make sense of him?
- Don't.
Just trying to stop him pissing
the bed like the other two.
You don't remember introducing
him to your dad, then, eh?
Not so I could swear it, no.
Can you ask him, next time you speak to him?
- He won't remember.
- Can you ask him anyway?
- Please?
- Same again, please, Stace.
And a Kronie.
Oh, can I stand you one, Nelly?
- I'm all right.
- Fuck me.
No, thanks, I'm already taken.
- That's the bollocks I mean.
- Luke, it's your go.
No, one minute. That's what I
mean. That bollocks right there.
- I'll get these drinks.
- Are you all right, babes?
He's trying to be funny, Stacey.
- I'll bring the drinks.
- I'm not trying to be funny.
Trying to get you to make sense
of that shit for me.
Make sense of that,
cos that's a convicted paedo
you've walked in here with.
- (ALL EXCLAIM)
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, hang on.
You know, walked him in,
him and his fucking juice box.
- Luke.
- Have a break, come on.
Sat next to him, back in their place for a point.
- You know what?
- Mate, shut up.
Point fucking taken.
Nelly Rowe is a good friend
to lady boys and sex offenders.
- Good for you!
- Oi, come on.
Step him right out of reach,
will you, Goz, please?
- Nelly, Nelly, we're gonna go.
- No, you're not.
- Yeah, we're gonna leave.
- No, come here, please. Please.
Have a seat, finish your drinks, please.
Gavin, get him out of here.
Please! He fucking rapes children!
- Get him out.
- Yeah, we're trying.
And you put your arm around him
like he's fucking sainted!
I ask you to take a drink from me
and it's like I spat in your mum's mouth.
You know, you treat us like shit
every chance you get.
- No, Stace, we should go.
- Wait until he's gone!
Explain that to me, Gav. What the fuck?
All the way out, Goz.
I'm in the wrong fucking mood.
If he takes a step towards me...
- Yeah, come on, mate.
- Luke. Let's go.
Come on, Luke, sort yourself out, mate.
Gav, have a word, yeah?
Luke, mate!
Has he gone?
Fuck him. I'll walk you out.
If you need anything...
Anything, yeah?
- Thanks.
- Thanks, Stace.
Can you get the door, please, babe?
- Here, I've got it. Got it.
- Cheers.
Look, it's not my business to say owt, I know,
but there's something I want to tell you,
to show you that I do want to help.
- Telling me what?
- Ah, look, maybe...
Maybe you should talk to Zita.
- Talk to her, why?
- Don't say I said anything.
Melon, why?
I'm just saying, if you was gonna ask around.
Like you said, whoever done this
knows you really well.
- Zita ain't had my kid away...
- That's not what I'm saying.
- I'm just saying...
- BERNIE: Melon.
That she's worth a word, maybe.
I'm coming.
Here you are. I'd best go.
Thanks, Nelly.
Thank you.
Like Stace said, you know where we are, yeah?
Yeah. Thanks.
Zita.
Zeets!
(RINGING TONE)
VOICEMAIL: Hi, this is Zita.
You know the drill.
- All right?
- How are you?
Tam. Tam, it's Nelly.
Is Zita up there working tonight?
Er... Zita? No, no, I haven't seen her.
You ain't seen her cos you ain't seen her
or cos she ain't there?
Hang on. She's down as being in.
Yeah, well, pull her out,
get her to call me, yeah?
I think she can help me. Cheers.
(BUZZER)
(MUFFLED MUSIC)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
This isn't really any of my business, Tam,
and I don't really want it to be.
Look, Z,
for Christ's sake, I'm asking
you, as a favour to him.
I've got nothing to tell him, Tam.
Nothing he's gonna wanna hear.
He was in and out and all over the place
when he came back to mine.
You should have seen him.
He was talking to her. To Jody.
- Well, tell him...
- Promising to find her.
Tell him he won't, and not to bother.
If he gets in this and she's
just run away or whatever else,
he's gonna be wading through some kinda shit.
You want me to tell him that?
I just thought I'd ask.
(SIREN IN DISTANCE)
I owe someone a drink, looks like.
I'm just passing through.
I've come to see Tam.
Whoever kicked the crap out of you,
I owe 'em whatever they're having.
You ain't backing off me at all, are you, Marky?
You've got Mum's car. I told you...
She gave it to me, Marky! Ain't
like I fucking robbed it. Tam.
On your way home tonight,
you leave back Mum's car
where you got it from, simple.
Ain't gonna do that, Marky.
I can't do that.
Well, then, no, bitch.
I ain't backing off at all.
OK.
You're not going? We can't.
- Why? Stace said to come.
- Bern, we can't go.
- Everybody's going. We should.
- Doesn't matter. We can't go.
- I am.
- Bernie?
We're on the second floor.
Don't be stupid.
Up the bloody chimney, I don't care.
- We haven't got a chimney.
- (LAUGHS) I'm not joking.
Stace invited us, stood there
in front of us, invited us.
- She's invited us.
- Bernie, you're not listening.
We had a drink in the pub, that's it.
And it wasn't as bad as we thought it'd be
because Nelly was looking after us.
But nothing's changed.
It's gonna be exactly the same
here as it is everywhere else.
You know, and that Luke...
that's just the start of it.
You said that we were staying!
I like it here!
- So do I!
- You said we could stay.
It's me they take it out on.
Every time.
You're in my way.
TANNOY: This is a security announcement.
Passengers are requested
to keep an eye on all personal
belongings at all times,
on trains and at stations.
If you see anything suspicious
or anyone acting suspiciously,
please inform a member of railway staff.
Are you OK?
I can't do this.
Would you mind taking one of these, please?
The number should be there. All right?
Yeah, thank you.
A missing girl. Jody.
Here. Have one of these.
See what it can jog.
- Give me a minute.
- Yeah.
Bernie! Up with me, please.
You said get the ones they let go.
I did, and now we're heading on
and I'm saying keep up.
Mind if I say hello? Stace?
I do, yeah. Bugger off.
- You know many of these people?
- No.
- I don't even know what to say.
- I'm all right. I am.
Doing the best I can, most days.
But...
Almost numb, Stace.
- Did you get my card?
- Yeah. You didn't have to.
- No.
- And for being out here,
all these you've brought,
what you're doing for Jody...
- It means a lot.
- It's the least we can do.
Well, when we catch him,
drinks at mine when we set light to the fucker.
Guys? There's a load
of people right up there.
- I'm Bernie.
- Hi.
Hi. It's Claire, innit?
Thanks for coming. Are you from The Palm?
Are you really not going up there?
No. Stace argued me out.
Said she'd get more done with
them floppy students than me.
- Hey, Nelly.
- Hey, Frankie.
Thanks, Tam.
You get hold of Zita?
Is she ducking me, Tam?
- Feels like she is.
- Why would she?
I erm...
I got, like, erm...
Like constant butterflies.
I can't get hold of myself.
I can't fucking name it, Tam.
- Over Zita?
- No. About...
Stace reckons it's what kids...
It's what kids do to you.
Stace ain't got none, so... (CHUCKLES)
- Well, I'm trying to...
- It's all right, don't worry.
And kids do do that to you.
You got kids, Tam?
Look, I don't want to put it about, he wouldn't,
but... a son.
And he gives you butterflies?
If I say, "Christ, yes,"
can we just leave it at that?
You see Zeet, tell her to hail me, yeah?
Yeah.
Errol?
MAN: What do you want, Melon?
I'll clean this for you.
You don't have to.
I'm sorry about this.
I'd rather not be involved.
I'll have that back, thank you.
- You all right, Melon?
- (BABY CRYING)
All right.
(BABY CRYING)
(FIRM KNOCKING)
(RINGING TONE)
VOICEMAIL: Hi, this is Zita.
You know the drill.
Zita, are you all right?
(NELLY'S VOICE MUFFLED)
I need to talk to you. Give me a call.
(LOW CHATTER)
You all right?
- How's it going?
- Yeah, good.
Nice to see you.
How are you, then? You all right?
...to a silver Ford Focus
waiting on the other side.
22 miles, 11 days, and the whereabouts of
13-year-old Jody McGory remains unknown.
Back to you, Kirsty.
Oh, God.
(DOOR OPENS)
Whatever Marky's been on about my car,
it ain't his business, right?
I told him, it ain't up to him.
- Have a drink, Teens.
- I came to set Marky straight.
- I've had enough by myself.
- Have one. One.
Went out of myself the other day, Teens.
Don't know what I'm doing.
- Well, when have you ever?
- I went after Melon, Teens.
I fucking went after him like...
Like I don't know what.
It's cos she's haunting me.
- Who is?
- Jody is.
- She's pulling at me.
- What do you mean?
She's waking me up.
She's following me all over the place.
She's running after me.
Haunting me,
is the best I can say. She's...
You're scaring me a little bit here, Nell.
Hey, ain't trying to scare you.
Sit down. Go on, sit down. (PATS STOOL)
Please.
I'll have a brandy and Stones, please.
You are allowed to be fucking
freaked out by this, you know.
You are allowed.
Thank you very much, Mr McGory.
Why would you ask me about her?
What's the matter with you?
We were having a nice minute.
I'm asking about Marky.
Yeah, and what he might have done to Zita.
So? Scared her off, he might have done.
- Why would I give a shit?
- Something has scared her off.
First round's on me. Only
singles come the spirits, mind.
Ah, all right? How was it?
Yeah, it was all right. Yeah.
Oh, Christ alive. Where'd you come from?
- We brought Claire with us.
- Yeah, you did.
I was just going.
Claire, Claire, Teens. Teens, like...
Abracadabra, this is Claire.
- Sorry.
- Hello. We met, years back.
Yeah, I think we have, yeah. Hello.
I can walk you back. I can walk you back.
No, I know you can, but I'm all right.
- Claire, what you having?
- Red wine?
- Red wine, that's brave.
- (THEY CHUCKLE)
♪ (ROXY MUSIC: Let's Stick Together) ♪
Some things never change.
Some things stay the same.
What are you on about?
Barely one drink in, you've already got me
in the darkest corner.
Just have a minute in private.
Catch up proper.
See how you're doing up close
cos I've been worried about you.
- I'm all right, Nelly.
- You're not.
I mean, you're giving it a go
and good on you, but you're not.
- So there you go.
(HE LAUGHS)
Now I know where I am.
I know it's really you.
So there you go.
Tell me how you're really doing.
Like a bus gets slammed into me
three or four times a day.
Have to remind myself... over and over.
That's the worst bit, reminding
myself that she's not here.
She's not here.
It shouldn't, but it does, it slips your mind.
It sneaks up on, takes you
by surprise that she's gone.
It's like a bus being slammed
into you out of nowhere
three or four times a day.
It's typical of buses, though, innit?
You're waiting for one and three come along.
(LAUGHTER)
Oh, fuck.
♪ (ROXY MUSIC: Let's Stick Together) ♪
♪ ...consider our child ♪
♪ How can it be happy
without its ma and pa? ♪
♪ Let's stick together ♪
♪ Come on, come on,
let's stick together ♪
You have to use two hands.
♪ You know we made a vow
not to leave one another never ♪
Finish!
(CHEERING AND LAUGHTER)
Ohh!
(RINGING TONE)
She said she'd make her own way back, didn't she?
- Yeah, she did.
- Then, she will.
Now, look, you need to call him,
Dad, so just call him.
He said he wanted you to as soon as you got back.
- Is that what he said?
- As soon as you got home.
- To call him.
- Yes. Yes.
Ooh, hello. Hello!
Christ. (LAUGHS)
Your car.
Stop that. Why are we doing that?
What? I'm kissing you.
I like kissing you.
I always fucking have.
I'm gonna keep trying
because I like the taste of you
and it's what I want to do.
So there you go.
Yes, it's really fucking you.
For Christ's sake.
Why couldn't you just leave it
at us having a good time?
Any particular way you want me to go?
You've heard what we're going through?
- Must have.
- Yeah, something on the telly.
Our daughter's been taken from us.
Hope you don't think
we had anything to do with that.
- Of course not, no.
- Really?
Serious bag you owe.
- What are you saying?
- 50 grand, Barry?
Who are you bloody trying to kid?
Eh? I'm onto 75 or a ton.
You're begging for the safe
return of a loved child.
You must have close to the ton, don't you, pal?
Cos it's 94 you owe us.
And it's 94 that's expected.
My brothers reckon you're playing us off as cu...
No, I won't use the word.
C-something-unts.
Trying to use what's going
on with your brown stepkid
to get out of paying us what's
owed cos you ain't got it.
I told 'em two things.
First, I told 'em you weren't that kinda scum.
And, second... you would never
take me for that kinda fool.
It's 94 grand come the first.
Bring me what you got, then you
got ten days to find the rest.
Can I tell my brothers we've
made ourselves clear, please?
- Yes, you can.
- Good boy.
Apologies, mate, you'll have
to find your own way home.
I'll Uber.
Fuck you will! You'll walk first.
It's freezing out here, Zeets.
Zita.
Why ain't you called me back?
- Why ain't you called me back?
- Shh.
Cos I ain't been feeling too good.
And I ain't in the mood for chatting.
Then we don't chat.
Just want to see you.
Said I wasn't in the mood for that.
Just asking why you've
been avoiding me. Just that.
Who's told you to ask me?
- Don't worry about who.
- Was it Tam?
Why won't you answer what I asked you?
- (SCOFFS)
- I'm just asking you why.
Cos it ain't an ask and answer type of thing.
It's...
It's the bloody worst years of my life.
It ain't something to get chatty-chat about.
It's shit I need to forget.
I don't know about that.
I beg pardon.
You always seem like your shit's together.
And your head's on like it should be.
(LAUGHS)
You think?
- Look who's in here next to me.
- Well, fuck. Thanks, Zeets.
I'm kidding.
So I'm a measure of how fucked up you are?
I was joking.
- (SCOFFS)
- It's a joke.
It was Melon.
He's the one said talk to you.
Course it was Melon.
You need to be fucking careful of that one.
Yeah? Why's that?
You don't know him.
You think you do, but you don't.
Why'd he say I should talk to you?
Cos maybe that's what he's around you to do.
(LAUGHS) What's that mean?
They come at you like that.
Hunt in packs.
Might be Melon's the one sent to keep you sweet.
While the next one comes in and reaches around.
The next what?
There ain't a pack around Melon.
It's just Bernie for him
and the same way back from her.
(CHUCKLES)
Ask me, he lets Bernie linger.
Cos, in the right light, she don't look like
she's quite aged out yet.
I know 'em.
I know the smell of 'em.
From how they turn their heads
to you... shit they say...
Shit they don't say.
I told you already, worst days.
OK.
OK? OK, like what?
Like you don't believe me?
- That's not what I'm saying.
- I can take you to my ex now.
If you want to know about Melon
or any fucker around here.
Your ex, who?
Like the fucking granddaddy of them.
Knows them all.
Will know Melon... if I ain't
wrong about him... which I ain't.
Richard Rosewall.
He's got a bar.
You said you could take me
straight to him right now?
- (EXHALES) You scared me.
- You were gone a while.
Oh, Stace wanted a drink, a catch up.
She makes me laugh. I fancied that.
Just Stace?
You look like you've been out.
Drove around to clear my head.
You all right?
Wanted to see what it was
being in here did for you,
see if it'd do the same for me.
(PHONE RINGING)
It won't help... me being there.
I'll poop myself...
or glass him, I dunno.
- All right?
Hey. Hey, Zita!
Hey, hey, hey.
I can't be anywhere near him.
- Nelly, I'm sorry, I just...
- It's all right.
Tell me where I'm going.
And he's "Richard".
- Not Ricky, Richie, Rich or...
- Dick?
He's Richard.
♪ When I expel ♪
♪ From this mortal shell ♪
♪ Will I die for living numb? ♪
Members only.
♪ Am I vital ♪
♪ If my heart is idle? ♪
20 quid membership dues
gets you in and a first drink.
20 quid?
♪ Am I vital ♪
♪ If my heart is idle? ♪
♪ Am I doomed? ♪
♪ I feel you ♪
♪ But nobody else... ♪
All right?
I... I don't know you.
Know me? No. No, you don't.
How'd you get here?
Erm... a mate of mine showed me over.
A mate of yours called who?
Can I just come in for a beer,
and we just leave it at that?
I mean, I've paid my dues, I've...
- This is a members' club.
- Yeah, that's what I was told.
I'm sorry, rules are rules.
I'm... I'm terribly sorry.
♪ ...cast me to the wayside ♪
♪ Well, I feel the peeling ♪
♪ Of half-painted ceilings... ♪
OPERATOR: Emergency, which service?
GIRL: Hello? I need help now.
OPERATOR: It's a bad line.
Could you repeat that, please?
NELLY: I don't know what
I'm doing here, Jody.
I don't know if I'm anywhere near
or if I'm anywhere nearer to you.
GIRL: Got me in a... (CRACKLING)
He had some... (INTERFERENCE ON LINE)
What'd get you to throw up a hand or er...
...dunno, set off a flare,
call my name, anything?
GIRL: (DISTORTED)
Hello, Mums. Can you hear me?
OPERATOR: Hello? Could you
give me your location?
- I am still coming for you.
- GIRL: I'm sorry...
- (LINE CRACKLES)
- (SCREAMING) I'm sorry!
I am.
That's her.
Jody!
♪ Am I doomed? ♪
♪ Cradle me ♪
♪ So I can see ♪
♪ If I'm doomed ♪