Subtitles by explosiveskull
Nelly?
I don't know what to do here,
Stace.
What's going on, Nelly?
If I lay a bare fucking finger
on him,
- I'll rip the life out of him.
- I won't let you!
So stop me!
- Who's next, Daisy?
- It's him!
It's him who got Jody!
Hey! You seemed convinced
it was Gavin.
I'm just...
I'm just trying to hear you,
Nelly.
The piece of shit
that got at Jody,
he coaxed her out with promises
of my mum's saltfish dumplings.
Did you know that? Cos it's
there in what he wrote to her.
I've seen it.
How many of you lot have...
seen it anywhere,
heard it on a whisper,
heard it from anybody
at any time?
- None of us, Nelly.
- Then how comes he has?
Cos he was just there,
arguing the toss about his mate,
saying that Gavin
wasn't the sort
to sit up
until the middle of the night,
talking about her grandmother's
saltfish dumplings.
That's what he said.
- Is that not what you said?
- He did say that, just now,
when Nelly had a go at him
about laughing.
- I heard it somewhere.
- No, you didn't.
Online somewhere, the police.
He's fucking lying, right there!
The filth never let it out.
They deliberately held it back,
made a point of it,
which is why I know
and none of you lot do.
So how comes he does?
Unless it was him
who was fucking writing to her,
how come?
- Luke?
- I'm calling it a night, Stace.
- No, you're not.
- No, you ain't. No, no.
You're staying put.
- Bugger!
- You've got to be sure, Nel.
- I want to leave, Stace!
- I can't stand this!
Please!
- Nelly! Nelly!
- Nelly!
Mum, stay over there!
Are you sure about this?
Goz, get Daisy out of here.
Park yourself!
♪ Hey, this is Jody ♪
♪ Sorry you can't get through ♪
♪ Why don't you leave your name
and your number ♪
♪ And I'll get back to you ♪
How the fuck did you do that?
Make it like it was her
calling me. How's that done?
I'm all right.
And it was you, right,
calling, right from the off.
The messages I left, the two
of you back there, laughing,
watching me spin.
And for why?
I mean, why did you do it?
I mean, why would you?
I don't know, Nelly, but if I
had to guess, I'd say
maybe it's because you're
such a supreme cunt of a man.
- Fucking Ada, Luke.
- What, Goz?
- Bit sociopathic!
- Get back in your box!
You're the worst of them,
making him out as the big 'un,
- kissing his ring every chance.
- Nelly has a pop at you,
and you decide to nick his kid?
- Does that plan make any sense?
- It wasn't a plan.
I just wanted to knock him down.
I've heard him more than once,
pissed up, going on about
his kid that he didn't know.
Thought we'd use her
to mess him about.
Mess him about?
Weren't hard.
Gavin found her easy as.
- Where is she, Luke?
- She sent herself half-naked.
It weren't us.
Didn't ask for that. She liked
the way she looked in it, or...
Stop it.
- It's sick.
- Stop it!
Some shit she wanted to share
with him. We weren't asking.
You used it, though, as bait,
didn't you?
I mean, once you had it...
once you started grooming...
It weren't grooming.
Didn't do that.
Didn't groom anyone!
I'm sorry, what the fuck did
you do if you didn't do that?
For a laugh.
To fucking see, like...
to see what would happen.
Well, you dangled her out there
for the nasties to feed on.
Cos that's what you did, yeah?
What happened just...
bloody happened.
Police.
All he said, call 'em.
Yeah, well, fuck this.
I'm not gonna...
- Marky, don't!
- Just leave it.
I want to go home now.
Let's go, mate.
Yeah, let's go home.
- Fucking stay there! Hear me?
- Nel, I'm taking Daiz home.
- Walk me home now.
- That's enough, yeah? Let's go.
Goz, listen to me. I'm staying.
I'm not going
until I know Nelly's all right.
Nelly, babes, just... triple 9,
and get Luke out of here.
- Marky, please!
- Go sit down!
Claire's gone
to get me 15 grand.
15, or as much as she can,
from that Barry she married.
- Nelly...
- Cos tomorrow...
Tomorrow me and Melon
are meant to walk into a room
and it's wall-to-wall nonces.
We're meant to go in there and
bid against all the rest of them
to see who gets to
first fuck my kid.
Jesus Christ.
That's where I am with this now.
Stace will tell you
what I'm saying.
That's what he has got me
doing with myself.
It's what he's done to Claire
and it's where he's put Jody.
And I know
I've been blind to myself,
stomping around
and throwing my weight.
I know what I've been like.
But it's got me this close.
It's got me...
...this fucking close
to getting to her.
And I need you, you fucker,
I need you to save tomorrow.
Just tell me to who and how
you passed her on,
and then I can end this
and my Jody don't have to
go through any more,
cos I fucking know
you know more. You do.
You know who's got her
or you can point me right.
And that is all I need you
to do, just point me right.
Tell me where she is!
Luke... please.
Tell Nelly where his kiddie is.
- I won't, Stace.
- Please.
We dicked around on YouTube,
found out how to make
bogus calls and made them.
Set the police on me for that
and get on with it, please.
And this ape can beat me
till I'm dead.
Still, I won't say a thing,
Stace, I won't.
Please, Luke, please!
Oh, Christ's sake, Stace,
can he not beg for himself?
All right, Nelly?
- You on your own?
- What's going on, Nelly?
I asked for it to be just you.
And it is.
What's this about?
Whose phone is this, Nelly?
♪ Hey, this is Jody ♪
- ♪ Sorry you can't get through ♪
- Where'd you get this?
It's his phone.
And it was him and his mate
that got at Jody.
Stay there.
Who's had a go at him?
That was me.
I did that. That was all me.
- Tell me why.
- I need a day.
Grow up, Nelly!
Doesn't work like that.
I swear down. Just one day.
- Nelly?
- Just... Just one.
- Nelly, don't!
- Just...
So she's 15?
I'm guessing, yeah, about that.
So you were that whole time
with a 15-year-old girl
that was... that was put there
for you to have, Melon?
What's her name?
Cerys.
Right.
Cerys was there for you
to do with as you pleased,
for you to prove yourself to
the men you'd been out with.
Oh, I...
I barely touched her, I swear.
Barely? Like you
barely did with me?
No.
No, nothing like that,
nothing like us.
I did everything I could
not to touch her.
Everything you could?
Melon, it sounds like
you were fighting yourself
- and had to keep on fighting.
- Myself?
Look, I was there for Nelly.
You know, I had to get...
get them to trust me,
to tell me what...
what they know.
You could have
grabbed her and ran.
I was there for Nelly's kid.
You had someone's kid
right there in reach!
Why is Cerys
only worth stepping over
on the way to
Nelly's little 'un?
I don't know.
- You don't know.
- No, I don't know.
I want what's going round in
my head to stop going round.
I swear. I swear to God,
I didn't touch her.
- I didn't go near her.
- What are you shaking for?
I'm not. I don't know.
- Why are you?
- I don't know!
You should have seen
the smile on his face,
like he was winning.
He wanted me to go too far.
I just gave him a dry slap
and I dragged him out. I had to.
A dry slap?
It's one of those. It's a blaps.
You think he sold her?
Piecing it, yeah.
A nonce wants what he sees
in her by the pool,
offers as much
as will get Luke chatting
and then they work out
how to hand her over.
What?
Tell me.
He probably wouldn't
but he might have told me.
- He wouldn't have.
- Not just because
I wouldn't have been
beating it out of him
but because I'm not you.
That's what it's all about
for him... you.
In his psycho,
nut-job brain, yeah.
Yes, in his psycho,
nut-job brain.
You're the last person
he'll tell.
He never will, will he?
She wasn't calling you, Nelly.
It wasn't her.
So whatever you think,
whatever you were so sure about
and what we were...
- The call was real.
- It isn't that.
That call
she made to the police.
- That was her, wasn't it?
- It was.
It doesn't matter that they
were pissing around calling me
because that was her
crying out for you.
That was her.
And she was in that room,
that room that those nasty fucks
Luke used, she was there,
so we've still got the same
chance at tomorrow.
So there you go.
- How much?
- 12.
It's all I could get.
I swear to Christ...
I mean, I weren't ever a Scout
but, dib-dib and all that shit,
I swear I'm getting her
back for you.
Claire?
You've got a visitor.
How does that even work?
I don't understand.
- We have to release him.
- It doesn't make any sense.
We can't hold him on
the evidence that we have.
We can charge him, maybe,
- with malicious communication.
- Maybe? Maybe?
But that's it.
Search the flat,
search their parents' houses.
Officers are up at the uni
as we speak.
So far we've found nothing
to contradict Luke's account.
Their intention simply was
to wind up Nelly.
- How'd they get Jody's number?
- Gavin got it.
They did more than make
calls pretending to be Jody.
They handed her over
to God knows who.
As convinced
as Nelly might be...
More than just Nelly!
Me and him and more than him
heard Luke admit what he'd done.
And it was more than just calls.
Is that when Nelly
had Luke here,
surrounded by your regulars,
and Marky Betts beat him
every time he tried to leave
or said anything
Nelly didn't appreciate?
Was it then
Luke started to confess?
- He's pressing charges, Stace.
- You're fucking kidding me.
Against Nelly and Marky.
We'll see what comes in
from the uni.
I wanted to tell you in person.
Luke won't be held
for much longer.
I can't believe that
he can press charges.
And you try and find me!
And I speed away.
No, that's wrong.
No, you're swimming.
You're swimming.
And I can't find you
and I have to dive in.
No, I have to dive in
and save you.
Come in.
I'm gonna have to beg
a short one, Stace.
It ain't too late.
It doesn't have to be you.
Please don't start again.
I know they messed up with Luke.
Sip it.
You could easily
bell that Shola.
She could send her mob in
and bag the lot of them.
That won't get Jody back.
Already said
they'd nick the lot of 'em.
Why would they say
jack about her?
You ain't got a clue
what's waiting for you in there.
Bell that Shola.
I'm just waiting for Tam to give
me a call and then I'm on it.
- Got the money?
- Yep.
I'll call you.
I think my head'll explode
if you don't.
Every five minutes, if you can.
I should probably go and get her
back for you, should I?
If you wouldn't mind,
yes, please.
Here.
Sips, Stace.
I don't want to go.
You've done a lot, Melon,
enough maybe.
I can make him hear that. Just
tell me where Nelly needs to be.
He won't get in without me.
Maybe not, but he does keep
finding a way, doesn't he?
I'm shitting myself here, Bern.
I'll take back to Nelly
whatever you tell me to,
and I'll make it all right
for you both.
I keep asking if she'll be here
when I come back.
She won't answer.
You should go.
You should.
Only way out, it seems like,
is to keep going through.
We'll come out the other side,
Mel, we will.
Get this done, come back.
I'll be here.
I will.
Fucking Nelly Rowe!
Oh, I hate him! I do.
Hate his guts!
And I will do forever!
I hate you, Nelson Rowe!
Really?
Those are her favourites?
Anything else she likes?
Minstrels at the cinema
but Caramel Eggs
every chance she gets. Why?
Do you pray, matey?
I mean, are you into that?
Not really.
Then good thoughts, yeah?
For Jody.
Spit and wish and spin around
and whatever.
Yeah?
- OK.
- Good lad.
See ya.
- You got your car keys?
- Yeah.
You all right?
Not exactly, no.
I'm near enough.
- This him?
- Yeah.
- All right, Ash? You all right?
Nelly, this is Ash.
Ash is the one who got you in.
You all right?
Down here on your left.
All right, Nelly, that's me.
- I've done enough.
- What's going on?
I should go and you should
let me. I'm done.
- What are you on about?
- I've done all I can.
I can't be in there with them.
I can't and I don't want to.
Stop fucking about, Melon,
and just wait.
- No. I can't do any more.
- Just... Please.
- Sorry. I've got to go.
- No, no.
- Melon? Melon!
- It kills me, and I'm sorry.
For fuck's sake!
I've seen that a few times.
Want to go without him?
Yeah.
Ash?
How much?
- Have I got?
- Mm.
- Erm, 12K.
- Whoa, whoa. Come on.
Let's have a look.
Nice. Phones?
- My phone?
- Mm.
Cool. OK.
Don't use your camera
and don't record anything.
Right? One call, one number,
that's if the money you got
ain't all yours.
Table three.
We're running a little bit late,
so be patient, yeah?
You can wait just in here, mate,
all right?
Yeah.
Sweet.
You here to stab me, Mel?
I'm not you.
That what you came in to prove?
Even if I have to stab you
to make that clear, yeah.
I'm not what you are.
It's wrong.
However much you want it.
Tell everyone you know.
You make it fucking clear.
- I'm not you.
- Mm.
I don't think you are.
I'm pretty certain...
I was you once, though.
Pretty fucking certain, I think.
Fuck!
Hey, Stace. Anything heard?
No, nothing.
- What's happened?
- Just calling to say I'm in.
- Is Jody there?
- You in the pub still?
- Yes. Is Jody there?
- I don't know, Claire.
I'm... in a fucking stinkhole.
Has it started?
Listen, tell Stace, and you
an' all, because I ain't sure.
A woman's voice on the end of
my call might do my day in.
- I'm just saying.
- He needs us to keep it down.
Guys, guys! Ssh!
He can keep the phone open.
So he needs you to shut up.
I can go upstairs.
Claire, Claire!
Stay, stay, stay here.
Hang about.
As I've said before,
we all know what we're here for,
and as this seems to be our
number, I'm going to push on.
The item is mine to sell.
Never ridden.
I hereby verify that fact.
100% unused.
1300cc caramel ash finish and...
ready for immediate delivery.
The item is a one-off, very much
desired, as advertised on TV.
All this to start us off
at £2,000.
Who'll start me?
2,000, I have.
Is there 2,250 in the room?
2,250.
Show me 2,500.
2,500 on black.
Looking for 2,750.
I don't actually fucking know
what I'm doing.
When am I meant to get started?
Nelly, I don't...
How much does he have?
- 12.
- Do I have three?
He shouldn't start till five
or six, I don't think.
- Tam?
- You shouldn't start till...
- No, I heard.
- ...five or six.
Is Melon with you, Nelly?
- One sec.
- £5,500.
Let's make monkey jumps
from here on,
rather than take all night.
The bid is £5,500 with pink.
6,000 with blue.
6,500 with pink.
- I can't bear this.
- Shouldn't he be getting in?
- Tell him!
- We don't see what he sees.
Seven... with pink.
The bid stands at £7,000.
Erm, eight, over here.
On me. Erm...
Eight, guys.
8,500 with pink.
Nine.
9,500 with pink.
10?
- 10,500.
- Yeah.
11 I have with yellow.
£11,500 with pink.
The bid stands at 11,500.
Going once.
12.
£12,500, pink.
- Jesus!
- The bid stands at £12,500.
CC, I'm so sorry.
12,500.
Going once.
£12,500, going twice.
13.
13,000.
13,500.
14.
Listen, I'm gonna get Jody
by hook or fucking crook.
You're gonna need the cash.
Cross that bridge halfway over.
- 14,500.
- 15.
You've shown your limit as 12.
Piss off back where you were
and don't embarrass yourself.
Only cash in the room counts.
Do you have 15,000?
I've got as much as I need.
Piss off back where you were
- and don't embarrass yourself.
- Al, please.
Oi!
- Get off me!
- What the fuck?
You fucking prick.
You must know where they are!
They didn't tell me
where they were going.
Find out where they are!
Oh, my God.
Who knows Luke the best?
Any of you?
Well, what for?
Where do his parents live?
Cos that's where he'll be.
I need to talk to him.
Well? What?
- You sure it was him, Gran?
- Yes, I'm fucking sure!
Where?
For fuck's sake!
Fuck's sake, Melon!
- All right, Goz?
- All right, Dave?
Luke, mate? It's Goz.
I'm, er... I'm here with Claire.
"Luke, mate..." Piss off, Goz.
It's Claire, Luke, just me.
Goz is leaving.
He showed me where you were,
but it's just me.
No, thanks.
I'm not here for Nelly.
I want nothing to do with him.
He's the cause
of the worst days of my life.
- I'm not here for him.
- What, then?
I'd rather not, Luke, through
the door, for everyone to hear.
I can do you a tea,
coffee or cider.
Just kidding.
Don't have any tea.
You've won.
Go on, then.
Nelly thinks he's something
he's not. He always has.
He's got you so wrong,
thinking that...
But you slapped him down, you
got him, well and truly, had him
running around
for God knows how long.
He hasn't got an idea
what he's doing with himself.
Headless, someone said,
and that's exactly it.
You've got him headless...
...with no clue what he's doing,
and he got us all to join in.
- You're here to beg.
- Only if you know where she is,
because otherwise
I'd rather not waste my time.
Do you know where she is, Luke?
Beg.
Wow! Bended knees
and everything.
Am I fucking wasting my time?
This is probably
a laugh for you.
Mm.
Just be honest,
this isn't gonna help, is it?
Should've given it a go
as you're down there.
I don't have time
to fuck around, Luke.
You did that with Nelly, but I
don't have the fucking time.
Now you've finished with Nelly,
please can I have my daughter?
For what? You're not begging.
So, what?
What? You tell me what.
Anything! Fucking tell me what.
I don't know.
Try money... or sex.
I'm a little bit old for you,
am I not?
Fuck's that supposed to mean?
Look, Luke, I don't have money,
not that I could get you now,
but there is someone
on their way to Jody.
Can you go, please?
- You've pissed me off.
- Yes, sex.
Right here, right now.
Anywhere you want it.
Just fucking get on with it,
can we?
Oh, my God, you're serious!
Anything.
Then I'll say fucking yes.
- Good.
- If you're pissing about...
Where do you want me?
- I don't do this.
- Yes.
No, I'm not doing that.
You said anything.
OK. Come on, we need to...
- Yeah, all right.
- I just...
- I need you to hurry up.
- I said all right.
I'm just saying, hang on.
OK, good.
- Take these off.
- Yeah.
Just...
- Hang on.
- OK.
I need you to just do
what we're doing here.
I need you to fuck me, then tell
me where my daughter is.
What is this?
Just fucking shut up and stop!
What is it? Am I too chatty?
Do you need me to whimper
or be scared of you,
- stick my finger up your arse?
- Let go of me!
There's some irony here, Luke.
Something to do with how long
you've been fucking with me
and then now you can't
actually fuck me.
Cos you actually can't, can you?
That's why you're still
so floppy in my hand,
cos there's something
a little fucking wrong with you.
Just fucking get off me
or I'll fucking kill you!
Breathe deep, Luke,
breathe deep.
Cos we're gonna do this, OK?
Cos we can.
We can, Luke.
I just need you to gird yourself
and stop pissing around.
Or you could just tell me
where she is.
- Oh, fuck!
- He's gone.
Why the fuck...
Why the fuck has he?
Melon, where have they gone?
Why would he fucking shut it up?
You what, you what?
You what? You what? You what?
Yes?
I'm texting you
where she is now.
How... How have you... What?
Where she might be.
Where Luke thinks she is.
Where he went
to collect the money.
Luke?
How have you managed that?
What does it matter?
I'm sending it now.
Give me your keys.
Your keys, Melon.
Tell me where you're parked.
- Er, just over there.
- OK.
Sure he's not lying? If this is
some bullshit from him...
Well, then,
you bloody go and find out.
Give me that.
- Where are you going?
- Give me the knife.
You get yourself back home
to Bernie. Will you do that?
- Get yourself all the way home.
- Where are you going?
Go, go!
Nelly!
Come on!
Jody!
Jody.
It's me. It's...
It's... It's...
It's Nelly. I'm...
Oh, look, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I won't...
I'm not here to hurt you.
I won't hurt you.
I won't even touch you, I swear.
I swear I won't.
Look...
Please, look. I...
I got you these. Dylan said
they were your fave, so I...
I know you don't know me.
I've been looking for you.
I have. I know you don't know
me, but I've been looking...
...all over.
I've been looking...
since the first minute
I found out what had happened.
And I found you.
I did.
I found you.
Oh, God!
Until the Devil turns to dust...
That's how much my mum
would say she loved me
and for how long she would.
"Until the Devil
turns to dust."
It's how long
I'm gonna keep going...
...because I found you.
I did. I did.
I found you...
...and that means I can find her.
I heard you rearrested Luke.
We have.
He was at it with, what's his
name, nonce from the auction.
All connected up,
so Claire reckons.
- I can't discuss the details.
- "Ongoing investi-blah-blah."
Here.
You ready?
As I'll ever be, Shola.
They've got me
with a foster family.
They're nice to you?
I mean, you like 'em?
Yeah, they're all right.
When Shola said that you
wanted to meet up, I was I like,
"What, really?"
I wanted to thank you.
You saved my life.
Yeah, you don't have to do that.
I mean, it's accepted and that,
and... but you don't have to.
Well, there you go, then.
So, do you live round here?
I do, yeah.
I'm kind of different places
around the Towers.
Always have been.
Is it nice?
It's, erm...
I'm not that fussy, darling,
so I'm probably
the wrong person to ask.
Look, you know when
you were where you were...
...you see other girls there?
- Nelly, don't.
- Girls that looked like you?
- They were others, yeah.
- Nelly!
- I don't know who.
- There were others?
Let's get going, Grace.
- Here, come here.
- No.
Oh. OK.
Pleased to meet you.
Don't believe you.
I don't believe a word.
- Why not?
- It don't make any sense.
- Every single one?
- All of them, every single one.
Well, how do they know that?
That's what I'm asking.
I don't know how they know,
but they do!
Who told you?
Who told you that?
Don't believe
everything you hear.
How did that go?
Huh.
You're all right, though, babes?
You know me all right, Stace.
Daiz, tell 'em.
All polar bears are left-handed.
- Thank you!
- Bollocks.
- But why? Why are they?
- Yeah, did he say that, Goz?
What's wrong
with their right hands?
What is wrong with them?
All of them left...
male, female...
And all badgers
are short-sighted.
All policemen are cunts.
All hedgehogs have a lisp.
Subtitles by explosiveskull