Subtitles : RaceMan
www.forom.com
* Love and marriage *
* Go together like *
* A horse and carriage *
* This I tell ya, brother *
* You can't have one *
* Without the other *
* Love and marriage *
* It's an institute *
* You can't disparage *
* Ask the local gentry *
* And they will say
It's elementary *
* Try, try, try
To separate them *
* It's an illusion *
* Try, try, try
And you will only come *
* To this conclusion *
* Love and marriage **
Let go of my hair,
you little psychopath!
Die, commie bimbo.
Now, Bud, I thought
we talked about this before.
What's that, Mom?
Sneaking up
behind your sister,
pulling her hair,
pretending to kill her.
Remember the effect
it had on Grandma?
Nobody likes it,
nobody thinks it's funny.
So cut it out, okay?
Sure, Mom.
Now go to school.
[HORN HONKS]
I hate you.
Good.
Hey, hon.
Anything going on?
Nope.
Sweetie, is this
your little cactus?
Uh-huh.
Any particular reason
you put it where
the alarm clock used to be?
I thought it would dress up
the room a little bit.
Gee, I meant to tell
you to be careful
before you slammed your hand
on the alarm this morning.
Well, you didn't.
Sorry.
That's okay.
I stopped the bleeding
with your slip.
Where are the kids?
They've left.
By the way, Bud has
show and tell at school today.
The subject is,
"What does daddy do?"
So when you come home tonight,
if there's a can
of beer missing,
and you can't find
the remote control,
that's where they are.
I hope he brings
that stuff back tonight.
The Bulls are playing on TV.
Oh, my God.
You're kidding.
It's not as exciting as your
Cookin' with Clyde the Cajun,
but at least it gives me
a reason to come home.
Al, do you have to leave
the refrigerator door open?
I'm getting a draft.
I'm sorry. Maybe I should look
for some food in the dishwasher.
We have no juice.
I didn't buy any.
I didn't have time.
That happens.
I understand.
You don't have a job
or anything, do you?
Well, I do sandpaper the stains
out of your shirts
and battle your socks
and underwear
into the washing machine,
but I guess that is more
of an adventure than a job.
What has that got
to do with juice?
Al, there's a store
on your way home from work.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't I think of that?
Sure. I don't mind
doing the shopping too.
Anything else I can do
to make your life easier?
You could shave
your back.
Hey, that hair is there
for a reason.
It keeps you off
of me at night.
Al, let's not start.
We were having
such a nice morning.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
You're right.
It's just that I got
a hard day ahead of me
and nothing to eat
to get me going.
I'm sorry, honey.
It's my fault.
Tonight, I promise,
there will be food in the house.
And juice.
Right.
Those kids.
I hate wasting food.
Yes, my little baby.
Have a nice day, honey.
There better be juice
when I get home.
I don't care what
your little ruler says.
I've been a 7 since I graduated
from high school.
Well, these are 7s.
The box says 9
because, well, uh...
Look, lady.
You're a 9.
I can accept it.
Why can't you?
You're very fresh!
No, ma'am,
that's impossible,
because
for the last hour,
I've been trying to squeeze
your foot into a shoe,
when I really should have
been easing them into the box.
I'd say I'm anything
but fresh.
By the way, you want
to tell John Henry there
to give the $100
pumps a rest?
Your ad says
"Courteous service."
That's not my ad, ma'am.
That's the former owner's.
He was killed, tragically,
on this very spot
when a size 9
exploded in his face.
Come on, Arnold.
We're leaving.
I want a balloon.
You've already
got one.
Hey, Al. You mind
if I go to lunch?
You just came
from lunch.
Yeah, technically.
Biologically, I was
in bed with some broad.
Luke, how can
you be happy
sleeping with every
woman you meet?
I don't know,
but I am.
I'll tell you,
as your friend,
I can't wait till you
get married.
Yeah. A wife and kids
who adore you.
A wife...
Kids...
The list goes on and on.
It's just seeing their faces
light up in the morning
when they see you.
They can't do enough for you.
It's heaven on earth.
No, Al. That is.
Luke Ventura,
at your feet.
Do you work here,
or are you
just loitering?
I'm sorry.
Can I help you?
I'd like to see
some shoes, please.
Uh, let me guess.
Uh...size 7s.
Yes. How did you know?
All women are 7s.
I know you've been
told this before,
but you have the instep
of a movie star.
Really?
Hey, Al. Meet Tawny.
Al's married.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Listen, Al,
I forgot to tell you.
I got an extra ticket to
the Bulls/Lakers game tonight.
Court level.
Want to go?
Hell, yeah!
Sure your wife
will let you?
Let me tell you something.
No woman tells
Al Bundy what to do.
Hey, you.
Get my shoes.
Yes, ma'am.
FEMALE ANNOUNCER:
We're here today
with our staff anthropologist,
Dr. Jim, who discovered
a tribe of women in the Amazon
who, like the praying mantis,
devour their males
after mating season.
Oh, my God.
Ladies?
[APPLAUSE]
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
[TURNS VACUUM ON]
Hi, honey.
Hi. Working hard?
Oh, yeah.
You know I like
to keep the house clean.
Whew! Hard day?
Yeah. You?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it must have been.
Even the TV's sweating.
Hey, get me
some juice, okay?
Oh, that's what
I forgot to do.
That's okay.
Juice isn't important.
Listen, honey,
I know you've been busy
around the house all day.
so you don't have to bother
making me dinner tonight.
I got a little
surprise for you.
I'm going to the
ball game tonight.
Al.
Hm?
You're not going
to the game tonight.
Sure, I am.
See, let me explain
something to you.
I work all day.
And when somebody works all day,
they need to have fun at night.
I don't actually expect
you to understand,
but trust me. I'm your husband.
I know best.
Isn't staying home
with me fun?
Don't wait up.
Al, you're not
going to the game tonight.
I see you misunderstood me.
You must have
thought I said,
"Is it okay with you
if I go to the game?"
You know,
like a question.
There's no question
about this.
No, there isn't.
You cannot go
to the game tonight.
Why not?
Because I invited
company over.
Company?!
Who the hell would want
to come over here?
You know that honeymoon couple
that moved next door?
No.
I invited them over.
I thought I told you.
You didn't.
Look, I worked hard
all day.
The last thing
I want to do
is spend the evening
with people I don't know.
Now, look. They are new
in the neighborhood.
They have lived here
for two months,
and they have no friends.
We have lived here
for 15 years,
and we have no friends.
Al, I want to have
some friends.
Are you implying
that it's my fault
you have no friends?
Oh, no. It's me who sits in
front of the TV set burping,
with my hand
thrust down my pants.
You keep it cold
in this house, Peg.
Al, every night
when the kids go out,
it's just you and me.
Can't you see how boring
that is for me, honey?
Look, all I am asking
is that we have
some people over for one night
and for you
to be nice.
Oh, I'm gonna be nice.
How's this for nice?
I'm not even gonna be here.
I'm going to the game.
All right, Al. Fine.
But before you go,
I would just like to say
three things.
The bank book
is in both our names,
the credit cards
are in both our names,
and the stores
are still open.
Why didn't you
get me juice?
Kids gone?
Yeah.
But they'll be back.
I can't believe you invited
these people over tonight.
I hate company.
Would you for once
think about me?
I am at home all day,
alone.
You're out there around people
all the time.
You know,
I need some fun too.
Too? Oh, sure,
on the surface
selling women's shoes
is fun.
But once you cut through
all the hype, the myths,
the glamour,
it's really very much like any
minimum-wage-paying slow death.
Hi, Mom.
Dad, can I
have $5.00?
When I was a kid,
I had to earn my money.
Did you ever once think about
trying to earn your money?
Okay, Dad.
Do you want to know
who Kelly was with
this afternoon?
Who?
You know the kid
they call Cobra,
the kid with the sore
on his mouth?
Good job, son.
Thanks, Dad.
Where are you going?
Joey's dad's
waiting for me outside.
We're going
to the basketball game tonight.
Mom said it was okay.
Bye.
The Lakers
are in town.
He really wanted
to go.
Hi, Mom.
Dad, can I have $10?
Who were you
with today?
Nobody.
Does nobody
have a name?
You know, Tom, Dick, Cobra
with a sore on his mouth?
Oh, Dad. It's not
that kind of a sore.
He just fell asleep
with a cigar in his mouth.
What?
You gave some to Bud,
you have to give to Kelly too.
Remember, Al.
No favoritism.
Peg, she's going out
with a guy
named after a reptile.
His real name
is Stanley.
They only call him Cobra because
he has one painted on his van.
And you find this
acceptable?
I've met him,
and he's a very nice boy.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[HORN PLAYING]
* Dum de dum dum *
That's his horn.
Isn't it great?
I guess that's why
I fell in love with him.
Bye, Mom.
Bye, honey.
You know, we must have
done something right.
We raised
two great kids.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
I'm sorry, honey.
I didn't hear you.
I was just thinking
of killing myself.
Not tonight, honey.
We have company
coming over.
Look, it's time
for the pre-game show.
Oh, no, you don't.
Every time we have company,
you turn on this TV
and immediately
separate yourself.
Not tonight. You can always
watch a basketball game.
Oh, but I couldn't always
meet our next-door neighbors.
Now I see.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
That must be Steve and Marcie
from next door.
Steve and Marcie?
I'm gonna miss a game
for people named
Steve and Marcie?
What's their
last name, Gorme?
And that is another thing, Al.
When they're in here, I do not
want you making snide comments.
That is why we have
no friends.
Excuse me, Peg.
I thought we had no friends
because I put my hands
down my pants.
[Doorbell rings]
Now, that's them.
Another thing. Do not
eat or drink anything.
One of them may have to use
the bathroom after you.
I'm gonna hate
these people.
You will not hate them
They are very nice.
If they were nice, they'd
be dead and I'd be at the game.
Get the door.
Get my juice.
Hello.
I'm Marcie.
I'm Steve.
You have
a beautiful home.
Yeah, so do you.
Come on in.
Howdy, neighbor!
Yeah, yeah.
I hate these people.
Why don't
we sit down.
Gee, you know,
I'm kind of embarrassed.
I have nothing
to serve you.
Listen,
if you're hungry,
there's a store
a few blocks away.
If you're going,
get me some juice, okay?
Al's only kidding.
He's just upset because
I didn't have time
to do the shopping.
You know,
Steve and I
decided to share
the household chores.
Gee, that's great.
You see, Al.
Steve helps around the house.
Way to go, Steve.
Say, listen,
who do you like
to win the NBA championship
this year?
Well, Al...
to tell you the truth,
since we got married,
I don't watch
much sports.
Marcie doesn't like it,
and we decided we'll only
do things we both like.
I feel that sports glorify
violence and competition,
and I don't think it's
psychologically healthy.
When we have a child,
we don't want it to grow up
with that "winning
is the only thing" attitude.
A child is better off
not being exposed to sports.
You gonna neuter him too?
Do you two have any kids?
Two.
Where are they?
I don't know.
So, Steve...
looks like life is really
shaping up for you two.
How long you two crazy kids
been married?
Two months, Al.
Well, Marcie,
looks like you got
a heck of a piece of clay
to work with.
We've been married
15 years.
Well, what's
your secret?
Oh, no secret, really.
Just to be considerate, accept
each other for what you are,
don't point out the fact
that the hair
he's losing on his head
is now growing
out of his nose.
And his ears.
And accepting the fact
that nowadays
it's harder to figure out
where her chest ends
and her stomach begins.
I'll get us
some coffee, Marcie.
I'll help.
Me too.
Hey. You know
another thing
that makes women
such a blessing to us?
It's like when you're
sitting somewhere,
and they come over
and they say to you,
"What are you
thinking?"
And you
start thinking...
"You know, if I wanted
you to know,
I'd be talking."
Isn't that
an awful lot of coffee
you're putting in there?
Yes.
That's for them.
Ours will be good.
You see,
if they enjoy
eating and drinking
at home too much,
they never
take you anywhere.
With men, if you ask them
for something,
you are never
gonna get it.
But if you
do some damage
to their
internal organs,
you got a shot.
And if it
doesn't work...
what have you lost?
Could you fill this
with tap water, please.
Well, I have
to be honest.
So far, Steve has been
the ideal husband.
Oh, really?
I bet the first couple
of weeks you were married,
you went to bed
at the same time.
Oh, yes.
Have you noticed how
in the last month or so,
he seems to be going to bed
a little later and later?
Why, yes.
How did you know?
You're letting him
slip away, Marcie.
You've got
a good thing going.
Don't start letting him
have a good time alone.
But we still have
a good time together.
Then why is he
staying up?
I'm telling you,
your son is gonna be a sissy
if you let that woman
take away your sports.
I used to love sports.
Of course you did.
You're a man.
But, Steve...
you can love it again.
Start with me
right now, Steve.
Turn on that TV.
I can't do it
for you.
Turn it on...
Settle back...
Relax...
and watch sports.
[CROWD CHEERING]
You know, lately...
he's been getting up
earlier than me too.
Mm-mm-mm.
That's not good.
Do you have PMS?
No.
Get it.
Steve!
Shh!
Hey!
I thought we agreed:
No sports.
Nice shot.
[COUGHS]
I demand to know
what you do late at night
after I've
gone to bed.
Are you
having fun alone, Steve?
No. I just like
to stay up and think.
What are you thinking?
Well, if I wanted you
to know, I'd...
Oh, just about...
how much I love you.
I'm going to the game
next week with Al.
My mother's coming over
next week.
Oh, yeah? She gonna
teach you how to bury me
like she buried
her three husbands?
Steve!
Are you implying
that their suicides
had something
to do with Mother?
Oh.
Well, if that's
your attitude,
then maybe I should just pack
my bags and move in with her.
Great. Then I could
go to bed at a normal hour.
All right, Steve Rhoades,
let's go.
We're going home.
It's time to redefine
our relationship.
Okay.
Al, I'll see you
next week at the game.
Peggy, I think we'll be spending
a lot of time together.
Come on, Steve.
We've got to talk.
Make it quick.
I'm gonna watch boxing.
You'll watch
nothing!
Yeah!
It's gonna be
rough for them.
Yeah. Well, it was rough
for us, and we made it.
Hey, you know what?
Bud got an A
in school today.
No kidding?
Yeah.
Hey, let's go out
Saturday night.
You know, to eat.
Just me and you.
Sure, if you want to.
We haven't been
to The Captain's
Table in a long time.
We always
like it there.
They have
such a nice menu.
Yeah.
You want to go
upstairs?
I thought you wanted
to watch the game.
Nah!
Who cares?
You know, I like
the coffee there too.
[***]