.
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Murders were thick on the ground.
Is it because the weather
is good these days?
I'm happy.
We've got to catch one of them.
But the director and the team
pretended they didn't hear.
What do we do?
We should do it.
- We?
- Yes.
You and me.
Lee Ji-Goo came here alone
last year and asked for a
refund of the prepaid coupon?
Yeah, right?
It wasn't allowed.
I said I'd ask my boss
and then I texted you, Officer.
That's a great job.
I showed you pictures a long time ago.
It just popped into my mind.
Did he say he will come again?
(OPPA INTERNET CAFE)
Are you happy to go home
without me on the weekend?
Are you staying with me now?
Then let's get married soon.
- You dozed off again.
- I just stop talking.
Keep talking.
That's why you should sleep
a little more tonight.
What if it's dangerous?
You don't get enough sleep
because you spend all day
doing latent work.
It's not that I can't sleep.
It's just that I don't sleep.
I couldn't sleep, so I lurked there.
Why didn't you catch Lee Ji-Goo and
Hong San-Oh three years ago?
Are there many people staying
in the dormitory on weekends?
He's busy because of the
Olympic math competition.
Why does a junior high school
student competing like that?
He's a science major, so he take after me.
I totally understand him.
It'd be nice to order any sushi.
I don't want to eat that inauthentic sushi.
I want to cook you something hot
when I'm around.
Can't you transfer to Lipo?
I want to have hot soup every day.
Our neighbor, Samantha.
Yeah.
She's pretending to be worried about me,
but secretly embarrassing me.
She said,
Six of the couples were seriously considering
divorce over the weekend and asked me if I'm okay.
So what did you said?
I say 55% of sexless couples
get divorced and asked her if she's okay.
(DECISION TO LEAVE)
After grabbing the rope and
climbed to the top of the mountain,
I think it was when he fell off the
top of the mountain and hit it.
Up there, over there, here, and here.
Wearing an expensive headphones.
Ten o'clock, Monday.
We'd better go up.
Is the helicopter coming?
I heard it's okay to walk.
Why do we have to go this way?
Because it's the way how the
dead have died, and we are the police.
Then, are we going to fall
when coming down?
Will we collide three times?
Why does anyone need to
climb rock like this?
Shouldn't it be prohibited by law?
Oh, it really hurts.
Ah, I got it.
60-year-old Kim Do-Soo's belongings
are engraved with initials.
He drunk soju.
And whiskey.
Please don't go near the cliff!
He retired after working as a civil servant
at the Immigration and Foreign Affairs Agency,
and until his death, he was
still there with the Minger interviewer.
It opened.
His daughter is charming.
Will you be able to open it that easily?
You dad's over here.
I'm Song Seo-Rae, Ki Do-Soo's wife.
I can't speak Korean
enough because I'm Chinese.
You must be quite shocked.
I was worried
If he climb up the mountain
and don't come back.
I'm afraid he'll die. At last.
At last.
You speak Korean better than I do.
I want to know the pattern.
Her husband died and
said she wasn't shocked.
What an amazing wife.
Go and tell her that an autopsy is required
for a dead person who has no witnesses.
Put it in a nutshell.
I don't think my wife will be scared.
She would say,
"I knew it would be like this",
"That's why I don't want to marry a cop".
A person who died for unknown reasons
in a place where no one saw him.
We need to open the body
and examine him.
That's the rule.
No, it is an order.
Is it easier if I say it like that?
More easily.
I told her to call the police.
I asked her if she could still laugh
when she saw the fracture.
And she still wanted to laugh.
This woman's body is very clean.
She's wounded in
places that are out of sight.
Wait a minute. Give me the mouse.
What does my husband look
like in real life?
Should I tell you in words?
Or do you want to see in pictures?
Tell me.
No, pictures.
He was found with his eyes open,
do you want to see it?
Head laceration is the
immediate cause of death.
It's a crack in the head that killed him.
There should have been a lot of blood but
it was raining so it was washed away.
It's a blessing that he died
the way he wanted to.
Isn't it fate?
Did you see her laugh?
He's a clean guy.
There's nowhere to go.
Just let me die like this.
That's cruel.
Am I that bad?
Am I so wicked?
We're good, right?
Yeah.
We have been very happy for
16 years and 8 months.
How can you count that?
As expected of science major.
They say sex is good for high blood
pressure and heart disease.
I read the latest research that says
it's good for cognitive function too.
Oh, here we go again.
We're gonna do it every week.
Even when we hate each other.
So vicious.
You were just thinking
about that, weren't you?
The Gilgok-dong incident.
No.
It's the case incident
of a young Chinese woman
whose husband died in the mountains.
I feel bad for her husband.
Seo-Rae goes to different elderly people
that are living alone from Monday to Friday.
You asked Monday, right?
Our patients may not be
able to express themselves very well,
So the person in charge
will call one by one.
Yes, 9 a.m... come here.
I can check if the caretaker
is there or not.
Song Seo-Rae.
Monday... oh, it's
grandmother Lee Hae-Dong?
I also called to confirm that day.
I'm sorry but
Can someone who can't express
their feelings answer the phone?
Of course the caretaker picked it up.
How's Song Seo-Rae doing?
That's what our grandmothers said.
Is she a nurse or a granddaughter?
Because she is a nurse,
she is very good at injections.
It's our company's ace. It's our ace.
She's a horrible woman.
Look at her. She's taken the ring off.
Isn't it sadness hits people like waves?
Just like the ink spreads, there will also
be people who are slowly getting stained.
Let me know when you will
publish your book of poems.
I'll buy one.
Do you understand the bitterness of life?
Right?
You spend bitter weekends
with a beautiful wife.
After sitting for 12 hours all day,
Screening out illegal
immigrants is hard work.
But the thought of climbing a mountain
completely changes my mind.
- Then...
- Come on.
They found someone else's DNA
under Ki Do-Soo's fingernails.
We need to collect the epithelial cells
from her wife's mouth first.
Ah, this oral epithelial cells word.
How do we explain that to her?
When I think of something
that's giving me a headache,
All of a sudden, all of my
gastrointestinal cells started to hurt.
Go and eat. Don't buy expensive food.
Really...
They found
someone else's DNA
under Ki Do-Soo's fingernails.
Now, come to the police station
and give us some DNA.
I can't.
Why not?
I'm working.
Your husband's dead.
Looks like you're back at work.
My dead husband
must not get in the way of
caring for the living elderly.
Ah, I see.
Ah, tracking is my main specialty.
I heard that you grew up in the hands of grandma,
so I entrusted Monday grandmother to you.
Do it well.
What time did Song Seo-Rae come on Monday?
Siri, play a song.
Jung Hoon Hee's Mist.
The song is great.
I got it from Seo-Rae.
♫ I WALK ALONE ON THIS FOGGY STREET ♫
♫ ONE DAY ♫
Open your mouth.
I thought you couldn't come.
Thank you.
What do you like about Seo-Rae?
Because she's beautiful?
Because she peeled apples skin
very thinly.
I've been praying since Friday night
to make Monday come faster.
That way, sometimes I think
Monday really comes soon.
Sidi, play a song.
Jung Hoon Hee's Mist.
Isn't the song good?
I got it from Seo-Rae.
We fought.
My husband wants to climb the mountains.
I hate mountains.
Did he scratch you
because you were against
your husband's climbing the mountain?
I'll call a policewoman.
It's okay.
I need to take a picture.
I did it.
Because he doesn't
understand my Korean.
After you hurt yourself,
did he understand?
At last.
What did your husband say
when he saw you hurt yourself?
So vicious.
Do-Soo is stopping me like this.
The DNA discovered under your
husband's fingernails is therefore yours.
Is it?
Yes.
You hate mountains that much, Seo-Rae?
Confucius said, "The wise love the water,
the benevolence the mountains."
I am not benevolent.
I like the sea.
Yes, me too.
Yes?
These are the dates you go to
the emergency room, right?
Is that because you don't want him
to go to the mountains and beat you up?
He is the only Korean
who shed tears after hearing my story.
What kind of Korean?
The only one...
Kor...
Ah, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't laugh.
Because you are too explicit.
When I'm not confident
in speaking Korean,
I laugh.
Have a sit.
I'll buy you a dinner.
How's it going? Everything alright?
Thank you.
Did you eat well?
No.
That...
Is that a sushi deluxe set meal?
Can it be reimbursed?
Please follow me.
We'll be back again.
It's waterproof.
Waterproof means even if it is wet,
the water can't get in.
Nurses use a lot of waterproof products.
I see.
Come back to that room by 6:50.
This way to the ladies'
restroom, to the right.
August 17, 2015.
The Coast Guard found a
Chinese illegal immigrants
on a cargo ship coming
from Pyeongtaek Port.
Thirty-seven others were deported.
You were the only one left here.
Because I'm not like everyone else.
My maternal grandfather...
is Gae Bong-Seok of the
Manchurian Korean Liberation Army.
What?
- Wh-what did she say?
- Hmm?
Thanks to Ki Do-Soo, he got the
Order of Merit for National Foundation.
(Nationality Certificate Presentation Ceremony for
Persons of Distinguished Service to Independence)
This is me.
All right, we'll be there in ten minutes.
Lee Ji-Goo appeared
at Oppa Internet cafe.
Roger.
Release Song Seo-Rae.
Go and investigate Gae Bong-Seok that won
the Order of Merit for National Foundation.
Yes, sir.
(OPPA INTERNET CAFE)
Goodness.
Even if you don't use it,
you'll feel safe with it.
Come here.
Lee Ji-Goo!
Fuck.
Gae Bong-Seok.
- Lee Ji-Goo!
In the mid-1930s,
he served as a company commander
of the Korean Liberation Army,
which actively engaged in
the anti-Japanese armed war.
More than 200 military
operations, large and small,
have been carried out
by wildcats known as Nammanju.
In Yanbian, China, the
legend of being beheaded
for biting the company
commander's neck
in a surprise attack on the
Japanese army has been handed down.
Lee Ji-Goo, you son of a bitch!
I'm done. I think I'm dying!
Goddamn it.
Let go.
I said let go.
Oh? Why is it so dark in here?
What are you doing?
Come on, get up.
Why did you fall?
Get out.
It wasn't you, right?
Fighting with you,
I see that you can't kill a person.
Bo-Mi.
San-Oh killed him, right?
You guys won't catch San-Oh.
Why?
Because San-Oh's memories are so beautiful.
Rather than getting
caught and going to jail,
He would choose to kill the
police and then kill himself.
He have the urge to commit suicide.
Didn't I told you not to commit violence?
Didn't a policeman get injured? Policeman.
I injured myself because I beated him.
What's the use of running
around with a gun?
You're out of breath and unable to run.
Also,
you have to let the
suspect speak for himself.
Why are you keep on talking?
Aren't you listening too much
to the suspect?
- Take Song Seo-Rae for example.
- What?
We should've summoned the suspect,
and the warrant's issued.
The police officer who did the work, Mi-ji,
brought in the surveillance footage.
Song Seo-Rae was caught entering
and leaving in grandmother's house.
This alibi is the proof.
Hello, Mi-Ji.
Didn't you say that
Hong San-Oh has a lot of women?
Type up the list.
Like dates and special events.
We're tracking the address
and attaching it to it.
Why would such a beautiful woman
marry that old man and live in Korea?
Just because
you're young, beautiful, and foreign,
do you want to become a suspect?
So you admit she's pretty.
It's reverse discrimination.
If the other person is not a
woman or a foreigner,
If it's just a Korean guy, the team
leader would have go lurking right away.
Isn't you're interest in lurking?
What a chatterbox.
She didn't put ice cream in the fridge.
Sleep uncomfortably with the TV on.
Good morning.
Why are you saying
'good morning' all of a sudden?
You make people flustered.
Anyway, I have slept well. I slept well.
Meow.
You gave me crow again
because I gave you food?
Forget it.
If you have to give me a present,
Bring me the heart of
that kind detective.
I kind of want to.
Eating ice cream again for dinner.
It's not okay to smoke after a meal.
Crying... at last.
Good morning!
Good morning.
The Geumjeongsan incident case,
Are you still chasing her?
Hurry up and get the case closed and
strive for greater victory,
like the Chilgok-dong incident.
Goodness.
- Please come back again.
- Goodbye.
I heard the Geumjeongsan
case is going to be closed.
What is this Chinese document?
Isn't the investigation over yet?
But there's nothing
suspicious of the suspect.
I want to catch a murderer
in Chilgok-dong area now.
It was Song Seo-Rae's murder suspect who
returned to China with at least a life sentence.
I even gave you the translation. See?
You.
Hong San-Oh met several girlfriends.
See the report within two days.
Ah, that's just now...
Hey.
Ah, look at it again.
She killed her mother.
It's so cold, what are you doing outside?
I like the idea of a foggy sea.
Even if I go to Busan, there's a sea.
Going to Lipo, there's a sea.
I am the man of the sea.
Your mouth is full of sea.
Isn't your hometown inland?
Ah, I want to smoke.
We need to get rid of that
before it's too late.
I'll go find dried bellflower.
Didn't you chew that to quit cigarette?
Hello, Lee Ju-rim. It's me.
Do you have dried bellflower there?
My husband wants to smoke again.
It's all used up when he quit.
Just this once.
(Seo-Rae)
(Detective Jang Hae-Joon
WHAT DO YOU THINK.)
(COME TO MY HOUSE.)
Ah, really.
Why are you calling a police
office to come to you house?
You come here often anyway, don't you?
It is said that you killed your mother.
Homi mountain is
you grandfather's hometown in Korea.
Your grandfather.
Go there and visit him on the mountain
Yes.
Kill me first
I want
to take care of my mom professionally
that's why I became a nurse.
Just because I'm a nurse
so you're asking me to
kill you professionally?
So I sent her off the
way she expected me to.
Four fentanyl capsules will do.
I got some for myself, too.
Where did you put it? Fentanyl.
If you're curious, open it.
Ki Do-Soo committed
suicide and gave this to me.
(I know that you took money and flesh by approaching
Chinese and Russians to help them stay in Korea.
I know that he manipulated the facts so that unqualified people can be naturalized,
and that he has often threatened to deport them if they do not give bribes.
You will lose your credentials and pension as an
interviewer if this becomes known to the world.
He will also lose his reputation as a
civil servant who has served 25 years.
(If you don't respond to this letter, I will report
you to the immigration office and the police.)
Okay.
Ki Do-Soo have been
staring at people's faces for more than
20 years and stamping your passport.
Without any expression and a friend.
Why are you with that kind of man...
In the middle of summer,
I was trapped in a barn of boat fish
and drifted at sea for ten days.
My face looks like a skeleton,
and I'm stained with shit and urine.
I stayed there like a crazy person.
He saw me,
smelled me,
and heard my story.
Does your wife know
that you stare at someone
else's house at night?
I can't live under the stigma
of a corrupt civil servant.
No matter what the cost,
sooner or later
I will prove my innocence.
The police must be responsible for
the suicide note and tell everyone.
Actually, It was my
boss when I was working.
- I see.
- I'm sorry.
Are you sure
it's a suicide note?
You haven't got a suicide note?
You too.
You're no different than any other cop!
How can you be the youngest
police officer in history?
If he's no different than any other cop,
I'm willing to dance.
Of course
the evidence that she killed her mother is
not the evidence that killed her husband.
But didn't you say that?
Killing is like smoking.
Only the first time is hard.
Hello?
I'm sorry.
Hey, Soo-Wan.
Soo-Wan, let's go.
Yes.
- Will you?
- Yeah.
Let's go home, rascal.
Hey, hyung.
Get up.
What's going on?
Let's go.
Our group leader
Hey, let's go.
He looks a little wilted, but
he's actually a pretty scary guy.
I'll catch you next time.
Let's go, let's go.
The next time you kill your husband,
you have to take care.
Hey.
Hyung, I need to take my bag.
It's okay, it's okay. Let's go.
Go, go, go.
- I've made it simple enough, haven't I?
- Let's go.
I went all the way to come to
Busan because I respect you.
No, don't do it.
I have one question.
Don't ask.
Why did you treat that woman a sushi?
Crazy.
Seo-Rae, can you move your feet?
The incident case is closed.
Seo-Rae, you're no longer
a suspect.
Are you happy?
What?
Why would I?
You're right. I'm happy.
Why?
I just think...
We're no longer...
We?
What?
Have you had dinner yet?
Ah, yes.
Ice cream?
The only cuisine I know and I can cook
is a Chinese Cuisine.
I do all sorts of things at night
due to insomnia
Ah, insomnia means you can't sleep.
Oh my... God.
Those are the unsolved cases
but I don't know when
it'll be done so I just...
An unsolved case is a case
that has not been solved.
Unsolved case.
Do ants eat people?
Ah, that...
The first thing that comes out is flies
Sooner or later, they'll
be there in ten minutes.
After eating blood and secretions,
they'll lay eggs in wounds
or holes in the human body.
If maggots come out of there,
the ants will flock to eat the maggots.
And then the beetles, then wasps.
That's how they start eating humans.
But it tastes good.
I gave out a taste award
That's why you can't sleep.
Because of the bloodshot pictures
of the dead are screaming.
That man is Jeon Hyo-seok was found
on the mountain a month after his death.
The hand axe that smashed his
own head was next to him.
Hong San-Oh.
He is the real murderer of the Gilgok-dong
incident, but I can't catch him.
I look at these photos whenever I can.
After interviewing more than
a dozen of his ex-girlfriends,
Now I feel that I've
become very close to him.
Have he been in jail?
Yes, he have only lived for a month.
He mistakenly thought her girlfriend was
going to date another man, so he hit the man.
Is he more afraid of prison than death?
I know.
This guy actually beat someone
with the consciousness of being in jail.
So it's the woman he loves to death.
Oh Ga-In?
He run away.
Go after him!
Hyung!
The bullets has been rotated!
Oh Ga-In lives far away though.
She opened a beauty salon in Gyeonggi-do.
And she got married.
In South Korea,
Do you stop liking someone you like
when they get married?
Hey, Hong San-Oh!
Hong San-Oh!
Hong...
You.
You didn't kill Bo-Mi for money, did you?
Right? I've know everything.
When you're in jail for a month,
Bo-Mi touched Oh Ga-In, didn't he?
Actually I...
But her husband beats her.
But the husband beat the woman
I really want to kill her husband.
Why do girls sleep with those trash guys?
I'm a trash too though.
I know!
No, why are you a trash?
You really love Ga-In.
Right?
Didn't you gave up everything
for the sake of Ga-In? Motherfucker.
You gave up...
Please tell Ga-In...
Although I have suffered
a lot because of her
Actually, without her,
my life would be empty.
Please tell her so.
Hong San-Oh!
Don't do this!
Looks like you don't need to tell her.
Are you okay?
Which cop will let someone like that
drive home right away?
Do you want me to go to Busan?
No, no, there's no need to come.
But still, whenever you cry, I...
I'm not crying.
Really?
I have to go to the restroom.
Oh, okay.
I'm hanging up.
After persistent inquiry,
they finally found him.
After killing her husband, Mr. Kang,
It has been confirmed that he and Oh
have been living together.
Who is it?
You...
Ah, I told you no need to come...
What's the matter?
Because I want to put you to sleep.
Do you think I'm an old
man who lives alone?
Are you going to squeeze
my arms and shoulders?
What are you doing?
Didn't you say these are unsolved cases?
I'll burn my husband's picture, too
This is too dark.
But still, you're pretty.
What did you say about me?
Try to say it in chinese.
You're pretty.
Then, you can have one.
I'll keep this.
This one too.
This is better, isn't it?
Can you get a good night's sleep now?
I'm not sure.
I have a way.
Way?
I upgraded the U.S. Navy development.
I'm from the Navy though.
What has the U.S. Navy developed?
Close your eyes.
Do you really want my heart?
Heart?
What are you going to do with my heart?
I mean I'll put you in ease,
not to get your heart.
I see.
Sleep.
Listen to the sound of my breathing.
Align your breathing with my breathing
Now you're going to the sea.
You went underwater.
You're a jellyfish.
You have no eyes nor nose.
You're not thinking anything as well.
You're not happy
nor sad.
You're emotionless.
You're pushing the water away
Push away everything that happened today
Push it to me.
Wait.
Korean women have a lot of trouble
with their hands, don't they?
Don't caregivers not use gloves much?
The calluses on your hands are...
I felt good from the start.
Because the cop in
charge of me has a class.
Are you saying that being a cop is classy?
As a Korean?
What about boyfriend?
As a modern man.
Seo-Rae, what era are you from?
Tang Dynasty?
Why don't you ask me why I like you?
If you know, are you afraid of
always thinking about it?
I already knew that you and I
were of the same boat.
When I said I wanted to see
your husband's picture
You're saying no
and I always
I will try my best to look good.
If you look at the body in the crime scene,
half of the corpses were eyed-open.
I promise I'll catch the last one
they saw with those eyes.
What I'm afraid of is
a crime scene with a lot of blood.
Because of the smell.
That's why you always wear
good-smelling hand cream, isn't it?
Do you have anything else with you?
Seo-Rae, what are you afraid of?
Because you're a nurse,
it can't be blood.
Heights.
I see.
Your pockets...
I have 12 on the jacket and 6 on my pants.
It was made to order at the
store I always go to.
Because I've helped them with cases,
so they give me a discount.
Because I had to go directly to the scene,
I would wear this on my day off.
It's not like a person can't kill someone
even if it's a day off, right?
I don't always wear the same clothes,
don't get me wrong.
I have a lot of clothes.
I'm...
a neat person.
She unfold the book and
notebook side by side.
No matter how many hours
she spend, she keep writing.
Even though she's writing,
She often look at her phone.
Or maybe she's looking at a
dictionary for translation.
She's watching drama again.
Talking to herself while watching.
Is it because you watch historical drama
that you speak in an old-fashioned way?
She's eating ice cream again for dinner.
It's not okay to smoke after a meal.
She's crying... at last.
Oh, shit.
I know that's a swear word.
In front of the Buddha, it's really...
You'll delete the recordings
after you solve the incident case, right?
Of course.
You password is the day
your mother died, right?
If you memorize event-related numbers,
There are many times when it's helpful.
Because the case is closed
So I will also forget the case number.
♫ I WALK ALONE ON THIS FOGGY STREET ♫
On this foggy...
On this foggy street.
How did you know this old song
♫ ONE DAY ♫
Everyone who lives in
this neighborhood knows it.
It's the theme song here.
♫ YOUR GENTLE SHADOW ♫
Twin flames also sang it.
Is that so?
I smell cigarette.
You must have smoked.
Cigarette!
Ah Soo-Wan, that rascal really...
He's too comfortable.
Makes me feel like I have lung disease.
(ARE YOU SLEEPING?)
(SONG SEO-RAE)
(I'M AT THE HOSPITAL. TUESDAY
GRANDMOTHER IS IN CRITICAL CONDITION)
(AH...)
(SHE SAID SHE WANTED TO SEE ME, BUT WHEN I GOT
HERE, SHE WAS UNCONSCIOUS, SO I KEPT WAITING)
(OH MY...)
(THEN HOW'S MONDAY GRANDMOTHER?)
(AH, I'M WORRIED)
(SHOULD I VISIT HER?)
(REALLY?)
(A ALONE LIVING ELDERLY IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN A DETECTIVE WHO CAN'T SLEEP.)
(HAHA IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT...)
(THEN I...)
(I'LL BE IN TOUCH WITH YOU AT 9)
(9AM?)
(I'LL ASK THEM TO SEND SOMEONE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE)
(THEN I...)
(TAKE THE GREEN NOTEBOOK FROM
MY TABLE AND READ IT)
(THEN...)
(SHE LIKE THAT^^)
(YES)
If you go 250 miles east,
there is a mountain of oil.
The peaks of this mountain
are hidden in the depths.
Only those who reach the top can see...
Man's hand really are just...
softer than Seo-Rae's.
It's because Seo-Rae have
calluses on her hands.
It's been like this lately.
Originally the palm of her
hand looked like lips.
Sidi.
Play a song.
Who is it? Who is that who sing Mist?
This kid is being disobedient to me lately.
You have the same phone as Seo-Rae's.
Of course, because we bought it together.
You shouldn't open too many apps.
(STEP TRACKER)
(138 STEPS
2020.10.26 MONDAY)
Seo-Rae came to your
house this Monday, right?
If it was Monday,
of course she would have come.
Looks like you two went somewhere.
I stayed at home for over ten years.
Grandma, what day is it today?
Where's the grandmother
you're talking about, oppa?
I'm not sure what day of the week today.
Our Hae-Dong, you're so smart, right?
Just in case,
Did Seo-Rae
came here today?
It's Monday today.
I set the time after
Song Seo-Rae was photographed
by the entrance
and exit surveillance.
Go.
It takes about 7 minutes to
exchange the phone and leave.
If you sneak out the back window
there will be no surveillance camera.
There are two routes.
Easy route and difficult route.
But it takes about the same amount
of time to reach the top.
Although I have been
climbing the difficult route
Today, especially for newbie friends,
I'll take the easy route.
Song Seo-Rae must have
chosen the easy route.
Because she can't be seen by her husband.
All right, Chief. I'm on my way to work.
Yes?
I'm okay.
Yes.
9:00 AM. Elderly Care calls
to confirm her whereabouts.
You don't have to be ashamed
to slip in a place like this.
Bird Peak was originally
known as Oil and Water Peak.
It's as smooth as oil. That's
why it's called oil peak.
Isn't the scenery is very pleasant?
If you start listening to
Mahler's Fifth Symphony
you will arrive at the end
of the fourth movement.
Sitting on the top of the
mountain and listening to
Mahler's Fifth Symphony and
then going down the mountain.
Isn't it perfect?
The perfect way to kill someone.
Song Seo-Rae must have been
hiding here and reached the top
before the end of the fifth movement
of Mahler's Fifth Symphony.
The final line of the fifth movement
will encounter some difficulties.
Anyway, you'll know.
Compared to the difficult route
I climbed the mountain
This one is...
It's like eating sushi with a dip.
If you grab the ladder and climb up,
you will not notice that your body
has already reached the top.
(138 STEPS)
Korean women have a lot of trouble
with their hands, don't they?
At 10 a.m,
I am currently at the summit of
my favorite mountain, Geumjeongsan.
The dirty world is far away.
It's good that I died like this.
Aren't you afraid of heights?
Why is he beaten like that?
And branded like a domestic animal
You didn't call the police.
Why don't you trust the police?
He said he would send me back
to China.
Is that why you sent threatening
letters to your husband?
That letter will never be strange
no matter when it is sent.
Because everything is true.
You wrote the letter that Ki Do-Soo
sent to the immigration office?
But the address and name on
the envelope are handwritten.
How did you do it?
I just revised the defense
written by the husband.
And changed it to look like a suicide note.
So it's not true that Soo-Wan
is violent to you, right?
Isn't it violent for the police
to go to a woman's house after drinking?
All the photos are burned.
I deleted all the files I recorded.
That must be easy for you.
You pretended to like me,
so that I'll take care
of everything for you.
Don't speak about
our time that way.
Us?
What kind of time was that?
The time I spent outside
your home each night?
Listening to your breathing
and falling asleep?
Whispering happiness in your ear
while holding you?
You said I have a taste.
Do you know where is my taste comes from?
It comes from my pride.
I'm a very confident cop.
But it's been crazy lately.
The investigation was sabotaged, right?
What about me?
I'm completely broken.
You changed my grandma's phone
and replaced it with the same model.
She didn't notice at all.
Throw that phone into the sea.
Throw it into the deep sea.
Don't let anyone find it.
(DICTIONARY)
(COLLAPSE)
(1. COLLAPSED AND BROKEN
Risk of collapse.)
Stress factors such as
not catching a criminal
(13 MONTHS LATER)
manifested as sleep disturbance.
Well, what you can do now is
Take a sunbath thirty minutes before lunch,
You can keep your clothes on
but keep your eyes open.
Doctor.
You just opened in
Lipo not long ago, right?
There is no sun here in the morning.
Because of the fog.
You have hot water at home, right?
There is.
Take a foot bath before going to bed,
and I'll prescribe dopamine for you.
Try it and if it doesn't work,
I have a equipment here that helps you
breathe through your nose while you sleep.
Oh, this.
I heard that pomegranate has
the effect of delaying amenorrhea
Wouldn't it be more
convenient to not do it?
I know, even so,
I've been eating at home
every day since you came back.
I eat home-cooked pomegranates
every day and feel healthier.
Why are you getting more
and more wilted?
What are you saying?
You think I'm a pomegranate?
Director Lee was taken aback
when he saw your photo.
How can such a handsome
person become like this?
56% of middle-aged men suffer from
depression and become a high-risk group.
I heard that a man Dr. Lee met
who drank turtle essence
had a particularly good
effect on male hormones.
I'm really happy
that you're back in Lipo.
I am also very happy.
You're happy if you're with
murder and violence.
Do you want to die?
I said where is your husband!
He left me and ran away.
You're crazy!
What's all this?
How can you buy all of this
if you're husband is not around?
While you're living like this,
My mother cries every day
and begging me to kill her instead.
What did the doctor say?
He said she won't last a month.
If my mother die,
your bastard husband
I'm done holding it in for ten minutes
Look at your mother.
Does your mother know
you're beating women?
Does she know what your nickname is?
If my mother die,
I'll put her in the freezer
I'll kill your husband
and then start the funeral.
I've had a hard time raising them.
Don't worry.
Our team leader
is the youngest person to be
commissioned as superintendent
but he's also the best in Busan.
Team leader.
The stolen items were 58 native turtles.
How much is the approximate amount of loss?
More than 3 million won in market prize.
Oh my, how can it be so expensive?
They say it's good for
middle-aged men with depression.
As expected, our youngest person
to become a superintendent.
How can you even know that?
Go outside and tell them
to turn off the lights.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Dohyuk.
You're stupid.
Didn't I tell you not to come?
This way I can see you.
There's no way to get out.
What are you going to do?
Honey, we have to pack
our things quickly.
Did you changed your number again?
Ah, hurry up and pack.
Chul-Sung has found out
where we are.
And next week,
you'll help me host the Chinese.
If they can't get through to
China, it'll be hard for me.
Oh? What did you send?
So he have already been there.
I don't think we'll be able to
see anyone for a while.
I love you.
We're good, right?
Let's forget about Chul-Sung.
Let's move first.
We have to.
Now that Chul-Sung have found you
Where do you want to move?
What's going on?
Is this a real fire?
Or just a fire drill.
If it's a fake fire this time,
nobody's coming out next time.
People say you're here
because of depression.
Because you failed to stop
criminals from committing suicide.
But now you're cured.
Do you think I'm still depressed?
That's because I can't sleep well,
that's the reason.
He's wearing shoes?
You're not even smoking,
why don't you go in?
Did you come to accompany me
because you saw me alone?
It's really quiet in the
remote mountain village.
If you want to smoke,
go outside and smoke.
I love you.
What are you doing here?
I just moved in.
Why?
There's nothing to see here.
I like the fog.
I'm Song Seo-Rae.
I'm Chinese so I don't speak
Korean very well.
Honey.
Honey, this is the detective
who suspected me.
Ah, I am her "next husband".
I'm Im Ho-Shin.
I'm Jang Hae-Joon.
Why did you come to Lipo?
I just touched the fish.
I just moved in as well.
My wife works here.
I'm Ahn Jung-An.
I've only heard of people
leaving here because of fog.
I've never heard of people
coming here because of fog.
Wait until you've seen how
moldy this place is.
Honey, really you are.
Actually, we came here
because of the nuclear power plant.
What? What's wrong?
The red alert?
Woo Bin starred in a drama about
solving the nuclear leakage accident.
Chinese women travel great distances
just to see the filming location.
Doesn't she need a tour guide?
Now that you're making money
from that point of sale,
I shouldn't have said this but
A TV drama featuring a
groundless nuclear crisis
is really giving us a headache.
Ah, she works at a nuclear power plant.
She's quite sensitive to such issues.
Actually,
Nuclear power is completely safe.
Ah, have you ever been on a
stock market show?
You've seen it.
I am a stock market analyst.
It's not an anal analyst in
korean word who likes the anus.
You look younger than I saw you on TV.
Swimming in morning is my
secret to staying young.
If you want to know
the investment tips,
Feel free to contact me anytime.
Please give me your business card too.
Your business card is gorgeous...
You don't have to run here.
What a beautiful woman.
Well,
the green coat is beautiful.
Isn't it color blue?
Whatever the color.
She's a chinese woman who
has been widowed.
Have I heard about that case?
I remember hearing about a
case where a Chinese wife
committed suicide and
became a widower.
There was a case like that.
Her last husband was a
criminal, wasn't he?
No.
I suspect the wrong person.
Didn't you doubt that woman too?
Yeah.
But it turns out that her
husband died by suicide.
Why do you always suspect
the wrong people?
That's why people hate us.
Us?
Us, the police.
(DETECTIVE YEO YEON-SOO)
Honey, answer the phone for me.
My hands are covered in blood.
Hello?
Honey.
Congratulations.
There's a murder.
The estimated time of death is 11:00.
Presumed to have been
stabbed 17 times.
There are 13 stabs in the
stomach and chest.
4 stabs on back.
He must be stabbed in the
back when you ran away.
Can someone run away with 13 stabbings?
By the way, why is the corpse
in that position?
The first person to find him
was his wife.
Team leader, should I bring her here?
The suspect is left-handed.
Write down.
That's why you came to Lipo?
Am I such a pushover?
Am I so wicked?
Song Seo-Rae, listen carefully.
An alibi this time
should be as hard as under the eaves.
Do you think his wife is the murderer?
Why?
Because there's no sign of invasion,
no sign of theft,
no sign of binding?
Because of sudden frontal stabbing
Do you think this is a
vengeful killing?
Or maybe because his wife
wasn't shocked or sad?
It varies from person to person,
some people grieve like waves...
Why do you always ask me questions?
Why didn't you ask to
anyone else like that?
I met her in Busan last year
because of the incident case.
It was also because her husband died.
Did she kill him?
I suddenly wondered if she
might be the killer.
That case was classified as a suicide.
And yet again, her husband died here,
and still under my jurisdiction.
But she's right-handed.
So think about it.
How could she be a criminal?
They want me to go
to the police station
Can I take my handbag out?
You went for a walk.
And you don't have a cell phone with you,
so you have no way to track your location,
Do you have way to prove your alibi?
I know.
It doesn't look like you're worried.
Does your husband ever had
a grudge against anyone?
I heard that he borrowed
other people's money
to invest a lot and
still lost a lot of money.
He have lost a lot of money lately.
He lost money and still
live in a high-end villa.
You have to see how much
money you spend to save money.
Ah, why did you marry such a man?
I married a man
to make up my mind about
breaking up with him.
What did you come to Lipo for?
We're here for no reason.
If there's one, the creditors
will find us.
You don't marry your husband
simply because you love him.
Your husband is threatened everywhere.
And later on, die.
Same as last year.
What?
My previous husband
committed suicide.
How can it be the same
to my recent husband?
Okay.
Your two husbands.
And it's a very distant jurisdiction.
In remote jurisdictions
One committed suicide
and one was killed.
If people hear something like this,
I'm sure they thinks so too
that's such a coincidence.
What do you think would
people say to you?
What a poor woman.
It's not this one, it's a blue dress.
There's no coat too.
Are you sure it's blue?
Not green?
Thank you.
She's right, it's blue.
What was she doing?
You really...
Why did you come
to this neighborhood?
Why do you keep asking?
Does it matter to you why I'm here?
Why is that important?
This is the only way I can see you.
What can I do?
What were you wearing for
a walk at Haenyeo Pier?
This one.
You're lying.
Where is the green dress?
The green one that looks blue.
With shiny buttons.
Did you take a closer look?
I'm not going to turn
everything upside down.
Ah, sorry, sorry.
You're here.
Did you see that?
Wow, there's also a murder
in our village.
I'm already sleepy now.
(FAMOUS STOCK ANALYST, LIM HO-SHIN,
FOUND DEAD IN LIPO WHILE ESCAPING)
What should I do at night?
After I came back from a walk,
The smell of blood is nauseating.
I thought of you.
You'll definitely come to see this.
You must be scared.
Song Seo-Rae.
You just admitted that you annihilated
important evidence in the murder.
As a suspect in the murder of Lin Ho-shin,
I'm putting you under
emergency arrest right now.
I don't like the police
following around my husband.
We have this smartwatch, right?
Extract the audio file.
It must be recorded in Chinese,
so please find someone to translate it.
Yes, sir.
Are you a male?
No.
Have you ever killed someone?
Yes.
Did you kill your husband, Im Ho-Shin?
I didn't.
Team leader.
What are you doing here?
This is the recording of the smart watch.
Aren't we checked the license plates around
the resort before and after the murder?
Among them, there are victims
of Lim Ho-shin's fraud.
He's the head of a gang.
His name is Sa Chul-Sung.
Is there anyone else with
the surname Sa?
Let go!
Are you okay? What are you doing?
Call her.
Mom!
He's left-handed.
270 million won.
My mother has been running
a food stall for ten years,
and she managed to
open a Chinese restaurant
for eighteen hours a day in this island.
I trusted Lin Ho-shin
with all that money.
At first, I only put 10 million won.
But it's always nice
to pay dividends and
pin everything to the ground.
Then he took a lot of money that I saved,
and go to hotels all
over the country.
He's just gambling
and buy his wife an expensive
bags and clothes.
He spend my money like a pig,
that son of a bitch.
It's worth 10 billion won.
My mom had severe diabetes.
But she had a nervous breakdown
after knowing that
the money was tricked.
She collapsed due to kidney complications.
Because she didn't get the
proper treatment,
It lead her ten toes to be amputated.
Do you know why my
nickname is Ironstone?
'Cause I'm good at slapping people
on the face with this iron slap.
That's why they call me Ironstone.
Hitting someone with a slap is lighter than
hitting someone with a fist.
That's why I can keep slapping.
But I...
But I can't even kill Im Ho-Shin.
Is that still a human being?
Do you know Song Seo-Rae.
Didn't you ask Song Seo-Rae to kill him?
Really, I...
I'm not the type of person who can
simply tell others what to do.
Song Seo-Rae, she really helped me.
She'll never know.
Why can't she escape from me
no matter how hard she try?
I installed a location software
on my phone.
Wow, is this Im Ho-Shin?
Why is he sitting like this?
It's scary.
You motherfucker.
Do you want me to slap you hard today?
Are you crazy?
Team leader, aren't you happy?
Why would I?
We solved the first murder
case in Lipo, didn't we?
Where is the best place to have dinner?
Case solved?
Who said the case is solved?
Now that the criminal has caught,
They should be able to let
Song Seo-Rae go home.
That's what I thought.
The turtle thief is on the run
on a motorcycle
in Greenstone Walls
3-way Village Hall bound.
I repeat, in Greenstone Walls
Hey, it's okay.
He won't be able to run again!
Gather the turtles!
Oppa, hurry up.
Get up.
Carry him on your back,
we need to catch him.
Yes, sir.
Hey, hey. Hop on my back!
Grab the big one first.
They're vicious. Watch your fingers!
We caught the turtle thief.
My husband and the husband
of a woman you know
I missed his phone calls in
the middle of the night
and he even called twice.
Is it a wrong number?
To a married woman you're meeting
for the first time for no reason?
Although this can pass like this
What if that man gets killed
a few days later?
Honey.
Did you kill him?
Did the two of you
kill him together?
Are your fingers all right?
This is Im Ho-Shin's illegal
cell phone number.
Track where he was before he died.
(TAKE THE OPPORTUNITY
IN YOUR OWN HANDS!
OPEN UP A NEW WORLD!)
Team leader.
Yes?
Why was the phone here
when the owner died at home?
The owner's phone turn on and off.
Put your arms around one more time.
Put your hands up a little higher.
Oh, my arm hurts.
Stop!
She dropped the phone.
Let's find the divers and
start searching the area.
Is it deep there?
Get yourself together.
We've already caught the criminal.
There's evidence and we got a confession.
Please stop clinging to that woman.
Don't you feel sorry for her?
He's wearing a shoes?
I can see his beard.
Is he lazy to shave
in the morning and night?
He looks no energy...
Is it because he haven't seen me?
When he made me that
strange chinese food,
I've been smoking next to him
and he couldn't hold back the smoke.
All he can say is "I love you", my ass.
I remember the nights
he peed at me.
I felt like a trustworthy man,
who can't sleep,
was protecting me.
He's coming.
As soon as he come,
he'll ask me if I came
to Lipo to do this.
What should I do?
Why do you keep crying,
Song Seo-Rae?
Should I tell him the answer?
No.
He may
already know.
I don't know if he'll ask me.
Is that why you came to Lipo?
Hello.
What's on that phone?
Answer me.
Open the door, hurry.
I'm not home.
Then where are you?
Homi mountain.
There must be something in Im Ho-Shin's
phone that you threw it into the sea.
Don't doze off.
Hold it for a while.
There's no fog here.
Why did Im Ho-Shin call my wife?
Moms who like mountains
often say this.
Whenever I'm upset,
If I go to Korea,
there will be this mountain.
Tell me the truth.
You also knew that Im
Ho-sin is going to call
my wife, right?
Despite the fact that
the state has spared him
even the most heinous sentence
But no matter what people say,
in my heart
Homi mountain is my mountain.
Mom.
Grandfather.
I've brought a man I can trust.
Help me out.
You know I'm afraid of heights.
Why did I marry a man like that?
Because an ideal man like
you wouldn't marry me.
If you want to take a look,
atleast a murder has to happen.
Is this the time to joke?
You've been unable to sleep
comfortably since I left you, right?
Even if you close your eyes,
you've always see me, don't you?
Aren't you?
That night when you ran
into me in the marketplace,
you suddenly felt like
you were alive again, right?
At last.
My hands are soft now, aren't they?
In the past 400 days, you...
You...
But even then,
the fact that I'm a police and you're
the suspect will not change.
You're a person suspected by the police.
I like that.
Just be comfortable and
treat me like you always do.
Treat me like a suspect.
Aren't you wondering why
I like you, Seo-Rae?
Or are you just not interested?
What about you?
My body is stiff.
There are few people who are
not nervous but who are so honest.
I think I've said that I like you a lot.
What's with the four fentanyls here?
I've been taking it back
and forth for the whole time.
It's too heavy.
Bye, grandpa.
Bye... Mom.
Didn't I let you throw it away
so that no one could find it!
Use this to do re-investigation.
Let's go back to the old days.
Looks like I want to unsloved your case,
that's why I went to Lipo.
Manager Lee!
Yes?
You've never seen him before, have you?
He said he recently got divorced.
I'm Lee Joon. I've heard a lot about you.
Isn't it snowing here?
What?
So how do we deal
with that problem?
What problem?
Even if I hate it,
I promise to do it every week.
Would you excuse me?
Can you sleep?
I went to the hospital for an examination
but I woke up 47 times in an hour.
Can you believe it?
I wish I could give you
a piece of my sleep
Just like a battery.
It's because of my deliberated breathing.
I have to use a nose-assisted
breathing machine when I go to bed.
It's weird.
When I'm awake,
I breathe through my nose.
But that doesn't mean
I snore when I sleep.
I know.
Sunbathing.
Vitamin D.
Isn't it good to do it
once after a long time?
It's been 30 minutes.
I told the haenyeo.
If they see a cell phone when
you're fishing for example,
I told them to make sure
they bring it to us.
Can this be restored?
(SEO-RAE)
(I WANTED TO PLAY THIS AMAZING
VOICE RECORD OF YOURS HAHA)
(I TRIED TO CALL HAE-JOON'S WIFE)
(BUT SHE'S NOT ANSWERING:()
(SHE'LL ANSWER IT IF I CALL HER
IN THE MORNING, WON'T SHE?)
(I CAN TALK TO CHINESE PEOPLE WELL NOW)
(DO YOU JUST WANT TO
SCREW UP LIKE THIS?)
(I'M GOING TO DIE ANYWAY)
(CHUL-SUNG'S MOM WON'T LIVE LONG.)
(HE PICKS ME UP WHEREVER I GO)
(OKAY
IF YOU DON'T GET ANSWERS FROM THE CHINESE
(BY THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW)
(I'M GOING TO UPLOAD THIS
AMAZING VOICE RECORD ON INTERNET)
(WHAT KIND OF OPERATIONS
THE POLICE PLAY WITH SUSPECT.)
(IN TERMS OF THE PUBLIC'S RIGHT TO KNOW.)
(I'M GOING TO HAVE LUNCH WITH THE CHINESE
THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW, )
(SO COME HOME BY 10 IN THE MORNING.)
(I'M GOING TO HAVE LUNCH WITH THE CHINESE
THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW, )
(SO COME HOME BY 10 IN THE MORNING.)
(ALL RECORDINGS)
(NO VOICE RECORDINGS SAVED)
On the morning of your mother's death,
did you saw Song Seo-Rae?
She came early in the
morning to visit.
She said that she felt bad
for my mother left like that.
After all, we're all Chinese
Didn't she advise her to take any medicine?
Something that is good for diabetes.
It's a green capsule.
Compared to that,
That woman knows how to
take care her patients.
She rub her here and there,
and my mom was in such a good mood.
So I went out for breakfast, too.
Later, I found out that
Song Seo-Rae has already left.
Mother lay off comfortably
with her eyes closed.
It's weird but she feel
drowsy for no reason.
And then...
But what does my mother's death
have to do with Song's rub?
Didn't Chul-Sung say he had
location software installed on his phone?
Hello, Hae-Joon.
I repaired Im Ho-Shin's phone privately.
There are no voice recordings at all.
It's true that the one who killed
your husband was Chung-Sung.
But you killed Chul-Sung's mother.
Because Chul-Sung said he'd
kill your husband if his mother died.
Your husband and Chul-Sung's mother.
Did you kill her because of me, isn't it?
She's a dying person anyway
but why are you so anxious
that you gave her fentanyl?
Because she said thank you.
What is the recording that Im Ho-Shin said
he was going to reveal?
Don't worry about that.
I'm not asking that
because I'm worried.
You've got the original, haven't you?
What is it?
It's your voice.
What?
The record of your voice
saying you love me.
Did I?
Because I like it so much,
I keep listening.
My husband found out.
When did I say I love you?
When?
The moment you said you loved me,
Your love is over.
The moment your love ends,
My love begins.
Please say it in Korean.
Seo-Rae.
Hae-Joon.
The cell phone that was
fished out of the sea,
Throw it away again.
Throw it deeper into the sea.
Why do you keep saying
irrelevant things?
Gosh, it's annoying, really...
Where are you going?
Seo-Rae.
Hello?
Seo-Rae!
(VOICE RECORD)
(BREAKS DOWN AND WAKES UP)
You burnedall the photos.
I...
It should be easy to delete
all the files I've recorded.
You just pretend to show
that you like me
so that I'll take care
of everything for you.
Don't speak about our-
Throw that phone into the sea.
Throw it into the deep sea.
Don't let anyone find it.
Throw that phone into the sea.
Throw it to the sea.
- Throw it into the deep sea.
Don't let anyone find it.
I probably want to unsolve your case,
That's why I went to Lipo.
You put a picture of me on the wall
and can't even sleep well,
thinking about it a lot.
Seo-Rae!
Seo-Rae, where are you?
Hey, we're sending out a
wanted warrant to the headquarters.
Here...
The tide began to rise
around the rocks of the sea.
Let all the people who can come along.
Song Seo-Rae is gone!
We can find her as soon as possible.
She hasn't gone far.
If you have time to ask me,
why don't you come here quickly?
In a little while,
we won't be able to see nothing!
But it's been crazy lately.
The investigation was sabotaged, right?
I'm...
completely broken.
You changed my grandma's phone
and replaced it with the same model.
She didn't notice at all.
Throw that phone into the sea.
Throw it into the deep sea.
Don't let anyone find it.
"Throw that phone into the sea."
It's your voice.
Your voice saying you love me.
Seo-Rae!
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.