Previously on "Cardinal".
What did you see?
A white guy
with blonde hair.
You saw Terri get on the bus, right?
I dropped her at the station.
But my prints are all
over that kilo of coke.
Make the fingerprints disappear,
and I'll tell you what I got on Cardinal.
We have confirmation.
A rival moving in on the
Northern Raiders drug trade.
I didn't know he was a dealer.
Is there anything at all
that you can tell us about him?
He had like this crazy tooth.
The Northern Raiders don't
own this town anymore.
Toof.
Keep your mouth shut about our plans.
No!
Never lose control.
No one uses our product.
Break any of my rules and I kill ya.
You left your meds at home.
Please, step back from the edge.
I'm working.
Jesus, John.
Go home!
♪ you and I
♪ do or die
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
What have we got?
Vic's been dead between twelve
and twenty-four hours.
Cause of death,
either blunt force
trauma or gunshot wound.
You'll understand when you see the body.
This must be the kill site.
You get a match on that
and you call me right away.
Hey.
When did you get back?
Last night.
Call Ballistics, Ash.
Give them a heads up we
got something coming in.
I want a quick turnaround on this.
Hey guys,
check this out.
Can I tell you how good I am?
Maggot casing?
Irrefutably.
What's so exciting?
The distance from the flesh.
Maggots will eventually
fall off a dead body.
But this little guy
was eight feet from the corpse.
Right inside a footprint.
Looks like a work boot.
Like the one Terri saw at the cave maybe.
Size 10, I'd wager.
Yeah, but why would a guy
have a maggot casing
on his boot?
My question exactly,
which is why I'm taking this
to the master of entomology.
Chin.
He'll be ecstatic.
The guy has an extra incisor.
Rachel Wells bought heroin from a dealer
with a tooth like that.
She OD'd.
I'm sorry.
No one stood up for her.
You did.
It wasn't enough.
Jordan, her boyfriend, said
that she bought the drugs
at the Corner Pocket.
From a guy who had a,
what do you call it,
a snaggletooth?
So maybe he's one of the new dealers
trying to cut out the bikers.
Lasalle's boys find him,
beat some Intel out of him.
Shoot him.
Or the other way around.
You knock somebody out
and then shoot him,
that's one kind of person.
You put two bullets in their brain
and then bash their head in,
what does that make you?
Sadistic.
Or maybe the owner of defective bullets.
I'm betting on both.
Thought you'd be happy.
I got no complaints with you
putting Lasalle out of business.
Hey, did it together, Alan.
No.
A couple bikers get
roughed up in a turf war,
nobody looks too closely at that.
But the mutilation,
the sacrifice,
I can't be part of that, Ray.
You're a big part of it.
You've earned this.
It's just the beginning.
You know what, you keep it.
I'm out.
There is no out. Take it or leave it.
I held up my end of the deal.
You work for me now, Alan.
Alive or dead.
It's your choice.
So,
what do ya got for me?
Cops found, uh, your friend Toof
with his head caved in.
What else?
Been looking for Leon's truck.
What about the redhead?
Terri Tait?
So you did shoot her.
The hell'd you do that for?
She had nothing to do with Lasalle.
Where is she?
She's in protective custody.
I don't even know where.
Find her.
So, Jordan gave us a description
of Rachel Wells's dealer.
I followed up at the Corner Pocket,
one of the regulars ID'd him as "Toof".
Sergeant?
Who is this?
Our shooting Vic.
There's only one "Toof"
alias in Northern Ontario,
Morris Tilley.
Local. Low level pot dealer.
Is he connected with
the Northern Raiders?
Ah, Clegg says no.
But we do think he's connected
to a drug operation
who are taking over from the bikers.
We're still digging.
Sounds promising.
Morris is a good boy,
you know, maybe too
fond of that marijuana.
I-I-I tell him all the time to lay off.
Always puts you in a fog.
Mrs. Tilley.
I'm sorry but your son is dead.
We found him this morning
on the edge of the forest,
just off the 17.
What?
No.
No, he's not.
He was just here
the other day
wolfing down a sandwich.
No, your son was murdered.
He's a sweet boy.
He never hurt anybody.
Could you tell us about
anyone he was friends with,
um might have been hanging around with.
I don't know.
Ah, he moved out two months ago.
Was he living with anyone?
Um...
Leon ah-ah-ah something.
And uh-
a native friend.
A fancy name.
Uh, Toof said he was psychic.
Um-
Northwind.
Yeah, that was it.
Do you have family or friends nearby?
You shouldn't be alone right now.
Is-is Terri there?
Terri Tait.
She works there.
I'm her brother.
Yeah.
The-
The-the cops said what?
No. No, thank you.
That's fine.
Thank you.
Give me a sec.
Well I'd offer you a beer
but uh, you probably shouldn't drink.
You're sending your boys to the rez
looking for drug dealers.
Tell me what you know about the guys
moving in on your territory.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You think they're Native.
Why?
I know how close you and Wombat were.
They cut off your
brother's head off, man.
So tell me what you know.
And then what?
We can offer you protection.
Before this escalates.
I'm sorry, man, I can't help you.
Fine.
The offer remains.
In the meantime,
you set one more foot on my rez,
I'm coming for ya.
I can now link your first body
to your second body through DNA results.
But we didn't give you DNA.
Abby Harris gave me a maggot casing.
We have the same DNA at both sites.
Whose DNA?
The fly's.
So the same species of
fly can be found at both sites.
No.
The DNA of the same individual fly.
The maggot that came out of this casing,
found in the footprint at
the second murder site,
has the same mother as
dozens of other eggs
found at the first site.
Chin's evidence
confirms that Toof's killer
was also at the waterfall.
We're waiting on ballistics,
but I'm betting the
bullets in Toof's brain
match the one in Terri's.
So you got one guy shooting people
and dumping the bodies.
And another guy who's
chopping up his vics
to gain spiritual power.
At least two.
Working together.
And the ritualistic one
likes to make his sacrifices
under a new moon.
Sacrifices?
That's definitely not part
of any Native ceremony
that I know of.
Any suspects?
Toof's mom said he
was staying with a "Leon"
and a,
a Native guy named "Northwind".
Doesn't ring any bells.
Northwind is a big name
on the Moose Bay rez.
We think that the
heroin's being shipped up
from a rez in Michigan, right?
Yeah.
This could be a brotherhood thing.
Native dealer wants to do
business with his own people.
So he gets rid of the white guy.
Could be how
Northwind cuts out the bikers.
We have two days until the new moon.
We have to find Leon and
Northwind before then.
It's been a while since
I've been to Moose Bay.
Hey.
Hm?
I heard about Rachel.
I should've pulled her out sooner.
Yeah.
You're lucky.
The drugs were incinerated.
Only thing left was a
fingerprint card and a
photo of the prints.
So.
You had something to tell me.
Yeah.
I have a friend
works in lock-up.
She says you signed out
a box of cold case files
but failed to mention
you'd hidden another case inside of it.
Things get misfiled all the time.
You lied.
You stole evidence.
And you're on tape.
You are exactly
what I thought you were.
Lise Delorme is an
excellent investigator.
NIS will be happy to have her.
She was good.
I'm sorry I put her in your path.
They make their decision
today, don't they?
Chief Northwind?
That's me.
Jerry Commanda.
Ndishnikaaz.
Aaniishna Nishkaa?
You're OPD.
Out of Algonquin Bay.
I'm trying to locate a man
by the name of Northwind.
But I don't know his first name.
And we think he's taken
over the heroin trade
in Algonquin Bay.
Northwinds are good people.
Traditional.
You ever heard of uh-
the Northern Raiders?
You see, a few days ago
we found the severed head of one them
in some drug dealer's house.
We think that Northwind has
something to do with it.
Without a first name,
I really can't help you.
Respectfully, I think you can.
I got nothing to say.
Did he threaten you?
Yesterday I took the body
of a girl to the morgue.
She overdosed on heroin
probably sold to her from this guy.
He's killing children.
All I need is his name.
Ray.
Ray Northwind.
He's not one of us.
Where's he from?
The guy just turned up here one day,
he showed me his status card.
Wanted me to say that I was his uncle.
Said some Peter Crowchild was gonna call,
Chippewa from Iron River.
I had to say that he was
born and raised here.
What did you say?
What do you think?
Kicked him out.
The next day,
I wake up.
There was this sound at the door.
You ever hear the sound a dog makes
with his paws cut off?
My grandkids over there.
He knew their names.
Ah-
I'm looking for John Cardinal.
Ah, he's not here.
You must be Catherine.
How do you know John?
I'm Tammy.
Lidstrom.
I used to go out with Kyle Corbett.
Ah-
Can-can you just-
Can you give this to John?
Tell him I can't take it.
You look like you could use a cup of tea.
I burned through the
last of the money John gave me.
And I didn't know what
I was going to do and,
then he called.
Said his partner
was paying the price for what he did.
Lise Delorme?
Yeah, she was investigating him.
Thought he was dirty.
When he was covering up
for your phone call.
I know he felt responsible
for that officer's death,
but all he ever wanted
was to protect you.
And I used that.
I don't want to be that person anymore.
(Ethereal Instrumental
Anything biting?
I'm parking the truck for now.
You gave me that truck.
It's mine.
I said, I'm parking it.
Take the other car, go into town,
wait for my call.
I'll have an address for you.
Have faith, Leon.
Even when you think you've messed up,
you find out it's all
part of a bigger plan.
Leon Rutkowski.
Did eight years for running
heroin and aggravated assault.
In Collins Bay.
His time overlapped Kevin Tait's.
How many Leons in Algonquin Bay with both
assault and drug charges on their record?
He's the only one.
Don't suppose he owns a black truck?
No vehicles registered under his name.
Let's get a BOLO out.
Leon Rutkowski.
- Delorme.
- Mhm?
I just got off the phone with NIS.
They want you in Ottawa next month.
I got it?
Apparently somebody over there
changed their mind.
Congratulations.
Okay. Thanks.
You're welcome.
Commanda got a hit on Northwind.
First name, Ray.
Yeah.
John.
I need to know.
What did you do to make
Musgrave back off?
You got it.
That's all that matters.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Listen,
you were right about Wasserstein.
We could've Skyped.
I went to Toronto to find Catherine.
Was she?
It was a mistake.
Things shouldn't be hard for you
because of-
because of this.
It's too late for that.
That's him.
He dumped me in the cave.
Leon Rutkowski?
Or the name Ray Northwind?
I don't think so.
Does he have Kevin?
Do you know where he is?
That's what we're trying to find out.
Oh.
Yo. Jesus Christ. Dude!
Hey.
What happened to you?
Nothing man.
I went for a hike.
Dude, your face.
Oh, ah-
I fell off a rock.
I guess I hit my head.
Hm.
Where you been, you been selling?
I just had some stuff to do in town.
Oh nice.
You uh, you got any extra stash?
I got some guys interested and I'm-
I'm running low.
You better not be using again, Kev.
No, no.
I'm not.
I swear.
It's just-
business is booming
and I'm all out.
Go talk to Ray.
Okay.
Aw man,
he got rid of my truck?
Guess so.
Alright,
go get some ice for your head,
you look like shit.
Ha. Sure. Okay.
Online shopping?
What's up, Jerry?
This guy calling himself Ray Northwind,
posing as Anishnaabe.
Wait, wait.
He's not from Moose Bay?
He's not from anywhere I can find.
I think he's pretending to be Indian
to get a deal from the
supplier down in Michigan.
Who's that?
Peter Crowchild.
Iron River Rez.
That's good work.
You know, I'm thinking that
Crowchild is flying the
heroin across Lake Huron,
up the French River to Lake Nipissing,
where he does the hand-off to uh,
"Ray Northwind".
Keeps the shipments out
of federal jurisdiction,
both sides of the border.
Does Cardinal have any leads
on Northwind's real identity?
He's working on it.
Cath?
Hi.
You're back.
I'm making stir fry.
Did you hit traffic on the way?
No.
I saw your medicines
in the cabinet and I thought
you had stopped taking them.
You embarrassed me in
front of my students.
What was I to do?
You wouldn't answer your phone.
I was working.
I have to be able to reach you.
If something were to happen-
I'm fine.
Why can't you see that?
The signs-
The signs were there-
Because you were looking for them.
You wanted to protect me.
And I'm grateful for that.
But where's the freedom-
For either of us?
How's Lise doing?
Delorme?
NIS wants her in Ottawa next month.
Special training.
She'll be hard to replace.
This is one of the good times.
There are so few.
And we both know, they never last.
Cardinal.
Send me the coordinates.
I'm on my way.
Anybody in the truck?
No.
The car's registered to Raymond Bedford.
Delorme's running his details.
Good job spotting it.
Anything yet?
The connection's bad out here.
I'm sure NIS will be better equipped.
You should have stayed out of it.
And let you take the hit.
It was my choice.
I won't be the one holding you back.
Here he is.
Raymond Bedford.
Ray Northwind.
There's drug paraphernalia in the truck.
Traces of heroin.
Rules, Kevin.
Maybe your brother thinks you're dead.
I mean, it's weird that he
hasn't checked the hospitals
or called the cops, right?
Maybe he can't.
Fire!
Everyone out now.
Leave your stuff.
Come on!
Naz. Come on!
Come on. We'll be fine. Come on.
Stay with me, you'll be okay.
Shut up!