Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
[indistinct chatter]
[Richard] Another, sir?
Keep them coming.
[silverware clattering]
[camera shutter clicks]
[beeps]
[elevator dings]
[beeping]
[safe beeps and clicks]
[camera shutter clicks]
[paper rustling]
[elevator dings]
[grunts]
[grunting and groaning]
[clicks]
Oh, crap.
And you are?
Dragon. Richard Dragon.
[thunder rumbling]
[bats screeching]
He is... preoccupied.
[woman giggling]
He'll want to hear this.
- [woman giggling]
- Come.
I'm sorry to interrupt...
No, no, Schlangenfaust.
We're quite finished here.
What is it?
[Schlangenfaust] One of our
facilities in France was...
compromised.
And?
Someone knows we have The Gate.
Then you know what to do.
[door opens and closes]
I'm afraid our time
has come to an end.
Honey, in my line of work,
it always does.
But, you know,
if you need any more help,
I'm only a phone call away.
Indeed.
- [gasps]
- [lock clicks]
[door rattling]
[scoffs] What the hell, man?
[grunts]
[thudding] Hey! Hey!
[breathing heavily]
[gasps]
Dance for me.
[sarcastically]
Real funny, wise guy.
Now, open the door.
You aren't the only customer
I have tonight.
[whispering] Dance... for me.
I'm not dancing for you.
You dig?
[shouting] Now open
the damn door!
- You hear me, freak?
- [chamber opens]
- [hissing]
- What the...
[whimpering]
[voice shaking]
Oh, please! God!
No, no!
This isn't funny!
[screaming]
Open the door! Open the door!
[frantically] Oh, God!
Please, no! Please!
- [crying]
- [squeaking]
[screaming]
This is my favorite part.
[woman] No, please!
[yelps]
[squeaking]
[screaming]
- [screaming]
- [train screeching]
[vehicles honking]
[funky music playing in club]
Hey. Slow down, Charlie Chan.
There's a line.
I'm not here for the music.
I'm a friend of the owner.
Buddy, I know karate.
So, how about you
get out of here,
before I kick your ass?
Karate?
That stuff only works
in the movies.
Oh, I assure you,
it's very real.
Why don't you show me?
I'll even let you have
the first shot.
[knuckles cracking]
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Not here.
In there.
You're about to enter
a world of hurt.
I'm going to enjoy this,
you little--
[gate closes]
Hey! What are you doing?
Come back here!
[shouting] Somebody get the key!
Hey! Hey!
Come on, man!
[Silver]
I'm sorry, Bruce.
But it's just not enough.
Look... I love you.
And, I know you love me.
What we have together
is rare. Special.
But after all these months,
there's still a part of you
that I just can't reach.
I know it sounds ridiculous,
but it's like there's some...
dark secret.
Something you're hiding
from me.
Whatever it is, just tell me.
We'll face it together.
Silver, honey,
it's not like that.
There's nothing...
Just... tell me.
I can't.
[jingling sounds]
- Silver...
- Don't call me. Ever.
Excuse me.
Bad time?
Richard?
Sorry about barging in.
I can come back.
No. No. Please.
It's good to see you.
Can I make you a drink?
Sure. Nice pad.
How long has it been?
I can't think of the last time
we saw each other.
Really?
I bet you can remember
the last time.
The first time, too.
Yeah.
- [wind blowing]
- [grunting and panting]
[thud ringing]
[grunts]
[echoing] Hello?
Anybody?
I've come a long...
way.
Screw you, then.
[door rumbles]
[thuds]
[creaking]
[O-Sensei] Welcome.
We've been expecting you.
No one answered when I knocked.
The door to destiny
is always open...
if you are brave enough
to walk through it.
Now shut the door
before you let the heat out.
Welcome to Nanda Parbat.
To find this place
took great skill and courage.
You'll need both.
Yes, O-Sensei.
I'm eager to learn.
They all say that...
at the beginning.
- They?
- Yes.
You'll be the sixth.
Shiva. My best student.
Disciplined. Honorable.
[blade whistling]
You can expect a speech
from her at graduation.
That is Ben Turner.
- [Ben grunting]
- Strong and fierce.
He came here, seeking a way
to control his temper.
[grunting and growling]
[breathing heavily]
We're still working on that.
That one is Jade.
[grunting]
A good student,
but she is always
asking questions.
Makes my head hurt.
And then, Rip.
A decorated war hero,
now looking for peace.
He's very dedicated.
Also, he makes
an excellent bowl of chili.
You said six.
Oh, yes. [chuckles] Yes.
He's been here so long,
I sometimes forget he's here.
[grunting]
That is Richard.
Richard Dragon.
Each are unique
in their own way,
as you will be.
Now, I have shown you
the grounds.
Where does that lead?
- What?
- That. The door.
It's set apart from
the rest of the buildings.
You didn't mention it.
Didn't I? Richard!
Show our new recruit
to his quarters.
Bruce.
This road is not an easy one.
It often leads to ruin
for those unfit to walk it.
You can still leave.
No, Sensei. I can't.
So, what brings you to Gotham?
Always to the point.
You haven't changed
at all, Bruce.
You might be surprised.
Someone has The Gate.
So, you came here?
What am I gonna do?
Help me find it.
Me? No, no.
In between the club downstairs,
charity functions,
my father's business--
Trouble with your lady.
Right. My calendar
is pretty full.
Now if you need some money,
I'm happy to write a check,
but the other stuff,
those days are over.
[Richard]
That's too bad.
You and I both know the skills we've
acquired don't fade that easily.
Besides, aren't you
some sort of
globe-trotting super spy now?
Why the hell do you need me?
My employers
would try to open it.
Use it to their benefit.
I can't do this alone.
I need someone I can trust.
Someone to see it through
to the end.
And you, Bruce,
are just about the most
driven man I've ever known.
Sorry, Richard.
I have my own scene going on.
Yes. I can see that.
[chattering on televisions]
I need to keep an eye
on the patrons.
Afraid they're gonna
rip off your napkins?
The truck will be there
at midnight.
What about the cops?
[scoffs] With what
we're paying them,
they'll help load the drugs!
Whatever this is,
it's not as important
as The Gate.
We owe him.
All right. Let's hear it.
Terrorist group
got their hands on The Gate.
A week later,
the terrorists were all dead.
Tying up loose ends.
You're a loose end.
That's why I came.
[screaming and shouting on TV]
[all screaming]
[crashing]
[Axe Gang member] Give us the
sword and your death will be quick.
Let's hope knife catching isn't
the only skill you remember.
[grunting]
[growls]
[O-Sensei] The stone
is indomitable.
But, it is just a thing.
Physical in nature.
But, you...
you are much more
than the physical.
Everyday, you will
hit the stone.
It will hurt,
but pain strengthens us.
It will burn,
but fire cleanses the soul.
And then, someday... maybe...
the stone will break.
But, the journey
will make your spirit
as indomitable as that stone.
Begin!
[all grunting]
Giving up already, mama?
If teacher's pet
doesn't have to do it,
I'm not doing it either.
Man says
the stone's going to break.
I'm going to break it! [growls]
[all grunting]
[grunting continues]
[Ben growls]
Man, this is bullshit!
[growls]
[clanging]
Ben, come on.
Naw. Have fun
breaking your hands.
I'm done, baby. [scoffs]
Maybe he's right.
Maybe we should turn in.
[Bruce grunting]
Good night, Bruce.
[groaning]
- [O-Sensei] Bruce.
- [gasps]
I didn't see you.
Darkness is a powerful ally,
if you know how to befriend it.
You will not break
the rock tonight.
Or tomorrow. Or the next day.
Or perhaps ever.
You said to break the rock.
I said to try
to break the rock.
I know what happened to you...
to your family.
The whole world knows.
Now, you want to stop that
from happening to anyone else.
But, evil is as eternal
as this rock.
Even if you break the rock,
there will be pebbles,
break the pebbles,
there will be sand,
and evil remains.
You cannot change that,
no matter how much you train.
Accept what you cannot change.
It is not your burden to bear.
Life is meant
to be lived with others.
It is too hard to do it alone.
[grunting]
[growls]
Bruce!
[all grunting]
Fine. Let's do it the hard way.
[grunting]
[screams]
[Jeffrey] Peace, love
and contentment, my friends.
Live low and humbly
like the snake.
At one with nature. Perfect.
Unchanged for
a hundred-million years.
Give me the numbers.
Ten new offices opening
throughout the country.
The penthouse you requested
in Los Angeles,
and, interestingly,
we've got a new recruit.
[scoffs] I hate his movies.
But, still, money is money.
[phone ringing]
Yes? Schlangenfaust.
Is the problem taken care of?
[Schlangenfaust] No, sir.
The Axe Gang failed.
It would seem our quarry is a bit
more formidable than we thought.
[Jeffrey on phone]
Too much for you to handle?
- No.
- Good.
And, Schlangenfaust...
make sure the Axe Gang
knows my displeasure.
It's already taken care of.
[straining]
[hesitatingly] So, uh,
what was that back there?
They've obviously been sent
to stop you from interfering.
Not that.
The mask. The costume?
Well?
It's a way
to keep my lives separate.
Safe.
It's more than that, Bruce.
Those guys were scared shi--
Let's concentrate on
the task at hand.
We need to get to the sword
before anyone else does.
So... we need Shiva.
We need Shiva.
[O-Sensei] This...
is Soul Breaker,
one of two swords
made centuries ago
by the master swordsmith,
Muramasa.
The metal has been folded
too many times to count,
making it as flexible as a reed
and as strong as stone.
It is said, the blade
was made with dark magic,
making it more than a sword.
It is a key to life and death.
So, it must be guarded
by one... who chooses life.
Shiva. Come forward.
Because of your focus,
strength, and integrity,
I bestow upon you
the responsibility
of safe-guarding this blade,
Soul Breaker.
[scoffs]
Jade, is there something
you'd like to say?
No, O-Sensei.
Please. We are family here.
There are no secrets.
What troubles you?
Shiva is, as you say,
a woman of integrity.
But, she is soft.
She lacks the killer instinct.
She doesn't deserve the sword.
Oh? And who does?
Anyone else. Rip, maybe?
He's been here longer than any of
us, besides Richard.
And you feel that tenure
is more important
than my judgement?
Very well.
Rip Jagger, stand.
Would you like to be
the caretaker of the blade?
Yes, O-Sensei.
Then, defeat Shiva,
and the responsibility
will be yours.
Yes, O-Sensei.
Oh, Shiva, one more thing.
You may use only
one finger in defense.
Say, what?
Yes, O-Sensei.
Begin!
[growling and grunting]
[grunting]
- [bones cracking]
- [groaning]
[straining]
[gags and groans]
[coughing and gasping]
Enough!
[groans]
Know yourself first,
then others.
Shiva...
the sword is yours.
[doorbell jingles]
- [thumping]
- [men grunting]
Listen, Richard.
Shiva isn't
the woman you remember.
She's changed.
Yeah. So it would seem.
[Bruce] She's the head of organized
crime in Gotham's Chinatown.
Known for
her ruthlessness and temper.
You haven't put on your Halloween
mask and tried to stop her yet?
I'm... working up to it.
[men grunting]
[all cheering]
Hey!
[grunting]
[groans]
[all laughing and cheering]
[fighter] Yeah!
[whoops] All right, yeah!
Winner! That's me! [laughs]
You dishonor my house.
Nothing dishonorable
about winning, darlin'!
Then, you should have
no problem defeating me.
Fine. Have it your way.
[all cheering]
[man] Give me
20 bucks on Shiva.
- [woman] Get him!
- [fighter laughing]
[growls]
[grunting]
You're gonna pay
for that, Shiva.
[man yelps]
[growls]
[all laughing]
Come on, then.
[grunting]
[all exclaiming]
This grows tiring.
[groans and gags]
[gurgling]
[all cheering and applauding]
Bruce, Richard.
I assume you're
in some kind of trouble.
You could say that.
Kill them.
[all screaming]
[grunting]
You know how to use those?
[grunting and groaning]
Bruce, this would be a great
time to put on that mask.
What mask?
Bruce has this mask.
He puts it on and it's like
he's a different person.
You're the Batman?
Can you both concentrate!
They're here
for the sword, Shiva!
[tires screech]
- No!
- We're not done yet.
[tires screech and car honks]
They're getting away.
Not for long.
[groans]
[yelps]
[tires screech]
That's handy.
[siren blaring]
[car honks]
He's heading for the overpass!
[gun fires]
- [gun fires]
- [tires screeching]
Is that what I think it is?
[sternly] Shiva, no!
[grunts]
Where's the nearest onramp?
Through the park.
- [crickets chirping]
- [car revving]
[blade whistles]
[grunts]
Shiva, get in.
They have the sword.
We failed.
Only if we quit.
Suggestions?
Ben.
[car door closes]
Master, the door
at the far end
of the monastery,
why is it forbidden?
You said there were
no secrets with family.
It is the place
where all destinies converge.
It is why I am here,
and someday,
if you train hard enough,
it will be
why you are here too.
That doesn't make any sense.
Ha! Since when did
I start making sense?
Geez, Ben.
Maybe try to chew your food
instead of inhaling it?
It takes a lot
to look this good.
Oh, no, you didn't.
There better be some rice left
in that bowl, chump,
or you and I
are gonna have to talk.
Sorry, I got the last of it.
I'd be happy to share.
[bowl clangs]
I don't need
your charity, fool!
What I need is for you
to know your place.
And where's that?
Behind me.
You think we're supposed
to give you a break
- because Mommy and Daddy got killed in front of you?
- [grunts]
Huh? Happens every day
in my neighborhood,
only it don't make the paper.
You only get what you earn.
And from where I'm standing,
you ain't earned
nothing, turkey.
[grunts]
O-Sensei, we have to stop them.
No, they need this.
Plus, my TV is on the fritz.
Come on.
Oh, you wanna go?
[both grunting]
[groans]
Where do you think
you're going?
All right, rich boy,
I ain't ever gonna turn down
whooping somebody's ass.
[both grunting]
- [Bruce exhales]
- You had enough?
[groans]
Not even close.
[both grunting]
Stay down.
[struggled grunts]
[grunts]
[panting]
You're crazy, man.
I can respect that.
[groans]
I got you.
Come on, white rice,
let's get you patched up.
You know what's strange?
I'm kind of hungry.
[chuckles]
Getting your ass beat
does work up an appetite.
[both chuckling]
[Bruce] Ow!
[train whirring]
[indistinct chatter]
[sobbing]
- You okay?
- I can't do it.
I'm not strong enough.
Who says?
- No one. I just--
- That's right.
No one.
When I was a kid,
I didn't think I was
strong enough either.
I thought,
if I trained hard enough,
acted tough,
that was gonna be all it took.
But it's not.
Martial arts is not about
mastering a punch, or a kick.
It's about mastering
what's in here,
and here.
So that when things are hard,
when you don't know
if you're strong enough,
you can reach inside
and remember the truth.
What's that?
The only thing stopping you...
is you.
[train screeches]
- I'm ready now.
- Hell yes, you are.
[Richard] The student
has become the teacher.
Why do I get
the distinct feeling
that you're not here to enroll?
They found The Gate.
And they have the sword.
They?
Let me get my coat.
[train whirring continues]
[Jade] I don't know
why he can't ever
just give me a straight answer?
He always has to be so cryptic
and mysterious.
[Richard] Come on, you should
be used to it by now.
I bet
he hides his most secret
techniques behind that door.
[Shiva] Or riches.
Ancient jewels and gold,
hoarded over time.
I bet it's something powerful.
Something he's too
afraid to use.
[Ben] You're all wrong.
It's probably a Whirlpool.
A luxury spa room
to help him achieve Nirvana.
Shut up.
[all laugh]
What about you, Bruce?
Got any ideas?
Yeah, it's obvious.
Really? Do tell.
It's a distraction.
Good night.
[Ben] I'm still betting
on that Whirlpool.
[distant woman screaming]
What was that?
[footsteps approaching]
Jade and Rip are missing.
So is Soul Breaker.
[Jade screams]
Quickly!
Be on guard.
Jade!
What have you done?
[Rip] What you have been
too afraid to do, old man.
Why do you think I came here
so many years ago?
For your teaching?
I came for The Gate.
The Gate?
What's he talking about?
What O-Sensei
is too afraid to tell you,
is that there is a god
on the other side of this Gate.
One that will make
the world right again.
He calls to me.
And I...
I will be the vessel
of his divine power.
There is no god
on the other side, Rip.
Only a demon.
You have to stop.
Stop before
it's too late, my son.
It's already too late.
The Gate requires
a sacrifice to open,
a soul.
And the sword...
is the conduit, the key.
Stop! Stop, you fool.
Do not open that Gate.
You're the fool, old man.
Rip, listen to your master.
[Rip] Oh, Richard,
he was never my master.
[blazing]
Stand back.
[rumbling]
Come! Your servant
welcomes you.
Yes, the heralds
of the great Naga!
I am Rip Jagger,
- your master's humble--
- [demon roars]
No!
[Rip groans]
[bones cracking]
[demon roars]
This is what
I've trained you for.
[roars]
[thuds]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[roaring]
- [grunting]
- [shrieking]
Hy-ah!
[grunting]
[portal whirring]
[grunting] Die, sucker.
[Ben] Shiva!
[grunting]
- [thudding]
- [grunting]
[hissing]
[grunts]
[demon growling]
Hey, over here.
[grunting]
The door, it's closing.
O-Sensei.
[O-Sensei] It takes
a soul to open the door,
and sacrifice to close it.
[all grunting]
No! O-Sensei,
there has to be another way.
- This is my destiny...
- [Richard straining]
My purpose.
Remember, you are
stronger together than apart.
- Never forget...
- [rumbling, slams]
[demon attacks]
[O-Sensei screams]
No!
We have to find a way back in.
We have to save him.
He's gone, Richard.
Whatever was
on the other side, got him.
[rumbling]
[Ben] Come on, brother,
we have got to go. Come on.
He wouldn't want you
to die with him.
[insects chirping]
[helicopter whirring]
[Eve] The Gate is secure.
And the sword?
It's en route as we speak.
Excellent.
Double the security
around the island.
Nothing can interrupt
the ceremony once it's begun.
[whirring]
- [hydraulic whirring]
- [thuds]
Aww, don't be sacred, children.
Not yet.
[airplane engine whirring]
[beep]
[Richard] Here,
aerial photography of the island.
There's anti-aircraft
artillery all over the place.
Here, here and here.
The place is crawling
with soldiers.
This isn't gonna be easy.
I say we land in the middle
and kill them all.
We're good.
But even O-Sensei
couldn't dodge a bullet.
You sure about that?
[Ben] The tunnels...
Dig this.
There is a series of catacombs
beneath the island
that lead to
the center courtyard.
But getting to it,
I don't know.
What?
There is a vertical cave that
drops a few hundred feet down.
So, we free-fall in,
open our chutes
and we're in business.
The entrance in 10 feet wide.
Oh.
Then we don't miss.
How is it that you know
so much about
this island, Benjamin?
I've been here before.
In fact...
it's my fault
we're in this mess.
[Ben] After what happened
to O-Sensei,
I needed to work
some stuff out.
[Ben grunting]
[man groans]
- [grunting]
- [groaning]
Aah!
[Ben] I came across
a cobra symbol.
It was identical to Rip's.
That's when I learned
about the Kobra Cult,
a worldwide organization
of murderous zealots.
They had temples
all over the globe.
Deeper I dug,
the more I found.
And I meant to stop
every damn one of 'em.
Each one led me to someone
higher up in the food chain.
[grunting]
I smashed their
operations all over the world.
[grunting]
In fact, Kobra started
getting a little scared of me.
[grunting]
I'd become
a sort of Boogeyman.
I read a file about some one
hassling those Kobras.
What did they call you?
Black Samurai?
Naw, man.
I was the "Bronze Tiger."
- Ah.
- Nice.
I like it.
[Ben] Turns out,
these cats believe
in some obscure prophesy.
Some chosen one.
A messiah of such power
that he can became the avatar
of their great snake god.
A dude names Jeffrey Burr.
[bones cracking]
- [Ben grunting]
- [swords clashing]
[thuds]
[Ben] All I had to do
was kill him.
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
[shuddering]
[Ben] He was just a kid.
I just couldn't do it.
I left. Came home.
Started to teach.
Help these kids
like O-Sensei helped me.
I forgot all about Kobra.
You did the right thing.
- [Shiva] Did he?
- Shiva.
If he had slit that
little bastard's throat,
none of us would be here.
He was an innocent.
So was Hitler,
once upon a time.
But give me a time machine,
and I'd toss his bassinet
into a volcano.
Enough.
What's done is done.
Let's focus on the mission.
We're near the drop zone.
Time to get ready.
And lucky for you,
I brought supplies.
[Ben] Tight.
Listen, we need every advantage
we can get out there.
So you damn well better be
wearing that outfit of yours.
[door whirrs]
[whooshing]
[all grunting]
The opening's about
a half a klick that way.
Let's go.
[hurried footsteps]
[footsteps approaching]
[Schlangenfaust] No use hiding.
I know you're there.
Please come out.
Move!
Unless you want me to add
your bones to the others.
Such spirit.
I will take great pleasure
- in watching you die by my hands.
- [hissing]
[hissing]
What the funky hell?
Please.
Do come closer.
[grunting]
[both grunting]
[groaning]
You really shouldn't
have done that.
- His hand.
- I can see that, Richard.
No, the other one.
[roaring]
So... No blades.
[growling]
[grunting]
[demon hissing]
Ha!
[grunting]
[groaning]
[growls]
Richard, Shiva,
[grunts] get topside.
Ben and I will take care
of these two.
The sword.
At last.
The time has come
for the great Naga
to walk this Earth.
No borders, no countries,
no politicians trying
to hold us down.
One king.
One ruler.
One god.
[Jeffrey] Take solace,
my children.
Your sacrifice
will not be in vain.
[whimpering]
[strangled cry]
I want my sword back.
Kill them!
[ninjas yelling]
[all grunting, groaning]
Hy-ah!
[groaning]
[Jeffrey] Stop them.
King Snake, Lady Eve,
do your duty.
[sword slashes]
I'll take the girl
Her look offends me.
- [sword slashing]
- [both grunting]
The infamous Richard Dragon.
And you are?
Sir Edmund Dorrance.
But you may call me...
King Snake.
I think I'll call you
"dead meat."
[grunting]
I can smell your fear.
[exhales]
[gasps]
[struggling] No, no, no.
Please, no!
[Schlangenfaust grunts]
[both grunting]
[hissing]
[roaring]
[both grunting]
[exhales]
[groans]
[screams, groans]
[rumbles]
[demon growls]
[roars]
[grunts]
[Ben] We can't keep doing this.
I might have something
that could help.
Mace? Against them?
Worth a try.
Hang on.
[hissing, growling]
[roars]
[Schlangenfaust screams]
Burn, baby. Burn.
[agonizing shrieking]
Next time, pack something
with a punch.
[Shiva grunts]
[Lady Eve grunts]
[both grunting]
[straining]
[grunts]
[struggled grunts]
[scoffs] Fool.
You gave up your weapon.
[wind whistling]
I am the weapon.
[sword slashes]
Aah!
[grunting]
[groans]
It's no use.
You're as loud
as a bull in a china shop.
[grunting]
[exhales]
[clatters]
[King Snake grunts]
[groans]
Argh!
- [pebbles clatter]
- [grunts]
[grunts]
[agonized scream]
My god is coming.
And when he does, you will die.
[grunts] You hear me?
You will... [groans]
Be waiting to kick his ass.
[metal door opens]
Lead them to
the jungle, quickly.
Wait.
When you're far enough away,
push this button.
Help will find you.
[indistinct chatter]
- Did you take care of "snake hands"?
- Damn right.
[boy whimpering, panting]
- [struggling]
- Don't come any closer.
Help me! [crying]
- [struggling]
- [whizzes]
[whimpers] Aah!
Your sacrifices are gone.
Your men, defeated.
You're finished.
No.
My god will come for me.
[Richard] You don't
wanna meet your god.
Trust me.
You're wrong.
I'm the chosen one.
It's my destiny.
That's what
they had you believe.
You were a child
when they took you.
They told you,
you were special.
But it's all a lie.
This whole thing is a lie.
No. [softly]
No!
Give me the sword.
Without a soul,
it won't open anyway.
Don't you think I know that.
[grunts]
No!
[wincing]
I am the chosen one.
He will save me.
You'll see.
He will...
Oh, God! [groans]
It burns!
The sword. It hurts.
No!
- [spirit roaring]
- [screaming in pain]
[whirring]
Get ready.
Whatever comes out of there,
we have to stop it.
No matter what.
[wailing]
For O-Sensei.
[thuds]
Master?
You're alive.
Yes.
[grunts]
Something like that.
I can feel your master,
scrabbling in the back
of my mind.
He's so disappointed in you.
Ben Turner, with his
uncontrollable anger.
Shiva, who failed
to guard his blade.
[scoffs] Bruce Wayne,
the perpetual child,
who thought
he could defeat evil.
And Richard...
Oh, Richard.
The plans he had for you.
[Batman] Who are you?
The one which was foretold.
The great Naga.
The harbinger of destruction.
Listen...
Even now my hordes are
making their way to The Gate
ready to lay waste
to your soft world.
Release our master.
[laughs]
There is no release.
There is only death!
[all grunting]
[groans]
It is time to bring your world
to its knees before me.
[grunts]
[evil laughter]
Good... Good.
Your master
has taught you well.
But it won't be enough.
[groans]
[struggling]
[Shiva grunting]
[Ben grunting]
[groans]
Argh!
[footsteps approaching]
[grunting]
[groans in pain]
[Batarang whizzing]
Hmph!
- Bruce.
- [Shiva groans]
O-Sensei has shown me
you are the least skilled
of them all,
though he admires
your determination. [chuckles]
Your private battle
to save Gotham.
Uh, but... the truth is,
you are just a sad little boy
trying to quiet
the ghosts of the past.
You should have heeded
your master's words.
Evil is eternal.
I'm coming for your world.
And you are powerless
to stop me.
- [beeping]
- [explosion]
What are you
going to do, Bruce?
[Batarang whizzing]
[slashing]
- [beeping]
- [explosion]
What do you have
that your comrades don't?
[Batman] A cape.
[muffling]
[struggled muffles]
[bone cracks]
As I said... sad.
[grunts]
[groans]
[groaning]
You don't deserve
to look like him.
- Don't worry.
- [choking]
This form is just temporary.
I can only exist in your world
with a proper shell.
Haven't you figured it out yet?
That to stay in this world,
I need an avatar.
[groans, gasps]
Someone strong enough
to hold my spirit.
Your O-Sensei was a clever one.
Hiding him in plain sight.
A young boy,
trained in the ways of war.
His true destiny
hidden from him.
The one who can
hold the great serpent.
The one they call... Dragon.
And here you are...
right in front of me.
It is your destiny.
I can give you power
beyond your imagining.
Purpose.
Isn't that what
you always desired?
[Richard] No.
You have such power
in you, Richard.
[groaning]
O-Sensei knew it.
You are the only one strong
enough to contain my spirit.
[groaning]
[panting, exhales]
[pants]
If I'm the only one
strong enough to hold you,
then I'm the only one
strong enough to defeat you.
[grunting]
Heh! You cannot defeat me.
Yeah, I think I can.
This is my destiny.
To be the best fighter
there is.
And no one...
Not even some
second-rate demon god
is going to stop that.
[grunting]
[straining]
[growling]
[groans]
[straining]
I had hoped
you would come willingly.
[straining]
But no matter,
I will take you by force.
[whizzes, beeps]
[explosion]
Richard!
[grunts]
[O-Sensei] You can't
destroy me, Richard.
I am forever.
- My soul will live on...
- [straining]
For eternity.
Soul, did you say?
No.
[rumbles]
[pained growl]
[pained shriek]
[groans]
Richard...
You are more than I...
I could ever hope for.
Thank you, my son.
[footsteps approaching]
And Bruce...
your parents would be proud.
[hurried footsteps]
[Shiva] O-Sensei.
Then it's over.
No.
We have to close The Gate.
Yeah. About that.
It needs a sacrifice to close,
and well...
I have a lot to atone for.
No, I should go.
O-Sensei left me the sword.
It is the honorable thing
to do.
You're both wrong.
This is my burden to bare.
Where's white rice?
You think I'm gonna
let your jive ass
take all the glory?
- Get out before they--
- [portal door rumbling]
[slams]
- You shouldn't have--
- Please.
I've had enough
of men telling me
what I should and shouldn't do.
We're in this together, Bruce.
Just like we've always been.
Like we're supposed to be.
We are "the Dragon."
[Ben sniffles]
Are you crying?
- No.
- [sniffles]
[demons roaring]
All right then.
Let's get it on.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org