Previously on WandaVision...
We are an unusual couple, ya know?
My wife and her flying saucers.
My husband and his indestructible head.
Hello, dear.
I'm Agnes, your neighbor to the right.
You're like a walking computer.
What? I most certainly am not.
Dinner with Mr. Hart
and his dear lady wife, Mrs. Hart.
What brought you here?
- How long have you been married?
- Why did you come here?
Damn it, why?
Stop it. Stop it.
Vision, help him.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
What was that?
Wanda?
Yes, dear?
Are you using your powers
to turn on the light?
Yes, dear.
Allow me, sweetheart.
What do you see?
Only your lovely rose bushes.
That's all?
Are you using your night vision, Vision?
I assure you, my love,
I see nothing amiss.
You have absolutely
no reason to be frightened...
You were saying?
Actually, I did overhear
a couple of lads at work
remarking on a few unsavory characters
settling in the neighborhood.
Now, who knows
what those ne'er-do-wells might be up to?
Robbing houses, vandalizing property.
Walking through walls,
moving objects without touching them.
Wanda, darling, you can't be suggesting
my colleagues were referring to us.
One of us should really
determine the source of that sound.
Yes, one of us should.
Oh, this is getting ridiculous.
I'm going to take a look.
Oh, God! Darling!
Well, I think we handled that well.
Yes, I must say
I'm rather proud of myself.
And look how you seized
on the opportunity to redecorate.
- This is better, isn't it?
- Mmm.
Wanda, darling?
Yes, dear?
Get the light.
WandaVision!
WandaVision Wa-WandaVision
Ladies and gentlemen, for my final trick,
I bring you the Cabinet of Mysteries.
- Darling, that's your cue.
- You said, "Cabinet of Mysteries?"
I said, "The Cabinet of Mysteries."
Oh, that's my cue. Ooh!
Holy Toledo!
Darling, do all the other acts
in the talent show
have such elaborate props?
Are you kidding?
Fred and Linda are building a moat
and a fully-functioning portcullis
and no one even knows why.
Let's keep going.
Yes, yes. Where was I? Um...
Watch closely as I, Illusion,
Master of Enigma,
make my captivating assistant,
Glamour, disappear.
You really are very dashing.
Mmm, thank you, darling.
Fear not, Glamour.
For I, Illusion,
vow to bring you back exactly as you are.
Abracadabra!
Ta-ta...
Yes, um, Wanda, you're not at all worried
that the audience might just see
through this little charade?
Well, that's the whole point.
In a real magic act, everything is fake.
Darling, the talent show fundraiser
is the most important event of the season
and it's our neighborly duty
to participate.
Plus, it's our chance to appear
as normal as possible while doing so.
Well, I don't think
that should be a problem.
This is our home now.
I want us to fit in.
Oh, darling, we do. We shall.
And we're gonna knock their socks off,
especially with you wearing this.
Oh, that's actually
the rest of your costume.
Oh!
Well, I better get going
If I'm gonna make
the planning committee meeting.
That's me off as well, actually.
There's a gathering
of the neighborhood watch
at the public library.
And after last night's excitement,
I want to make sure
this town's security is up to snuff.
That's a swell idea.
You tell those tree branches who's boss.
Would you look at us?
Wanda and Vision, Westview fitter-inners.
I'll see you at curtain call.
Look, it's the star o' the show.
Agnes.
I'm sorry. What did you say?
Oh, I brought my pet rabbit.
For your magic act.
Yes, of course! Thank you, Agnes.
We will take good care of him.
Señor Scratchy just loves the stage.
He played baby Jesus
in last year's Christmas pageant.
Oh.
Oh, morning, Dennis.
Morning, Agnes.
Stick 'em up.
Don't shoot. I'm just a messenger.
Pew-pew!
Mmm.
- Shall we?
- Oh, we shall.
So, are you ready to meet Queen Cul de Sac
and her Merry Homemakers?
Agnes,
Dottie can't be as bad as you say.
Hmm, well, you'll notice
her roses bloom under penalty of death.
Wanda, can I give you
a bit of friendly advice?
Is it about the way how I'm dressed?
Yes, but it's too late for that.
Dottie is the key
to everything in this town.
Country club memberships, parties,
school admissions...
Well, let's not
get ahead of ourselves.
You get in with Dottie and it'll be
smooth sailing from here on out.
Just mind your P's and Q's
and you're gonna do just fine.
Or maybe I could just be myself?
More or less?
Oh, Wanda, that's good.
Everybody, hurry up please.
Hiya, Dottie! Your roses are divine.
Well, thank you.
The Rotary Club is finishing
the stage set-up as we speak.
They've given the gazebo
a fresh coat of paint
and will be installing the final
decorations all through the town square.
And if you recognize
the antique footlights,
it's because they're from my store.
And the chairs?
I'm sorry, Dottie.
I didn't ask about the chairs.
So you better not ask me if you can
chair any committees in the future.
The devil's in the details, Bev.
That's not the only place he is.
As you all know, the talent show
is the sole fundraiser
for Westview Elementary.
This might help.
In the eight years
since I founded our little club,
this event has gotten
bigger and better every season.
Say, those pants are peachy keen.
Do you really think so?
The other ladies are in skirts.
I was worried.
We only have a few hours until show time,
so a little less cross chatter
and a little more focus.
Okay.
Those little boys and girls
are counting on us.
All of this is for the children.
"For the children."
So, I want you all
to give yourselves a big hand...
...at the appropriate time, of course.
But first let's review event etiquette.
Dress code is upscale garden party...
The only reason I didn't clap
is because I'm afraid to move.
Yeah.
I actually don't know what I'm doing here.
I'm starting to feel that way myself.
I'm Wanda.
- I'm, uh... Geraldine.
- Hi.
And I'm irritated.
Tickets for tonight
are completely sold out.
Now, you can clap.
And stop.
Really, how is anybody doing this sober?
- Let's say green.
- Yeah.
I mean, the other side could be dirt.
Pardon me.
Is this the neighborhood watch meeting?
Oh, hiya, Vision.
Didn't expect to see you here.
This is sort of
a "members only" type deal.
Ah! Certainly. Right. Well...
I'll just stay here
and be as quiet as a church mouse
till you open up the floor
for new business.
Well, in truth,
we were just getting to new business.
Oh, splendid! Could you tell me
how often you rotate security patrols?
Do you interface directly
with local law enforcement?
What are your protocols for threats
such as burglary,
graffiti, and reckless driving?
- No, Vision.
- I know these are indeed grave matters.
"New business"
actually means another round of Danish.
Raspberry or cheese-filled?
Oh, neither for me, thank you.
I don't eat food.
What I mean to say is that I don't eat
food in between meals but at mealtimes.
I'm a regular eating machine.
Hey, fellas.
Vision here has got a point.
Now, listen up. I got some
top secret intelligence for you.
Oh, excellent.
Now, you know
how Johnson's been braggin'
about that treehouse
he built for his kids?
Yeah.
It's a prefab job.
That blockhead can't even swing a hammer.
I can do you one better.
You know those bowling trophies
Arthur's always polishing?
He bought 'em all
at a yard sale in Hackensack.
I knew it. I've never once seen him
down at the lanes.
I too have
some top secret gossip to share.
Norm here's a Communist.
Vision, you're a real cut-up.
You know, I always
thought you were kind of a square.
Me? No, I'm as round as they come.
Hey, care for a stick o' Big Red?
Well, hold on there a second.
Didn't you hear the man?
He doesn't eat food.
Is gum food?
Well, my understanding
is that it's purely for mastication.
No, I don't do that.
Well, when in Westview... Cheers.
Who knew you were such a funny guy?
And to think you came here all hot
and bothered about protocols and nonsense.
We actually thought you were serious.
He's funny.
All right, so, back to this barbeque.
That is why you never do
a seating chart on an empty stomach.
Golly, you're a whiz
at all this committee stuff, Dottie.
Thank you for choosing me to help
you clean up today. I feel so lucky.
You are.
I can't help but wonder if you and I
haven't gotten off
on the wrong foot, Dottie.
And I would like to correct that if I can.
And how would you do that?
I've heard things about you.
You and your husband.
Well, I don't know what you've been told,
but I assure you
I don't mean anyone any harm.
I don't believe you.
Wanda. Wanda, can you read me, over?
- Wanda?
- Who is that?
Wanda?
Who are you?
Wanda.
Who is doing this to you, Wanda?
Wanda? Wanda? Wan...
Dottie!
You... Oh!
Pop quiz, Wanda.
How does a housewife
get a bloodstain out of white linen?
By doing it herself.
They say a man is never fully-dressed
without two important accessories.
His special lady...
and his Strücker.
Strücker. He'll make time for you.
Glad I don't have to follow this guy.
Huh? What?
Oh, but you're gonna be great.
What time is it now?
Mmm, two minutes
after the last time you asked.
I don't know where he could be.
Oh, is that him?
Well, it looks like
he's got a little hitch in his giddy-up.
Whoa!
Wanda, my little cabbage,
you look smashing!
Whoa!
- Vis.
- Hmm.
- Where have you been?
- Oh.
Uh, well, me and the boys were playing
a rather thrilling
game of horses with shoes.
No, that's not it.
Shoe horses! No.
Ah! Horse's shoes.
Listen, something strange
happened with Dottie.
Well, something strange happened
before that, too. It's hard to explain.
I was just playing with his shoes.
What is going on?
You are!
Huh?
I want to thank you all for coming out
to support Westview Elementary,
"For the children."
And for our final act...
I give you, Wanda and Vision.
Hey! Hey! You're up, Cowboy!
What?
Oh! Yeah! I've to go!
Hello, Westview! Good afternoon.
It's so lovely to be...
I'm so sorry. Excuse me.
I am Glamour and this
is my delightful assistant, Illusion.
I am Glamour and he's Illusion.
Yeah, what she said.
Today, we will lie to you and yet
you will believe our little deceptions
because human beings are easily fooled
due to their limited understanding
of the inner workings of the universe.
Flourish!
You just do it,
you don't say it out loud, honey.
And now my wife and I will delight
in your dumbstruck little faces.
Flourish!
Ha! See there? He's using a rope.
Wanda, what's... Oh, no!
Oh! No! Wanda, please!
- Darling, let me down!
- Oh!
I'm feeling pukey!
Ooh!
Uh, what's next?
Oh! Yeah, this is...
This is gonna be great!
A staggering feat of strength.
- Ah?
- Illusion... Uh... Uh...
- Illusion, Master of Enigma, allow me.
- Yeah?
What?
Oh!
Whoops! You weren't supposed to see
how we did that trick.
That was my grandmother's piano.
Oh, Sherbert! Yeah,
this is my old mate, Sherbert.
Stand up, Sherbert.
Say hello to the crowd.
It's Herbert, Herb.
Pipe down, Sherbie, and pick a card.
Any card.
Yeah, put it back in the deck.
I'm not looking. All right. Watch this.
Is this your card?
Uh, no.
I beg to differ.
Mmm-mmm.
Really? Is this your card?
- Vision...
- Mmm-mmm.
Is this your card? Is this your card?
- Is this your card?
- Mmm-mmm.
Argh! Is this your card?
Is this your card?
- No. No. No. No.
- Is this your card?
Is this your card? Is this your card?
Is this your card?
Oh, it is!
It is what?
It's my card.
Well, pardon me, Herb. Have it back.
Oh, no, you did the trick right.
Well, of course I did the trick right!
I'm Illusion!
Flourish!
And now, for my next trick...
Oh, goodness me.
Who stole my hat?
Oh! Oh, stop that rabbit!
I gotta need to pull a hat out of it.
Señor Scratchy's got real star quality,
don't you think?
Maybe we leave the poor bunny
out this one, shall we?
Well then,
I will just have to pull this hat...
...out of myself.
Vision, no.
I'm doin' it.
Ah-ha!
If only you all knew our secret.
Oh!
Is that how mirrors work?
Shut up, Bev.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
for our grand finale.
I bring you, The Magnet of Crysteries!
The Cabinet of Mysteries!
Yeah, yeah. What she said.
I will now make my wife...
...disappear.
Are you sure you don't want an audience
volunteer named "My husband Ralph?"
No. Abracadabra!
- Uh, sweetheart?
- Yeah?
- Hi.
- Oh.
What's in the box?
What's in the box? What's in the box?
Yeah, what's in the box?
What's in the box?
Oh!
Oh, yes!
Flourish.
Let's get outta here.
Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- I'm so stupid.
- Vis? Vis, it's all right.
It's all right.
It's all right. It's all right.
But what is going on with you?
I have no idea.
I've been feeling weirdy all day.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Oh!
Would you look at that?
That really gummed up my works, didn't it?
Hmm.
I'm not as funny without it, am I?
Well, you're back to yourself
and that's all I care about.
Now, let's get out of here before Dottie
and the planning committee
string us up for ruining the show.
You two, stop right there.
Nothing like what you two just did up here
has ever happened
in the history of our talent show.
Dottie, we are so...
Hilarious.
That was the most hilarious act
we've ever seen.
Wouldn't you all agree?
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
You two, come on up. Come on.
On behalf of the planning committee,
I would like to award you
with the inaugural
Comedy Performance of the Year.
Oh, thank you.
- I have to ask.
- Hmm.
One second, I'm backstage and in the next,
I'm in a dark cubby hole.
How'd you do it?
Oh, a magician never reveals his secrets.
He leaves that to his assistant.
And she's not talking.
I had a feeling you'd say that.
"For the children!"
You were tremendous, Glamour.
As were you, Illusion.
I don't know what I was so worried about.
It wasn't so hard to fit in after all.
And all we had to do was be ourselves.
Well, with a few modifications.
- And it was all for the children.
- For the children.
Well, I think the children
might need some popcorn.
Wanda.
Hmm, what?
Vision... Is this really happening?
Yes, my love.
It's really happening.
If it's that damn tree again,
I am going to rip it out by the roots!
I don't see anything.
What is that?
Wanda.
No.
Vision... Is this really happening?
Yes, my love.
It's really happening.
Vision...
Wanda?
Who's doing this to you, Wanda?
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org
Watch Full HD Movies & TV Shows