To be a husband
and a father again...
that's all I've ever wanted.
There must be no question
that Diana is a de Clermont.
And with this mark, you're
forever a member of our family.
Madam de Clermont, such a
recent blood vow is deafening.
A vampire
is murdering warmbloods.
Whoever is doing this
is infected with blood rage.
Our priority has to be the
missing pages from the Book of Life.
It's possible that Diana
Bishop's aunts already have it.
I have reason to believe
they're being sheltered.
A witch
born to daemons.
If you ever go near
my grandchild again,
I'll kill you
with my bare hands.
Sleep now.
Diana will unite
all creatures.
and she will avenge me!
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app
Oh, she's gone.
I don't know what to do.
I can't believe
Em's gone.
I can't imagine the baby
not knowing her.
Two heartbeats.
Two babies?
Yes.
These children
are our future.
The Congregation will
never harm our family again.
I promise.
Welcome home,
old friend.
It's been far too long.
Gallowglass,
welcome.
It looks like
we have another guest.
It's so good
to see you.
Hey, it's only been a
few days for you, Diana.
Some of us have been
waiting centuries.
This is
the darkest of days.
When Peter Knox
murdered Emily Mather,
he killed a woman that
was like a mother to my wife.
He killed a woman that
was truly beloved by Sarah.
He killed a woman
who was under the protection
of the de Clermont family.
And, therefore,
Peter Knox has brought
about, his own end.
Knox has powerful allies. Let's consider
the consequences before we take action.
None as powerful
as the de Clermonts.
Killing him will be too easy.
It'll make him a martyr.
People need to know what
he did and not just to Em.
That's why Mum's
on her way to Venice.
She's told Baldwin to hold an
immediate meeting of the Congregation,
so she'll have a chance to tell the
truth about what really happened here
before Knox and Gerbert
can twist it.
And they will. They'll
portray us as the aggressors.
I'm afraid they'll use what's been
happening in Oxford for the same ends.
What has been
happening in Oxford?
There's been
a series of killings.
They've rather captured
the imagination of the press.
They're calling them
"The Vampire Murders".
And for once,
the newspapers are right.
The victims were killed
by a vampire with blood rage.
A lot has been happening while
you were in the 16th century, Matthew.
Gerbert will use this
against you.
I thought I should
introduce myself.
There hasn't really been
the right moment until now.
I'm Phoebe Taylor.
Marcus and I... I know what you are
to each other, Miss Taylor.
Right, well, I only wish we were
meeting under better circumstances.
Indeed.
Now there is a
great deal to be done
and Marcus has many
important responsibilities, so...
I am well aware
of my responsibilities.
Really?
As Grand Master of the Knights
of Lazarus, your primary task
is to, at all costs, uphold
the sanctity of Sept-Tours.
And you think I failed?
Knox shouldn't have been allowed
to get within ten miles of this place.
You make it sound like he went
unchallenged! Marcus could have been killed.
Emily was killed!
Matthew, enough!
You know, I always used to take
your disappointment personally.
But I'm finally beginning to understand
that nobody's beyond reproach.
Not even you.
Blood rage?
It seems the rumors of its
defeat are somewhat exaggerated.
After all,
there are two blood-raged
vampires just in this room.
You're not
a blood-raged vampire.
You're not.
You... carry the disease.
So you thought it was okay
to lie to me for centuries?
There was no need
for you to know.
That wasn't
your decision to make.
Hey.
Why was Em
at the temple?
She'd been having dreams.
Nightmares about the page.
Em thought they were
some sort of premonition.
She needed someone
to help her with them.
She needed...
Rebecca.
Mum?
No.
No, Em was against
higher magic.
She told me that any witch who was fool
enough to think they could handle it...
...deserved to find out
they couldn't. The hard way.
You do realize she was
speaking from experience?
Yeah. She didn't
want you to know.
What was
she thinking?
I don't know.
I wish I could ask her.
We could.
We could ask her.
Sarah...
You know
we can't do that.
I can't use my power to
change things in the past.
Not deliberately.
Why not?
Do you think it was Em's destiny
to be murdered by Knox? Her fate?
You think this was
all meant to happen?
No, of course not.
None of this is how
it was supposed to be.
She's meant to be here
with you.
So, I can tell you
both together.
I know these babies
won't fix our problems...
Babies?
Twins.
Twice blessed.
What are they?
Witch? Vampire?
I don't know.
Or something else?
I'll love them
no matter what.
But how will you
keep them safe?
This meeting is at the request
of Agatha Wilson of the daemons.
We relinquish the floor to her.
I'm sure whatever
she wants to discuss is fascinating.
I have the floor,
Gerbert.
However, there is an issue that
needs our immediate attention.
The murders in Oxford.
It's a human matter.
Not for discussion here.
Even when the murders
are the work of a blood-raged vampire?
There hasn't been a case of
blood rage since the 12th century.
I've been tracking the
killer's movements for the last few months.
He's killed six people
in that time.
Humans are quite capable
of violence.
Not like this,
Baldwin. The victims were torn apart.
No human I've ever known
has the strength
to inflict wounds of that
nature. Only vampires.
Do we know who this vampire
is supposed to be?
I tracked and confronted him
after his last kill.
Who is he?
I was fighting for my life.
I didn't see his face.
I didn't recognize his scent.
He's not a vampire I'd met before.
And he's still at large.
This puts all creatures at risk.
We only live safely amongst humans
by not drawing attention to ourselves.
The vampires
must deal with this.
And we will. I will.
Wasn't it your family who assured us
that blood rage had been consigned to history?
I can remember Philippe sitting in that
very chair declaring the scourge defeated!
I can only imagine his disappointment
at the current state of affairs.
Vampires, witches, daemons
mixing, marrying and even mating.
I understand there are
people here today
who are complicit in it.
Yes.
Agatha Wilson's family are breaking
the Covenant even as we speak.
They are at Sept-Tours along
with other daemons, witches,
vampires, and even humans.
Is this true?
Perhaps, Baldwin,
you should see for yourself.
I'm sure you're looking forward
to reuniting with your brother...
and his wife.
Matthew and Diana
are at Sept-Tours?
Yes.
And they arrived home
to find that Diana's aunt,
the witch Emily Mather,
had been murdered
by Peter Knox!
That is not true.
Emily was practicing higher magic
and, sadly, it overwhelmed her.
And how did Marcus Whitmore
come by his injuries?
I was forced to defend
myself. He attacked me.
What were you doing there? How dare you
question my work?
We daemons know only
too well how you all see us.
How you question our
position on this council.
Let's see what we can do with the
little power that you so kindly afford us.
I move that Peter Knox
be removed from the
Congregation for his crimes!
You can demand
whatever you please,
but without a witch or a
vampire to second your motion...
It is an act of war for a witch to
enter Sept-Tours without invitation.
I second the motion.
You still
need a majority.
I'm well aware
of that Knox.
I have served this council
unstintingly for years.
I have ensured the safety of not only
my fellow witches, but all creatures...
All those opposed to Peter
Knox's expulsion from this council?
And those in favor?
What do you think
you are doing?
Peter, you killed
a witch.
Justice must be served.
And with my vote,
the motion's passed.
No! BALDWIN:
Peter Knox,
you are no longer a
member of the Congregation.
You will no longer hold
a key to the chamber.
You will have no power,
no privilege,
and you must remove
yourself and your possessions
from this island
and never return here.
You think that this keeps
your family safe?
Or those at Sept-Tours?
You are wrong.
I'm proud of you.
Listen.
You, Sophie, and Margaret
should leave tonight.
You need to get
on a plane and go.
Knox is dangerous and
he's got nothing to lose now.
I don't want you to
call me or get in touch.
Not until all this
is over.
If I know where you are,
then Peter Knox
can use me to get to you
and our family.
I love you, Mum.
I love you, too.
I don't think I can.
Okay.
Emily,
we offer your spirit light
in every direction.
We offer you protection
along the way.
We release you
from your earthly ties.
And with the path lit
and free from danger...
...we...
We send you
on your next journey.
It didn't feel quite right to attend a
witch's ceremony, considering my history.
They'll be cold
when they get back.
Let's relight the fires and
say our own prayers for Emily.
What I said
about the babies...
I was lashing out.
Your children are
gonna be very special.
She would never let it
fall into Knox's hands.
I will make Knox pay
for all of it.
For everything
he took from us.
From our family.
Where the hell have
you been for the last few months?
London, mainly. Don't lie to me.
I've had people looking
for you and the witch.
I'm not lying, Baldwin.
We were in London.
Just... a few
centuries away.
Is there no end
to the witch's talents?
Not so far, and that witch
is now my wife.
I can only imagine
what Philippe would say. Philippe?
He was there
at the wedding.
I don't believe you.
Well, his blood vow was
his wedding present to Diana.
Now no one can question
her position...
in the family.
The same cannot be said for
everyone you've assembled here.
If you think you're offering
them a place of safety,
you are sadly mistaken.
Peter Knox made sure
of that.
And what he did
demands justice, Baldwin.
I agree and I've already
dealt with him.
He's dead? No. He's been expelled
from the Congregation.
He's lost his job? He
killed someone here at Sept-Tours!
He killed a witch. A member of
my wife's family!
You can't have it
both ways!
If she is your mate and
Philippe's blood-sworn daughter,
then she answers
to this family and me!
And I am ordering you and every other
de Clermont to leave Peter Knox alone.
There are more pressing
matters that need to be dealt with.
The blood rage murders.
Fingers are already being pointed.
I want the infected
vampire found, killed,
and the outbreak contained.
And you're expecting me
to do it?
At a time of crisis, we should
all play to our strengths.
We can discuss how to undo
the rest of the damage over dinner.
Family only.
But do bring
the witch.
I'll be the judge of whether
she is a de Clermont.
I can't help but feel that we've got
the better end of the deal tonight.
I know where
I'd rather be.
I would like to think that
there will never be a time
that we cannot sit down
together as a family.
Even if it means our guests aren't
welcome to join us at the table?
I'll not apologize
for observing the Covenant.
It has been keeping us safe
for centuries.
Do you still believe that?
Of course I do.
Do you believe that
this is what your father imagined
when he established
the Congregation?
I believe that my
father always had the best intentions.
No one questions that,
but the world has changed.
Indeed. There is
a witch at the table,
who bears my father's
blood vow.
There was a time
when that was unthinkable.
Philippe's mark
is an honor,
but it is also
a privilege.
My concern is for the creatures
who are not afforded that.
For them, the Covenant
has outlived its usefulness.
Speaking
against the Covenant
in the house that Philippe de
Clermont built is inexcusable.
We should have been dining in
honor of a lost friend this evening.
We are.
To Emily.
Perhaps we should look
to brighter things.
To my brother's mate
and their unborn children.
Whatever they are.
I seem to remember
that this isn't the first time
a vampire had a child
with a witch.
Matthew may recall
better than I.
What happened
to the child?
It's not relevant.
The witches banished it
along with the mother.
I believe they died
in the desert.
Why would
they do that?
Superstition
and ignorance.
Wasn't that around the time
that you sired Benjamin?
Enough, Baldwin.
I hadn't thought
about him in a long time, but then,
with all the talk of blood rage
at The Congregation
and Gerbert reminding us of
the de Clermonts' involvement,
it did set me thinking about
our family's past exploits.
Well, thank you very much
for supper, Baldwin.
Excuse me, maman. I'm sure I'm
not the only one who has had their fill.
One more thing.
Anyone who is not a de Clermont
should leave this house by morning.
The Congregation is watching and as de
Clermonts, we will uphold Philippe's covenant.
Look, it's clear.
We can't stay here.
We'll leave for London
first thing. All of us.
Who is Benjamin?
Another de Clermont?
Not exactly.
At the end
of the first crusade,
I was in Jerusalem.
Philippe dreamt of establishing
a homeland for creatures,
but in order to do so, it was
necessary for us to reveal ourselves
to some humans that
we thought we could trust.
And, Benjamin
was one of them.
So when Benjamin threatened
to expose us all,
it crushed
Philippe's dream.
Well...
I lost control.
Matthew,
I think I met him.
No, no, that's not possible.
In Bohemia.
He said he could hear
Philippe's blood vow.
But he called himself Fuchs.
Not de Clermont.
He certainly didn't say
he was your son.
He's not my son.
Not in any true sense.
By God, I wanted
to punish him.
Death would be
too quick.
I made him a vampire,
so that he couldn't reveal our true
nature without revealing his own.
And then...
I abandoned him.
A new blood-raged vampire.
I thought it would kill him
eventually or get him killed.
It was the most
terrible miscalculation...
So, this place is as welcoming
as I always remember.
Especially with Baldwin
in residence.
Yeah. Just like his father. A
right bastard when he wants to be.
I know.
We're not meant to say a word
against the great man on this...
hallowed ground.
Philippe wasn't always the
easiest man to get along with.
Why do you think
my father and Fernando
struck out on their own
and formed a scion?
Maybe history needs
to repeat itself?
Any male with full-blooded
children can establish a scion,
which will be a branch of the
original family, but with autonomy.
And think of who
we can take with us.
Everyone you've sired,
Matthew. Everyone they've sired.
Our children.
Baldwin will never see the
problems that the Covenant cause us
or stand up
to the Congregation.
But if we establish a scion,
we can chart our own path.
Marcus, you are asking me
to disregard the history
and the family who
made me who I am.
You ask too much.
My answer is no.
We have enough problems
without splitting our family.
They're all leaving.
Matthew and Marcus as well.
It would appear so.
I'm surprised you're
not going with them.
Another hollow victory.
If Matthew crosses the line,
I won't protect him.
Goodbye, Baldwin.
This will not end well.
Bem-vindo,
Matthew. Welcome home.
Fernando.
I knew I could
rely on you.
You were there for me
when we lost Hugh.
Thank you.
Who's that?
He was mated
to Matthew's brother Hugh.
So you think the page
itself can give us some answers?
Miriam, the pages
are made from the skin of creatures.
I want to see if it's even
possible to extract the DNA.
It might tell us more about
the evolution of creatures.
Our possible extinction.
Maybe even the underlying
cause of blood rage.
If we can trace it back
to its origins then...
perhaps we can begin to
understand what activates it.
Why does it lie dormant in
some vampires and not others?
The Book of Life, species decline,
blood rage. Somehow this is all connected.
We need a lab.
Somewhere discreet.
I think I know someone
who could help with that.
Okay. He said
he'd meet us here.
Chris.
Oh!
Hello, stranger.
Where the hell
have you been?
It's a long story.
It better be a good one. You don't
call. You don't write. You don't email?
I know. Uh, things got
a little complicated.
Dr. Christopher Roberts.Dr.
Matthew Clairmont.
Really? Your paper on cell
cycle regulation was interesting.
You finally got yourself out the library
and got yourself a boyfriend, huh?
Uh... Husband.
Married to a Brit?
French.
Any more surprises?
Uh, well, we're expecting
twins.
It really has been
a long time.
So where's this lab?
And you are?
Dr. Shepherd.
Perhaps we can do the
formal introductions on the way.
Shall we?
So, this is my place.
What do you think?
Is the equipment
well-maintained? It's state-of-the-art.
Hmm.
Miriam runs my research.
And what
is that exactly?
I mean, Diana was pretty vague
about your current interests.
I could do with a little more detail
before I, uh, take this project on.
What am I
looking at here?
Why don't you
tell me?
There's some damage
to the blood cells.
Viral?
No, genetic.
But it's not anything
I've seen before, is it?
No.
I thought
you might need a coffee.
No one talks about Em.
It's blood rage
and scions.
You vampires always
look after your own.
Do you know who
Hugh de Clermont was?
He was Philippe's
eldest son.
Hugh and I were mated.
For six centuries.
But Philippe refused
to recognize our union.
And when Hugh died,
neither my loss, nor my grief
were acknowledged.
When did he die?
Seven hundred years ago.
I'm sorry
for your loss.
Grief never...
really goes away.
It gets
quieter, slower...
and sometimes it comes
rushing back like the sea.
The de Clermonts
accepted you and Emily.
More than that they...
embraced you.
And they recognize your loss.
They should recognize yours.
I live in hope.
You're asking me to believe
in witches and blood-raged vampires?
I mean,
you realize how this sounds?
I mean, sure,
as a scientist,
I'm trained to suspend disbelief
until something is disproven,
but without any evidence, you're
asking a hell of a lot from me.
I know.
Are you working on a
molecular level when you do that?
Okay, uh...
What do you need?
What these groups
have in common
is that they're all, in some
way, suffering decline.
Vampires can no longer sire.
Witches' powers are waning...
And daemons seem to be
slipping into actual mental illness.
And there
is a killer on the loose.
We need a cure
for blood rage.
Do you think you might
be able to help with that?
I can give it
my best shot.
What do you have to say that couldn't
be said in front of the Congregation?
This blood-raged vampire.
All the murders in Oxford were very
close to where Matthew and Diana had been.
Photos from the crime
scenes. All the victims.
Why would he be following
Matthew and Diana?
This is just another attempt
to smear the de Clermonts.
The killer stole
their portraits.
Miniatures painted in the 16th
century. Nothing else was taken.
You denounce me,
now you're helping me. Why?
No, I denounced the
blood-raged killer. Not you.
Gerbert used it
to attack me.
Gerbert, not me.
I don't have to be
your enemy.
When did they get back?
I'm leaving now.
Auf Wiedersehen. Auf Wiedersehen,
mein Herr.
This is my DNA.
I'm a vampire.
Philippe
charged me to look after Diana.
I've spent her whole life
keeping her safe.
And Diana is
with Matthew now.
He is not here. I'm sure he'll turn up.
And when he does, you'll
let me know, won't you?
You can't control me
anymore. Your time is over.
Even the de Clermonts' secrets
come out eventually.
It's about time Matthew de
Clermont learns who he's dealing with.
Diana Bishop.
Father Hubbard,
why are you here?
You left something
in my keeping.
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app