I don't want any
surprises out there today.
"9-1-1 Lone Star,"
all new Mondays.
And check out our other Fox
shows "9-1-1," "Prodigal Son,"
and "The Resident," only on Fox.
It all comes down to this.
The next 60
seconds are critical.
There can be no hesitation.
No second-guessing.
Are you ready?
It's a word game.
There's gonna be
second-guessing. And third guesses.
I'm just making a point, okay?
I'm sure you'll do great.
Judd, tell 'em how
much we up by.
We're up by nine.
The Ryders are up by nine.
Nine words in a minute?
Okay, well, we should
change the name of this game
to " Mission Impossible," then.
Are they always like
this during game night?
Insufferable? Yeah. Yes.
Crush them, please.
Please. Please crush us.
I got this.
- Please, please.
- Right.
- Ready?
- Okay, let's go. Okay.
Have fun with that one.
Okay, TK's fourth birthday.
Bronx Zoo. Second cutest animal.
- Meerkat.
- The third cutest.
- Aardvark.
- Yes!
Okay.
Famous American outlaw.
Al Capone. John Dillinger.
- Jeff Goldblum.
- Okay, no.
Bruce Springsteen's
most underrated ballad.
"Ballad of Jesse
James." Jesse James.
Yes. Yes! Yes. Okay.
I am terrified of...
Male-pattern baldness. Bacne.
Rachel Maddow.
Pennywise the Clown.
Yes, yes! Score it. Okay, good.
Leningrad. Carrot Top.
Squash ball. Molly
Ringwald. Marianas Trench!
Yes!
- How is this possible?
- Wait, wait, wait.
No, we are experiencing
a full-on mind meld here.
- Come on, just one more.
- Okay.
One more. You got this.
Okay, beautiful place in France.
- Paris.
- That we never got to.
Riviera!
No, no, no, no, no!
That ain't fair.
- Whoo!
- That ain't fair. No.
Is it because you
have been dethroned?
Because they've
been married so long,
they have an unfair
advantage... it's obvious.
I'm pretty sure
we've been divorced
longer than anyone
here's been married.
Which is why they
never stood a chance.
Wait, I don't follow.
I don't really
understand either.
What, you think
you know each other
when you say "I do"?
Forget it.
You really start to
learn who someone is
when you are sitting
across the table from them
in a deposition carving
up your life savings.
And you know how
their mind really works
and how cunning and
ruthless they can be.
Wow. I'm blushing.
No, but I mean,
divorce has been better
than couples' therapy for us,
'cause when we were
together, we were miles apart.
Now we're not together,
and we've never been closer.
So I think there
should be a term for it.
Somebody should come
up with a term for people
who are better
together not together.
There is a term for that.
It's friends with benefits.
Who wants to play Scattergories?
Right? That's a good idea.
Girl, I got you. Yes.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Let's go, Marj!
Get off!
That's it.
- Let's go!
- Ooh.
Ooh!
Let's go, Marj!
Come on, ref!
What are you, blind?
How do you miss that elbow?
Wait, here it comes,
here it comes.
She's about to bring the pain!
That's my girl!
Yeah! Go, Firefox!
- Yeah!
- Good job, six!
Go, Firefox! Yeah, Marjan!
Whoo!
Looks like Marjan's got a fan.
Guys, enjoy.
Thanks.
Hello.
What can I get for you?
Three IPAs, a mineral
water, and an iced tea, please.
You're thirsty.
Only four of those are for me.
I've seen you
here before, right?
Yeah, were you here the night
that Kitten Crusher got impaled?
I was one of the
firefighters that responded.
Firefighter. Sign me
up for the calendar.
And his boyfriend is a cop.
Cool.
Well, that was aggressive.
I think it's the atmosphere.
But I do like people
to know you're mine.
Well, then I think we
should come here more often.
Maybe we should.
Thank you.
She come out yet?
Not yet.
Feels like maybe we aren't
the only ones waiting for her.
I keep telling her to make
her social media private.
You don't get three million
likes by being private.
Or creeps showing
up after your games.
You think he's a creep?
Marjan.
What do you think?
How did you know I'd be here?
Instagram.
Surprised?
Hey, Marj?
Everything good here?
Yeah. Yeah.
These are my friends
from work, Paul and Mateo.
This is Salim.
So you know this guy.
Only our whole lives.
You Marjan's
brother or something?
Salim's my fiancé.
Hi, guys.
How's it going?
Marjan got engaged.
What?
No way.
Congratulations.
So when did this happen?
When we were 12.
Excuse me, ladies and gentlemen.
If I could have your
attention for just one second.
Then you can get
back to drankin'.
I'm Drew.
I'm Jeff's best man.
You may recognize me
from the wedding just now.
Jeff and I have been best
friends since third grade.
We've shared everything.
And now I get to share
in your greatest joy.
You found a really
great girl in Kelsey.
You're just lucky
you found her first.
Kelsey
you know, I've never
seen Jeff so happy.
I really do love
you for loving him.
We love you, too, brother.
You know, seeing the two
of you together makes me...
Makes me...
Makes me.
I'm so...
My God!
But is it even legal?
I mean, 12 years old?
Doesn't that make
you, like, a child bride?
They're engaged,
not married, Probie.
You do realize that half
the marriages in the world
are still arranged?
I did not know that.
But, like, you don't
even get a say?
It's not like my parents
drew his name out of a hat.
Our families have
known each other
since our grandparents
immigrated here.
We have similar values.
We're a good match.
We were babies together.
That almost makes it weirder.
You know, you should
probably stop talking now, Probie.
Can he, though?
From what we can tell,
only the guests
who had fish got sick,
though I can't say we got
a lot of compliments
on the chicken either.
Score one for red meat.
What are you
thinking? Salmonella?
Not if it all came out
of the same kitchen.
Scombroid poisoning...
Improperly stored seafood.
Nancy, radio dispatch.
Tell 'em all RA
units need to bring
as much Zofran, saline,
and Epi as possible.
Captain, can I
borrow a few hands?
Marjan, Mateo, Paul,
assist the captain.
Help! Help, please!
Please, please, please!
No, they're still in there.
Who who’s in there?
Jeff and Kelsey,
the bride and groom.
Okay, you get yourself
taken care of with medical.
You don't look good.
We'll take care of your friends.
No, I'm okay.
I got most of it up
all over the bride.
Coming in.
Hello?
Over here! Over here, over here!
Thank God.
We we tried Toto lift
it, but it was too heavy.
Hey, Cap, these
trusses are aluminum,
but they're bearing the
weight of all these lights,
so he's got, like,
900 pounds on him.
All right.
Hey, Jeff. How
you doing? Big day?
Yep.
Can you tell me where it hurts?
Pretty much everywhere.
I think my leg's broken.
All right, let's
secure this area.
Get some saws and
some gas masks.
Gas masks, Cap?
Yeah. Can't you smell it?
- Okay.
- So how long is he in town for?
Who?
Your fiancé.
The guy you're totally into
and haven't seen in a year.
He flies back to
Miami on Monday.
So kind of a surprise visit?
He's been meaning to
come visit once I got settled.
So there's no
particular occasion?
I am always the occasion.
It is a little odd, though,
that you've never
mentioned him before.
It never really occurred to me.
- What?
- Okay, maybe it's not that odd.
I mean, I didn't
see a lot of heat
- coming off you two last night.
- Seriously? You too?
It's not a cultural
thing, all right?
It's just an observation.
I just didn't peg
you two for a couple.
No, you thought
he was my stalker.
I thought he was your brother.
Guys, your thinking
is so Western.
When you marry for chemistry,
there's a 50% divorce rate.
You know why ours
is ten times lower?
Because we don't
start with heat.
We believe that love is
something you grow into.
That's kind of
beautiful, actually.
So when's the big day?
Hell if I know.
He still has to
finish dental school,
and we agreed to hold off
the wedding and our parents
until we'd established
ourselves as individuals.
You gonna have a
big to-do like this?
Hopefully a lot less vomit.
Does that mean you'll
move back to Miami?
Eventually.
It's years away.
Is it?
Let's get him out of here.
One, two, three.
Is he gonna be all right?
You may have to
postpone the honeymoon,
but he's gonna be fine.
Well, we've waited this long.
A little while longer
won't kill us, right?
Somebody get
her a chair, please.
No, I'ml'm fine.
Really, I’m it’s okay.
Not if you had the fish.
She didn't. She's vegan.
You were in there when
the tent came down.
- Were you hit on the head?
- No.
But you're feeling nauseated?
She's been sick all week.
Maybe she's pregnant.
I mean, my cousin Sophia
barfed at her wedding.
It was morning sickness.
Also at her graduation.
It can't be that.
We're proudly waiting
until the wedding night.
Right, babe?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you,
but I didn't want
to ruin our wedding.
Wait, hold on. You're
pregnant? Why didn't you tell me?
Why would she tell you?
Because it's not your business!
How is it not my business?
How is it your business?
- My God.
- Okay.
Let's get him to the ambulance.
You're gonna have to
get him an ambulance!
I'm gonna kill you, Drew!
I was saving myself!
See?
Bad match.
All right, everybody,
hit the showers.
Gladly.
And what am I supposed
to do with these turnouts?
Burn 'em.
Is it weird that I'm hungry?
- Hi, Gwyn.
- Hey, Gwyn.
Gwyneth. What
are you doing here?
Hey, Owen.
Did you bring
processed snack cakes
into my firehouse?
It's a Ho Ho, and I
found it in the cabinet,
hidden behind the kale
chips, but I sniffed it out.
You sniffed it
out? Like a truffle?
Who brought processed
sugar into my kitchen?
I'm assuming
everyone who isn't you.
What are you doing here?
You have a minute?
If a bell doesn't go
off, I got a minute.
So, remember the other night
when you were talking about how
whatever this
thing is is working
because we're
together not together?
Please don't make
me explain that.
That sounded so much
better when I was a little drunk.
No, I just want to
know, what is this thing?
- "Thing"?
- Us. This.
We're having that talk.
No, it's not
that talk. It's a talk.
Right now, in the
middle of my shift?
A bell has not gone off.
And yet you've
come out swinging.
Well, I'm just looking
for a little clarity.
When you asked me to stay,
you said we should
see where this would go.
Yes, yes, I did say that.
So where did it
go, or is it still going,
or how do we know
when it gets there?
You are really
putting me on the spot.
Well, that is not my intention.
I just thought that was
the beginning of a dialogue,
not the end of one.
Are we having fun?
Yes, fun. Yeah, it's been great.
I just want to
know what to call it.
Why do we have
to call it anything?
I mean, we know what this is.
- Do we?
- Yeah.
It’s it’s... it's us.
It’s it’s... this.
You're gonna need more
clarity than that, aren't you?
Yes, Owen, that would be nice.
I am running a
Manhattan law firm
from 1,700 miles away
and carrying a
two-bedroom in So Ho.
Yeah, there are
practicalities to consider.
I'm not making any
demands or ultimatums.
I just really
looking for some...
- Some clarity.
- Clarity. Yes.
Yeah. No, I think
we're... I think we're clear
on the
clarity.
Is this time-sensitive?
After a certain age,
most things are.
Then I will do
some thinking on it.
Great. That is all I'm asking.
I'm not making any
ultimatums, nothing.
No, no, no. I totally hear you.
Okay.
Well, I should probably go.
You smell a little like vomit.
Are you sure I got it
all off? I can still smell it.
- Can you sniff me?
- I ain't sniffing you, Probie.
Hey, Marj, you good?
Salim just texted.
He wants to go for dinner
before he heads back.
He's making reservations
at Osteria Cielo.
Baller move.
Place is nice.
Wait, so why do you look like
someone just drowned your puppy?
This is a big deal.
We've never been on a
date without a chaperone.
Unmarried couples
aren't really supposed to.
He's here for a reason.
Yeah.
Reason? What reason?
He's tired of waiting.
I think you might be right.
Tired of waiting for what?
The man is here to
claim his bride, Probie.
What?
No. We had a deal.
He's supposed to
finish dental school first.
I mean, do we even know
what kind of grades
he's been getting?
This is wrong.
You can't move to Miami now.
You said we still
had a few years.
I thought we did.
- Wow. Back to Miami.
- Maybe, yeah.
I guess that was always the
plan once they got married,
but I just think
Marjan expected it
to, you know, happen after
she was 30 or something.
Kind of a long time to wait.
For him, I mean.
She's very beautiful.
Yeah, I would not be
able to hold out that long.
Yes.
I recall the 15
minutes after we met.
So why does it have to be Miami?
We have teeth in Texas.
Why can't he open up
a dental practice here?
Well, both their
families are in Florida.
Family. Right.
No, I-I get it.
Take a lot to leave that behind.
Would you?
For the right person, sure.
You're kidding me...
What? What is it?
Carlitos.
Hey!
Mamá. Hi, Dad.
Are these your parents?
Well, you wouldn't
know by the way
this one still hasn't
hugged his mother.
Come here!
So nice to finally meet you.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Mom, Dad, this is my friend TK.
We work together.
You're police, too, TK?
Firefighter, actually.
Well, I won't hold
it against you.
He will. Dad's a Texas Ranger.
So, since when do
you eat micro greens?
Ever since he gained
his quarantine 15.
Mira
he's running out of
notches on that belt.
Fat-shaming isn't
okay anymore, Mom.
Yeah, well, tell that
to his hypertension.
Why do I need a belt
when she wears the pants
in the family anyway?
And at 15 bucks a bag,
I should arrest
them for larceny.
Come on, mi amor.
I see Swiss chard
with your name on it.
The only thing I want
charred is a nice rib eye.
See you Sunday at Tia Lucy's.
For sure. Love you guys.
Nice meeting you, TJ.
Yeah, you too.
So that was a little weird.
Our specials this evening are
a saddle of venison
with a pistachio crust
and a Sicilian branzino
on a bed of pappardelle.
That all sounds amazing.
I'll give you a couple
minutes to think about it.
Can I bring you anything
from the wine list?
Just an iced tea for me, thanks.
I'll take an Old Fashioned,
with rye instead of bourbon.
- Excellent choice, sir.
- Thank you very much.
"With rye instead of bourbon"?
Who is this guy?
Don't look so surprised.
You always knew I was a bad boy.
Seriously, though, I've
never seen you drink before.
- We've always had a chaperone.
- True.
What would the parents
say if they could see us now?
My dad would show all your
Firefox videos to the waiter.
"5 million likes, this one.
And we used to walk
her to the nursery school."
Your parents are the best.
I miss them. How've they been?
Much better lately
other than giving me
the biweekly full-court
press on grand kids.
Thanks again, by the way,
for leaving me with both sets
and running off to a
different time zone.
You will always be my hero
for holding down the fort.
I feel like a Jordanian
Davy Crockett
defending the Alamo, and
no reinforcements are coming.
You know he died, by the way.
Read about it in an
in-flight magazine.
Well, the Alamo's just
an hour down the highway.
We can go if you want.
I know the parents are a lot,
and they've probably been
squeezing you to set a date,
but I'd rather we just
stuck to our time line.
Just a few more years.
Five years.
Five more years.
Yeah, like we
always talked about.
When we're 30.
I feel like I'm just
getting my footing here.
I know. I know. I
follow you on IG.
I see how happy you are at work,
the new mosque, now
with the roller derby.
I’d never ask
you to give that up.
Really?
Really.
So are you saying
you'd move to Austin?
It is a very nice town.
But you have two years
of dental school left.
How would that work?
It wouldn't.
Look
I know you're not
ready to get married,
but I am.
Just not to you.
Wait. Are you
breaking up with me?
Answer me one question, Marjan.
Have you ever
been in love with me?
What? Of course I love you.
No, that's not what
I asked. In love.
I mean mean romantically.
I mean passion.
"Passion"? What, did
you read The Notebook
- on the plane, too?
- I'm serious.
In all the years we've
known each other,
have you ever felt one
spark when you looked at me?
- We've never been about sparks.
- Really?
B-because let me tell you
what I feel when I look at you.
I feel the world getting warmer.
The walls get closer.
I-I lose my breath
when I look at you.
You should probably
get that checked out.
And of course you make a joke.
Well, what do you
want me to say, Salim?
That you feel
something, anything?
Do you know how
soul-crushing it is
to be the one
who's always pining?
Well, maybe I don't swoon
every time I'm near you,
but those kind of feelings
will grow with time.
Will they?
Because I've had them
for you since I was ten.
It was love at first sight.
And, quite honestly, I'm
not comfortable gambling
that after two decades,
you'll suddenly
catch feelings for me.
But we made a commitment.
I don't want to be with
someone who's only with me
because someone else
made a promise for them
when they were 12.
But we are such a good match.
I met someone.
What do you mean
you met someone?
I met someone else, Marjan.
Someone else.
What did you lovebirds decide?
Why are you so mad?
- I'm not mad.
- Really?
Then why didn't you
say more than two words
the whole drive home?
I thought you
were talking to TJ.
Seriously? Is that
what this is about?
My mom gets people's
names wrong all the time.
And you didn't
correct her, Carlos.
I will next time.
No, you didn't correct
her 'cause it didn't matter
and you don't think there
is gonna be a next time.
Stop it. What are you doing?
"Friend from work"?
You know, if I was
your friend from work,
then what we did this morning
was very unprofessional.
Yeah, HR would definitely
have its hands full on that one.
I'm sorry.
I just wasn't expecting
to run into them.
Yeah, and ever
introduce me to them.
That's not true.
I thought you were out to them.
I am.
Wow. Well, that's even worse.
You're out to them, and
you still didn't tell them
I was your boyfriend.
It's more complicated than that.
How complicated
can it be, Carlos?
Look, not all of us were
raised in Manhattan with parents
who couldn't tear the
closet door off fast enough.
My parents are more traditional.
I just don't like to...
rub their noses in it.
"Rub their noses in it"?
You didn't want to rub
their noses in the fact
that you have
somebody who loves you
and that you
supposedly love back?
I freed some more space
in your closet, Carlos.
You're up early.
I had an early
meeting with Shanghai.
No, I mean before that.
It seemed like you
were up in the night.
No, I don't think so.
Seems like you were restless.
Not restless. I
slept like a stone.
A restless stone.
Like a rollin' stone.
So now we're awkward?
This is the awkward stage?
I don't think so.
Because if every time I attempt
to have some kind of
conversation with you
we get three days of
awkward, it's gonna be less fun.
Well, I want it to be fun.
It should be fun.
Let's make it fun.
- TK.
- Morning.
- When did you get home?
- Last night.
I thought you were
staying at Carlos'.
We're in quarantine.
From each other.
Honey, what happened?
We got in a fight.
- You want to talk about it?
- Not really.
It's not good to keep
things bottled up.
Your father is so right.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
We ran into his parents,
who I've never met,
and I've been
dying to meet them,
and he introduced
me as his friend.
No, he did not.
Well, maybe he's
not out to them.
He's out to them.
Well, what did you
want him to do?
Not treat me
like I didn't exist.
I wanted him to tell them
who I was and
what I mean to him.
Maybe he did. Maybe
we are just friends.
With benefits.
You're more than that.
I mean, we've all
seen you together.
Why does he have to make
some official announcement?
I just want him to
acknowledge what we are.
That is so reasonable.
Is it?
You're having
fun together, right?
Yeah, of course.
You're not seeing anybody else.
- No.
- And you have history.
Those years count for something.
Months, but okay.
My point being,
what does it matter
what label somebody
wants to put on something?
It matters, because if
you can't agree on one,
it indicates deeper problems.
But if you force someone
to put a label on it
and they're not ready,
you can create a problem
where there isn't one.
Well, if that creates a problem,
it suggests to me
underlying conditions.
The real issue is, do you
feel safe in the relationship?
You can have all
the fun in the world,
but if you don't feel safe,
you're never gonna be happy.
So you're saying
I'm being too pushy?
What? No, I don't
think I said that.
So then I should
force the issue?
Not necessarily.
Okay.
Thank, guys.
Marjan.
So?
So are we gonna be visiting
your wedding registry or what?
Wedding's off.
What? That's great!
I-I'm sorry. Are you sad?
You're sad.
You broke it off?
No. He dumped me.
Bet you didn't see that one
coming, Sherlock, did you?
No. No, I did not.
I
I guess I just never imagined
anyone letting you go.
He met somebody else.
Her name is Madison,
and she's training
to be a periodontist.
You know, I never
liked that guy,
even when he was your brother.
It's not all his fault.
Eventually anybody gets tired
of being a friend
with no benefits.
Wait, you you guys never...
Probie. Boundaries.
He said I'd never felt a spark.
He accused me of never
having been in love with him,
and the truth is, I never
really thought I was
until he dumped me.
So wait, you... you
are in love with him?
I doubt it'd feel
like my heart's
literally been ripped out
of my chest if I weren't,
so, yeah, I'm in love with him.
I think I have
been my whole life.
How did I not see that
until it was too late?
Maybe because
for the first time,
you didn't feel like you had to.
You need to tell him.
You can't be serious.
Deadly.
You cannot let that man fly away
without knowing
how you really feel.
No.
He made his decision.
I'm not gonna show
up at his hotel room
and humiliate myself.
Look, it's a risk.
Love hurts, Marjan.
But regret
that hurts a lot more.
I think he's right.
I mean, the last thing I
want is for you to leave.
But the heart
wants what it wants.
Okay, you sound
a little far away, sir.
I'm calling with Siri.
Okay. What's your name?
Mistress says I should
only be referred to as Imp.
Okay, Imp.
Um, my name is Grace.
What's wrong with Mistress?
She was stung by
a bee. She's allergic.
I think there's a
hive in the wall.
Okay. She has an EpiPen?
Yeah, but she
was reaching for it
when she collapsed.
All right, I'm gonna need you
to grab it for her, okay?
See, that's the problem.
I'm a little tied up right now.
Rescue 29, I have
a 40-year-old female,
multiple bee stings,
possible anaphylaxis.
Be advised, there may
be a hive in the wall.
Sir, do you know if there's
anyone within earshot of you?
No, Mistress keeps her
dungeon soundproofed.
I suppose it would be.
Is there anybody
else I can call?
No. I'm in Mistress' basement.
She's choking.
She's trying to cough,
but air can't get in.
Okay, listen, I think her
airways are closing up.
Did you say you are
completely bound?
There's no room for
you to wiggle free?
Unfortunately, that's
the point of this position.
What position would
that be exactly?
Hogtie frog legs?
Spread eagle strappado?
"Shouldering the
rifle" is the official term.
Okay. All right, Imp. So
your right arm is the one
that's up above
your head, correct?
- Yes.
- And your hands.
Are they touching in the back,
or is there a gap of space?
- Yeah, there's some space.
- Okay.
Is there anything hard
or sturdy in the room
that's within your reach?
Not really. My feet are bound.
Really? You're
sure there's nothing.
Look all around.
I have enough slack to
reach a couple of rods
that are sticking
out of the wall.
Tell me those rods are
pointing towards you.
- Yeah. Why?
- I do have an idea, Imp.
- It is a bit unorthodox.
- Anything for Mistress.
I need you to take your shoulder
and slam it up
against one of the rods
and dislocate it.
What? No.
I may be a masochist,
but I'm not crazy.
Can't the people coming
here just untie me?
Yeah, I'm afraid they're
not gonna make it in time.
But if you dislocate
the shoulder,
you should be able to bring
your arm up over your head
to untie yourself.
She's turning blue!
Imp, you have to help her.
I can't! I'm afraid.
I don't come here
to be frightened.
I come here to be humiliated.
Well, what a sorry
excuse for a sub.
I-Iwhat?
You're not worthy to be making
this call right now, are you?
Cowering like a
worthless little nub.
Tell me, Imp, what
comes after beta?
Permission to speak, Your Grace?
Permission denied!
See, you've crossed
the wrong queen now.
We both know how
pathetic you are.
You look at baby
carrots with envy.
You haven't earned the right...
To be speaking to me.
Please, Your Grace.
I'll do it. Is it gonna hurt?
Like hell.
And I expect a
thank-you for the pain.
Yes, Your Grace.
Thank you. I freed myself.
Just a minute. Just a minute.
Okay, I got the EpiPen.
Okay, good. Jam it
into her thigh now.
She's alive. She's breathing.
Thank you, Your Grace.
That was amazing.
I didn't feel a thing.
"Fifty Shades of Grace."
What do you say,
Cap? You need a spot?
No, I'm good.
But, you know,
there is something
I wouldn't mind
getting off my chest.
Okay.
So the other night, when
we were all together,
how did Gwyn seem?
Well, hell, Owen, I don't...
She seemed fine. I
don't really know the lady.
Well, I do know the lady,
and I can tell
you, she was fine.
In fact, she was
better than fine.
And I would say, collectively,
over the last couple months,
we have had more
good days than we had
over the entire ten
years of our marriage.
And I think it's because
none of this was planned.
She was gonna come down
here, stay for a week or two.
We didn't know that we'd
be quarantining together.
We didn't know that
we would start having...
The best sex...
All right, I-I get the picture.
And that was the beauty of it.
You know? The spontaneity.
You know, nobody
had any expectations.
And now...
Now she wants to
define what this is.
And you don't want to do that?
Every time I put a
label on something,
it ends up being
an expiration date.
I don't want to
ruin it, you know?
I do.
You want the cream
without having to buy the cow.
No. I didn't say that.
I want the cow.
But I'm not really thrilled
with this metaphor.
I mean, you can call
it whatever you like to,
but what I'm seeing is,
you get all the benefits
with none of the commitment.
What are you talking about?
I'm the one who
asked her to stay.
And she's the one
who left everything.
It's not like she joined a cult.
It's all out there still.
I mean, I guess I can see
why she might not
feel 100% secure.
"Secure."
So is that your
word, or is that hers?
No, I think the word
she used was "safe,"
but she was
speaking theoretically.
Hey, look
you love her?
I never stopped loving her.
She knows that.
Yeah, but does she?
Does she, though?
That's what I'm saying.
Like, I-I would
walk through fire
so that Grace knows I love her.
She knows I love
being married to her.
Right? So that she
knows she's safe.
And then we got you,
sitting next to the woman
that you claim to love,
just going on and on
about what a thrill it is
to be divorced from her.
Yeah, I guess I did
kind of do that, didn't I?
Yeah, like you was
giving a stump speech.
You know what to do, Cap.
Hey.
Hi.
Can I come in?
You've got a key.
Yeah, I thought maybe
you might want that back.
Why? Are we breaking up?
Or did that already happen?
Because it kind
of felt like it did.
No. I mean, I hope not.
Come in.
Okay, look, I know
I was a little bitch.
No, you weren't.
Yes, I was.
And I just wanted to say that
I'm not sorry.
I'm not sorry, Carlos.
I know I made it seem
like your relationship
with your parents was about me,
but really, it's about us.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Not really.
Um...
When you didn't
tell your parents
that I was your boyfriend,
it made me feel insecure
about our relationship
and what I mean to you.
And that kills me,
which is exactly why I was
avoiding introducing you,
because I didn't want
that to happen, and...
I-I knew it would.
Yeah, but did it have to?
I mean, they knew you were gay.
They know, yes.
I came out to them
when I was 17,
and they were shocked.
I-I knew it rocked their
world, but they hugged me,
told me they loved
me, and that was that.
You know what we talked
about the next morning?
The Astros bullpen
the price of unleaded,
a new calf on our family ranch.
Not one mention of what I shared
then or
since.
They seem like such nice people.
They are nice people.
But they're not perfect people.
You know, my parents
may be very queer friendly,
but they're not perfect either.
They just gave me a
pep talk that felt like it was
more about them than about me.
That explains a lot.
There was something
that my mom did say, though.
She said I felt triggered
because I didn't feel
safe in this relationship.
I see.
I'm sorry to hear that.
But you know what
I didn't consider?
Is how unsafe you feel,
and have felt
for so much of your life.
I want you to know
that I am fully on board.
You can tell your
parents I'm your friend,
your colleague,
your personal shopper.
I don't care.
Okay? As long as you need.
And if it never changes?
Well
nothing ever stays
the same, Carlos.
Marjan.
Can I come in?
Yeah. Yeah, of
course. Come on in.
So?
What are you doing here?
Look, I know it's
over between us.
I get it. You made
that really clear.
And, I don't want to
make things weird,
but I can't let you leave
without telling you something.
I love you.
Not because I have to
or because someone made
a promise when I was 12,
but because when I look
at you, the walls get closer,
the world warms up,
and I lose my breath.
Okay.
So I got a little weird.
I've been waiting my whole life
for you to say
something like that.
What's wrong?
I didn't come here for that.
Okay.
Okay, um...
Maybe I'm not exactly
sure what I came here for,
but suddenly I'm starting
to feel like the other woman.
There's never been
another woman.
I think there has,
and her name was
Madison, if I recall.
Okay, Madison
is a wonderful girl,
but she's not you.
She never was.
I can break it off
with her tonight.
Wow. Just like that?
I'm confused. Isn't
that what you want?
Yes.
But that's the problem, Salim.
I can't be with someone
who doesn't honor
their commitments
to their family,
to their values,
to their periodontists
on the side.
- I didn't think you wanted me.
- I know.
I helped put us
in this position,
but now here we are, and,
and I'm sorry.
This really can't
work out now, can it?
No.
I don't think it can.
We were such a good match.
And such bad timing.
Owen?
Dear.
Can you bring my
reading glasses?
I can't see anything in here.
It's Château le Sommet.
I haven't had that since...
Those are stargazer lilies.
And Geneva chocolates.
That's the same...
Setup we had waiting
for us in our wedding suite.
You charming son of a bitch.
16 years ago,
I blew the great
relationship of my life.
And I'll be damned if I'm
gonna do it again, so...
And this time,
we're gonna get to
the French Riviera.
Gwyneth Lynn Morgan,
will you make me the
happiest man in the world
and marry me again?
What?
- No. Get up.
- Wha...
- We're not doing that.
- Wait a minute.
I thought this is
what you wanted.
What do I want
with a wedding ring?
I-I said I needed clarity,
not a proposal.
Okay, I think I'm the one
who needs some clarity.
If you weren't interested
in getting married,
why were you suddenly so intense
on nailing down where
this was all going?
I'm pregnant, Owen.
Sorry?
Knocked up. Bun in the oven.
Two lines on a
pee test. Pregnant.
- Well, that's...
- Ridiculous.
Yes. Surreal, sure.
But, impossible, apparently not.
Well, that clears that up.
See "911 Lone Star."
Don't miss all new
episodes Mondays on Fox.
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN