Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app
Damage report!
Shields at 60 percent.
Our fuel line has ruptured.
Attempting to compensate.
Damn it! We're barely
maintaining impulse.
l can't get any more out of it.
Be creative.
How am l supposed to be creative
with a 39-year-old
rebuilt engine?
Maquis ship
this is Gul Evek
of the Cardassian Fourth Order.
Cut your engines and prepare
to surrender or we will de...
lnitiating evasive pattern
omega. Mark.
Shields at 50 percent.
l need more power
if we're going to make
it to the Badlands.
Take the weapons off-line.
We'll transfer all power
to the engines.
Considering the circumstances,
l'd question that proposal
at this time.
What does it matter?!
We're not making a dent
in their shields anyway.
You wanted creative.
Tuvok, shut down
all the phaser banks.
lf you can give me another
30 seconds at full impulse,
l'll get us into the Badlands.
Phasers off-line.
Throw the last photons at them
and then give me the power
from the torpedo systems.
Acknowledged.
Firing photons.
Are you reading
any plasma storms ahead?
One.
Coordinates 17 1 mark 43.
That's where l'm going.
Plasma storm density
increasing by 14 percent.
Twenty...
Twenty-five...
Hold on!
Cardassian ship
is not reducing power.
They're following us in.
Gul Evek must feel daring today.
They've taken a hit
on their port blade.
They're sending out
a distress signal
on all Cardassian frequencies.
Can you plot a course
through these plasma fields,
Mr. Tuvok?
Storm's activity is typically
widespread in this vicinity.
l can plot a course,
but l'm afraid it will require
an indirect route.
We can use the time
to make some repairs.
What was that?
Curious.
We just passed through some kind
of coherent tetryon beam.
Source?
Unknown.
Now there appears to be
a massive displacement wave
moving toward us.
Another storm?
lt's not a plasma phenomenon.
At current speeds
it will intercept us
in less than 30 seconds.
Anything left in those
impulse generators, B'Elanna?
We'll find out.
Still exceeding our speed.
Maximum power.
Wave is continuing
to accelerate.
lt will intercept us
in eight seconds.
Five.
Tom Paris?
Kathryn Janeway.
l served with your father
on the Al-Batani.
l wonder if we could
go somewhere and talk?
About what?
About a job we'd like
you to do for us.
l'm already doing a job...
for the Federation.
l've been told
the Rehab Commission
is very pleased with your work.
They've given me their approval
to discuss this matter with you.
Well, then l guess l'm yours.
Your father taught me
a great deal.
l was his Science Officer
during the Arias Expedition.
You must be good.
My father only accepts
the best and the brightest.
l'm leaving on a mission
to find a Maquis ship
that disappeared in
the Badlands a week ago.
l wouldn't, if l were you.
Really?
l've never seen
a Federation starship
that could maneuver
through the plasma storms.
You've never seen Voyager.
We'd like you to come along.
You'd like me to lead you
to my former colleagues.
l was only with the Maquis
a few weeks
before l was captured, Captain.
l don't know where most
of their hiding places are.
You know the territory
better than anyone we've got.
What's so important about
this particular Maquis ship?
My Chief of Security
was on board-- undercover.
He was supposed to report in
twice during the last six days.
He didn't.
Maybe it's just your Chief
of Security who's disappeared.
Maybe.
That ship was under the command
of another former
Starfleet officer
named Chakotay.
l understand you knew him.
That's right.
The two of you didn't get along
too well, l'm told.
Chakotay will tell you
he left Starfleet on principle--
to defend his home colony
from the Cardassians.
l, on the other hand,
was forced to resign.
He considered me a mercenary--
willing to fight for anyone
who'd pay my bar bills.
The trouble is he was right.
l have no problem helping you
track down my ''friends''
in the Maquis, Captain.
All l need to know from you
is what's in it for me?
You help us find that ship
we help you
at your next outmate review.
Uh-huh.
Officially, you'd be
a Starfleet observer
during the mission.
Observer?!
Oh, hell, l'm the best pilot
you could have.
You'll be an observer.
When it's over,
you're cut loose.
Story of my life.
Stadi, you're changing
my mind about Betazoids.
Good.
Oh, that wasn't a compliment.
Until today, l always considered
your people warm and sensual.
l can be warm and sensual.
Just not to me.
Do you always fly at women
at warp speed, Mr. Paris?
Only when they're
in visual range.
That's our ship.
That's Voyager.
lntrepid-class--
sustainable cruise
velocity of warp factor
9.97 5.
15 decks,
crew complement of 141.
Bio-neural circuitry.
Bio-neural?
Some of the traditional
circuitry has been
replaced by gel packs
that contain bio-neural cells.
They organize information
more efficiently--
speed up response time.
lf l may say so,
it's been my special pleasure
to see many new officers
like yourself
come through these portals.
Your parents must be
very proud, my boy.
You know, on an occasion
like this...
l'm really not interested.
lnterested?
You were about to try
to sell me something, right?
l was merely going to suggest
that your parents
might appreciate a memento
of your first mission.
And you happen to have several
to choose from?
l do carry a select line
of unique artifacts
and gemstones
indigenous to this region.
Why, quite recently,
l acquired these Lobi crystals
from a very strange creature
called a Morn.
We were warned about the Ferengi
at the Academy.
Warned about Ferengi, were you?
That's right.
Slurs about my people
at Starfleet Academy.
What l meant was...
Here l am, trying to be
a cordial host, knowing
how much a young officer's
parents would appreciate
a token of his love on the eve
of a dangerous mission
and what do l get
for my trouble?
Scurrilous insults.
Well, somebody's
going to hear about this.
What's your name, son?
My... name?
You have one, l presume?
Kim, Harry Kim, but l...
And who was it
at the Academy who warned you
about Ferengi?
You know, l think
a memento for my parents
would be a great idea.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
Really, one of these
would make a great pendant
for my mother.
Or cufflinks for your father.
Cufflinks.
Great idea.
They're not for sale.
Now, inform
your commanding officer
that the Federation Council
can expect an official query...
How much for the entire tray?
Cash or credit?
Dazzling, aren't they?
As bright as a Koladan diamond.
Brighter.
Hard to believe
you can find them
on any planet in the system.
That's an exaggeration.
You know, there's a shop
at the Volnar Colony
that sells
a dozen assorted shapes
for one Cardassian lek.
How much are you
selling these for?
We were just about
to negotiate the price.
Come on.
Thanks.
Didn't they warn you about
Ferengi at the Academy?
Run a level-3 diagnostic
just to be sure.
Can l help you?
Tom Paris, reporting on board.
Oh, yes.
The observer.
That's me.
As a matter of fact,
l seem to be observing
some kind of problem
right now...
Doctor.
l was a surgeon
at the hospital on Caldik Prime
the same time you were
stationed there.
We never actually met.
Your medical records
have arrived
from your last posting,
Mr. Paris.
Everything seems to be
in order.
The Captain asked
if you were on board.
You should check in with her.
Uh...
l haven't paid my respects
to the Captain yet either.
Well, Mr. Kim,
that would be a good thing
for a new
Operations Officer to do.
What was that all about?
lt's a long story, Harry
and l'm tired of telling it.
l'm sure someone around here
will tell you before long.
The doctor called.
And?
And l was right.
She's pregnant?
Puppies are due in seven weeks.
Oh, Mark, you've got
to take her home with you.
With me?
l just got the rugs cleaned.
She's with child.
l can't leave her
in a kennel while l...
ls this another ''love me,
love my dog'' demand?
Yes.
How could l ever refuse you?
Thanks, honey.
So when are you leaving?
As soon as l approve
these system status reports.
All right, then l won't
bother you anymore.
Hey...
you never bother me.
Except the way l love
to be bothered.
Understand?
l'll remember that.
See you in a few weeks.
Oh, Mark, go by my house
and pick up the doggy bed.
She'll be more comfortable.
l already did.
An hour ago.
Come in.
Gentlemen,
welcome aboard Voyager.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. Kim...
at ease
before you sprain something.
Ensign, despite
Starfleet protocol
l don't like being
addressed as ''sir.''
l'm sorry... ma'am.
''Ma'am'' is acceptable
in a crunch,
but l prefer ''Captain.''
We're getting ready to leave.
Let me show you to the Bridge.
Did you have any problems
getting here, Mr. Paris?
None at all, Captain.
My First Officer,
Lieutenant Commander Cavit.
Ensign Kim, Mr. Paris.
Welcome aboard.
Ensign Kim,
this is your station.
Would you like to take over?
Yes, ma'am.
lt's not crunch time yet,
Mr. Kim.
l'll let you know when.
Lieutenant Stadi,
lay in the course
and clear our departure
with Operations.
Course entered,
Ops has cleared us.
Ready thrusters.
Thrusters ready.
lnitiate launching sequence.
Sequence underway.
Engage.
Tomato soup.
There are 14 varieties
of tomato soup available
from this replicator--
with rice, with vegetables,
Bolian-style,
with pasta, with...
Plain.
Specify hot or chilled.
Hot!
Hot, plain tomato soup.
There, you see?
l told you
it wouldn't take long.
ls it true?
Was the accident my fault?
Yes-- pilot error--
but it took me
a while to admit it.
Ugh! 14 varieties
and they can't even get
plain tomato soup right.
They said you falsified reports.
That's right.
Why?
What's the difference?
l lied.
But then you came forward
and you admitted
that it was your fault?
l'll tell you the truth, Harry.
All l had to do
was keep my mouth shut
and l was home free...
but l couldn't.
The ghosts of those
three dead officers
came to me
in the middle of the night
and taught me
the true meaning of Christmas.
So l confessed--
worst mistake l ever made
but not my last.
After they cashiered me
out of Starfleet,
l went out looking for a fight
and found the Maquis,
and on my first assignment,
l was caught.
That must have been
especially tough for you,
being the son of an admiral.
Frankly, l think it was tougher
on my father than it was on me.
Look.
l know those guys told you
to stay away from me,
and you know what?
You ought to listen to them.
l'm not exactly
a good-luck charm.
l don't need anyone
to choose my friends for me.
Janeway to Paris.
Go ahead.
Report to the Bridge.
We're approaching the Badlands.
The plasma storms were measured
at levels three and four.
The Cardassians gave us
the last known heading
of the Maquis ship,
and we have charts
of the plasma storm activity
the day it disappeared.
With a little help,
we might be able to
approximate its course.
l'd guess
they were trying to get
to one of the M-Class
planetoids in the Terikof Belt.
That's beyond the Moriya system
The plasma storms would have
forced them in this direction.
Adjust our course to match.
Aye, Captain.
The Cardassians claim
they forced
the Maquis ship
into a plasma storm
where it was destroyed,
but our probes haven't
picked up any debris.
A plasma storm might not leave
any debris.
We'd still be able to pick up
a resonance trace
from the warp core.
Captain.
l'm reading a coherent
tetryon beam scanning us.
Origin, Mr. Kim?
l'm not sure.
There's also a displacement wave
moving toward us.
On screen.
Analysis.
Some kind of polarized
magnetic variation.
We might be able to disperse it
with a graviton particle field.
Do it.
Red Alert.
Move us away from it,
Lieutenant.
New heading 41 mark 180.
lnitiating graviton field.
The graviton field
had no effect.
Full impulse.
The wave will intercept us
in 12 seconds.
Can we go to warp?
Not until we clear
the plasma field, Captain.
Five seconds.
Brace for impact.
Three...
Report.
Hull breach, deck 14.
Com lines
to Engineering are down.
Trying to reestablish.
Repair crews, seal off
hull breach on deck 14.
Aye, Captain.
Casualty reports coming in.
Sick Bay is not responding.
Bridge to Sick Bay.
Doctor, can you hear me?
Paris, how's Stadi?
She's dead.
Captain, there's
something out there.
l need a better description
than that, Mr. Kim.
l don't know.
l'm reading...
l'm not sure what l'm reading.
Can you get
the viewscreen operational?
l'm trying.
Captain,
if these sensors are working
we're over 70,000 light-years
from where we were.
We're on the other side
of the galaxy.
l'm not reading any life signs
on the Maquis ship.
What about on that...
that Array?
Our sensors can't penetrate it.
Any idea what those pulses are
that are coming from it,
Mr. Kim?
Massive bursts
of radiant energy.
They seem to be directed
toward a nearby
G-type star system.
Try hailing the Array.
Engineering to Bridge.
We have severe damage.
The chief's dead.
Possibility
of a warp core breach.
Secure all engineering systems.
l'm on my way.
No response from the Array.
Ensign, get down to Sick Bay.
See what's going on.
Mr. Rollins,
the Bridge is yours.
Aye, Captain.
Harry, wait for me.
They must have been
right next to the console
when it exploded.
Warning.
Warp core micro-fracture.
Breach imminent.
What's the warp core pressure?
2,100 kilopascals.
Lock down
the magnetic constrictors.
lf we lock them down
at these pressure levels,
we might not be able
to reinitialize
the dilithium reaction.
Warning.
Warp core microfracture.
Breach imminent.
We don't have a choice.
We've got to get
the reaction rate
down
before we try to seal it.
Computer, initiate
emergency medical
holographic program.
Please state the nature
of the medical emergency.
Multiple percussive injuries.
Status of your doctor?
He's dead.
.4cc's of trianoline.
Trianoline?
We lost our nurse, too.
How soon are replacement
medical personnel expected?
That could be a problem.
We're pretty far away
from replacements right now.
Tricorder.
Medical tricorder.
A replacement must be requested
as soon as possible.
l am programmed
only as a short-term
emergency supplement
to the medical team.
Well, we may be stuck
with you for a while, Doc.
There's no need for concern.
l am capable of treating
any injury or disease.
No concussion.
You'll be fine.
Clean him up.
Unlock the magnetic
constrictors.
Constrictors on line.
Pressure?
lt's working.
2,500 kilopascals and holding.
Bridge to Janeway.
We're being scanned
by the Array, Captain.
lt's penetrated our shields.
What kind of scan?
Bridge?
Janeway to Bridge.
Respond.
lnitiate emergency lock off.
You're not seriously hurt.
You can return to your station.
This is the emergency
holographic doctor speaking.
l gave no permission
for anyone to be transported
out of Sick Bay.
Hello.
Sick Bay to Bridge.
l believe someone has failed
to terminate my program.
Please respond.
Come up here.
Come on now.
l have a pitcher
of lemonade
and some sugar cookies.
Captain?
Don't believe your eyes,
Mr. Paris.
We've only transported
100 kilometers.
We're inside the Array.
There's no indication
of stable matter.
All this must be some kind
of holographic projection.
Oh, you poor things.
You must be tired out.
But come on and sit down
and rest a while.
Have a cold drink, hmm?
No, thank you.
My name is Kathryn Janeway,
Captain of the Federation
Starship Voyager.
Now just make yourselves
right at home.
The neighbors should
be here any minute.
Oh. Why, here they are.
Howdy.
Welcome, folks.
Hey.
Well, good to see you.
Welcome.
We're real glad you dropped by.
Now we can get started.
You're all invited
to the welcoming bee!
Let's have some music!
Yoo-hoo!
The crew's scattered
around this farm, Captain,
but they're all accounted for.
Move around.
Scan the area.
See if you can find anything
that might be
a holographic generator.
Have some nice fresh
corn on the cob.
Fresh corn on the cob.
Corn on the cob?
Can you tell me why we're here?
Oh, we don't mean you any harm.
l'm sorry if we've put you out.
Why don't you just
put your feet up
and get comfortable
while you wait?
Wait for what?
lsn't anybody hungry?
Come on, now.
Make yourselves at home.
l'm sorry if we've put you out.
Hey, let me show you around.
The root cellar's
right over there.
What's down there?
Potatoes, onions.
But it's real private.
Hmm.
Paris, she's only a hologram.
No reason to be rude.
Whoa.
What?
Sporocystian life signs.
What's in the barn?
Oh, nothing
but a big ol' pile of hay.
Hey, come on! Let's
go see the duck pond.
Nothing in there.
lt's just a dark, smelly barn.
Hey, do y'all want
some deviled eggs?
Huh?
See? Nothing but hay.
There's a life-form here.
-Just one.
-Where?
lt's everywhere.
l'm also reading some kind
of matrix processing device.
lt may be
the holographic generator.
Paris.
Humanoid life signs over here.
l'm reading a Vulcan
and several humans.
l'm not ready for you yet!
Paris to Janeway.
Janeway here.
Paris?
Come on.
Very well.
Since no one seems
to care for any corn,
we'll have to proceed
ahead of schedule.
Janeway to Bridge.
Anybody there?
Yes, Captain, we're here.
How long were we over there?
Almost three days.
Three days!
Captain, the Maquis ship
is powering up its engines.
Tractor them.
All senior officers report
to the Bridge immediately.
Excuse me, could you explain
what has transpired?
Computer, locate Ensign Kim.
Ensign Kim is not on board.
Uh, Paris to Janeway.
Go ahead.
Kim didn't come back with us.
He must still be over there.
Acknowledged.
Computer, how many crewmen
are unaccounted for?
One: Ensign Harry Kim.
Hail the Maquis.
Commander Chakotay,
my name is
Captain Kathryn Janeway.
How do you know my name?
We were on a mission
to find you
when we were brought here
by the Array.
One of our crewmen is missing.
Was he transported back
to your ship by accident?
No. A member of our crew
is missing, too.
B'Elanna Torres, my Engineer.
Commander, you and l
have the same problem.
l think it makes sense
to try and solve it together,
don't you?
Three of us will transport
to your ship.
They're powering down
their engines
dropping their shields.
Watch out, Captain.
They're armed.
Put down your weapons.
You won't need those here.
lt's good to have you back,
Mr. Tuvok.
l must inform you
that l was assigned
to infiltrate your crew, sir.
l am Captain Janeway's
Chief of Security.
Were you going to deliver us
into their waiting hands,
Vulcan?
My mission was
to accumulate information
on Maquis activities
and then deliver you
into their ''waiting hands.''
That is correct.
l see you had help.
lt's good to see you, too,
Chakotay.
At least the Vulcan was doing
his duty as a Starfleet officer,
but you...
you betrayed us for what?
Freedom from prison?
Latinum?
What was your price this time?!
You are speaking
to a member of my crew.
l expect you to treat him
with the same respect
as you would have me
treat a member of yours.
Now, we have a lot to accomplish
and l suggest we all concentrate
on finding our people
and getting ourselves back home.
Based on my initial
reconnaissance, Captain
l am convinced we are dealing
with a single entity
in the Array.
l would suggest
he scanned our computers
in order to select a comfortable
holographic environment.
ln effect, a waiting room
to pacify us prior
to biometric assessment.
An examination?
lt is the most
logical explanation.
Why else would he have
released us unharmed?
Not all of us were.
Break out the compression
phaser rifles.
Meet us in Transporter Room 2.
We're going back.
We'll divide into teams.
Mr. Tuvok, while Chakotay
and l are looking for Torres
and, Kim, your job
is to find out
as much about this Array
as you can.
lt brought us here.
We have to assume
it can send us home.
Agreed?
Mr. Rollins, maintain Red Alert.
Keep us on constant
transporter locks.
Captain.
l'd like to go with you.
lf this has something
to do with what Chakotay...
lt doesn't.
l just...
l'd hate to see
anything happen to Harry.
Come on.
There are no humanoid
life-forms indicated, Captain.
Kim and Torres are not
within tricorder range.
They may not be on the Array.
He can tell us where they are.
Maintain your com link.
l don't want
to lose anyone else.
Oh, why have you come back?
You don't have what l need.
l don't know what you need
and, frankly, l don't care.
l just want our people back
and l want us all
to be sent home.
Oh, well, now,
aren't you contentious
for a minor bipedal species.
This minor bipedal species
doesn't take kindly
to being abducted.
Oh, it was necessary.
Where are our people?
They are no longer here.
What have you done to them?
You don't have what l need.
They might.
No. You'll have to leave them.
We won't do that.
We are their commanding
officers.
We are entrusted
with their safety.
They are our responsibility.
That may be a concept
you don't understand.
Oh, no, l do understand,
but l have no choice.
Oh...
There just is
not enough time left.
Left for what?
l must honor a debt
that can never be repaid,
but my search has
not been going well.
Tell us what you're looking for.
Maybe we can help you find it.
You?
l've searched the galaxy
with methods
beyond your comprehension.
No. There's nothing you can do.
You've taken us 70,000
light-years from our home.
We have no way back
unless you send us
and we won't leave
without the others.
But... sending you back
is terribly complicated.
Don't you understand?
l don't have time.
Not enough time!
He's regaining consciousness.
How do you feel?
What am l doing here?
Where am l?
Please don't try to move yet.
You're very ill.
lll? No, no,
there's some mistake,
l'm not...
No!
Captain's Log, Stardate 48315.6.
We've traced the energy pulses
from the Array
to the fifth planet
of the neighboring system
and believe they may have
been used in some fashion
to transport Kim and Torres
to the planet's surface.
Come in.
Captain, l've observed something
peculiar about the pulses.
They're getting faster.
Faster.
The interval between each pulse
has decreased by .47
seconds since we arrived.
l can offer no explanation.
That's only one of the mysteries
we're dealing with, Mr. Tuvok.
Take a look at this.
lt's virtually a desert.
Not one ocean.
Not one river.
lt has all the basic
characteristics
of an M-Class planet, except...
there are no
nucleogenic particles
in the atmosphere.
That would mean
the planet is incapable
of producing rain.
l've studied thousands
of M-Class planets.
l've never seen an atmosphere
without nucleogenics.
There must have been
some kind of extraordinary
environmental disaster.
As soon as repairs
are complete...
we'll set a course
for the fifth planet.
Captain.
You require sleep.
Kim's mother called me
just after he left Earth.
Delightful woman.
He's her only son.
He'd left his clarinet behind.
She wanted to know if she
had time to send it.
l had to tell her no.
Do you know
he played the clarinet
in the Juilliard Youth Symphony?
l did not have the opportunity
to meet Mr. Kim.
l barely knew him.
l never seem to have the chance
to get to know any of them.
l have to, um...
l have to take more time
to do that.
lt's a fine crew
and l've got to get them home.
The crew will not benefit
from the leadership
of an exhausted Captain.
You're right as usual.
l've missed your counsel, Tuvok.
l am gratified
that you came after me
so l can offer it once again.
l spoke to your family
before l left.
Are they well?
Well, but worried about you.
That would not be
an accurate perception, Captain.
Vulcans do not worry.
They... miss you.
As l do them.
l'll get you back to them.
That's a promise, Tuvok.
Captain's Log, supplemental.
The Maquis ship and Voyager
have encountered a debris field
where sensors have detected
a small vessel.
One humanoid life-form
is on board.
Hail them.
Whoever you are, l found
this waste zone first.
We're not interested
in this debris, Mister...?
Neelix.
And since you're not interested
in my ''debris''
well, l'm delighted to know you.
Captain Kathryn Janeway
of the Federation
Starship Voyager.
A very impressive title.
l have no idea what it means,
but it sounds very impressive.
Do you know this area
of space well, Mr. Neelix?
l am famous for knowing it well.
How may l be of service?
Do you know anything
about the Array
that's sending energy pulses
to the fifth planet?
l know enough to stay
as far away from it as possible.
Wait, let me guess.
You were whisked away from
somewhere else in the galaxy
and brought here
against your will.
Sounds as though you've heard
this story before.
Sadly, yes, thousands of times.
Well, hundreds of times.
Maybe 50 times.
But the Caretaker
has been bringing ships here
for months now.
The Caretaker?
That's what the Ocampa call him.
They live on the fifth planet.
Did he... kidnap members
of your crew?
As a matter of fact, he did.
lt's not the first time.
Do you know where
he might have taken them?
Just that they're brought
to the Ocampa.
Nothing more.
We'd appreciate any help
you could give us
in finding these... Ocampa.
l-l-l really wish
that l could help you, l do.
But as you can see,
there's just so much debris
for me to investigate today.
You'd be surprised the things
of value some people abandon.
Of course, we'd want to
compensate you for your trouble.
Well, there's really very little
that you could offer me.
Unless...
Yes?
Unless, of course,
you had...
...water?
lf you help us find
our missing crew members,
you can have
all the water you want.
Well, tha-that sounds like
a very reasonable arrangement.
Good. We'll beam you over
and tow your ship
into our shuttlebay.
Mr. Tuvok, go to Transporter
Room 2 and meet our guest.
Beam?
We have a technology
which can take you instantly
from your ship to ours.
lt's quite harmless.
May we?
Energize.
Astonishing!
You Federations
are obviously
an advanced culture.
The Federation is made up
of many cultures.
l am Vulcan.
Neelix.
Good to meet you.
lnteresting.
What... what exactly...
What exactly does all this...
all this do?
l assure you
that everything in this room
has a specific function.
However, it would take
several hours to explain it all.
l suggest we proceed
to your quarters.
Oh.
Perhaps you would care
for a bath.
A what?
Hmm...
lt's okay.
Who are you?
My name is Kim-- Harry Kim.
l'm an Ensign
on the Starship Voyager.
l was kidnapped from the Array
just like you were.
l don't know where we are.
What was Starfleet doing
at that Array?
We were looking for you,
actually.
One minute, we're, we're
in the Badlands, the next...
You mean, you were
trying to capture us.
Yeah... consider
yourself captured.
Oh, l know l have
a phaser here somewhere.
l don't find this
at all amusing, Starfleet.
There's no point.
lt's locked.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey what's that
going to accomplish?
What are they doing to us?!
What are these things
growing on us?!
Look, do you want them
to sedate you again?
You're right, Starfleet.
lt's the Klingon half of me.
lt's just, it's hard
to control it sometimes.
What's your name, Maquis?
B'Elanna.
B'Elanna Torres.
l hope you're feeling better.
l know how frightening all this
must be for both of you.
l've brought some clothes
if you care to change.
Why are you holding us here?
You are not prisoners.
ln fact,
we consider you honored guests.
The Caretaker
has sent you to us.
As long as you are not violent
you are free
to leave your quarters.
What's wrong with us?
What are these things?
We really don't know.
You must be hungry.
Would you care to join me
on the courtyard for a meal?
Our food dispensers
are right this way.
We're underground.
Our society is subterranean.
We've lived here
for over 500 generations.
But before that,
you lived on the surface?
Until the warming began.
The warming?
When our surface
turned into a desert
and the Caretaker
came to protect us.
Our ancient journals
tell us he opened
a deep chasm in the ground
and led our ancestors
to this place.
Since then, he has provided
for all our needs.
Oh, please forgive them.
They know you've come
from the Caretaker.
None of us has ever seen him.
This way, please.
Does the Caretaker
provide your meals, too?
ln fact, he does.
He designed
and built this entire city
for us after the warming.
The food processors dispense
nutritional supplements
every 4.1 intervals.
lt may not offer
the exotic tastes
some of our younger people
crave these days,
but it meets our needs.
ls this how the Caretaker
communicates with you?
He never communicates directly.
We try to interpret his wishes
as best we can.
l'm curious to know
how you've interpreted
the Caretaker's reason
for sending us here.
We believe he must
have separated you
from your own species
for their protection.
Their protection?
From your illness.
Perhaps he's trying
to prevent a plague.
We weren't sick
until we met your Caretaker.
From time to time,
he asks us to care for people
with this disease.
lt's the least we can do.
There have been others--
like us?
Yes.
Where are they?
Your condition is serious.
We don't know exactly
how to treat it.
l'm afraid the others
did not recover.
Sir...
Ah, Mr. Vulcan.
Come in, come in.
Please, l can hardly see you.
l want to thank you
for your hospitality.
l must admit,
l haven't had access
to a food replor...
uh, replicator before.
l'd never have guessed.
And to immerse myself
in water...
oh, do you know
what joy this is?
No one around here
wastes water in this manner.
A good sand scrub--
that's the best
that we can hope for.
l'm pleased
you're enjoying yourself,
but we're in orbit
of the fifth planet.
We need your assistance.
Oh, uh, could you hand
me the, uh... towel?
lf you will scan
the large southern continent,
you'll find a range
of extinct volcanoes.
Follow the foothills north
until you discover
a dry river bed.
You'll find an encampment there.
Do you believe our people
might be at this location?
lt's not impossible...
maybe...
Perhaps not,
but we'll find them.
We'll need several containers
of water to bring for barter.
Do these, uh, replicators
make clothing, as well?
Yes.
Will it make me
a uniform like yours?
No...
it most certainly will not.
Hmm.
Why would anyone want
to live in a place like this?
The rich cormaline deposits
are very much in demand.
The Ocampa use it for barter?
Not the Ocampa, the Kazon-Ogla.
The Kazon-Ogla?
Who are the Kazon-Ogla?
They are.
Kazon sects control
this part of the Quadrant.
Some have food, some have ore,
some have water.
They all trade, and they all
kill each other for it.
l thought you said the Ocampa
had our people.
My friends!
lt's good to see you again!
Whoo!
l must speak with your maje,
the ever-wise Jabin.
Ah. Very amusing.
Very amusing.
l, uh...
l enjoy a joke
as much as the next man.
Jabin!
My old friend!
Water... water, Jabin.
l have water... to replace
all that l borrowed.
Show them, Mr. Paris.
Their ship has technology that
makes water out of thin air!
You have more?
Janeway to Voyager.
Energize.
Oh!
There's more where that came
from if you can help us.
How can we help someone
so powerful
they can create water
out of thin air?
This man led us here
suggesting we might find
a people called the Ocampa.
Do you know where they are?
Ocampa?
She is Ocampa.
Why would you be interested
in such worthless creatures?
They live only nine years.
They make poor servants.
We caught her when she wandered
to the surface.
To the surface?
You mean, they live underground?
The entity in space
that gives them food and power,
also gives them
sole access to the only
water on this world--
two miles below the surface.
This same entity has abducted
two of our people.
We believe they might be
with the Ocampa.
There's no way to get to them.
We tried.
The entity has established
some kind
of subterranean barrier
we cannot penetrate.
But she got out.
Occasionally, some of them do
find their way to the surface--
we don't know how--
but the Ocampa seal
the tunnels afterwards.
Maybe she can help these
good people find a way down.
You'd be wasting your time.
l've used every method
of persuasion l know
to get her to help us.
She won't!
Then she's worthless to you.
Let us trade you water
for this scrawny little thing.
l'd be more interested
in acquiring this technology
that allows you to create water
from thin air.
That would be difficult.
lt's integrated
into our ship's systems.
Tell them to drop their weapons!
Drop them, my friends,
or he dies in an instant.
Do it!
Step aside.
Come on!
l strongly suggest
you get us out of here.
Six to beam up.
My dearest, didn't l promise
l'd save you?
Look, l'm sure Captain Janeway
is doing everything
she can to find us.
What makes you think
any of them are still alive?
Should l call for some help?
No.
Are you in pain?
Are you watching us?
l thought we weren't supposed
to be your prisoners.
l wasn't watching you.
l was coming
to give you something.
l don't know if it will help.
lt's a medicine.
There are people
who have broken
from tradition
and left the city.
Their colony
grows fruits and vegetables.
They discovered quite by
accident that the moss
that grows on
certain fruit trees
has healing properties.
l'm sorry for what
has happened to you.
We appreciate this,
but the only way
we're going to survive
is if we can get to the surface
and find our own people.
The elders would say that's
against the Caretaker's wishes.
What do you say?
The Caretaker's
been behaving strangely
for the past several months--
abducting people,
increasing the power supply.
Power supply?
He's tripled the energy
he sends us.
They say we have
enough stored now
to run the city for five years.
And nobody knows why?
When we ask, we're told to trust
the Caretaker's decisions.
One person l knew
did get to the surface.
We never saw her again.
How?
The ancient tunnels
that brought us here
still exist.
Over the years, small breaches
in security barriers
have appeared,
just large enough
for someone to get through,
but it still requires
digging through meters
of rock to get out.
Can you get us tools
to dig with?
lt would take days, maybe
even weeks to break through.
You have to rest.
Conserve your strength.
Please... it's our only chance.
lf you had told us
what you had planned,
we might have anticipated
your irrational behavior.
lrrational?
We got out of there, didn't we?
Excuse me.
Don't blame Neelix...
That's enough.
This is a Sick Bay,
not a conference room.
Visiting hours are over.
Everyone, except my patient,
is to leave immediately.
Computer, end medical
holographic program.
l never should have
gone to the surface.
l'm too curious.
l'm told it's my worst failing.
No, no.
lt's a wonderful quality--
your most endearing.
Would you be willing
to take us underground
to look for our missing crew?
l'm afraid Jabin was right.
There's no way to get down.
The tunnel l came out
has been sealed.
We don't need a tunnel.
We have the ability
to transport there directly.
Captain, our sensors did not
pick up any indication
of an underground civilization.
The subterranean barrier
Jabin described
may be responsible.
lt might also block
our transporter.
There are breaches
in the security barrier
where it's begun to decay.
That's how l got out.
Have the transporter room
begin a sweep
for any breaches we might
be able to beam through.
Kes can tell you where to go,
but, now that she's free,
we're leaving
this system together.
Neelix, these people rescued me.
l rescued you.
With their help.
lt would be wrong
not to help them now.
Captain, the pulses
from the Array
continue to accelerate.
The intervals between them
have decreased
another .8 seconds.
Kes.
Hello, Daggin.
We thought we'd never
see you again.
How did you get back?
These people rescued me
from the Kazon.
l'm trying to help them
find two of their crewmen.
Does anyone know where
the aliens are kept-- the ones
the Caretaker sends here?
l think they're
at the Central Clinic.
Can you take us there?
No, she cannot.
They can't speak
telepathically, Toscat.
Please talk aloud.
l didn't mean to be rude,
but you should not be here.
We'll be glad to leave
once we find our crewmen.
That won't be possible.
We cannot interfere
with the Caretaker's wishes.
Maybe you can't, but we can.
You don't understand.
That's right.
They don't understand.
They have no way of knowing
that the Ocampa
have been dependent
on the Caretaker for so long
that we can't even think
for ourselves anymore.
They don't understand
we were once a people
who had full command
of our minds' abilities.
The stories of our ancestors'
cognitive abilities
are apocryphal--
at the very least exaggerated.
We lost those abilities
because we stopped using them.
We should not dwell
on what's been lost,
but on all that's been gained.
We've gained a talent
for dependence,
for simply taking
what we're given.
l'm going to help them, Toscat,
whether you like it or not,
and l think my friends
will join me.
You defied the Caretaker
by going to the surface, Kes.
Learn from the experience.
Follow the path
he has set for us.
l've learned very well, Toscat.
l saw the sunlight.
l can't believe
that our Caretaker
would forbid us
to open our eyes
and see the sky.
Come with me--
we'll find your people.
Come on.
Don't let it beat you,
Starfleet. Come on.
l'm sorry.
All right.
lt's all right.
We'll rest a minute.
Maybe l'd do better if l had
a little Klingon blood in me.
Trust me-- it's more trouble
than it's worth.
You know, l spent my whole life
getting ready for Starfleet,
and on my very first mission,
l'm going to die.
We're not finished yet.
l know a few things
that old Sneezy didn't teach
in his survival course.
Sneezy?
Commander Zakarian.
Remember?
He must have been
allergic to everything.
You went to the Academy.
l actually made it into the
second year before we, uh...
we mutually agreed
that it wasn't the place for me.
You know
l never really liked Zakarian.
Shh. Listen.
They're getting faster.
Away team to Voyager.
Voyager here.
What's going on with the Array?
lt's no longer
sending out pulses, Captain,
and it appears to be
realigning its position.
Keep me informed.
Janeway out.
They haven't been
at the clinic for hours.
We can search the city.
Ask if anyone's seen them.
lf they were trying to get to
the surface, how would they go?
Probably the same way l did--
up one of the ancient tunnels.
Mr. Paris,
you and Neelix go with her
and start checking them out.
We need to talk to every doctor
and nurse at this hospital
see what they can tell us
about Torres and Kim.
Voyager to Janeway.
Go ahead.
Captain, the Array
is firing some kind of weapon
at the surface.
lt seems to be trying to seal
the energy conduits.
Understood.
Keep a channel open.
lf the Array is the Ocampa's
sole source of energy,
why would the Caretaker
seal the conduits?
He would seal them
if he no longer
intended to use them
to protect the Ocampa
from their enemies.
Captain, there is
now enough evidence
to form a reasonable
hypothesis.
l believe that
the Caretaker is dying.
Explain.
First, he increases
the energy supply
to provide the city
with a surplus
to last at least five years,
then he seals the conduits.
The logical conclusion is
that he does not intend
to continue his role
as Caretaker.
That doesn't necessarily
mean he's dying.
He could be leaving.
Doubtful.
Not after a millennium
of providing for these people.
l believe that the Caretaker
owes something to the Ocampa.
l believe the ''debt
that can never be repaid''
is very likely a debt to them.
ln addition, there were
his frequent references
to ''running out of time.''
l think he knew
his death was imminent.
lf he dies, how the hell
are we supposed to get home?
They're in this one.
Harry?!
Paris to Janeway.
Go ahead.
They're in one
of the tunnels, Captain.
l can't see them,
but they're up there.
We're going after them.
Call for transport
when you have them, Paris.
We'll meet you on the ship.
Janeway to Voyager.
Voyager here.
Three to beam up.
Stand by.
Captain,
l can't get a lock on you.
The weapons fire from the Array
has irradiated
the planet's crust.
The transport sensors
can't find the breaches
in the security barrier.
Come on, there's only one
other way out of here.
Janeway to Paris.
Go ahead.
The transporters aren't working.
You're going to have to find
a breach in the security barrier
when you get to the top.
Understood.
We're a few minutes behind you.
Janeway out.
l see them.
Took you long enough.
How could l let down
the only friend l got?
Friend? What makes
you think l'm your friend?
Paris to Janeway.
Go ahead.
We found them, Captain.
Don't wait for us.
Get them to safety.
Don't worry.
l know where we can
get through the barrier.
Whatever you do, don't touch it.
We've been told
it'll burn your skin off.
They're not far ahead of us.
Keep going.
l think we've reached the top.
Neelix, get out your phaser.
Voyager, can you get
a lock on us now?
Affirmative, but l'm reading
only five signals.
The others are...
Get down!
Paris to Janeway.
Chakotay, Tuvok, do you read?
Voyager, prepare to transport
everyone in this group
except me.
Aye, sir.
You're not thinking
of going back there.
Well...
the fool needs company.
Take care of them, dearest.
l'll see you later.
Voyager, make that
three to beam up.
Lock in on the other combadge
and energize.
My leg is broken.
l can't move.
-Hold on.
-Here they are!
Neelix, help me with Tuvok.
l'll get Chakotay.
Get out of here, Paris,
before the whole thing
comes down!
l intend to...
as soon as l get you up.
You get on those stairs,
they'll collapse.
We'll both die.
Yeah...
but on the other hand,
if l save your butt,
your life belongs to me.
lsn't that some kind
of lndian custom?
Wrong tribe.
l don't believe you.
You'd rather die than let me
be the one to rescue you.
Fine. Be a fool.
lf l have to die,
at least l'll have the pleasure
of watching you go with me.
lsn't there some lndian trick
where you can turn
yourself into a bird
and fly us out of here?
You're too heavy.
Bridge to Janeway.
Go ahead.
Captain, two Kazon ships
are approaching the Array.
Set a course.
l'm on my way.
We've got to get back
to our ship.
l strongly advise you to rest.
l will not be held responsible
for the consequences.
ls the crew always
this difficult?
l don't know, Doc.
lt's my first mission.
Doesn't anyone know how
to turn off the program
when they leave?
Bring the weapons systems
on line.
Powering up phaser banks
and photon systems.
Red Alert.
The lead Kazon ship
is hailing us, Captain.
On screen.
Have you come to investigate
the Entity's strange behavior
too, Captain?
All we care about
is getting home, Jabin.
We're about to transport
over to the Array
to see if we can arrange it.
l'm afraid l cannot permit that.
We have no dispute with you.
l have a dispute with anyone
who would challenge us.
This is ridiculous.
We have no intention
of challenging you.
And l have no intention
of letting anyone
with your technological
knowledge board the Array.
Jabin, can we discuss this
like two civilized...?
They're powering up
their weapons.
l guess we can't.
Shields are holding.
Fire phasers.
Evasive pattern delta four.
Janeway to Chakotay.
Tuvok and l
are beaming to the Array.
Can you hold off the Kazon?
l think so, Captain.
Good.
Mr. Paris, take the conn.
Yes, ma'am.
Maintain transporter locks,
Ensign.
Emergency beam out status.
Aye, Captain.
The data processing system
is behind this wall, Captain.
You know what to do.
Well... you're, you're nothing
if not persistent.
We need you to send us back
where we came from.
Oh... that isn't possible.
l have... barely enough strength
to complete my work.
You're sealing the conduits
before you die.
lf l don't, the Kazon
will steal the water.
But, in a few years,
when the Ocampa's energy
runs out, it won't matter.
They'll be forced
to come to the surface
and they won't be able
to survive.
Something you did turned
their planet into a desert,
didn't it?
That was the debt
that could never be repaid.
Well, we're explorers
from another galaxy,
but we had no idea
that our technology
would be so destructive
to their atmosphere.
Two, two of us
were chosen to stay
behind and care for them.
There's another like you here?
Not anymore.
No, no. She...
she went off to look
for more interesting places.
Why were you bringing
ships here--
infecting people
with a fatal illness?
Oh, they...
they didn't die of an illness.
They died
because they were incompatible.
''lncompatible''?
l've been searching the galaxy
for a compatible
biomolecular pattern.
Now, in some individuals,
l found cellular structures
that were similar, but l...
You've been trying to procreate?
l needed someone to replace me--
someone who'd understand
the enormous responsibility
of... caring for the Ocampa.
Only my offspring could do that.
Did you ever consider
allowing the Ocampa
to care for themselves?
They're children.
Children have to grow up.
We're explorers, too.
Most of the species
we've encountered
have overcome all kinds
of adversity
without a Caretaker.
lt's the challenge
of surviving on their own
that helps them to evolve.
Maybe your... children
will do better than you think.
Voyager to Janeway.
Go ahead.
We've got problems here.
Kazon just got some backup.
We need more time.
Can you hold them off
for another few minutes?
We'll do our best.
Kim out.
Their weapons array
has been hit.
They're in trouble.
Neither of us has enough
firepower to stop that ship.
l'm setting a collision course,
but the guidance
system is disabled.
l'll have to pilot
the ship manually.
Get the crew ready
to beam to Voyager
and drop shields for transport.
Paris, my crew is coming over.
Tell one of your crackerjack
Starfleet transporter chiefs
to keep a lock on me.
l'm going to try and take
some heat off your tail.
Acknowledged.
But don't think for a second
this makes us even, Chakotay.
Your life is still mine.
Paris out.
l'm holding a lock on him, sir,
but he's getting too close.
l'm getting you out
of there, Chakotay.
Not yet!
You're breaking up!
Stand by to transport.
Wait!
Now!
Transporter Room 2,
do you have him?
They've got me.
Captain, l can access the system
to send us back
to Federation space,
but it will take
several hours to activate.
Unless you help us.
Oh, l wish l could,
but l have
very little time left.
So l have initiated
a self-destruct program.
lf you destroy the Array,
we'll have no way to get home.
The Ocampa's enemies
cannot be allowed
to, to control
this installation.
ln minutes,
it will be destroyed.
You have to go.
Go now!
The Caretaker.
Voyager, report.
A Kazon vessel
just collided
with the Array, Captain.
Are you all right?
Affirmative.
Stand by.
The self-destruct program
has been damaged.
Now, this installation
will not be destroyed.
But it must be.
The Kazon must not be allowed
to gain control of it.
They will annihilate the Ocampa.
Shall l activate
the program to get us back?
And what happens to the Ocampa
after we're gone?
Captain, any action we take
to protect the Ocampa
would affect the balance
of power in this system.
The Prime Directive
would seem to apply.
Would it?
We never asked to be involved,
Tuvok...
but we are.
We are.
Mr. Tuvok, ready
the tricobalt devices.
Aye, Captain.
Open a channel to the Kazon.
Channel open.
Be advised, Captain.
l have called
for additional ships.
l'm calling to warn you to move
your vessels to a safe distance.
l intend to destroy the Array.
You can't do that.
l can and l will.
End transmission.
They're increasing fire,
Captain.
Shields are holding.
Move us 400 kilometers
from the Array, Mr. Paris.
Yes, ma'am.
What do you think you're doing?
That Array is the only way
we have to get back home.
l'm aware everyone has
families and loved ones
at homes they want
to get back to--
so do l-- but l'm not
willing to trade the lives
of the Ocampa
for our convenience.
We'll have to find
another way home.
What other way home is there?
Who is she to be making
these decisions for all of us?
She's the Captain.
The tricobalt devices are ready.
We're in position.
Fire.
The lead Kazon ship
is hailing us.
On screen.
You have made an enemy today.
They are withdrawing, Captain.
Come in.
You asked to see me, Captain?
Mr. Paris...
you have a problem.
l've invited Chakotay
and the other Maquis
to become part of this crew.
lt seemed the only
reasonable thing to do
under the circumstances.
Will you provide
a bodyguard for me, Captain?
lt seems you already have one.
l do?
Mr. Chakotay said something
about his life belonging to you.
He'll be taking responsibility
for your safety.
l think l'm going to enjoy this.
Don't be so sure.
He'll also be my First Officer.
Everyone aboard this ship
will report to him--
including the Lieutenant
assigned to conn.
Me?
l've entered into the Ship's Log
on this date
that l'm granting
a field commission of Lieutenant
to Thomas Eugene Paris.
Congratulations.
Um, for the first time
in my life,
l don't know what to say.
You've earned this, Tom.
l'm only sorry
your father won't know.
Oh, he'll know...
when we get back.
Ah, Captain, we were
just coming to see you.
We've supplied your ship
with water, Neelix.
lt's ready to go.
Well, you see that's what
we wanted to discuss.
We'd like to go with you.
l'm sorry.
This isn't a passenger ship.
Of course not.
We won't be passengers.
We'd be valuable colleagues.
''Colleagues''?
Whatever you need is
what l have to offer.
You need a guide,
l'm your guide.
You need supplies, l know
where to procure them.
l have friends among races
you don't even know exist.
You need a cook?
Oh, you haven't lived
until you've tasted
my angla'bosque.
lt will be my job
to anticipate your needs
before you know you have them.
And l anticipate your first need
will be me.
Captain, we both want
very much to be a part
of your journey.
We're alone in
an uncharted part of the galaxy.
We've already made
some friends here
and some enemies.
We have no idea of the dangers
we're going to face,
but one thing is clear:
Both crews are going
to have to work together
if we're to survive.
That's why Commander Chakotay
and l have agreed
that this should be one crew--
a Starfleet crew.
And as the only Starfleet vessel
assigned to the Delta Quadrant
we'll continue
to follow our directive
to seek out new worlds
and explore space.
But our primary goal is clear.
Even at maximum speeds
it would take 7 5 years
to reach the Federation,
but l'm not willing
to settle for that.
There's another entity
like the Caretaker
out there somewhere
who has the ability
to get us there a lot faster.
We'll be looking for her
and we'll be looking
for wormholes, spatial rifts
or new technologies to help us.
Somewhere, along this journey,
we'll find a way back.
Mr. Paris, set a course...
for home.
Aye, Captain.
www.tvsubtitles.net
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app