Previously on
Dexter: New Blood...
Almost ten years without a kill.
James Lindsay, huh?
Jim.
Girlfriend's a cop, huh?
Edward Olsen heading up
to his chalet.
Everyone's favorite
petro-billionaire.
- Shame on you!
- Thank you, everyone.
Gonna need a new knife
and a big-ass gun.
All right.
No body, no pattern,
no case.
You're not from around here.
Taking the first bus out
tomorrow.
A-Are you Dexter Morgan?
- Harrison.
- You can't.
Everyone close to you dies.
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
Bagged me a white fucking buck!
Jim.
My dad, he is gonna rain down
a world of pain on you, man!
Life is short.
Tonight's the night.
I'm Dexter Morgan.
Come home.
My father protected me.
And that's exactly what
I'm going to do for my son.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
What do I say?
What can I possibly say
to the son I abandoned?
You got big.
Happens.
If you're cold,
I can put some more wood on.
I'm fine.
You hungry?
I could whip up
some blueberry pancakes.
You used to love those.
Yeah, I'm not five anymore.
Maybe a sandwich.
One sandwich, coming right up.
Must've been a long trip.
Yeah.
Yeah, we got second place
at the Harvest Fest Tournament
last year.
Cool.
So...
You're not dead.
He's owed an explanation.
But the only one
is that his father is a monster.
I'm sure this is hard.
This?
No.
Growing up without a dad,
that was hard.
And opening up that letter,
finding out you let me believe
you were dead all those years...
that was brutal.
- Hannah showed you the letter?
- No.
I found it when she died.
Hannah died?
How?
Cancer.
Pancreatic.
I didn't know.
When did she die?
Three years ago.
What happened to you?
Where have you been?
A social worker
put me on a plane
from Buenos Aires to Miami.
I bounced around a bunch
of shitty foster homes.
No one wants a teenager.
And finally I decided
to find you.
Mm.
The return address
got me that town in Oregon.
And I found where you worked.
Also found that you'd left.
That's when it got
a little harder
to track down Jim Lindsay.
You know how many Jim Lindsays
there are on the Internet?
It's kind of the point.
Then I found
a shot of you on Instagram.
Pictures don't lie.
Some Fred guy
on some bowling team...
bragging on you bowling a 300.
Right here in Iron Lake.
So why all this Jim bullshit?
What happened to Dexter Morgan?
He killed dozens of people,
got your mother
and your aunt killed, too.
It's not who I am anymore.
Dexter had to die.
What are you talking about?
It's a long story.
We should get some rest,
and I'll tell you everything
in the morning.
I promise.
Uh, you want my room?
I can take the couch.
The couch is fine.
Well, if you need
anything else...
Where's the bathroom?
Stop.
You're not listening!
I need him here.
It'll keep me
from killing again.
You selfish psycho.
You emotionally handicapped,
crazy fuck.
If by some goddamn miracle
you don't end up killing him,
you will sure as shit
fuck him up.
I'm not gonna fuck him up.
Let's get back
to the daily routine.
This is what happens
when I give in
to my dark passenger.
But I can fix this.
Teenagers sleep till noon,
right?
Well, this is one storm of fuck.
Matt Caldwell disappeared in
the woods near here last night.
Oh.
That's not good.
Your place is close to
all the public hunting grounds,
so I was hoping we could set up
base camp for the search here.
Yeah. Of course.
- Whatever you need.
- Don't worry, Jimmy.
Dude probably got wasted
and skipped the hunt.
We'll get a call he's
sleeping it off in some motel
and be out of here by lunch.
Or he could be out there,
freezing to death.
You can set up by the firepit.
The searchers can stay warm.
I'll get some coffee going
and breakfast, too, if you want.
You're a godsend.
By the firepit, guys!
Okay, guys!
Let's unload the tables,
set up the tents.
Let's move quickly!
You mind if I use
your kitchen table for a sec?
Got to mark this up,
and I'd love some Earl Grey.
Oh, wait.
What's going on?
Jim? And this is...?
Harrison.
I'm Jim's son.
Son?
Add that to the list
of things I need to clean up.
Welcome to Iron Lake, Harrison.
I'm Angela.
It's really nice to meet you.
Yo, Jimbo!
Wood's gonna rot if you
don't cover it with a good tarp.
Yeah, I'll get right on that.
Well, hell, Jim,
you got 'em at your own store.
Just pick up a good canvas one.
As long as there's wax on it.
Or a polyurethane one, yeah?
Thanks for the tip, Teddy.
So, you came here by yourself?
It's no big deal.
Used to moving around a lot.
Your mother wasn't worried?
What are you two talking about?
Mom. That she passed away.
Oh, I'm-I'm so sorry.
Mm. Um...
Then, of course,
when that happened,
I came up here to be with Jim.
So, you're here for good?
- Well, you'll love Iron Lake.
- Actually, we haven't...
really talked about it yet,
but...
You should meet
my daughter Audrey.
She's about your age.
Thanks for covering for me.
Didn't do it for you.
Just didn't want a cop
all up in my business.
Huh. Like father, like son.
You'll each be assigned into
groups of four and given a grid.
Search for any sign of Matt.
We'll do two-hour shifts,
then we'll return
to base camp to warm up
and pick a new grid.
- Oh, a-and stay hydrated.
- Okay.
Let's get a move on.
We'll keep
the store closed today, Jim,
but if anybody needs supplies,
feel free to make a run.
- Sure thing.
- Teddy.
- Get the drone in the air.
- On it!
A drone. Perfect.
Hey.
You didn't include
any Seneca land
in your search area.
I mean, the last thing we need
is a bunch of townsfolk
trampling reservation land.
I asked Abraham Brown
to organize the search
on their side.
They're already in the woods.
Copy that.
That deer was killed
on Seneca land.
They're gonna find it soon.
If I missed a blood trail
to my own cabin,
- what else did I miss?
- Hey.
I was thinking Harrison and I
can take that area
into the woods.
We got it covered, Jim.
No, we want to help.
The terrain gets rough.
My RTV will
get through it faster.
Okay.
Fine.
You and your son can take it.
Ouch.
That thing police-grade?
Of course.
Built-in mapping software?
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, crap.
I might get away
with this after all.
Sorry, boss!
- What now?
- Logan.
Get the search teams launched.
- Yes, boss.
- I'll be back.
Yep.
Jesus.
Fucking champagne.
Do you have an appointment?
You're-you're kind of
swerving a lot.
I'm just avoiding rocks.
Usually blood sets
my teeth on edge.
Now it's giving me whiplash.
So, uh...
you and the police chief, huh?
I've only been in Iron Lake
for a couple of years.
This whole Angela thing
is recent.
So-so, why here?
You... do you, like,
hate nice weather?
No, it's quiet, peaceful.
No crime.
No temptations
from the outside world.
No crime?
What, y-you think
this missing guy
just, like, got lost out here?
Probably.
People get lost in these woods
all the time.
Wh-What is that?
You know what,
this could be a crime scene.
That deer was shot
on Seneca land.
It's against the law
to kill them.
We need to tell Angela.
My phone won't work out here.
- Can you drive the RTV?
- Yeah, I should be fine.
All right, just follow the trail
back, and get them here
as fast as you can.
I'll make sure
no one disturbs the scene.
Got to find the source
of that blood trail.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Gauguin's A Farm in Brittany.
Well, look at you.
Chief, if you're here
to apologize
about that little protest
yesterday...
We've got a hunter
who disappeared
in the woods last night.
We're searching
on foot, but we have
over 100 square miles to cover.
You need my helicopter.
It would really help.
Then it's yours.
My pilot was an Army Ranger.
He-he knows the area.
I'll have him coordinate
with your office.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
I'll be going.
Oh, hold on.
That young woman yesterday, the
one who was leading the protest,
uh, she by any chance
your daughter?
Audrey.
Hmm. Unfortunately,
her generation
sees the world
only in binary terms.
Black and white, good and evil.
And that, uh...
climate change-denying oil baron
persona that people are
all too happy to pin on me,
it ignores all of the good I do.
All of my charity work,
including to the Seneca people.
The supplies I donate every year
to keep that,
uh, reservation
medical clinic running,
the food during the holidays.
It's very much appreciated.
Mm-hmm.
We'll get that bird
up in the air for you.
The mystery is,
where did I screw up?
They always say
killers return to the scene
of their crime,
but this is fucking ridiculous.
It's not fucking funny!
Mystery solved.
You think Windexing that rock
is gonna solve
your fucking problem?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
He has your brain.
He's smart enough to know
that people don't fake
their fucking death
if they have nothing to hide!
Who the fuck do you think
you're fooling?!
I told you, the Matt thing was
a one-time screwup.
What the actual fuck
do you think you're doing?
Harrison's been here one day,
and you have him
in the woods looking
for a man you killed?
He'd be so much better off
without you.
He's my son.
I lost him once.
I won't lose him again.
Once again, I have to stay
a step ahead of everyone.
With Matt's help,
I can do that.
Thanks... dude.
Perfect.
More people to mess up
the crime scene.
Hey, Jim.
White buck.
Left here to rot.
Such a waste.
None of us would have done
something like this.
You think maybe
Matt Caldwell would?
He was hunting out here.
It could explain
why we can't find him.
We need to secure the perimeter.
You got it, boss.
This is bullshit, Angela.
I'm betting
the Caldwell kid did this,
then panicked and ran.
The highway is just a couple
of klicks in that direction.
He could've hitched
and ran out of town.
It's plausible.
But there's no evidence
tying Matt to this deer.
So we'll process the scene,
which you're all trampling
right now, so please back up.
Shit. Why does my girlfriend
have to be such a good cop?
For now,
the search for Matt goes on,
including here on Seneca land.
Even after he did this?
If he did this.
Pretty amazing
how the entire town
turns out for a Caldwell.
When one of our girls
goes missing...
"Runaways always come back."
After Iris,
you of all people should know.
Things are different
in Iron Lake now.
Sooner or later,
you're gonna have
to pick a side.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Harrison was great, by the way.
Good job.
It's no big deal.
Logan, let's get
the processing kit.
Let's see what we can find.
Officer coming through!
Looks like the slug's
still in the carcass.
There's no exit wound.
I sold Matt a rifle and bullets
a couple of days ago.
I could bring in
some of the ammo,
the same stuff, to the station,
see if it's a match.
Oh, my God! I just found this
about a mile down the trail,
right before I got to the...
The highway.
Thank you, Fred Jr.
You magnificent outdoorsman.
Told you.
Chickenshit cut and ran.
How long you been a cop again?
Two weeks... and a half.
Look, this may not even be
Matt's glove.
Someone could've dropped it
a month ago.
Matt had gloves like that
when he was in the store.
Indeed, he did.
I mean, there are
smudges of blood on this.
Let's get this
and the deer back to town.
We'll test the blood.
We'll see if it matches.
Well...
thanks to you,
we got some real leads.
Not bad for your very first
crime scene.
Just lucky we stumbled on it.
You can use my deer sled
to get it back to town
if you want.
If you don't stop being
so helpful, Jim,
I'm gonna have to deputize you.
Y-You guys bring this deer
back to your place,
and we'll take it from there.
Harrison,
the high school just got out,
so the students are
joining the search.
Maybe you can meet
some kids your own age.
That'd be great.
We'll see you back there.
Okay.
Why aren't you a cop anymore?
Technically,
I wasn't actually a cop.
Well, Mom said you were a cop.
And you had to be better
than these guys.
Maybe.
But being at those crime scenes
day after day,
it just got to be too much.
I'm happier now.
Selling night crawlers?
Really?
- Hey, here, take my hat.
- I'm good.
You doing okay with all this?
It's fine.
Kind of cool, actually.
Yo, Coach!
Okay, everyone.
Do exactly
what the officers tell you.
Yo, Zach. Scott. What's up?
Vete.
Go. Y ten cuidado.
Hey, you want to help me
with the goats?
Uh, yeah, sure.
You're good with animals.
We had a goat back in Argentina.
Sheep and chickens, too.
I miss 'em. You okay?
What's the black one's name?
Uh... I've just
been calling him Goat.
Haven't gotten around
to properly naming him, I guess.
What was your goat's name?
Vincent.
Vincent van Goat.
Ha.
Well, Harrison,
meet Vincent van Goat II.
I got to head to the shop
and check on those bullets
I sold Matt.
If you want, you can just hang
inside the cabin
until I get back.
I know how awkward
it can be, meeting new people.
It was hard for me
in high school, too.
Yeah, I survived the last
ten years without you, Jim.
I think I can go two more hours.
Well, he's not
an awkward-as-fuck
budding serial killer
like you were.
Does that mean you're gonna
start laughing at me again?
I don't know, you tell me.
I know he shouldn't be
around you.
Around this version of me.
Jim Lindsay, he's safe.
You're starting
to sound an awful lot
- like the old Dexter to me.
- I'm not.
You are.
You fucking love that you're
getting away with murder.
You can't wait to kill again.
You are a fucking serial killer!
You are gonna fail this boy
a thousand different ways
because of it!
Stop!
Peace.
I wish.
I guess you met my mom.
The cop.
Chief of police.
The one dating your dad.
That part I figured out,
which-which makes this
not awkward at all.
Yeah. Don't worry.
Knowing my mom,
it won't last long.
She's pretty much married
to her job.
You want to come
on the search with us?
Sure.
Hey, guys.
Zach and Scott.
They're smarter than they look.
Well, Zach is.
Duh.
Me Scott.
Harrison.
Appreciate this, Gig.
Glad to help.
Hey.
It's not a big deal.
A lot of folks get queasy
at the sight of blood.
- Yeah, it gets to me every time.
- Yeah.
Looks like the shooter
didn't know what he was doing
or was a piss-poor shot.
Deer's got a shattered shoulder,
uh, bone splinter everywhere.
You feel the slug?
Yep.
What do you think?
Looks like a hollow-point
seven Mag to me.
The bullets I sold Matt were...
160-grain hollow-point
seven-millimeter
Remington Magnums.
The plot thins.
Looks like there's
some striation on the base.
We might be able to match it
to Matt's gun when we find it.
Thanks, Gig.
Looks like my work's done here.
I better get back to Harrison.
Harrison's with Audrey
on the search. They're fine.
You and I, on the other hand,
need to talk.
"We need to talk."
Words you never want to hear
from your doctor
or your girlfriend.
Cool shirt.
You mean her "myew" shirt?
Wh-What does it even mean?
Married monsters in...
Missing and Murdered
Indigenous Women.
Oh. Fuck.
Hey, yo. It's just up here.
Where?
Sorry you ended up in Iron Lake.
Sucks here.
I think I'm just
passing through, actually.
Yeah?
Well, lucky you.
- So, where...?
- So, what is it...?
You go.
Uh, I was gonna ask,
what's it like being
the police chief's daughter?
So much fun.
She never checks up on me.
Never assumes
I've been murdered
when she hasn't heard
from me for, like, ten minutes.
It's great.
That kind of reminds me
of my stepmom.
My dad, not so much.
Oh, and you live
with your stepmom?
Yo, this is it!
Shit, hide!
That had to be Olsen.
Who's that?
Petrochemical
billionaire asshole.
Aren't we supposed to be
looking for this Matt guy?
The whole town and
the reservation are searching.
They even got a helicopter.
They don't need us.
And Matt Caldwell's
an entitled prick,
so fuck him. We're gonna party.
Hold up.
They put new locks
on the cabin doors.
Leave it to me.
Son of a...
I got it.
Give me a sec.
Mom is really not gonna
like you.
Here it comes.
The moment
the girlfriend tells me
I'm too closed-off,
that it's not gonna work out.
I'm thrilled Harrison is here.
Then again...
You are?
Yeah.
I know you've been private
about your past.
It's okay.
Everyone has secrets.
Ange, I never meant
for it to be a secret.
It's fine.
We all have things
we keep from each other,
right?
For instance...
I'm not Audrey's birth mother.
Oh.
You adopted her?
Yeah.
Did you ever look
for the birth mom?
I've spent pretty much
my entire adult life
looking for missing women.
But one who abandons
her own baby?
Fuck her.
You could have shared your
Harrison situation with me.
This whole time, I've been
struggling with Audrey,
thinking I couldn't share
that part of my life with you.
But now Harrison's here,
and maybe that's
an opportunity for us, too.
We can talk parenting...
the pressures,
the worry, the guilt.
So that's me,
sharing,
giving you
an opening to share back.
- Right.
- 'Cause that's...
that's how it works.
I don't know that
I can always be the father
Harrison needs me to be.
I feel that way
about being a mom every day.
- You do?
- Yeah.
But it doesn't matter
because Audrey needs me.
Just like Harrison needs you.
So the good news is,
all you really have
to do is just...
show up.
Show up?
You make it sound so easy.
Also gonna have
to enroll him in school.
Obviously.
And get him
some real winter clothes.
And he's probably gonna
need a car.
College apps are coming up,
so add tutors and exam prep.
Harrison's been here
less than a day,
and now I'm talking
about college prep.
Just wait till
he starts dating.
Maybe just start
with a cot or something.
A cot. I can do that.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Harrison's gonna love it here.
In fact, I bet Audrey
and her friends
are taking great care
of him right now.
No, I'm good.
Scott?
So, what are you, like,
straight edge or something, man?
Don't think
that's a thing anymore.
Wait. Are you a Mormon?
I kind of have
a history with drugs.
I got clean
a couple years ago, though.
Whoa. Anyone want a kick-ass
Roaring Forks beach towel?
No.
So, where are you
headed after this?
Uh, I-I just got up here
from Florida.
- Is that where your mom lives?
- Stepmom.
Um, actually, my mom died
when I was really young,
and my stepmom died of cancer
a couple years ago.
I'm so sorry.
- Was your mom sick?
- What?
You said your stepmom died
of cancer,
so how'd your real mom die?
You know what?
I shouldn't have asked.
It's none of our business.
No, it's fine.
I'm freezing.
I'm gonna go get
some wood for the fire.
Well, that's on you.
- You made that worse.
- Either way, dude's weird.
And we're trapped
in an abandoned cabin
in the woods with him.
Stop watching slasher films.
Just saying
we know nothing about him.
But we can.
Sick.
That's fucked-up.
Relax.
Just making sure he doesn't have
a fucking manifesto in here
- or some shit.
- Okay, no manifesto, so stop.
We got an artist here.
So he's actually good
at something,
- unlike the two of you.
- We're good at stuff.
Pinning half-naked guys to mats.
Wrestling is
an Olympic sport, Audrey.
So is Ping-Pong.
What the fuck
are you guys doing?
Stop. Put that away.
Shit.
Got the wood.
Cool. Thanks.
Where the fuck is my phone?
Hello?
Hello?!
Is anyone there?
Hey! Let me the fuck out!
What the fuck is...?!
Oh.
Thank you.
- There you go.
- I hide the blood.
I plant a glove.
I match the bullet
in the deer to Matt's gun.
All to get the good people
of Iron Lake off my land.
And yet here I am,
feeding them hamburgers.
If I prayed,
I'd pray for this to be over.
Everyone!
We do not think Matt Caldwell
is in these woods,
so we are shutting down
the search!
Wow, prayer answered.
- So the glove was a match?
- Matt's friend
confirmed it was his.
And the smudges on it
were deer blood.
So he did shoot that deer.
And then probably fled
to avoid prosecution.
I'm guessing he's halfway
to New York by now.
Great job cracking the case.
And completely buying
into my narrative.
It's not closed yet.
We're still trying
to get in touch with his dad.
Take the compliment.
Thank you.
And I'm glad
the idiot's all right.
I mean, last thing
this town needed
was finding a body
in the woods.
Yeah.
So, we'll be out
of your hair soon.
And when Harrison is settled,
you should bring him
over for dinner.
I'll make my grandmother's
hulled corn soup.
I'm sure he'd love that.
But...
it'll have to be after Audrey's
done being grounded.
What?
Are you kidding me?
So you didn't just spend
the entire afternoon hanging out
at the Roaring Forks
Summer Camp?
What? No way.
That's-that's crazy.
Scott, you're literally wearing
a Roaring Forks T-shirt
that's two sizes too small
right now.
Shit.
Who cares?
Matt Caldwell's an asshole.
Audrey!
And since everyone's packing up,
I'm guessing you found him
and he's fine?
Not the point.
I didn't know where you were.
It's dangerous out there.
- You have no idea.
- Nó'yëh, stop.
I've heard it all before.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I'm not Iris.
Get in the SUV.
We're going home.
- Let's go, Zach.
- Well...
I kind of don't want
to get arrested, so...
She's not gonna arrest you.
She only acts like a crazed,
overbearing dictator with me.
Come on, Zach.
Sorry you and Harrison
had to see that.
Parenting's just learning
as you go, right?
It'll be okay.
Thanks.
It's just a few things,
in case you decide
you want to stay.
I'm not sure.
I-I didn't come here
for all this.
I came here for answers.
Ask me whatever you want.
Why did you leave us?
Was it because of
what you wrote in the letter?
What I wrote?
"Reach out to me if Harrison
shows any dark tendencies."
Dark tendencies?
What does that mean?
What was so wrong with me
that-that you not only left
but faked your own death
to hide from me?
- It wasn't you.
- But...
"Dark tendencies"?
Wh-What did you see in me?
Nothing bad.
You were perfect.
You were this sweet, smart,
trusting little boy
with a huge heart.
It wasn't you I was scared of.
It was me.
I've always had...
...my demons.
And I was scared
that I'd mess you up,
that I'd pass that on.
And so...
I went away.
Because of what I am,
not because of who you are.
I-I-I don't understand.
I was in a dark place
after I lost your mom.
And then Aunt Deb,
and all that death.
I got lost.
And I thought you would thrive
in Argentina with Hannah.
She was always so good
with you.
Walking away from you
is the hardest thing
I've ever done.
And I regret it
so much now, because...
I never imagined
you'd be left alone.
After Hannah told me
you were dead,
I-I kept a photo
of you by my bed.
I would look at it every night.
And for a long time,
I cried myself to sleep.
And then I found that letter.
I...
I was so angry.
Of course you were.
But maybe I can be there
for you now.
Do-do you really mean that?
If you're willing to risk the
chance that I'll screw you up.
Stop acting like
you're such an evil person.
I-I don't remember a lot,
but all of my memories
of you are good.
The... the worst thing
you ever did was...
Uh-oh.
...leave me.
So, yeah, I'll stay.
For a while.
Great.
In the morning, we can talk
about getting you
set up at school.
But not over
blueberry pancakes.
I mean, regular pancakes
wouldn't be completely
out of the question.
Regular pancakes sound good.
Ugh. How did you know
this is exactly what I need?
Lucky guess.
You don't have to enjoy
the win so much.
You smug fuck.
Angela.
I came as soon as I...
as I could.
What's going on?
Did you find him?
Tell me he's okay.
Kurt, we've been trying
to contact you for hours.
We found evidence that Matt
may have committed a crime.
What?
What... what crime?
Killing an animal
on reservation land.
Evidence points to him
fleeing the area.
- What are you talking about?
- My son and I
found a dead white deer,
Mr. Caldwell.
Matt killed it, realized
he screwed up and left town.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
He would've called me
if he was in trouble.
He always does.
And a poaching fine
isn't gonna scare him.
It's not just poaching, Kurt.
Matt killed a white buck
on reservation land.
And I'm telling you
that he would've called me.
He's out there.
Look, I know Matt's not perfect
and he's made mistakes in life,
but he doesn't deserve
to freeze to death
in the woods tonight, 'cause
that's what's gonna happen
if you call the search off.
Kurt, can we talk
about this inside?
No, goddamn it!
My son has disappeared,
and we need to find him now.
Everybody!
Hey.
I need...
I need you to stand up for me,
for my family.
Same way we've stood up for you.
I mean,
we-we've donated the trucks
to the volunteer
fire department.
Uh, we sponsor the Harvest Fest
every year.
I mean, Fred, when-when your
dad's store's roof fell in,
who fronted him
for the repairs, huh?
Right.
I mean, come on.
Half your kids grew up
working at my truck stop.
This is Iron Lake.
We look out for each other.
So, please, I'm begging you.
Do not give up on my son now.
Now, when he needs us the most.
Okay. We'll keep going
through the night.
Thank you, Angela.
Thank you so much.
Whatever resources you need,
anything at all.
Means the world to me.
Okay. We're going back in.
Stay in your groups
and bundle up.
It's gonna be
a long, cold night.
So... I guess we'll be
here a little bit longer.
That's not a problem.
This your boy, Jim?
Yes. Harrison,
this is, uh, Kurt Caldwell.
Nice to meet you,
Mr. Caldwell.
Likewise.
Matt's out there.
I know it.
I'm gonna find him,
if it's the last thing I do.
No stone will go unturned.
Well, maybe some stones
will go unturned.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/96zj9
Help other users to choose the best subtitles