You've proven to be
quite a letdown.
Ahh!
My chorus grows louder
with each new life.
But we're still
missing the key.
Mooncake!
He resides with
the Gary.
The Gary?
I've killed him
many times.
Not this one.
He still eludes you.
My Patience with you
grows weak.
Ahh!
Bring him to me.
Or meet the fate
of the ones
I find useless.
Where are they?
I feel the presence
of ash.
What we seek
is on earth.
Ehh?
Ahh!
Ohh!
Hey,
how you holding up?
Okay, I guess.
And ash?
I'm not sure,
but I think there's hope.
Hey guys! What are you
talking about?
- Me?
- Ahh!
Do you really think
that crackpot Van Newton
Can get us
out of here?
Time to find out!
H.U.E., take us in.
Coordinates received.
Whoa!
Take us in.
In.
We're going in. In.
In is where we're going!
In. Not out.
In. In-wards.
In-side.
In-victus.
Wait!
Why did I say that?
Delete!
Wonderful!
What the heck was that?
The quakes have been
growing stronger
For the past
three days!
Is the hyper-transdimensional
bridge up and running?
Well, yes...
And no.
Hmm. Which is it?
You got me, no.
Ha!
See, I knew it!
Wait! What...
What do you mean, no?
Remember that wrinkle
I told you about?
The summer khaki wrinkle,
or the space-time wrinkle?
Both.
My biggest fear.
That's as wrinkly
as it gets.
Have you made
any progress?
A little, yeah.
Ohh...
Slap my thunder nipples!
That's big.
Where does that lead
to? That's the problem.
Right now, it's not
connected to anything.
Oooh! Genius.
I love it!
Well, how do we
get it to work?
By connecting it to the doorway
on the other side.
That's just lovely!
Oh boy!
Let me just get this straight.
We have to contact someone
outside of final space
And get them to turn this on,
or we're screwed?
Newton says...
Yes.
Yes, and.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
*FINAL SPACE*
Season 03  Episode 09
Episode Title:
"Hyper-Transdimensional Bridge Rising"
Aired on: May 15, 2021
Alright, who do we know
that doesn't live on earth
That we can contact
to activate the... the...
The hyper-transdimensional
bridge?
Yes, that.
All my friends are dead. Same.
Oh!
I got... Uh.
No, yeah.
No, they're all dead.
Oh, come on.
Well, what about...
Clarence.
Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Okay, I would rather
be swallowed by my own colon
Than to ask that sulfurous
fart nozzle for help!
Okay, I would. I really would.
He could do it.
And who is he?
He was my dad...
At one point.
I guess in some weird way,
he still is.
He wanted to marry me.
It's a long story,
but he betrayed us and you!
He really is the actual worst.
He is
the actual worst.
Do any of you have
someone else in mind?
Besides...
He deserves to
know about fox.
Oh, man.
Okay.
Clarence it is.
I only have enough power
to relay one message
Out of final space.
We have one shot, people.
I get it.
Clarence, incoming wide
band unsecured transmission.
Well, tell them
I'm not here.
You may want to hear
this message.
No one cares about me,
am-me.
And why should they?
Delete it.
Clarence?
It's... it's me. Ash.
Ash?
Is it really you?
Yeah.
Listen, um...
I don't know
where you are,
And... frankly,
I don't really care.
That hurts,
but it's fair.
Before I get to what
I'm calling you for, um...
You should
know that fox is, um...
Fox is dead.
Ohh. Oh.
Listen, we made it
to final space.
Gary found Quinn,
And now we're trying
to come home.
That's a strange word
for me nowadays.
Look, I'm calling you
because we need your help.
Me?
You really need me?
We need you to
activate a bridge
Located on a planet
called kalden 1.
I've never asked
anything of you.
Ever.
So if there is one shred
of a decent person in you,
Do this,
for me.
I can do it.
I will do it.
And hurry up, yo!
Shut it, primate!
Clarence, every person in the
galaxy heard that transmission.
Ah, here we go.
Oh, this is it.
What are you doing?
Going to save
my daughter.
Yes!
That's all of them.
Oh no, it was
the back pocket.
Yes, there it is.
Here!
The place is yours.
You're giving me...
All of it.
Everything I own
on 67 worlds,
Including my world's greatest
artisanal toffee brand
"Clarence's nuggets".
Full disclosure...
They're not
the "world's greatest".
They're
not even nuggets.
You're not
coming back?
But you built
all of this.
It's just stuff.
Kalden 1!
That's not far
from here at all!
Tribore, you better
be on the way.
Sure am.
Just tying up some loose ends.
Ready to do
some liberating?
Si, papa.
Oppressed peoples
of the quadrant of...
Where the hell are we?
Quatro, where are we?
Oh, heavens,
not there.
Those people were
too stupid to be saved.
Them I liked, they had
excellent slippers,
But they did not
like me.
Screw it.
Oppressed peoples
of here and there!
Freedom is not a gift.
Freedom is your right!
Consider yourself liberated.
For I, tribore, am
the great liberator!
Mnh-mnh. No, papa.
Oh, heavens.
Let's get clarity on this from
the great Tim belts himself.
Everyone,
be ready to bounce!
We'll be back in
a hip thrust.
Let's get right to it,
Tim.
Am I the great liberator
or is quatro?
And make it snappy.
I've got people waiting.
Yes! The time has come to
unbound the chained!
Uh, to raise up the...
Oh, shut the hell up
and pick one already!
You are the great liberator.
Yes!
Or is it me?
Uhh, yep.
He's absolutely
useless.
Uh-huh!
Okay, this is how
it's gonna work.
Mondays, wednesdays
and sundays,
You're
the great liberator.
Tuesdays, Thursdays,
and Fridays, it's me.
Papa!
Quatro!
Yeah!
Uhh, uhh-uhh!
Uhh, muh-huh.
Gary, the tremors
are getting worse.
Oh, this is bad.
This is fascinatingly bad.
They're coming
from the earth's core.
At this rate, earth
will break apart in...
Calculating, facticulating...
Four hours.
What's
causing it?
Nothing I've
ever seen before.
Excuse me, small question.
London.
London. Interesting.
How's the shopping?
Everyone is dead!
Good!
So, no lines, then.
Be there in a couple
hip thrusts.
And by the way,
I'm bringing guests.
Did you say "guests"?
Did I? I did.
Putting... gah.
Boy.
I'm just gonna say
this out loud...
Putting all of our eggs in the
Clarence basket was a bad idea.
Why didn't we save
a non-Clarence basket
To put the eggs in,
or half the eggs?
He'll do it.
He'll turn on
the bridge.
I know he will.
Kalden 1.
That must be it.
Back away,
Clarence!
Todd?
I'm going to give you
a choice, Clarence.
Either you stop
what you're doing,
Or this becomes
your grave.
O-or perhaps,
Can I interest you
in a nugget?
Full disclosure...
They're not
the "world's greatest".
even nuggets.
You're not
going anywhere!
Do we know each other?
No, we do not!
But I know
Gary goodspeed.
He murdered
my sweet Melanie
And wore her flesh sack
like a poncho.
I lost my job
because of that guy, Gary!
I used to be
time swap Sammy.
Now I'm just
spare some change Sammy!
Ahh!
And you're ours,
Clarence!
Oh, come on!
We're gonna cut off your junk
and wear it as a necklace!
Get out of my way!
He's mine!
Here are
the divorce papers!
I'll happily sign them!
Yes, you will!
With your own blood!
Clarence!
Fraskenhauer?
How have you been,
friend?
I haven't seen you
in a minute!
Now look, I'm turning
on this bridge!
Over my dead body!
Ahhh!
Ahh!
Oh.
Impossible!
I'm invincible!
And I'm fraskenhauer!
Clarence! Dinner!
Thursday!
My god!
You are a smoking
hot stack of woman.
And what a thick
piece of meat you are.
I'm getting
divorced.
Marry me!
You had me at divorced!
Oh, yes!
Hyper-transdimensional bridge
is primed.
Searching for connection point.
Searching...
Let's go, big boy!
Connect!
Gah!
Ahh.
There is honor
in failing.
Clarence is ours.
I didn't see
that coming.
You can't be free
of your own pain, can you?
Ah...
I don't have any pain!
Ahhh!
I lived a life hinged
on stealing and dealing.
In that
kind of life...
...You learn to
read people.
What were
their names?
The... the love
you lost.
Holly and jed.
They would probably be ashamed
of what you've become.
I've lived in
that shame,
Betrayed the only people
that care about me.
You don't want it.
It destroys
every piece of you.
Ugh!
I'm... s-sorry.
Ow...
It's not you.
I'm sorry.
It's Gary
I'm killing.
And now
I'm going home.
Connection point found.
Waiting for
activation of bridge.
Ahh...
Turn on!
Hyper-transdimensional bridge
activated.
Clarence!
Noooo!
We had dinner
on Thursday!
Hyper-transdimensional link
is complete.
My god. Clarence did it!
He did it.
Does that mean...
We're going home?
Yeah, no.
What?
Why the hell not?
All it means is he
took care of his side.
That has to work, too.
Okay, who wants to press it?
You do it.
No.
You.
I'll do it!
Out of my way! Out of my way!
'Scuse me!
Press!
Bridge connection is stable.
Yes!
Yeah!
We're going home.
I am detecting massive
energy signatures
Coming towards the bridge.
Gary, you should see this.
Oh snap, let's peep it!
Reclaim your dignity!
And reclaim your freedom!
And as always, remember,
You don't have
to floss all of your teeth.
Just the ones you want to keep.
Strong freakin' finish,
tribore.
man.
I know I don't always appreciate
all of you as much as I should.
But to be fair, you've given me
precious little to work with.
Okay, so long.
That's it?
I was kinda hoping that was
going to end with a compliment.
Look to the titan's
wiener.
I'm not... what? No!
I'm not looking to the titan's...
If it points north,
I will be south.
If it glitters
in the west...
I'm not looking at a glittery
titan's wiener, alright?
Quatro, you need to fly
through the bridge, too.
And as hard as I know
this is to hear...
I will be going with you.
Okay, let's go!
Welcome to
my dimension.
Priority one?
Matching windbreakers
and moccasins.
The rest will take
care of itself.
Huh.
What is a windbreaker?
Oh, my sweet child!
I have so much
to teach you.
Bridge is stable.
What the hell are
y'all standing around for?
Leave! Go!
Alright!
Grab what supplies you can.
We're leaving in
5 minutes!
Ah!
Unhh.
The kvn net?
What is this?
It doesn't matter.
You're leaving.
Hurry up!
This is...
- This is a weapon, isn't it?
- Yes!
This weapon is why I made
the kvns to begin with!
Originally, the kvns were
designed to protect earth
From attacks of
an extradimensional nature.
Like what?
Oh, donkey birds!
Like titans!
This thing is powerful enough
to kill titans!
What the hell
did I just hear?
Kevin just said
kvn can kill titans.
I can kill titans?
You can't!
That can!
It's really too bad,
too, since you're
Getting the hell
out of this place.
It was never
quite activated.
Would've been nice to rid
the universe of those monsters.
Right!
Everyone on the ship!
Wait.
We can't go.
What are you talking about?
We can take out the titans
once and for all,
And that just might be
enough to cripple invictus.
We'll never have
this chance again.
The bridge is open!
We can leave right now!
We can escape
final space.
Home is
right there.
Gary's got a point.
We came here to get you.
That's done. Now let's go.
And then what?
What happens when invictus
breaks free
With this
army of titans?
How many people
will die?
This isn't over.
Not until all of us
are dead
Or all of them are.
Where you go...
I go.
Always.
Oh, come on!
You're staying and taking out
the titans now?
Every last one of them.
Sync corrections by srjanapala
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/7wvf5
Help other users to choose the best subtitles