Scan of sector 32
is complete, Gary,
But I am still unable
to locate the rest of the crew.
Chookity pok.
H.U.E., how do I
put this politely?
You've been out of the ai game
a while.
Do you think maybe
it is possible that...
Go ahead and say it, Gary.
That I'm incompetent?
Aaah! Oh, god.
Oh! H.U.E.!
Did you just uppercut me
with a monitor?
Oops.
I guess I'm still
getting my groove back.
Cheerio from old blighty,
constable goodspeed.
Ha! I'm making some progress
here in london,
But these jx10 trans-vector
plasma coils are really...
...Well, "snogging
my bum," as the brits used to say.
Yeah, you should definitely
stop saying that, okay?
But do you think
you can get it to work?
Yep. I'm hoping in
four to five days, tops.
We'll be there.
Have you found
the others yet?
Not yet.
oh! Uh, gotta run!
Remember Gary, uh,
9 to 38 days, tops.
'Scuse me?
What? What?
Newton out!
And goodspeed? God speed.
The souls of
these prisoners strengthen me.
But they are not enough.
I need the key.
I need mooncake.
Well, I wish we could've
spent more time together,
But since you all failed
To tell me where
mooncake is,
You can rot here
like trash.
Except her.
uh, sorry.
I thought you were
talking about me.
Are you?
Yes. You.
Let them go!
Soon, you'll join
the voiceless chorus
And bend to invictus.
You're going to love it.
Ahhhh! Ahhhhh!
Oh, and just how did you think
that was gonna go, girl?
I am the lord commander.
Come on, ash!
Kill him!
Aaaaaahhhh!
Agh!
Intriguing.
Aaaaahhh!
Agh! Ah. Oof.
aahh!
Ugh!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Nothing in sector 33.
There is no sign of avocato
or the rest of the crew, Gary.
Keep looking, h.U.E..
Lil bud?
Chookity?
Can I bounce a hypothesis
at you?
Pok pok.
Okay, good, okay.
You just got back,
but maybe you've noticed,
Quinn and I have been
a little distant, okay.
Hmm.
Separate rooms and...
Mm-hmm.
...Y-you get the idea...
Ohhhhhhhh,
chookity pok.
Maybe I'm just not...
Mysterious enough.
I've read the manuals,
okay.
Like, a lady like quinn
needs intrigue.
A mustache!
Excitement!
Pok pok?
What?
You think I excite?
Mmmwow!
Chookity pok pok.
Whoa.
You think I excite
and bring it?
Chookity.
Oh, my.
I asked for a slice, and you
give me the whole dang pie!
Pok pok pok pok pok,
chookity pok.
You have no idea
how much I needed that.
Gimme that muffin top,
little buddy. Pow!
Yeah! There we go.
Chookity chook!
Breathe.
Just breathe.
Excuse me, quinn.
Not now, h.U.E..
I know what's going on.
My biodiagnostic scanners
have detected
The rapid progression
of your final space poisoning.
Allow me to show you.
No, really, I'm good.
doctor's orders.
Ugh.
Scan is complete.
Projected life span...
Facticulating...
36 hours.
I'm sorry, quinn.
36 hours?
Ugh. Ah.
H.U.E., no one finds out,
especially Gary.
But, quinn, keeping secrets
is not part of my protocol.
Whatever happened to
doctor-patient confidentiality?
Uh, I am not your doctor.
You just said,
"doctor's orders."
Ah! It appears you won
this argument.
Maybe ol' h.U.E.
Has lost a step.
Then it stays between us.
I need that.
I need to make these last
moments with my Gary count.
We gotta help her.
Ugh. How?
These chains are impossible
to get out of.
Yeah, see you later,
fellas.
Sheryl!
Get us out of here.
No time, hon,
Not even for
a pash and dash.
Would you believe it?
There is time.
Ample time. Please!
No, no! Ugh.
And there she goes.
I admire her independence,
but...
She just bailed on us,
right?
Thanks for
rejoining the party.
But she's comin' back,
right?
Uh, what's the answer
that you're looking for?
Quatronostro?
Eh.
Mm!
Do not "eh" me.
I will not be "eh"ed!
I uncorked my baby hole
for you, mister.
I will not be ignored.
Eh.
Whoever said parenthood
was a roll in the hay
Doesn't know what hay is.
We need to bond.
Would a fatherly swaddle
do the trick?
It would.
Did I know that
all along?
I did.
Swaddle!
No sere envuelto!
Oh, well.
Then it's on!
Cha!
Ha, ha!
Quizás eres mi padre
pero yo soy tu superior!
I don't know what
the hell that means,
But it sounds
very continental.
Oh, heavens!
You are strong, my child.
As we tumble
on the ground mightily,
Man to man.
An undiscovered
new civilization?
They'd better
have shopping.
Si.
Mm-hmm.
Remember, don't buy
from the first seller,
And never pay full price.
Hut! Uh. Ugh!
Ah! Aah! Aaah!
Agh. Ah!
Help me, please!
Come on, ya little...
Work!
Ah, yes!
Gary, we're in trouble.
Come asap.
Oh.
Only 33 hours.
Sector 34.
Empty, Gary.
Still no sign of the crew.
Hey! Uh...
...You look nice.
Thanks.
Oh, my god.
You smell nice!
Why do you smell so nice?
Why do you...
I mean, uh, so extra nicer
Than the normally
natural nice?
I mean ah!
Pits! There's...
There's... I...
I'm sensing some pits
of lavender.
Did I save it?
I saved it, right?
Saved it?
You never lost it.
Love truly is blind.
I don't know what the hell
is going on,
But it's nice.
It's real nice.
Ah!
Incoming transmission, Gary.
Play it.
One moment, Gary.
Biskit, what exactly are you
doing with my pristine temple?
That's my business.
That was my golden chariot.
Play the dang message.
Gary, can I be honest
with you?
You're just letting
your robot arm go to waste.
Mind if I just cut it off
And attach it
to my h.U.E. Project?
If Gary's cool with it.
Gary, are you cool with it?
Oh!
That's my arm, okay?
And I... wait.
What do you mean,
my arm is going to waste?
can it do things?
H.U.E., will you please
play the message?
Two seconds. I want to hear
more about my sweet robot arm.
If you haven't figured it out
by now, there's no hope.
No hope?
What... what is...
What is that suppos...
You know what? Just...
H.U.E., play the dang message.
Gary, we're in trouble.
Come asap.
That's it?
Any more to that?
Mnh-mnh.
That's disappointing.
Whatever.
Lock onto her location, h.U.E.
Lightfold.
You're so much more
than you know.
I could make you whole.
All your fear, weakness...
Gone.
Become my..."prote-gzege."
Ha ha! It's pronounced
"protégé," ya dink!
That's what I said.
"Prote-gzege."
Nah, ya dingus.
It's pronounced "protégé,"
like matinee.
wait!
Are we roasting
a speech impediment?
No, I think he's just
mispronouncing "protégé."
Does it make a difference?
Totally!
In one version I'm the dick.
In the other...
You're the cool rebel dude,
Taking down the man!
exactly.
Ash, your powers
are beyond these fools' comprehension.
I can show you the way up,
the way to true power.
I never wanted them.
They were a gift.
A gift?
I couldn't save my sister
from being sacrificed.
I killed my parents.
And yet, against all odds,
here you stand,
Alive.
Aren't you even
a little curious why?
I don't want to know why.
Because deep down
you already know, don't you?
You're still here
Because you're one of us.
Leave it to a market
in final space
To sell a crocheted sweater.
Is this peach?
Because it better
not be fuchsia.
We are in great danger,
outlander.
Our enemies draw closer
with each passing moment.
Our people live in fear.
Help us, please!
Shut the hell up.
You don't know what danger is
until you've read
My customer satisfaction
survey.
Now, how much
is the frock?
they approach!
Ew. Bug thugs.
To be fair, if I looked
like that, I would be mad, too.
I mean, what kind of
frankenstein nonsense is this?
Be something,
or be nothing.
Whoa!
But those were
just the scouts.
Their army won't rest
until they destroy us all.
Please, stay!
Fine, you win.
What do you win?
World's worst shopkeep.
That's what you win.
I think we're next.
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
Dad? When invictus
took you over, did it hurt?
Yeah.
But not as much
as hurting you.
You lost one.
Ughhhh!
Gary, your mother's
signal emanated
From this quadrant
of the asteroid field.
Alright,
let's set her down.
Mom?
Where the hell are you?
Gary.
Oh...
Oh, I... oh.
Okay, I'm just...
Ah!
Ah.
Well, I mean,
we're new to this, Gary.
Sorry, I... ah, whoops.
Didn't mean to...
sorry.
Yeah.
Well that was just
horribly awkward.
Yeah!
It's a Gary thing!
Uh, you know...
...We could just stop.
Ah, thank you.
Gary, listen,
The lord commander
has returned.
And he has the others.
What?
He's back.
This time
we kill him.
Mmmmm.
Don't worry,
mooncake.
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you.
You just tell h.U.E.
What you need, Gary.
Guns.
Lots of guns.
Hell yeah, dawg.
Hell yeah!
H.U.E. Oh... o-okay.
We're good.
Okay, you can stop now!
Okay, okay, h.U.E.
H.U.E.!
You want guns?
I give you guns.
By the way, quinn,
I'm not just
In the excitement
distribution business.
I don't even know
what that means.
It means I bring it.
Then maybe we should do it
already, goodspeed.
It's about to be brought,
ergon.
The warning horns.
The slyban army
draws near!
Save us, please!
Please!
What is this?
A burlap sack of horror?
One star.
Outlander,
we're all going to die!
Do I want to help?
Yes, I do.
Will I?
That depends on how fast
you can say the magic word.
Would you say, you want us
to help you... Resist them?
Mm. I'd say more like,
uh, fight back.
Are you absolutely married
to that phrasing?
For instance, could the help
you require be characterized
As a resistance?
Could we maybe discuss
the wording later?
Honestly? No.
Agh!
Sure, whatever!
We'll call it
your thing.
Just help us!
Just say the word, hon.
Will you please lead
the resis...
Shh!
Tribore already knows.
Quatro, to arms!
♪ Whoa-ohhhh ♪
♪ whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ whoaaaaaaaaaaaaaa ♪
And now quatronostro
and I will take our leave...
And that frock.
And this helmet.
Oh, heavens.
Never mind.
The helmet remains
with your people.
Take us with you.
Wherever you go,
we will follow.
That's a very big
responsibility.
How the hell am I supposed to...
Yes, I'll do it!
Tribore, and to a much lesser
extent quatro,
Will lead you
out of final space.
Now, cheer for me.
Cheer!
I am not one of you!
My child.
Are you certain?
Such dark power.
Ahhhh! No!
At last you can see
who you truly are.
Now stop fighting.
You're finally home.
What have we here?
The Gary!
H.U.E., take him out!
On it, Gary.
Your taquitos are here,
jack!
No, mooncake, you stay.
Huh: Pok! Pok! Pok!
I'm sorry,
but that's an order.
Eat lasers, jerk-face!
Agh!
Oh, my craaaaaappppp!
Never thought
I'd see you again.
But you just
keep showing up,
The Gary.
It's just Gary!
agh! Ah! Ah!
Chookity pok!
No, mooncake,
Gary is too close.
Dieeeee!
Agh! Ugh!
Do it!
Arggggghhhhhhh!
Your robot arm, Gary!
Use it!
Come on!
Turn into something!
Diiiiieeeee!
It's not working!
It's just a hand.
Oh!
Ohhhhhhhhhhh!
What? Ah!
Oh, my siiiiick!
Ugh!
Did you see that?!
Yes!
This is tight!
I can do things!
Look!
I so told him.
You were there when
I said it, right?
You were there.
Oh! It's a sword!
Oh, how did I
not know this?
Goodspeed?
You brought it.
Okay, that's new.
Run!
Hang on! Fox!
Goodbye, dad.
Always short of tomorrow.
Ash, get out of here!
I'm not leaving you.
There is no escaaaape.
Ash, go!
I'm gonna get you
out of here.
Bring them up, kvn.
You calling me in, coach?
I'm not your coach, kvn.
Pull them up!
But you have to
call me in.
Okay, you're in.
Kvn is in!
Agh.
Whoo!
You right on time, baby!
Peace out, dickweed.
Gary!
I need your help with fox!
Don't worry, fox.
We got you.
Let's cut these things
off you.
It's gonna be okay.
No! Ash!
Get out of here!
It's too late!
You're mine now!
- Watch out!
- No! Fox!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaahh!
No! Fox!
Ash!
Blast invictus out of him.
Ah! I can't!
Alright! Everyone,
back to the ship.
We can't leave him!
We stay, we die.
Oh, I have much more
in store for you
Than death.
Chookity poooooooookkkkk!
Mooncake!
Aggggghhhh!
Lightfold!
You let the key escape.
I never should have
trusted you with this.
bring me my ship.
Fox.
Incoming.
It's the lord commander's ship.
iSubDB.com - fast, modern, simple
Subtitles search by drag & drop