Am I becoming...
Nightfall?
Because if I'm her, then...
I no longer exist.
You're whatever
you decide to be.
I just want to be Quinn.
I'm sorry I shut you out.
I should have told you
what was happening to me.
Nah, it's good.
We're good.
Gary?
Uh...
Ash is back.
Oh.
Oh, snap! Really?
I'll be back.
Ohhhh, boy!
Ha ha ha ha!
Yo, Avocato.
Did you hear Ash is back?
Yeah, and that's why
I have these, baby.
Yo, cool those thrusters, okay?
This is Ash we're talking about.
Look, man, she flew
into a black hole after
Invictus, survived it,
and came back.
That is true.
Hey. So.
Uh, don't get weird.
Okay.
You just made it weird by
saying, "don't make it weird."
Yeah, it's, uh,
pretty weird now.
Well, Ash is uh, uh, uh...
Diff... different now.
She was already different.
Wait, are you saying she's even
more different than before?
Uh, she... yes.
Oh, god, that might be
too different.
Heeey...
Ash?
Hey.
It's me.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
You've done something
with your...
Hair.
Her hair?
She's an adult.
Gary, uhh... I think
we should go get a cookie.
Follow me, buddy.
Come here.
Oh, yeah, it's always
a good time for a cookie.
If you could feel
my danger glands right now.
Yes, I mean, like, how did she
get a haircut in a black hole?
Like, how?!
I got an idea.
I gently ask her is she good,
right?
Like, "hey, hey, you good?"
ya know, what about that?
Yeah, it's simple but effective.
Hey...
Hey, you good?
Good?
My brother is still missing,
or have you forgotten?
I haven't forgotten.
If you must know,
Invictus and I
are working things out.
Working things out.
Okay, one second.
Working things out?
That doesn't sound
very promising.
Oooh, a team huddle.
Iiiiiiiii like it.
I mean, is she even on our side?
You have a comment?
Tell me to my face.
Oh, hi. Yeah, we were
just saying how terrified
We are of you right now.
Especially these guys.
We were just, uh... ha ha.
We were just talking about,
bah-ohhhh...
Avocato's pecs.
Yeah, they're
just like crystal balls.
I mean, I-I can look inside,
and I can see the future.
I mean, look!
Yes! Yes!
Future things!
Yes!
Oh, things are happening.
I see it!
Get the hell off of me!
You don't have to be
scared of me.
Okay. I believe you.
Then we're glad you're back.
Alert.
Incoming energy signature
approaching this location.
Oh, double snap!
Let's go!
Where is it, H.U.E.?
Oh, I see it!
The blue ball, right there!
Oh, where, son?
Oh, yeah, I see that.
Really? Where?!
Oh!
Oh! Oh, oh, guys!
I see it, I see it!
You're late! Again!
Oh, no. What? Ohh!
Why are you here?
Oh, god!
Why are you so sassy?
Why?
You came here...
Oh! Gah! Oh! Gah!
What the hell,
you discarded milk dud?!
It's about Bolo.
He's in trouble!
Trouble, I tell you!
What's going on?
Nightfall? You're back?
No, Nightfall is dead.
Are you...?
Ash. Yeah.
Which means, you're...
I'm Quinn.
Just Quinn.
Can everyone
stop introducing themselves
To people they already know?!
We have to save Bolo!
Right... Now!
H.U.E., where the hell
did this idiot face take us?
We have been transported
five sectors away.
We are now inside
a class 9 nebula.
Bolo?
Bolo's mind is lost.
He's gone crazy!
Crazy, I tell you!
Yeah, I don't think we're
catching him at a great time
In his life right now.
Yeah, I mean, honestly,
he looks okay to me.
Oh, okay.
Just rip your arm off.
Great.
Thanks, Bolo.
Thanks for making me look bad.
Ooh!
Space crazies!
Iiiiiii like it!
How the hell did
this happen to Bolo?
A wound, I think.
It's gone bad, but not too bad.
Bad enough to rip your arm off!
This is bad!
Is this bad?
It's bad.
Yes, it is bad.
Very bad.
Uh, I think he's looking at us?
Um, oh, yeah, it's bad.
Okay, that right there
is no good!
You know what?
My eyes are locked with him,
And I am going to
telepathically send him
A powerful message of peace.
I think he's...
No! No, no, no!
No, no, no, no!
Let's get the hell out of here.
If we don't cure Bolo,
he will be lost to us!
What do we do?
And quickly, before he hits
a home run with us.
We need to travel into his mind.
There, we can find
his last spark of sanity.
With that, we can expel
the madness within.
This is just another delay.
Fox is out there!
We need to be looking for him.
Look, we will find Fox.
I promise.
Alright, new plan, everybody.
Help Bolo, find Fox,
and then we're gonna talk about
Ash's very sudden,
weird transformation.
And then...
We're gonna get the hell
outta final space.
Together.
Alright. Sit tight.
Ready, love?
Let's go!
Alright, milk dud, open him up.
Why are you giving me
this kind of sass?
Lightfold!
My god.
This is a horror show.
Where are we?
We've entered the deeper part
of Bolo's mind.
Darkness has begun to seep in.
Be careful.
It's possible to lose yourself
in such a place.
Oooh, sounds amazing!
I've been wanting
to lose myself forever now!
Alright, show us, guide us.
Nurture us...
Idiot face.
Wait, where's Ash?
Ash?
Chookity!
H.U.E.,
is Ash aboard the ship?
I'm not detecting
her life signs aboard.
Where could she have gone?
The mind is a place
of infinite space.
She could be anywhere.
Oh-ho-ho, the sass!
Feel this.
Holy Archimedes!
Told ya.
Don't ever let me
touch that thing again.
Gary.
You guys done?
There are a lot Bolos.
But only one of them is sane.
We have to find it!
We must hurry!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Aaaaaahhhhh!
Where are the others?
Hello?
Don't worry, Ash.
I will guide you.
Bolo?
'tis I.
Gotta say, you're sounding
pretty put together for a guy
Who just tore his own arm off.
Even in the depths of madness,
a spark of sanity endures.
I am that spark.
What do we have to do
to fix you?
Follow me to where
the troubles began...
To the chamber of doubt.
You think Ash is okay out there
In the infinite unknown
of Bolo's mind?
Yeah, just as about as good
as any of us.
Yeah, and I got to say,
this is pretty trippy.
Leave my nightmares alone!
Jill, tell me you and oreskis
aren't sleeping together!
Don't leave me here!
Please!
I beg of you!
Anyone!
Someone
find the dimensional keys!
These are all fractured
pieces of Bolo's mind.
Whoa. Oh, my god!
It's a cookie head Bolo!
That's new.
In his younger years,
he was experimenting
With hallucinogenic stars.
I told him not to.
Oh, no. Wait.
I gave them to him.
When the sands of time explode,
Piercing the veil
of tomorrow's hug.
Uh, whoa!
That made no sense.
But... It's kinda deep.
Well, his head
is made out of a cookie.
Hey, yo! Cookie head!
We gotta hang out sometime!
Dude blows my mind.
Gary is no hero.
His father was.
You will be the death of
everything!
Oh, he doesn't mean that.
The stars will fall
dark because of you!
That's rude.
You will silence
everything and everyone.
The tone of this is beginning
to change quite a bit.
Bolo, how did this
happen to you?
A parting gift from
my old friend oreskis.
Trapped in my cell for eons,
it was easy to maintain clarity.
But with freedom comes change,
and with change comes...
Confusion.
Confusion? About...
Invictus?
I have lived many
of your lifetimes.
There are constants.
Light, dark, life, death.
As I am consumed from within,
I realize these constants
are in flux.
The scales must be
balanced again.
Where are you taking me?
To meet someone that can help.
Fox?
Look at you.
You're all grown up.
Is it...
Is it really you?
You tell me.
What do you see, with both eyes?
If you're really Fox,
tell me the story again.
The one you only told me.
You sure?
You hate this story, baby sis.
Okay, but no tears this time.
Like so many tryvulians,
I was a child of war.
We were a peaceful people once.
A culture
that nurtured life and art.
And that's all I wanted, Ash...
To play music and share
that joy with others.
But they took that from me.
What did they take?
My dream.
My music.
My arm...
Fox...
Don't cry, Ash.
I didn't get
to the sad part yet.
They took my hand
so they could orchestrate
This symphony of war.
The dirge of tryvulia.
The anthem played
on this instrument of death.
They destroyed me
from the inside out.
And I was never even
given a choice.
I am so sorry.
But we do have
a choice now, Ash.
We can choose to make
our oppressors pay.
You know then,
where my powers come from?
Doesn't surprise me.
I knew you were special
since the moment we met.
You don't think
that makes me disgusting?
No! Proud.
Invictus chose you.
Invictus wants me to join you.
I want you to join us.
I love you, little sis.
What about Gary?
Everything that man
touches dies or breaks.
I won't let him break us, too.
- But...
- Trust me.
What the hell are upipiums?
Scuba divers do it underwater!
My summer house is a dodecagon.
I am not your hypotenuse
to triangulate.
What is that?
It's the spark!
The last spark of sanity!
Okay, is it just me,
or is he beginning to dim?
He's for sure getting dimmer.
Spark!
What do we have to do
to save your mind?
There's only one who can.
Ash.
Ash isn't here.
We don't know where she is.
The chamber of doubt,
I can feel her there.
Along with it...
Argh!
She's being deceived.
By who?
Invictus.
Get to the chamber of doubt.
Before it's too late.
Yo!
Can you get us there?
I don't have access.
He changed his passwords.
Uh, pink squirrel 89.
Uh, 84 is the best.
Oooh, the sass of it!
Now you do.
Do it, yo.
Us against the world,
just like old times.
What do you say, ashy?
Hold on.
I'm going!
Gary!
Ash!
Ash, come back.
It's invictus!
Nooo! No! No!
Uh!
Gary!
You will lose, the Gary.
Oh! Aah!
She belongs to me now.
You lost the moment
you let her go.
No! Invictus!
Don't make me do this!
No! No! No!
No!
Ashy?
I-I just wanted to be
a family again.
Fox...
Fox!
Gary!
What did you do?!
I-I didn't.
You killed my brother!
It's gone.
Invictus has left.
That's unsassy.
Why would it do that?
It got what it wanted.
May I offer you a cookie, Gary?
Sometimes, cookies help.
Fox...
Your pain is real, Ash.
But know this.
Fox was already dead.
He seemed pretty alive to me.
Invictus inhabited him.
Invictus also inhabited
Gary and Avocato and you.
And all of you are alive.
This was different.
Stop!
I want my brother's body.
And you shall have it.
Fox.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/7q7rw
Help other users to choose the best subtitles