Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Mr. Hamilton.
Yes.
You have water in the door.
Great.
Straight to
the convention center?
Absolutely.
You're American.
Mm-hm.
Arkansas.
Ah, Southern girl.
Yes sir, I am.
Call me Peter.
Sir makes me feel like
I'm retiring to Florida.
Oh, I'm so sorry about that.
What's your name?
I'm Brandy.
I've had one of those
fuckers of a morning, Brandy.
Mm, I'm so sorry to hear that.
I had this meeting, and this
passive-aggressive motherfucker
insinuates all
this shit about me.
Why was I so blind to this
fucking prick who was suggesting
I wasn't very good at my job?
Which I am, by the way.
God love him.
You know, Croesus once said,
"Count no man happy
until the end is known."
Ah. Look at you.
Let's make a deal.
I don't know you,
and you don't know me,
and since we don't
know each other,
we've got nothing to lose.
We can just be real.
Okay?
No masks.
Just the experience
of Brandy and Peter.
What do you say?
Does this usually work?
Okay.
No masks, no bullshit.
I'm up here thinking that I'd
love to pull the car over,
get in the back, have a
drink with you, and then...
see what else happens.
Oh, I wish I could.
I thought...
I said I'd
love to have a drink.
I have one sip of that,
and someone's going to jail,
someone's going to the ER.
I didn't come back here
for a drink, Peter.
I wanted to see what you
looked like from this angle.
You like what you see?
Your pictures do
not do you justice.
Come here.
Hold on a second, Peter.
I just want to ask
you a question first.
Yes, ma'am.
You're the boss now.
What'd you do?
What did I do?
Well, I don't know
when you did it, but...
I know you did something, Peter.
What are you talking about?
Why would someone not want
you to be alive anymore?
You know, if you modernize it,
what Croesus actually said is,
Count no man happy until
he's had a good death.
I genuinely try to give my
subjects a good death
when I can.
But I can't do that unless
I know what you did.
This isn't funny.
Who put you up to this?
Was it Ronny?
Aw, that bastard.
I knew it was.
Let's give him a call.
Put the phone down, please.
Ah, fuck!
Oh, please!
Please don't, please!
Don't beg.
Just think of it as though
it's already happened,
because it has.
Now answer my question.
Nothing!
I'm a nothing!
I'm a nobody!
I just move money
around for companies!
So you don't have
an answer for me?
No! No, no, wait, wait.
Okay, okay.
I know why.
No, you don't.
Subjects rarely do.
Okay, okay, please.
I'll pay you.
I'm sure you hear
this all the time,
but I'll give you every cent
that I've got. I'm in finance!
Executive code 74598CG.
Management Code 840227.
Confirmed.
Subject's closed.
You sound a little off, kiddo.
Anything to share?
Nope.
Nothing to report?
Gotta get a new set of wigs.
I don't know if they've
shrunk, or my head's grown.
Any hiccups?
You can stop worrying
about me now.
I'll stop worrying
when I stop worrying.
How's the mind?
Clear.
Fine.
You don't sound clear.
Shut up.
Or fine.
Just please shut up.
I'm just still in it,
that's all.
Did you close this subject
with dignity?
Yep.
Was management compromised?
Nope.
Then move the fuck on.
I think I might go back
to Boston for a bit.
Is that a good idea?
It's personal, Duke.
You want to talkprep for Riyadh?
Later?
Okay.
Well, let's go over
it like it's your S-A-Ts,
'cause management asked
for you specifically.
They'll be watching.
We cover every exit on this one.
Duke.
I'll call you
if you don't call me.
Keep your head down and
your powder dry, kiddo.
Head down, powder dry.
Got it.
Just doing the final
boarding check.
Flying time to Boston
will be approximately
six hours and 40 minutes,
bringing us in just
ahead of schedule.
Checking in.
Campbell.
Hello?
Management code 980456.
Executive Order 98602FT
We have a situation.
She's one of our own,
so do nothing
until you get the green light.
Just keep her in your sights.
Financial
advisor Peter Hawthorne
has been discovered outside
Paris inside a burned car.
French police are describing it
as an assassination
style killing.
Hawthorne, a key advisor
to the International
Monetary Fund,
had recently been accused
of money laundering
and election tampering
after several high level
officials of the...
♪ You can kiss me again
If you want to ♪
♪ I don't mind ♪
♪ You can kiss me again
If you want to ♪
♪ That'd be fine ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ And I guess We
have to play ♪
♪ The cards we've been dealt ♪
♪ And I guess I
got nothing ♪
♪ Whatever happens happens ♪
♪ 'Cause my life
Is falling apart ♪
Yeah,
should be an early flight.
Hey, Jude.
Can I walk you home?
Well, the funeral was a joy.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Yeah.
I know you had to do
it all by yourself.
I managed.
I managed big time.
- How's Mom?
- Irritable.
Oh. So she's fine, then.
Here.
Michael hates it.
So that's still happening, huh?
I'm sorry, okay?
You're my fuckin' sister.
Yeah, and you fuckin' left.
It happened.
I haven't seen you
for eight years.
I called you.
Yeah, every six months, for you
to deflect all our questions
about where the fuck you are.
You just quit
drinking, disappeared,
and left me holding
all these bags of shit.
I liked you better
when you were a drunk.
Nice.
I'd invite you in...
but Michael lives
here with me now.
I'll be at the hospital at nine
if you want to meet me there.
Hospital?
Are you fucking kidding me?
I emailed you last week.
What?
I figured that's
why you're here.
Ava, Mom had a heart attack.
It wasn't a heart attack.
You're such a drama queen.
It was angina.
It's nothing.
Heart attack.
Baby, will you get me that
other blanket, please?
The one on the chair?
Thank you.
You don't have to
stand in the doorway.
Now that you're finally here,
you might as well join us...
in the actual room.
Here.
Oh. No vase.
Hey, which nurse is on tonight?
Is it Gloria,
the-the tall redhead?
It's Sophie, Ma.
Oh, she's nice too.
Maybe she can get us a vase.
Mm.
They're very sweet to me.
They give me extra desserts.
Not that my waistline
could use it.
Well, I think you
look great, Ma.
Hm, I would have thought
maybe you'd be shocked
to see me this old,
considering you
haven't laid eyes on me
in such a long time.
You look exactly the same age.
It's really great work.
Come on, Ava.
Thank you, Ava.
But really,
it's just my moisturizer.
It's on the shelf
in the bathroom
if you want to grab
some for yourself.
It's funny,
I never would have thought
that the Netherlands
would be that hot,
but it seems like you're
getting a little sun damage.
Sun is a great idea.
Let's get you in the chair, Ma.
I'm not in the mood.
Dad only thought
about himself.
Nonsense.
Your dad was always pushing.
Always indestructible, always
thinking he was invincible.
And charm?
Pfft.
To burn.
He just charmed them all.
He had that manipulative
thing, like Ava.
Your hair looks terrible.
Thank you.
Well it just... it just
sits there, like, meh.
You could wear it
with some style.
You're not in the army anymore.
Well, I don't have
anyone to impress.
I could cut it for you while
you're here, if you want.
Well, I don't want
to put you out.
I cut Judy's hair all the time.
It is how I earned my living
before I gave up
everything for you two.
I do know what I'm doing.
I'm sure you do, Ma.
Forget that I mentioned it,
I wish I never brought it up.
Fuck, if you want to cut my
hair, you can cut my hair, okay?
Honey, how's Michael?
- Uh...
- Have you seen him yet, Ava?
No, not yet.
When you do, just remember,
try not to make it all about you
and your feelings, huh?
So...
Come on, let's hear it.
Tell us all about the fancy job.
Nothin' much to tell.
So this one could be tricky.
The approach should
be flirty but classy.
Anything aggressive is going
to scare the General off.
Is he married?
Separated.
What's the front door key?
Larry Sullivan,
a good friend of your father's
and the General.
Sunday lunches at your
childhood home in London
is a primary memory.
Sullivan used to tell you and
your little brother war stories
after the meal.
Got it, that's good stuff.
Stick to the script this time?
The General's a big
weapons mover and shaker
internationally, and management
stressed that it has to appear
like natural causes.
The necessary materials along
with your personal effects,
will meet you in Riyadh.
Go gentle on this one.
all eyes are on us.
Message received.
You be great, kiddo.
Head down.
Powder dry.
I know, I know.
You think that is funny?
I'm sorry.
You really have
a charming laugh.
It's your third best quality.
So what are my first and
second best qualities, then?
Of course, well, we could
discuss this upstairs...
I think at this time it's best
if we both leave you alone.
Miss Porter.
I'm so glad Larry sent you.
Mm.
Mr. Sullivan's a good
friend of my father's.
Practically grew up with him
at our house every weekend.
Well, so leave us now,
gentlemen.
So, the ambassador is a
very good friend of mine
and lets me use his office to
escape these horrible parties.
May I see it?
Yes. Please.
So how are you enjoying
this trip in Saudi Arabia?
I must warn you...
I'm a little slut.
Oh, my God.
I... I really like you.
It's completely painless.
It'll take about 15 minutes.
Everyone will think you died of
a stress-related heart attack.
You did something bad.
Right?
They wouldn't have
sent me if you hadn't.
I wish I knew what it was.
It was the name, right?
Sullivan.
Faulty fuckin' intel, right?
I said the name wrong.
Fuck you.
Help!
Help! Help!
Get her downstairs, it
looks like she's been hit.
Help the General!
Oh, my God!
Let's get you down to safety.
It'll be all right.
Calm down.
Almost there.
Keep moving, please.
I'm going to throw up if I
don't sit down for a second.
Don't move.
Fuck.
Sullivan, O'Sullivan.
It's a typo.
I disagree.
Who was responsible?
Well, let's say for the
purposes of this conversation,
it's my fault.
I'm supposed to get
you in and out safely.
I failed.
I'm sorry, darling.
It was meant to look
like natural causes.
I can do natural causes.
I know you can.
I can do an accident.
I can do gentle.
I know.
Duke, if you're gonna
close me, just do it now.
Management knows
it's not your fault.
Okay.
They arranged for one of the
more obscure Middle Eastern
terror factions to
claim responsibility.
So some anti-Western group's
gonna get 20 rocket launchers.
It's an error.
Let's move the fuck on.
How did the General fall
into our parameters?
Ava, don't tell me you've been
asking the subjects
what they did wrong again.
We're not going to survive
another episode of that.
Have you been using again?
No.
You're an addict.
Do you remember what that
behavior led to last time?
Yeah.
The hospitalization of three
wait staff 'cause they...
It's not like that this time.
It's just,
sometimes I just want to know
why I'm closing somebody.
Who gives a shit?
You're client-facing.
You're not a member of the
parole board or a prison shrink.
You're there to get the
SignEasy on the toe tag.
Yours is not to reason why,
yours is to do or die.
You know, I'm not going to
be able to protect you
a second time.
Duke.
I'm good.
All right?
I promise you.
Well, management is going
to be extra cautious.
Okay.
They want you off the
grid for a beat or two.
My father died.
I know.
You didn't kill him, did you?
Okay.
I need to go back
to Boston anyway.
Tie up some loose ends.
Finish some stuff.
That's a lot of pain points.
I know that.
You want me to tell management
you'd like time off?
Yeah.
I already did.
You asshole.
You're such an asshole.
And there you are.
Michael?
You look good.
I don't. I don't.
But thanks for saying it.
You do, actually.
Judy's inside with your mother.
Oh. Some things never
change, do they?
Some things do.
I'm happy for you guys.
I really am.
I probably should have told
you my sister's in town.
Yeah.
You gonna start showing
up without calling first?
To visit my mother?
I can hear you out there,
you know.
Come help me with
this fucking TV!
Can you believe
Michael remembered?
Thank you, Michael.
Ava, can you believe Michael
remembered I love irises?
Uh, yeah, I can believe
that he'd remember
something like that.
Want me to take a look at it?
Nope.
Leave it, you're going to
break the whole damn thing.
Uhh, it's fine, it's
just the antenna.
I've almost got it.
The three of you should go
out and have a nice dinner
tomorrow night.
- Uh. Ma, I...
- No, no.
Ava, take them somewhere nice.
- Uh, I don't...
- No, go on. Go on. Go on.
I need to know the
three of you get along.
In case anything,
you know, happens to me.
Touch wood.
Ma, stop it.
Wow, you fixed it.
Good work.
Hm.
I guess there was
nothing wrong with it.
About 10 years ago,
at my most fucked up,
I caught my dad
having an affair.
And I told him that
if he didn't tell Mom,
that I was going
to do it myself.
So... he cried.
And he promised me that he
would tell her about it.
But what he did instead was...
tell her that he caught me
stealing money from his wallet.
He said that I tried to
blackmail him into giving me
$1,000, and that if
he wouldn't do it,
that I would make up a story
about him having an affair.
I was a total alcoholic-addict
piece of shit at the time who
had been caught stealing
money for drugs, so...
naturally, she believed him.
I don't blame her.
But him...
The look on his face when she
was confronting me about it.
It was like he was amused...
for using me to save his ass.
I couldn't get through
that day without using.
Made me want to kill him.
Oh, I fuckin'
fantasized about it.
And I knew that if I didn't
leave immediately, that I would.
So...
I left and I joined the army.
When I heard he was dead,
I knew it was safe to come back.
That's all I got.
Thank you for sharing.
Hey, I'm Tony and
I'm an alcoholic.
Hi, Tony.
- Hey.
So when are our Syrian friends
going to claim responsibility,
has that been arranged?
Being arranged, as we speak.
Okay.
Goodness gracious me.
That was a hiccup.
That was more than a hiccup.
The Saudi branch has
completed refurbishment.
They say they're ready to
chase returns and get filled.
They say there's no way
it can lead back to us.
There's one way.
No, not her.
I recruited her, I trained her.
You recruited me,
you trained me.
I say she's a liability.
Simon.
She's best of breed.
There's no way she can be ID'd.
There's a risk factor.
Have you forgotten?
That was two years ago.
And she had valid doubts
about the ethical merits
of a couple of closures.
Valid doubts...
the pursuit of which led her
to have a fuckin' meltdown.
And she got back on track.
She's talking
to the fuckin' targets!
Again!
You told me...
when soldiers disobey the
chain of command, people die.
H-How do we know this?
I heard her.
I was in France.
Saudi Arabia wasn't her fault,
that's all I'm saying.
So whose fault was it?
My executive, my care and
feeding, my responsibility.
Well, thank you.
Thank you for saying it.
All right, then.
She is the most gifted
we have, you know that.
Okay.
She'll take a rest.
Let the dust settle.
I'll re-engage her
when the time is right.
That's the best decision.
It's your decision, Duke.
Just lettin' you make it.
Yeah.
Now get the fuck out of
here and let me enjoy
me son's christening.
Yeah.
Congrats.
So?
She's always been
Duke's favorite,
but she's a loose cannon and
a danger to the organization.
I wanted her killed in Riyadh
so he wouldn't know it was us.
But now...
Call Alain.
Tell him tooth or finger,
I don't care which.
I want to see a piece of her.
Hm.
What about Duke?
Don't you worry about Duke.
- But Dad...
- Listen.
Five days,
that man was tortured,
and he didn't give me up.
Five days.
But won't he know it was us?
Doesn't matter,
go outside to the party.
Spend some time with your
little brother, will you?
Go on.
Half-brother.
I'm good.
- I know you're angry...
- Stop talking.
I just...
You know how I always say
stop talking and you don't,
and it's part of our
hilarious banter?
This time I'm actually
telling you stop talking.
You're showing me a gun?
You know what happened to the
last person who showed me a gun?
And the person before that?
And the person before that, and
so on, if you follow my drift?
Saudi Arabia was their fuckup.
It was your fuckup, Duke.
You're trying to close me?
I know it may look like that,
but honestly, and no offense,
the company is not
trying to close you.
If they wanted you closed,
you'd be closed.
Uh-huh.
And you're sure of that
because...?
Because it was discussed.
Right.
Of course it was
fuckin' discussed.
You keep breaking protocol.
I warned you.
Anyway, I told Simon
you're not to be touched,
and if he wanted to do
something like that,
he would have to involve me.
And kill me.
Say that again.
The company had
nothing to do with it.
I got an ID on the guy from
my sources at Boston PD.
He's ex-French Special Forces,
dishonorably discharged,
and MIA for years.
He had a drug problem.
So it would seem that an
exceptionally unlucky junkie
tried to mug you...
You don't believe that, Duke.
Uh, because operatives with
black arts combat training
can't be addicts?
I know you don't trust anybody.
But I'm not anybody.
So, I'm gonna take my
hands out of my pockets,
I'm gonna put them up like this,
I'm going to step toward you...
place them on your shoulders
in a comforting,
but firm, fatherly manner...
and I'm going to ask you.
Are you sure you
don't want me to
hang around for a few days,
keep an eye on you?
I came here to get a
break from you, remember?
Here's his gun.
Can you run it for me?
Will do.
- He's a punk.
- No.
He's a punk.
- Teddy's a great bass player.
- He's a fine bass player.
And 'fine' not as
in, Oh, he's fine.
'Fine' as in average.
You can do better.
He hates Teddy coz he hit on
me at the first gig we played.
What? That's not true.
I don't even remember that.
Oh, you don't?
- No?
- No.
Oh, she can't drink that.
But first,
bullshit you'd forgotten?
Mm-hm.
And second, he just didn't
know that I had a boyfriend.
Hm. Yeah, okay.
Judy's in this incredible band,
you gotta hear 'em.
She heard actually.
Thank you, by the way.
She heard us play
the other night.
They're great.
You should come hear them
play at Wally's on Friday.
You're playing Wally's Cafe?
You're gonna blow up, Jude.
Well, you're biased.
Wow, you always wanted
to play at Wally's.
Come on, with all
the fake modesty.
You know you rant and
rave every night about
how underappreciated
you guys are.
Don't fucking say that.
What?
Could you not say that kind of
fuckin' stuff in front of her?
What kind of stuff?
What did I say?
You didn't say anything.
Why are you fuckin' asking her?
Don't laugh at me.
Judy, he's not laughing at you.
Okay, just don't do that.
Listen, what I say at home,
I say it at home.
And I... I've just been
complimenting you for the past
10 minutes, I was talkin'
about how brilliant you are.
Was that hard for you?
No. Look, you know, what?
I'm not gonna do this.
- Was it a chore for you?
- You're drunk. Okay?
That's what it is, you're drunk.
So.
So, what's... what's
your job like?
How's it work?
Oh, uh, it's not
that interesting.
Events and functions and endless
cocktail parties where the
food's terrible and I can't
drink the free booze.
What's the point?
So...
running around Beijing trying
to find almond milk for the
delegate from France
who's lactose intolerant.
Sounds like a glorified
flight attendant.
Oh, it's so weird being here.
There's so many memories here.
What memories?
- Babe.
- What?
She said it.
Let her explain it.
I didn't mean what
you're thinking, Jude.
No? You did.
You guys have fun.
Je-sus.
Well...
she was happy for a while there.
Mm-hm, and then?
And then your father died.
And she was the only one here
to take care of everything.
Then that, Ava.
Okay.
No, it's not, actually.
What does that mean?
Fine, I'll go talk to her.
No.
You don't get to come in here
and try to fix everything.
Okay?
You don't get to be that person.
Sorry.
I'm the one who
should apologize.
I left without saying goodbye.
You did.
Yeah?
Ava?
Sorry it's so late,
I don't know what to do.
What do you mean you
don't know what to do?
Uh, Michael hasn't come home.
He went out and he
hasn't come home.
Well, I'm sure he's just cooling
off like he always does, right?
You must be fucking loving this.
Why would I love you waking
me up at 5 am, yelling at me?
Fine, you know what?
I'm gonna go.
Jude.
I know you don't trust me.
I know I let you
down and disappeared.
But I'm here now.
Please...
just talk to me.
It's happened before.
Sometimes he doesn't
come home from...
Come home from where?
When did he start
gambling again?
He never stopped.
Right.
He's good at it.
You know that.
And we could really make a
start with what he could
pull down at the tracks.
But I told him...
no cards.
I told him no fucking cards.
Those people are...
they're so crazy.
You're sure he's playing cards?
It's okay.
I fucking... I hate it.
'Cause part of me is hoping
you know where he is,
and the other part is
gonna be pissed if...
So do you?
No.
Sorry.
Haven't seen you in a while.
Huh.
Is she expecting you?
Isn't she always?
Fuck no.
Hey, Toni.
My little lost lamb...
who threw up on my floor.
That was eight years ago.
I'm out.
I found this pretty thing
outside my door half-dead
with a needle stuck
between her toes.
A lot has changed.
I can see that.
She's not a thankful person.
I cleaned her up,
let her live on my sofa.
And then she took
my rabbit's foot.
Now she thinks she
can take him again.
Cash him out.
He's got someplace
he's gotta be.
That someplace isn't
with you anymore, is it?
Looking good.
How long you been clean?
Long enough.
Tick-tock.
That's enough, Toni.
Let's go.
I always liked you...
in my way.
Don't push my patience.
You need to go.
I'm going to be here
maybe a hour or so.
How much are you into her for?
He's not leaving this game.
Listen... You heard her.
Time to go.
Get your fuckin' hands off me.
Come on, Michael.
Lead the way.
Let's see how many holes
I can put in her face
before you shoot me.
Put it away.
Put it down.
Who taught you those
slick moves back there?
You always were a quick
study though, weren't you?
You had everyone's
number, right?
I'm going to leave you here.
You can get out now.
It's tomorrow... and the next
day and the day after
that you need to worry about.
How much?
I don't care about the money.
Let's pretend for a
second that you do.
How much does he owe you?
Seventy five, give or take.
Give me 36 hours.
You don't fuck with him.
That'd be mighty
magnanimous of me.
You got a lot of fucking nerve.
I guess we both do.
Yeah.
What the fuck was that?
Judy came to my hotel,
she was worried about you.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
All the stuff
you was doing.
Who the fuck is in
front of me right now?
Wonder Woman?
I started studying martial
arts when I was in rehab.
Nah.
No.
Don't give me the story
you give everybody else.
You tell me the truth.
Or get the fuck outta my face.
Oh, it's like that now?
You want to talk
about my honesty?
Look, I'm just trying
to get out of debt.
You do realize the number's
meant to get smaller, right?
No shit.
Toni's no joke, Michael.
Well, she's the only
one who would stake me.
That's helped you.
Oh, yeah?
Just what have you
been up to, Cakes?
Don't call me that,
I'm not that person anymore.
Oh, yes you are.
You'll always be Cakes to me.
I asked you to marry me,
and you said yes.
And then you just disappear
for eight fuckin' years!
I made a mistake with my family
and I had to get away from it.
You couldn't talk
to me about it?
So I got you a few days.
How much can you rustle up?
Not enough.
Well, do you need cash?
Not from you.
What is your alternative,
Michael?
This is my alternative...
right here.
What the fuck are you
going to do with that?
You gonna kill her?
I owe her 80 grand.
Crush or no crush, lucky charm...
she's gonna come for it.
And I gotta think
about Judy and...
Hey.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
I'm not yours anymore.
So you're happy.
I asked her to marry me.
And she said yes.
Ava.
Ava!
What'll it be?
Scotch, double.
You got it.
Shit.
You want it on the rocks?
Sure.
Good.
'Cause you got it on the rocks.
You a guest here at the hotel?
Room number please?
Ma'am?
You want me to charge
this to your room?
Sure.
Hey, man.
Hey.
I finally got me
73-year-old mother
to agree to come over here.
She's never been on a plane,
she's never left Ireland.
She's gonna be here
within the hour,
so at the expense of
sounding like a pushy prick,
what's on your mind?
So, Saudi Arabia wasn't
an error, was it?
You set her up, you wanted
her to get killed, right?
I underestimated her.
That was an error.
I can see that now.
And the executive you sent
to Boston to close her?
You haven't heard from
him in 24 hours or so?
That may count as
an error as well.
Go ahead and activate
cleanup protocol
on all of Alain's aliases.
- But...
- He's dead. Go on.
I really didn't want to put
you in the position
of having to sanction the kill.
Which you would have
had to have done.
The buck stops with me now.
I gotta make the hard calls.
You taught me this.
You're not my superior
officer anymore.
Now, if that causes you any
discomfort, Jesus, I'm sorry,
but get the fuck over it.
This isn't like the war.
There are no sides.
This is business,
and it's brutal.
And I know you like Ava.
Wanted to spare your feelings.
Rely on your understanding
afterwards, you know?
What does she think happened?
Let's hope she thinks
what I told her to think,
that she was
attacked by a junkie.
I lied to her.
Good.
You need to rescind
the kill order.
You know I can't do that.
Sure you can.
Hey, what the fuck, man?
Duke! Duke! I knew it was you!
You did? Oh, boy.
You knew it was me?
Really?
Hey, is it true that you are
the prettiest in your family?
Yes.
Is it true that you're the
smartest in your family?
Yes.
Your whole family?
Come to Daddy, Monster.
Come here.
Oh my God, where's your mother?
Shower.
Yeah, did you sneak
out on your own?
Crafty.
Well, Uncle Duke's gonna have a
job for you with those skills.
Oh, no, he won't.
One daughter's enough?
The field is no
place for a lady.
I think we've established that.
Say goodbye to
Uncle Duke, Monster.
Bye, Uncle Duke.
Bye, beautiful.
All right you, get in there.
Bring her out to her mother, and
don't let her back out again.
Yes, sir.
No! Stop! It's not
your fight, darlin'.
Go on, get out of
here, leave us alone.
Leave us alone!
Come in.
You should have stayed
at the hospital.
You sure you don't want to
give it a few more days?
I certainly did not want
to give it a few more days.
I mean, just in case
you're not completely...
Ohhh!
I hate that kind of talk.
You can go to hell with
your just in case garbage.
Touch wood.
Go on, touch wood.
Both hands.
Hearts.
Anyone ever talk to you about
going on some OCD medication?
Ha.
That's what you
would like, isn't it?
Drug me up and then throw
me away in the loony bin.
Here we go.
Ma.
I have to talk to
you about something.
You should choose carefully
what you tell me, Ava.
'Cause you can't...
un-say it, and I
can't un-hear it.
And I would love to believe that
you work at the United Nations,
honey, I really would.
I'm sorry.
I... I knew who your father
was when I married him.
I didn't want to look at
that part of him, so...
I focused on the half of him
that made me happy and I, uh,
ignored the half of him
that broke my heart.
If I'd have called him out
then for screwing around,
it'd be not only
for his betrayal,
it'd be because he lied
about his daughter
to save his own ass, and...
well, any decent mother would
have to leave the man then,
right?
I was scared to be alone.
I chose him over you.
That's why I didn't
want to talk to you.
I dreaded you calling every
six months, because...
you knew what I'd done.
Whatever it is, whatever it
is that you've been hiding...
I don't care.
Because I can see
in your eyes
that it's given you
a strength...
You would never do
to your child...
what I did to mine.
I can see, you are not scared.
And that...
makes me very proud.
Mom.
Ava, it's your turn...
and I have to win so
I can get some rest.
Okay? So...
Day like this
reminds me of home.
Does it?
Yeah.
And I'm going to go to Boston.
Take care of Ava meself.
Mm.
Good luck.
Is there anything you'd
like me to say to her
before I put her in the earth?
Well, tell her I'm sorry I
couldn't be there to watch her
cut your heart out.
Will do.
Yep?
Management Code 980456.
Executive Code, please?
Executive Code 74598CG.
Confirmed.
Who's this?
Hello Ava, I'm Simon.
Did Duke ever tell you about me?
No?
Well, I'm not surprised.
I was his first protégé.
Broke him in for you,
so to speak.
I always said about Duke,
if he didn't teach me everything
I know, he certainly taught
me all the useful shit.
Well, I never fuckin' heard of
you, man, so what do you want?
I just killed him...
because of you.
If that's true, Simon...
I'm gonna fuckin' kill you.
I imagined you'd say that.
Duke asked me to tell you he's
sorry he won't be there to watch
you cut out my heart.
Is Judy here?
No, Judy's at a gig right now.
She, uh, she'll be back
at around 1:00, 1:30.
Come away with me.
What?
Come with me.
Come with you where?
Uh, I don't know.
Just... go away together.
Go someplace nobody can find us.
Judy's pregnant.
We weren't even tryin'.
We just found out.
She's here.
Stay back.
I asked Michael to
run away with me.
Do you believe that, Toni?
My own sister's fiancé.
I didn't even think about
the consequences for Jude.
I've never told anyone this...
but I've been paid
to kill 41 people.
And even after all that...
it wasn't until I did
that to my sister...
that I really knew
what I was capable of.
I know my secret's
safe with you.
Aaah!
Now we're square.
It's paid.
Never, ever bother
my family again.
We're done now.
Simon.
It's a lovely
morning for it, Ava.
I see you took a
trip to the minibar.
What would Duke say?
Tsk, tsk, tsk. Shocking.
I'm a little bit rusty.
Hey, come here!
You know what, Simon?
Shut up, babe.
Oh, that's right.
You don't like it when I
talk to my subjects, do you?
This time...
I know what you did.
Fuckin' hell.
Count no man happy...
Until the end is known.
Yeah.
Yeah, Duke made me read
all that Greek shit too.
I see why he liked
you so much, Ava.
You've got moxie.
If I see you again, I
will fucking kill you.
Go that way.
Attention, hotel guests,
please evacuate the building.
Do not attempt to
use the elevators.
Please use the stairwell.
This is not a drill.
Evacuate the hotel immediately.
Management Code 98045FT.
Put security around my
family on high alert.
Double the guard detail.
The object is still open.
Agh!
My family.
I have no interest in them.
I do understand that if you...
...if you wanted to take
your time with this.
Count of five?
Why not?
One.
I'm here for my sister.
Holy... Oh my God, get
in here, get inside.
I need to talk to you alone.
We're fine.
What happened?
I need you to listen to me.
Go get Mom and get out
of the country tonight.
Just for a month or two
until I can contact you.
What?
Don't go to Europe or the UK.
You sound crazy right now.
Here's an account
number and a code for
an offshore account in my name.
Memorize this and
then burn it, Jude.
There's $500,000 in there.
Use whatever you need.
Here's $20,000.
This will be enough to get you
all out of the country and safe.
What the fuck?
Jude, come on, listen.
Are you fucking listening to me?
I need to you to do exactly
what I'm telling you to do.
What? What is going on?
Why would I do that?
Because I need you to
take care of the family
the way I was never able to.
All right?
You're a momma now.
Okay?
You need to take care
of your baby.
I could never make him as
happy as you obviously do.
This came for you.
Thank you.
Ava.
Who are you?
Nobody that you want
your child to know.
Count no man as happy
until his end is known.
What Simon would call
all that Greek shit.
It's not until you
know how someone dies
that you know what
really mattered to them.
What they cared about,
what they'd sacrifice for.
What they would die for.
Who they loved and who
loved them in return.
We don't have much
control over our lives.
But our end?
Sometimes we write that story.
If you're getting this,
you know my end.
I've never been happier.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN