_
But we can also always keep
track of what you need...
a heart or a liver.
You can extract them intact?
Yes. We know where not to grab.
Then we don't squash the
part of the specimen you need.
And you can change its position?
If we need to. Again, ultrasound helps.
With the added dilation, we
can change it to a breach.
- So?
So you have to tell me
what you're thinking.
- I can't guess.
- I think you can.
Well, you're against abortion,
so my guess is you're repul...
I'm a human being. And yes, I am appalled
by a doctor calmly eating yogurt
while talking about selling...
- No, not selling.
- $100 a specimen.
To preserve, package and deliver.
- That is legal.
- Oh, God, do you hear yourself?
Parts of babies.
Preserving, packaging and
delivering parts of babies.
- Parts of fetuses.
- So you think there's
anything wrong with that video?
I think it's shop talk.
I think if you listen to any two doctors...
- Or abortionists.
- Talking over
drinks or yogurt
about an appendix removal,
it would sound just as bad.
- So you know it's bad?
- No, I know it's an effective
piece of propaganda. That's all.
And why is it so effective?
Because the majority of Americans
only support abortion if they
don't have to face the fact
of it, if they don't have to hear the talk
- about where to squash...
- The majority
of Americans only support anything
if they don't have to face the fact of it.
How the hamburger ended up on their plate.
Except this has a face.
It's not an appendix.
It's a human being.
Well, that's the difference between us.
I don't believe it.
- How did you even get it?
- The video?
- Citizens for Ethical Medicine.
- Oh, God.
That radical anti-abortion group?
It's not radical. Why is something radical
- merely because you disagree with it?
- What, they pretended to be
a bioengineering firm needing human tissue?
- Aborted fetal organs.
- And, what...
you're-you're planning
to do what with that?
- Sue.
- Who?
- Her. Her organization.
- For what?
- Well, that's where you come in.
- No.
- It's not about you being a lawyer.
- Oh, really?
- Thank you.
- It's about you telling me
- how Mr. Dipple can sue.
- Well, he can grow a uterus.
You don't have standing.
What are you gonna sue for?
- Selling of fetuses.
- No.
What, $100? That's nothing.
The repositioning of
fetuses for a breech birth?
- That's it.
- No.
Right?
You need a woman who had an abortion there,
a woman who was lied
to about the procedures,
and a woman who suffered
measurable harm as a result.
- Those are the three criteria?
- Yes.
You have someone?
You tell me.
Stacy Groom. 27 years old.
Had an abortion, regretted it.
She fulfills all three criteria.
I'm not asking you to take her case.
I won't take her case.
I'm asking you to cross-examine her.
Do your worst. See if
she's ready for court.
Mr. Crouse. Can you start today?
Sure. What do you need?
Information on this woman.
She regrets an abortion
and is suing the abortion clinic.
What's the cap on hours?
Cap?
Whenever the work is done, it's done.
I'm on my way.
The bills are piling up
and we do not have enough revenue
coming in to pay our bills,
so we need to compensate.
We can't keep living DUI to DUI.
- I'm open to suggestions.
- Well, for one thing,
we need to ration. We're spending too much
on investigator hours.
- Should I leave?
- No.
Look, we still need to be effective.
We can't ration our way to success.
- Then what?
- We cancel our Westlaw subscription
and we double our efforts
to bring in new clients.
- We eat what we kill.
- What does that mean?
It means that Lucca and
I both get two-thirds
of whatever business we
bring in. No more 50-50.
It'll make us hungrier, work harder.
- If you want it, I want it.
- I want it.
Where you going?
Business lunch.
Thank you for agreeing to meet.
What do you need?
I'm a fan.
Uh, here, have some wine.
I... I-I'd pour it, but it'd...
- get all over the place.
- How exactly are you a fan?
The T-Port case.
You're scrappy, you're aggressive.
You deserve better.
- What's better?
- $90,000 a year.
Another 30 guaranteed as bonus.
Plus ten percent of whatever
business you bring in.
No, thanks.
You're four years out of law school, Lucca.
You don't have that much room to negotiate.
Oh, I'm not negotiating.
I just don't want to be bait.
You're trying to lure Alicia, right?
So, either make it clear why you want me
or save your money.
Hey, Mom?
I want to help.
Don't worry, we'll be fine.
No, mom, let me help. What can I do?
Okay.
Cold call.
Go through the phone book.
Call businesses, one after another.
See if they need legal representation.
Where would I start?
Mid-level insurance firms.
And maybe real estate.
How do I know it's mid-level?
Look at the size of the
ad, see how big it is.
Okay. And do I get a
percentage if I find anyone?
I thought this was to help.
It is. But do I get a percentage?
Okay. I will give you
half a percentage point for any booking.
One percentage point would
be even more of an incentive.
You're right.
But what I'm offering
is half a percentage point.
Stacy Groom. I work as a copy
editor at Myrtle Publishing.
Did the 8th Street clinic
perform an abortion on you?
They did. Ten months ago.
And did Dr. Hallie Fisher
perform that abortion?
- The woman on the video?
- Yes.
Did she accurately represent
the procedure to you?
No. She tricked me into
donating fetal tissue.
She never told me it would be sold.
She even...
flipped the baby into a
breech position to help
- better harvest the organs.
- And what, if any,
damages did you suffer as a result?
Well, I, um...
I cry all the time now.
I can't eat. I can barely sleep.
It's, uh,
hard to get to work every day.
My work has suffered.
Are we boring you, Diane?
No, quite scintillating.
- Anything?
- You tell me.
Why don't you work for us full-time?
I like keeping my options open.
We need a dedicated investigator.
You could make more money.
Money's not everything.
Yes, but sometimes it's something.
I'm good.
I may need more of this.
Call me.
You said that Dr. Fisher
tricked you into donating tissue,
but isn't that your signature
there on the release form?
It is. So?
So were you under the influence
of anesthesia or some other
drug when you signed this?
- No.
- So how did she trick you?
Well, she said it was for
medical research purposes.
Not to make money.
Uh-huh. And how do you
know it was to make money?
I saw it on the video. And is
that when you started experiencing
these symptoms... the symptoms
that kept you from work...
right around the time you saw this video?
- I guess.
- So the procedure
was ten months ago,
and you've been experiencing these symptoms
for one week?
- Two.
- Any chance you
went to a doctor and got a
diagnosis in those two weeks?
- I haven't had time.
- But you have
had time to go to the
Church of God in Christ
eight times since you
joined... two weeks ago.
Uh, what do you mean by "join"?
Well, did you accept
the Lord as your savior
two weeks ago during an altar call
at the Church of God in Christ?
- Is that illegal?
- No, not at all.
But two months ago, did you give this
anonymous quote to the Tribune?
"Choice is under attack
by right-wing forces
in this country."
So?
So it seems like you tend to
go from one extreme to another.
How did you get that quote?
It's why you pay us.
So what are you gonna do...
bring the case or not?
- Not.
- Really?
You made your point.
Wouldn't it be odd if the
person who respected you the most
was the person you agreed with the least?
- That would be odd.
- I'm putting those undercover tapes online
and seeing if anybody takes it seriously.
Well, that was easy.
_
Enjoy Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Hey, Grace, what's up?
No, I don't know anyone
in need. Why do you ask?
Are things that bad over there?
Oh, Grace, hold on a minute.
But I'm the one who just wrote a check.
Grace, I got to go. I'll
call you if I think of anyone.
Uh, Ms. Paige. Hello.
Mr. Gold. Hi.
I was wondering if I'd see you.
Eli, please.
Do you have a minute? There's
something I'd like to...
you know, say or-or discuss.
Uh, th-this is temporary.
Mm. It's fine. Very... cozy.
Um...
Oh, thank you.
Actually, I'm sorry, I
have to... Could I just...
Oh, sorry.
Excuse me.
I have something to discuss.
Have I done something wrong?
No, no, no... What do you mean?
Well, you sound serious.
Oh, well, that's just
who I am.
I'm working on that.
I... I told a joke yesterday.
What was it?
Um, how do you...
No, wh...
No, I forgot.
It'll come back.
It-It's about your business.
And-and actually, it is a bit serious.
I think I know what it's
about. The salary floor?
Yes.
- It's communism, right?
- No.
- Socialism?
- No. Well... y-yes, it is a bit.
I like my employees. They work hard.
So I decided to give them all a raise.
To $75,000 for everybody?
Yeah.
It's my money.
Why is that bad?
Oh, it's not bad... for your employees,
but... for Peter.
Oh. Ah, he's suddenly
a socialist sympathizer.
All the campaign asks is that you wait
until after the election
before you give your raises.
Oh, so, there are two fish in a tank.
And, um, one fish says
to the other fish, "How
do you drive this thing?"
That was the punch line, because, you know,
we-we think they're in fish tank,
but actually, they're in a... tank tank.
Funny.
So, have-have you thought
of the legal ramifications
of giving everybody $75,000?
Yes, I've discussed it with
my in-house counsel.
How about you hear from a second opinion?
I don't want to hear it.
No, I... What do you mean?
You yelling at me about Landau.
What did you do with Landau?!
Wait. Why are you here?
Because I have a client.
What happened with Landau?
The election board.
I punted a vote on the machines
by ordering a study, and Landau's furious.
Because you two had a deal.
I knew it!
Well, let's just file that one
under ongoing disasters, shall we?
I'm sending you a client who
just happens to be a billionaire.
Courtney Paige?
Yes. It's probably just
a couple of hours work,
but you can bill what you want.
Thank you.
Yes, that's all I want is-is...
- is your thanks.
- Thank you.
And... I need you to talk Courtney
out of what she wants to do.
I know, I know,
you can't promise anything...
that would be unethical...
but she's planning to give everybody
in her company a raise to $75,000 a year.
It is in her best interest,
both legally and politically,
not to do so.
Also, it hurts Peter.
That's just my opinion.
I'm not telling you how to advise.
You want to encourage
her to chase socialism
to the graveyard of history...
be my guest.
Yes?
Dr. Hallie Fisher is suing
to take down the teaser,
and block the release
of our undercover video.
And?
And that's bad.
Not for you, but for me.
No, it's prior restraint.
No judge will allow it.
Go ahead, just put it online.
Judge Margovski already granted
an emergency hearing today.
I know you're no fan of
Citizens for Ethical Medicine,
but this isn't about abortion anymore.
This is about the First Amendment.
Which you're using as a weapon
to attack women and medicine and choice.
"Anyone can defend a sympathetic
client with popular beliefs.
"The real test of the First Amendment
"is whether we are willing to stand up
for people and ideas we hate."
Well, that's more persuasive
and plainspoken than you normally are.
I was quoting you.
You said that in a speech to Emily's List.
You may not agree with our
tapes or how they were made,
but prior restraint is just wrong.
And you know it.
Why do I have to be so damn convincing?
= synced and corrected by Shahrazade =
...www.addic7ed.com...
Just remember,
you're representing the Constitution.
Diane, hello. God bless.
I'm Heidi. I shot the video.
- I'm your client.
- Hi.
Stay away from my uterus!
We don't want your dirty uterus!
Sorry, Diane. Just ignore her.
You know I'm not pro-life.
Yes, I know technically,
but you're here to show your support.
No, I'm not here to show anything.
Stop killing women!
Stop killing children!
This secret tape is already
causing irreparable damage
to the important work that
Dr. Fisher does, Your Honor.
Stand up, Hallie.
- Yeah!
- No!
No! No! People.
Let's get this clear.
You're guests here.
That's all.
No waving of signs, no...
In fact, John, let's
collect those signs, okay?
Thank you.
Go ahead, Counselor.
When I was growing up in the Bronx,
there was one thing I was always told.
Sneaks can't be rewarded for sneaking.
Your Honor, this isn't about sneaks.
This is a textbook case of prior restraint.
If we're against it
with the Pentagon Papers,
we should be against it here.
Now that offends me.
I know Danny Ellsberg, and
this woman is nothing like...
Then sue... after the fact.
If you think there is harm,
the proper remedy is a suit for damages.
She's not wrong, Ms. Steel.
The law strongly disfavors
this kind of censorship.
Yes, except that this secret
tape was made illegally.
Illinois again requires two-party consent.
Hallie, did you consent to this tape?
- I did not.
- There. One party.
Consent wasn't necessary here, Your Honor.
The conversation took place
in a crowded yogurt shop.
There was no reasonable
expectation of privacy.
Of course there was expectation of privacy.
- Your Honor...
- She's alone at a table...
No, no, no.
Let's look at the tape
and see if this yogurt shop was crowded.
Actually, Your Honor,
I would suggest that the very reason
for this pre-trial motion
would preclude the gallery
from seeing this tape,
this secret tape.
You want me to clear the court?
Until you rule on our motion,
Your Honor, this tape should
not see the light of day.
John, let's go.
All right, everybody, I'll ask you
to grab your things, step out.
God bless you, Diane. Thank you.
There was one day where,
as I was working my forceps
into position, trying to get a good grip,
I was literally almost
doubled over from cramps.
As you can see, Your Honor...
I think it's pretty clear...
the yogurt shop was crowded,
- and there was no expectation of privacy.
- Wait, wait.
Is that all you need from the tape?
- Yes, Your Honor.
- John, bring them back in.
Let's go, everybody in.
Okay, go ahead.
There is no expectation
of privacy, Your Honor.
They were three feet from the next table.
Which was occupied by children.
- So?
- So, like my mom used to say...
stick to the main tent
and avoid the sideshows.
- What does that even mean?
- It means that children do not undermine
the expectation of privacy
because they don't have the capacity
- to understand what it means.
- But their mother
came and joined them at the table,
and Dr. Fisher still carried on
with no expectation of privacy.
- That is not true.
- Look at the tape.
You're kidding.
Sheriff, we need to clear the court.
Come on!
I don't remember when he got divorced.
Um, maybe seven, eight years ago. Why?
Oh, just curious.
Well, Eli has a daughter. Marissa.
He loves her very much. So do I.
He's a good guy... for a political animal.
Well, I know why Eli doesn't want
a salary floor, but what
do you think of it, legally?
Well, shareholders may feel devalued,
and clients may feel insulted.
You think they'll sue?
Potentially.
Senior employees may be
upset that new hires are making
almost as much from day one.
You might want to offer a sliding scale
where senior employees
get the largest raises.
Do you know Matthew 20?
Do I...? No.
Um, I'm sure my daughter does.
All the hired hands
are given the same pay.
The last who arrived
and the first who worked
in the heat of the day.
- Why?
- Because "The last shall be first
and the first shall be last."
Okay, um, but I do know
that Bible stories aren't
usually the best business plans.
Yes, but you know what the bottom line is.
It's your money.
Amen.
_
There. That's the mother.
No kids, no sideshow. Adults.
Yes, but Dr. Fisher was whispering,
which demonstrates her desire
to keep the conversation private.
Oh, come on. It demonstrates
her awareness that she was
in a public place where
she could be overheard.
Wait a minute.
Sheriff, you know what we're missing.
Oh, do I, Your Honor.
We're open for business. Hear ye, hear ye.
So what does whispering mean?
I think it means Ms. Lockhart is right.
The yogurt shop did not afford a reasonable
expectation of privacy.
Motion denied. Any other motions?
Your Honor, yes.
We ask for a recess to prepare a new one.
Lockhart, Agos & Lee.
- Please hold.
- Bea.
I didn't know we had an appointment.
We don't, but we need to talk.
Ms. Wilson, Ethan Carver.
I recognize you from your appearances
for National Council on Women's Rights.
And I recognize you
from the congressional hearings
on defunding Planned Parenthood.
Uh, why don't you two wait in the office?
- I think that's a good idea.
- Mm.
- How can you do this?
- Bea,
if you're talking about this
case, it's not about choice.
It's about the First Amendment.
That's a nice, neat justification.
The pro-choice position isn't
so weak that it can't stand up
- to the marketplace of ideas.
- This isn't about censorship.
This is about an orchestrated,
right-wing war on women.
Bea, I will join you in arguing
against the substance of these tapes,
but only after they're made public.
But that's insane. We wouldn't
have to argue against them
if they weren't made public.
Oh. Excuse me.
Hey. I think I know what
they have, the opposition.
What is it?
A non-disclosure agreement.
The Citizens for Ethical
Medicine employees signed a NDA
at the conference before
sitting down with Dr. Fisher,
which expressly prohibits any
recording or dissemination of information.
I see that.
This seems pretty ironclad, Diane.
It's a contract of adhesion, Your Honor.
It's an asymmetrical agreement foisted
on someone ill-equipped to
know what she was signing.
"Ill-equipped?" Really?
Three pages of non-optional legalese.
This is no different than the
preposterous user agreements
- we all click "agree" on.
- There's a big difference.
The online agreements don't leave any room
for you to make alterations or amendments.
And, Your Honor, sneaks...
Can't be rewarded for sneaking.
I know that, and I agree.
This non-disclosure agreement holds.
Do you have any other arguments, Diane?
Courtney's ex-husband's suing
her for breach of fiduciary duty.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
He's still a partner in the company.
I thought her lawyer would know that.
Who are you calling?
Well, she wasn't the
duped, she was the duper.
Your Honor, once again,
this is an overbroad interpretation.
Listen, if she was not willing
to accept the conference's rules...
Alicia, did you find a new client?
Yes and no. Eli referred someone.
Not just someone... a very rich
- and a very powerful someone.
- Shh.
Her husband is part-owner of her company.
I need you to look into him.
- His name...
- Larry Oliver.
Did you get that?
I got it. What am I looking for?
Any weaknesses, vulnerabilities.
Maybe it would help to
know why they divorced.
Jason, do you have a minute?
I need an answer, now.
You have to go?
Yeah. Can I call you back?
Sure.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Yes, I'm calling from
the law offices of Florrick/Quinn.
The Midwest offices.
I'd like to set a meeting
to discuss what our firm can do for you.
Okay, sure. Thank you.
_
Good afternoon, I'm calling from the
Midwest offices of Florrick/Quinn.
I'd like to set a meeting
to discuss what our firm can do for you.
Oh, could you hold on a second.
Let me close my door.
That's much better.
Would you mind transferring me
to whoever deals with outside counsel?
Oh, really?
You're looking for a new firm?
Well, that's great news.
Do you mind transferring me to...
whoever I should talk to.
Thank you.
This is Bea Wilson at National
Council on Women's Rights.
Who am I speaking to?
Grace Florrick
at Florrick, Quinn & Associates.
I was hoping we could discuss possibly
representing your organization
in all of its legal concerns and issues.
And so on.
Yes, I would like that.
We're just in the process
of considering moving our legal business.
When would you be able to accommodate us?
Accommodate you?
As in becoming your law firm?
Yes.
This is Florrick/Quinn as
in Alicia Florrick, yes?
Yes.
We've worked with her before.
When could we make the transfer?
Wh...
Wh-Whenever you want.
Good.
Please call me tomorrow,
and I'll send over the necessary papers.
Mrs. Lockhart,
if you ever need anything,
I'm one of the new associates... Brian.
Ms. Lockhart.
Oh, that's right, sorry.
Use me in any way you want.
Carrying boxes, killing spiders.
Brian, can you give us a minute?
Sure. That I can do.
Get out of the way.
Good hires, these smart ones.
That was Mike and Ginger
from the Justice Center.
They're leaving.
This is a First Amendment case.
I know that, and you know
that, but they don't know that.
Then have them talk to me.
They don't want to be
argued out of their position.
There isn't much neutral
ground on abortion.
On free speech.
Your Honor, we will stipulate
that the non-disclosure agreement
applied on the premises,
but the conversation
did not take place there.
They met at the conference and were on
- an officially scheduled break.
- Off-premises.
You're saying the
conversation wasn't covered
by the non-disclosure agreement
because it happened somewhere else?
- Yes.
- Your Honor, we can show that the trip
to the yogurt store was just
an extension of the conference,
but we will need to see the video again.
Canning & Associates.
Lucca.
I will see you now.
Don't look now, but the guy
I kicked out of your office
just walked by.
Why would you do that?
Well, where else are you going to work?
A shared office? Out of your home?
I haven't taken the job
and you haven't made your pitch.
If you really want me here...
We're gonna play let's make a deal.
But if you say "yes,"
you get what's behind all three doors.
Montego-Portmore Estates.
It's the second largest
hospitality chain in Jamaica
and soon to be your client.
Your dad's Jamaican; they'll like that.
Arthur Beadle and Sons.
The department store?
Yeah, one of the sons had some trouble.
He's in and out of prison.
Your work as a bar attorney
will go a long way with Arthur.
This one's special.
Inner Heart Hope?
They perform low-cost surgeries
in Third World nations via remote feed.
They need someone like you.
Look, I want you, Lucca,
not Alicia,
so give it some thought
but I need to know within 24 hours.
So?
You ever hear that joke about the Irish guy
who goes to confession?
I can't say that I have.
He says he's committed adultery.
The priest asks,
"Was it Mrs. O'Leary?"
The guy says no.
"Mrs. O'Grady?"
No.
"Mrs. O'Donnell?"
Still no.
Guy walks out of confessional and says,
"I got three good leads."
Canning gave you names?
Montego-Portmore Estates, Arthur Beadle,
and Inner Heart Hope.
They add up to $10 million.
I called them all on the way over.
We can pitch them tomorrow.
Mm-hmm.
Not here... it'll look like a hobby.
Hey, Mom.
I got a client.
That's great, honey. Good job.
We'll be right back.
Hello, Florrick, Quinn & Associates.
This is Grace. How may I help you?
Hello, this is Ginger Gaye
from the Justice Center.
Bea Wilson from NCW gave me your number
and said you might be open to new clients.
Yes. I think we are.
What was your business again, ma'am?
The Justice Center.
I know we're not as big as NCW,
but we have $2 million a
year in billing, and growing.
We're moving on from Lockhart, Agos & Lee.
Yes. I mean, we are a little busy,
but we're never too busy
for a business like yours.
I have a couple minutes. Walk and talk?
Great.
As you can see, the conversation
starts at the conference
in the hotel and continues as they walk
across the street to the yogurt shop.
Ms. Steel is right.
The conversation was continuous,
which makes this meeting essentially
an extension of the conference.
The nondisclosure agreement holds.
The release of the full
video is hereby enjoined.
Your Honor, we ask for a recess
to prepare another motion.
Let it go.
Granted.
Recess for lunch.
Ms. Lockhart, do you have a moment?
Uh, no, I don't.
There's still a way you can fight this.
Maybe we can talk another time.
Cary.
She's a whistle-blower.
Try the whistle-blower statute.
Quote the Bible all you want, Court,
but you're just trying to
screw me out of what is mine.
No, Larry, I'm trying to make a difference.
Which is something you
would know nothing about.
I went to Cambodia. Sri Lanka.
All to film footage for Citizen
Nonino. What do you call that?
Squandering my money on
making experimental films
that nobody has or will ever see.
If I may offer a solution.
What if instead of a salary floor,
your employees received
unlimited vacation and sick days?
Alicia?
Yes. That is one way you could go.
Do you, um, rent out that conference room?
Your Honor, at this time
my client would like to file
pursuant to the Illinois False Claims Act.
The whistle-blower statute?
All due respect, Judge,
but this is what my mother
would call "fercockt."
Who is your whistle-blower?
- She is.
- Diane, you are amazing.
I admire you so much.
Your Honor, as my father would say,
this is like putting an ass's
bridle on a Model T Ford.
Okay, I don't even get that one.
The 8th Street Clinic receives
state funding for procedures they perform,
which they are misrepresenting.
The tapes demonstrate that fraud,
and therefore they cannot be censored.
It's a creative claim, Ms. Lockhart.
Please approach.
We need to talk.
This is not ex parte, but we need to talk.
Whenever you want, Your Honor.
Now.
Diane, what are you doing here?
Your Honor?
Please, stop with the "Your Honor."
This is just "Ben."
You really think your
client is a whistle-blower?
She was reporting a public fraud.
To whom?
She didn't serve notice to this court.
Did she notify the SA's office?
The Attorney General? The FBI?
- No, but...
- Then under the statute
she has not provided proper notice.
Then she posted the video online.
Are you telling me that
this doesn't satisfy
the spirit of the notice requirement?
I'm telling you it's too much of a reach.
And even more so, I don't understand
why you're trying so damn hard to make it.
Diane, I've known you for a long time
and this...
this is not your case.
Are you saying that I
shouldn't pursue this case
because of my politics?
I'm saying you shouldn't be pursuing this
because it's not you.
This is about free speech, and you know it.
No, I don't know it.
This undercover tape is disgusting.
It's like James O'Keefe with ACORN.
It's like all right wing Republicans.
They don't play fair.
This is...
You can't be telling me this.
And yet I am.
I want you to stop
trying to make this work.
So let's go back out there,
put this to bed, and make sure those videos
never see the light of day.
What happened?
Your plaintiff who had the abortion,
Stacy Groom.
The one you ripped apart?
Yes.
We're putting her on the stand.
- Thank you for coming.
- We-we know you're very busy.
I am, but...
- We understand you're not entirely hap...
- As my father would say, wha gwan.
We'd like to tell you about our firm.
It's not as big as Canning's,
- but we see that as a plus.
- Do you travel?
Do I? Oh, yes, I love to.
We're opening hotels
throughout the Caribbean.
We need manpower. How
many partners do you have?
- Six, currently.
- Two.
But what we lack in numbers,
we make up for in aggressiveness.
And experience, Mr. Beadle.
At a firm like Florrick & Agos,
- Quinn.
- We... What? Oh. Excuse me.
At a firm like Florrick & Quinn,
what we're most proud
of is our corporate work.
I'm sorry, not corporate.
Our charitable work.
So... we'll look forward
to hearing from you.
Well, that didn't go... well.
Nope.
- Florrick/Agos?
- Criminal litigation?
His son.
No, he doesn't want to be reminded of that.
Plus, six partners?
- I was thinking futuristically.
- Lucca...
No, there's no question.
Diane Lockhart's an excellent lawyer.
But we have the expertise...
One second, Jojo.
Lippincott Mutual.
Sorry, Jojo.
One of our lawyers is
actually dealing with horses.
I know.
Good help these days.
So, yes, I actually do think
- we can squeeze in a meeting tomorrow.
- Ms. Groom,
did the 8th Street Clinic
- perform an abortion on you?
- Objection.
What is the relevance of this witness?
- I was wondering that myself.
- Ms. Groom is
a private citizen who
believes she has been defrauded
and is now reporting it.
Here. To this court.
She is our whistle-blower.
Objection overruled.
Proceed.
Ms. Groom, did the 8th Street Clinic
- perform an abortion on you?
- They did.
- Ten months ago.
- And did Dr. Hallie Fisher
perform that abortion? The woman
- in the video?
- Yes.
And did she accurately
represent that procedure
- to you?
- No.
She tricked me into donating fetal tissue.
She never told me it would be sold.
She even flipped the baby
into a breech position
- to help better harvest the organs.
- Objection.
Misstates evidence. There's
been no testimony to this effect.
Are you denying that Ms. Groom's
abortion involved a breech?
No. I'm saying there's
no evidence as to cause.
Yes, because you've
denied us that evidence.
We need a hearing on acquiring
the 8th Street Clinic's
- medical records.
- Objection sustained.
Do you have any more questions
for this witness, Ms. Lockhart?
I do not.
Ms. Groom, these symptoms you discuss,
have you reported them to a doctor?
Yes. I received
- a PTSD diagnosis.
- Really?
When was that?
- Yesterday.
- Yesterday?
Great. Before your testimony here.
- Objection, Your Honor.
- Overruled.
You said that Dr. Fisher
tricked you
into donating tissue.
- How did she do that?
- She said
the donation was for research purposes
and my health wouldn't be compromised.
- And it wasn't, was it?
- She said on the video
babies are moved into a breech position.
Ms. Groom, when did you join
the Church of God in Christ?
- Objection, Your Honor.
- Goes to state of mind.
No. It is an indictment of this
woman's beliefs, and that's outrageous.
- What happened to constitutional freedoms?
- This woman was pro-choice.
She had an abortion of her own free will...
Yes. Yes.
Uh, absolutely.
Mm-hmm.
Um...
sure.
Well, when?
Okay.
Um...
Uh, tomorrow.
Thank you. Okay.
Bye.
Nice picture of you and the Pope.
Thanks.
Did you decide what you wanted to do
with, you know, the
unlimited vacation days?
Eli, what are you doing here?
Why am I...
I thought that you wanted me to stay.
And your concern is Governor Florrick?
Yes. What do you mean?
Well, it's important to understand motives,
don't you think?
- Always.
- Unlimited vacations is a ploy.
It's-it's cynicism
disguised as benevolence.
And you know that.
I know... H-How do I know that?
Oh, give me some credit.
When companies offer unlimited vacations,
employees take even less vacations.
They're so paranoid about
pulling their own weight,
they don't even use their usual two weeks.
That was not my intent.
Well, then... what is your intent?
What are we talking about now?
You're in my office.
The door is closed.
You still trying to "help" me?
I'm not good at this.
What is this?
You're beautiful.
And I'm...
Well, I have my moments, but...
My office is the size of your bathroom.
And I don't have...
the money you have.
Come here.
Okay.
Well, I'm sorry we won't
be working together.
Yeah. Thank you for your time.
That was the last one.
I thought Canning's clients
would be easier to pick off.
What do we do?
- Mom?
- Yeah, Grace, just give us a minute.
No, actually, I think you want to
hear this. I got four new clients.
That's great, honey. I'll
be in in a few minutes.
NCW. Justice Center.
Preservation Basin. And Jojo Lee's company.
Excuse me?
- Excuse me?
- NCW.
The Justice Center. Preservation Basin.
And Jojo Lee's company.
I...
You-you talked to them?
- Yes.
- NCW?
Who did you talk to at NCW?
- Um, Bea Wilson.
- Bea Wilson?
The Bea Wilson?
Well, a Bea Wilson.
How did you get all those firms?
Apparently they're unhappy
with Diane Lockhart.
So, can you make time to meet with them?
Y-Yeah. Yeah.
The reason we haven't been able
to produce the medical records
to substantiate our claim
is that we have been denied
- the minute-by-minute procedure notes.
- You have no basis
- for discovery.
- It's a catch-22,
Your Honor. I need the evidence
they have to get the evidence they have.
That is a problem, Ms. Lockhart. For you.
Well, you could fix it
with an evidentiary order.
Let me think about that.
No.
Your Honor, per Illinois rule 735
ILCS 5/2-1001, I would
like to file a motion
- for substitution of judge.
- You're asking me
- to remove myself from this case?
- Yes.
- On what grounds?
- Political bias.
Motion denied. There
is nothing in the record
to reflect any bias on my part,
- political or otherwise.
- There is nothing on the record
because you pulled me into chambers
for an improper ex parte conversation.
- You stop right there!
- Which revealed
your bias against both me
- and my clients' case.
- Denied!
Again. Want to keep getting knocked down?
It is not fair that you, who are
biased, get to rule on your bias.
It is fair. And you are way over the line.
- Your Honor, I am asking...
- Ms. Lockhart,
I have made my ruling!
You're welcome to proceed with your case.
And I assure you I will
give it all the consideration
it deserves.
I'm sorry. I tried
my best, but I've just become a liability.
It's in your clients' best
interests for me to withdraw.
Nicely played.
You found a way out without
backing down from anyone. Kudos.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Okay. But it's time to
get our clients back.
I'm on it.
Here we go.
We did it.
- Bravo.
- Jason, you're just in time.
- For what?
- To celebrate.
New business. New life.
And we owe it all to Grace.
Well, congratulations.
Oh, Mom, do you have a minute?
Sure. Thanks for all your help, Grace.
No problem.
Um, so it works out to $35,800.
For the year.
What's that?
A half percent of the billable hours.
That's what you owe me.
Cash or check is fine.
= synced and corrected by Shahrazade =
...www.addic7ed.com...
Enjoy Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP