Cary asked me.
I know.
He's just on a call.
So, the IRA agreed to
an Offer and Compromise,
on your tax case.
The IRA?
The... the IRS.
You'll have to
pay a penalty,
we can deal with all
the specifics later,
but you have some un-cashed
checks in your file.
You should take a
look at those.
Thanks.
I'm not gay.
You asked
whether I was gay?
Yes...
two years ago.
I know.
I wanted to answer.
I'm not gay, I'm...
...flexible.
Okay.
Flexible. Good.
And, uh...
Lana Delaney,
this FBI agent,
that's... flexible?
Yeah. Sort of.
Because as your lawyer,
I wouldn't...
You know what, it's your life.
You do what you want.
What?
It's the Veriscene case.
The judgment's in.
We find out tomorrow.
That's good.
I don't know. I've got a bad
feeling about this one.
How's everyone this morning?
Well, Your Honor.
We seem to have
a designated hitter here today.
Yes, Your Honor.
My partner, Will Gardner,
couldn't be in court...
Oh, you don't have to cover for
him. I know Will's suspended.
- How's he doing?
- Very well, thank you for asking.
Like a kid
with five days until Christmas.
Well, tell him
he's missed.
Shall we get started?
Plaintiff alleges
that Veriscene,
a drug administered
for the cure of acne,
caused Mr. Goode
irreversible sterility.
Accordingly, I am entering
judgment for the plaintiff,
in the amount of $25 million
in compensatory.
I acknowledge that this amount
is in excess of the $18 million
requested by the plaintiff,
but I find the actions here
particularly heinous.
- Your Honor...
- Yes, Mr. Canning?
You want to appeal?
- Oh, I do. Uh vehemently.
- As is your right.
Mr. Goode, no matter where this
ends up, I want you to know,
justice was done here today.
Whoo-hoo! Yes!
Congratulations.
I am rarely speechless,
but I am speechless.
Thank you.
Thank you both.
It's not over yet.
They're going to
drag this out in
appeals, so...
I thought it was
going against us.
Sometimes fate smiles.
Will, are you
standing or sitting?
Which one do you
want me to be?
You're kidding.
Do you know what this means?
That we can pay off
our balloon payment.
And dodge the executioner
for another quarter.
If you get a settlement.
Where's Canning at?
He'll appeal.
For effect.
$25 million should motivate him.
Peter, you okay?
We have a problem with the house.
We?
Uh, Jackie.
She paid ten percent in
cash on the down payment.
Apparently, she was
bidding against someone.
Me. She was bidding against me.
So I'm planning on going
ahead with the purchase
and then flipping the
house in a few months.
Okay.
Are you moving in?
Just temporarily.
I think
I could get more
more money for the house
if I did some work
in the backyard.
Why are you
telling me this, Peter?
Look, I don't want you
to worry about these...
decisions.
This is all temporary.
I'm not trying to...
Colonize our past?
Well, I don't think
I'd exactly put it that way,
but yes, I don't want these
decisions to be misunderstood.
Okay. I won't.
So... we're making
this work, right?
Oddly, yes, we are.
I heard Cary is
back with you guys.
- Yeah, starts today.
- Oh.
He's a good guy.
Wish him luck.
So, we'll need you out here until
we get an office cleared out,
- if you're all right with that.
- I am.
Good. It'll just
be a few weeks.
Welcome back, Cary.
The best IPTV in the UK
WWW.ALLIN1BOX.CO.UK
Whew.
AN:
Yeah?
Um, is this F&E Construction?
Hello?
Who is this?
Uh, I'm a lawyer following up
on a un-cashed check
from F&E Construction.
Unfortunately, we'll need you
to reissue the check.
Who is this?
Um... is this F&E Construction?
Yes.
I don't recognize your voice.
I'm a lawyer representing...
someone...
uh, who has an un-cashed check
from F&E Construction,
and she can't access her funds,
uh, unless you reissue, so...
Who's the check made out to?
Cash.
Where are you
calling from, lady?
Can you just reissue
the check, sir?
Sure. Give me a check number.
You know what, um, I'll call
you back with that information.
Thank you.
Wow.
Oh, hey, Cary.
- How are you doing?
- Good.
You seem to be, too.
Oh, it's just from being
liaison to Eli Gold.
As soon as he's back
on the campaign trail,
I'll be out there with
everyone else. Where are you?
I'm out there
with everyone else.
Well, then you'll have company.
Canning.
Oh, Cary.
- Good to have you back.
- Thank you.
The Veriscene case-- we're
in the middle of negotiations.
Yeah, go for it.
I know my way around.
We're not committing
to an offer yet, but if you
have a number, we'll listen.
Mr. Canning,
are you with us?
Oh, I'm sorry, I was
just texting my lawyer.
It's funny, isn't it,
lawyers having lawyers?
And my lawyer probably
has a lawyer, too.
We should all be getting
progressively smaller,
like matryoshka dolls.
Yes. So are we
negotiating,
- or what are we doing?
- No, we're negotiating.
I-I think I have
an offer for you.
A one-time offer.
- Zero? Really?
- Yeah, unfortunately
you have five minutes to
decide whether to take it.
I see.
And if we don't,
you have a bomb or something?
Sort of.
Hi. We're all here.
Where are you?
Just changing.
I'll be right in.
The rash is
back, Michael.
I know. I'm trying the
ointment three times a day.
You have to stop
eating so much spicy food.
Yes. No more Thai
food for you.
Oh, please,
it's just poop.
You shovel the stuff
all day, buddy.
Oh, God.
Patti Nyholm.
- Well, look at you.
- And you.
Poster child
for Motherhood Today.
You have no changing tables
in the restroom, Will.
- It's a lawsuit waiting to happen.
- Yep, doing our part
to suppress the birth rate.
So, I need
some legal advice
on my contract.
Oh, my God, wait.
You can't practice
law any more.
What was I thinking?
No, thank you.
I'll be right out, Michael.
This'll take a few minutes.
That must be really
hard on you, Will,
just sitting around
watching all these lawyers
while you're, what,
surfing the Web?
- Clipping coupons?
- What's up, Patti?
- A lawsuit.
- Really? Which one?
A new one. It'll be great being
on opposite sides again,
dusting it up...
Oh, wait. Darn it.
You're not a
lawyer any more.
I keep forgetting.
So sorry I'm late.
Here's my lawyer now.
Ms. Nyholm, I believe
you know everybody.
I think I do. Hello.
How are your
negotiations going?
Well, I don't
know, I gave them
five minutes to agree to my settlement
offer, and that time is up... now.
We're suing you.
On behalf of
LOC Pharmaceuticals,
makers of Veriscene
and Elvatyl.
And their insurer, LifeState.
We joined forces
to sue you for
$50 million
- for fraud and malicious prosecution.
- Come on,
- this is harassment.
- Is that your legal opinion, Will?
No, it's mine.
Your company
doesn't like being sued,
try making products that
don't kill and maim people.
Here's a better
idea-- stop intentionally
and wrongfully instituting
legal proceedings
- you know are without merit.
- We were just
awarded $25 million--
I'd call that merit.
No. I would call that
judicial bribery.
Oops.
Is that a sensitive topic?
This case was
built for a jury.
You requested a bench trial.
It's a million-dollar case,
and your basketball buddy
awarded you $25 million.
- I was cleared by a grand jury.
- No.
You weren't indicted
by a grand jury.
You gamed the system;
I know you, Will.
You can't do that with me.
- Or with me.
- That's right.
We're the dream team.
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
Jackie?
Mr. Gold?
Hi.
Peter said you were here.
Shouldn't you be
in synagogue?
Uh... no.
How are you feeling?
- Better.
- Good.
Then I won't feel bad
about saying this.
Your son is
going to lose.
Without Alicia, he will
lose the governorship.
Uh, I-I don't know...
She was on our
side, Jackie.
Alicia was offering
to help Peter,
then you got involved.
How did I get involved?
This friggin' house!
My God, I've never
heard so much
real estate talk
in all my life.
If their separation goes
wide, everything collapses.
Eli, what do you want?
I want you to apologize to her.
Your son will
not win without Alicia,
and I will not
manage his campaign
without her.
So say, "I'm sorry"
even if you
don't believe it.
I dreamt I died.
Everybody just did
what they always did.
They didn't care.
Um, do you want me
- to get you a nurse or some...
- Are you religious?
Am I, um... I...
I thought Jews believed in God.
Yes, we all do;
Every one of us.
I don't want to die.
I'll get you a nurse.
It's a scare tactic.
Look at Ketter Sum Holdings.
They sued the lawyers
bringing class actions
against their artificial knees
in order to scare them off.
There might be more.
I think Patti is using
this suit to fact-find.
- For an appeal?
- Yes.
Look who they're deposing.
Kalinda, me.
Patti doesn't have enough,
so she's using this suit to find
out if we did anything wrong.
I wish I could agree,
but if the law
taught me anything,
it's that never,
ever trust a man with a limp.
Look, if they want
to find out more
about our tactics,
we turn it back on them.
Right, every time they ask a
question, ask for more detail.
What did you mean by that?
Can you explain?
Good. Anything else?
- Sorry.
- Okay,
I will sit in with Will;
Who do we have for Kalinda?
Most of our litigators
were in on this.
So, they're all subject
to being called.
All but one.
Miss Sharma, have you ever
misrepresented your occupation
in order to interview
a witness?
Could you be more specific?
Sure.
Have you ever misrepresented
your occupation
in order to interview a witness,
as you did with my wife
to get into my house?
Objection, what
does that have to do
- with the Veriscene case?
- Well, Miss Sharma
claims she's never broken
the law in pursuit of a case.
I have firsthand knowledge
of such law-breaking.
So, Miss Sharma, can you
please answer the question?
Could you repeat the question?
Sure. Were you Kalinda
Sharma's direct supervisor?
We don't have
direct supervisors here.
Did you tell her to investigate
on the Veriscene case?
In what way, "investigate"?
Okay, Will.
I get it.
We can do this all day.
You obfuscate,
I pull the judge out of court,
he raps you one the knuckles
for being unresponsive,
and all you've done
is waste half a day.
I take exception
to your suggestion
that we're wasting anything.
But remember,
I'm not the one with a balloon
payment due on his office.
Oops.
Was that the elephant
in the room?
Hello.
AN:
You were gonna get back to me.
I... Who is this?
F&E Construction.
You wanted me
to reissue a check.
Yes, I did.
I said I'd get back to you,
though.
I know, but you didn't.
So I decided to call you.
Okay, um, let me get all
my ducks in a row, sir,
and I'll get back to you.
Sir?
No, you won't.
Excuse me?
You won't call me back.
You have no intention
of calling me back.
I said I would, and so I...
Actually, um,
I think we're done here.
No, we're not.
Could you be more specific?
Did you introduce judges
to bookies at your Wednesday
night basketball...
Objection, relevance.
Isn't Judge Wynter relevant?
The man who awarded
you $25 million?
Isn't he one of the judges
you introduced to bookies?
Objection.
And weren't you confronted
about this at the grand jury?
Excuse me, Ms. Nyholm,
you have referenced proceedings
that resulted
in a sealed transcript.
Yes, but Mr. Gardner can
answer to his own testimony.
This question requires
your knowledge
of the grand jury investigation.
No, it merely requires
Mr. Gardner's knowledge
of the grand jury
investigation.
All right, we're taking this
to the judge.
Okay, okay, okay.
You are all new to me,
so my apologies if I need
to be reminded of your names,
but Ms.--
Lockhart.
You are arguing
the only way these questions
could be asked
is if they were taken
from sealed transcripts?
Yes, Your Honor,
someone is leaking them
grand jury testimony,
and we would argue this
line of questioning
should be stricken.
If I may interject, Your Honor,
we're merely asking questions
based on our own knowledge.
And if you can allow me
an explanation,
these movements that you see,
uh, these random movements,
they're the consequence
of a neurological disorder
I suffer from called
tardive dyskinesia.
And I just didn't want you
to misinterpret
any of movements.
Okay, I won't.
I've had this condition
since childhood.
Are you going somewhere
with this, Mr. Canning? - No,
- I just wanted to explain.
- Okay, thanks.
I will allow these
questions to proceed.
Your Honor...
But if you produce evidence
these questions are based
on sealed grand jury evidence,
I will exclude
all such testimony
from this suit.
We need to get Kalinda
to follow Patti and find out
who's leaking this grand
jury testimony. - No.
We need to talk settlement.
Will, we're vulnerable.
No, we're not.
There's nothing there.
But what is there
doesn't look good.
You played
basketball with him,
you introduced him
to a bookie, and he awarded us
seven million above our ask.
Here's what I suggest.
We offer to drop the
Veriscene class action.
It's what they
want, anyway.
- Damn it.
- I know, but it's the smart move.
We need to get
this behind us.
This balloon payment,
our clients...
Patric Edelstein
is making noise.
I mean, he's 20%
of our quarter.
Everything's falling
apart as we fight this.
Uh, do you want me...
No, it's all right,
we've just been...
riding close to the edge
this whole year.
It's not for anyone to know.
I understand.
Okay.
Let's make this go away.
They brought
out the buffet.
This must be serious.
You drop the lawsuit,
and we drop the
Veriscene class action.
That's our offer;
Take it or leave it.
Fruit?
Please.
Uh, no.
- But thank you.
- Don't you want
to take it back to your client?
No. We're not caving
on the appeal.
- We know.
- You have no case.
- Not without some grand jury leak.
- You don't understand.
This isn't about a case.
You-you want to tell them?
No, no.
You're much better
at the nasty stuff.
We're not here to settle.
We're here to destroy you.
Our clients are tired
of being sued by you.
Four class actions in two years?
They've taken it personally.
Look at you.
- Hi, boo-boo.
- They've set aside
a large sum of money to
put you out of business.
That's why we're here,
to make an example of you.
You've seen Butch Cassidy
and the Sundance Kid.
We're the Super-posse.
So, thank you for the offer,
but no.
We're getting paid a lot of
money to make you go bankrupt.
Thank you for the fruit, though.
Peanut.
Hello, hello.
Hi. That's pretty.
Well, Kalinda,
funny seeing you here.
Yeah, almost as funny
as seeing you here,
with Ms. Nyholm, leaking
grand jury testimony.
Mr. Wiley
is legally sharing
his own testimony
before the grand jury.
- Really?
- Yeah, the state's attorney
wasn't interested in pursuing
the case against Will Gardner.
Ms. Nyholm is.
And our kids love
playing together.
So it's all
perfectly legal.
Hi.
Cary, we're having some trouble
with Andrew Wiley,
an investigator from
the state's attorney's office.
- Yes, I know him.
- He's the one working
with Nyholm and Canning.
I doubt that.
Wiley doesn't break the rules.
Unless he's using
his own testimony.
Yep. So we need
something from you.
Well, you know that
I can't share what I know
about the grand jury
because that would be unethical.
Yes, but you
can use your knowledge
in another way.
Thank you for coming.
It means so much to me.
I didn't come here
to visit, Jackie.
I came to recommend
that you retain a lawyer.
You... Why?
You took money
from my children's trust
so that you could outbid me
on my family home.
I intend to sue you.
I'm sorry, Alicia.
This family's been
through so much, and I...
I thought I knew best.
I'm so sorry.
Jackie, please.
What do you want?
I want you to
accept my apology.
- No, you don't.
- I want to make things right.
It'll be good
for Zach and Grace
and... and Peter.
You want Peter to win.
That's what you want.
Eli was here, wasn't he?
I-I-I don't know.
I...
He...
He can't do it without you.
Here's what I want, Jackie.
You sign the house
over to the kids,
you put it in their names,
I won't sue.
You want me to accept your
apology, show me you mean it.
Sign the house over to the kids.
Excuse me.
Watch your toes.
Everyone, please,
indoor voices.
Your Honor, like you, I look at
life a little differently--
with a little more caution,
- a little more quiet.
- Why like me?
I'm sorry, I...
You said "like me."
What do you mean?
What we mean, Your Honor,
is that the defense's motion
is a desperate ploy
to avoid
responsibility.
Mr. Canning asked
Ms. Sharma one question
that couldn't have been
in Mr. Wiley's
grand jury testimony,
Your Honor.
The $2,000 in cash
Mr. Gardner gave to a judge--
money that was supposedly
for UNICEF.
Was for UNICEF.
This was evidence that Mr. Wiley
personally witnessed,
Your Honor.
Yes, but the question isn't
whether he personally
witnessed it or not.
Andrew, did you testify to it
or did you witness it?
Wait a minute, you can't
talk to our client.
Andrew, which one did you do?
- Oh, my God.
- Andrew, no, stop right there!
He's right, I just
- witnessed it.
- Due to this admission,
Your Honor, all the evidence
regarding Mr. Gardner's
bribing of a judge
should be excluded.
Your Honor, I'd like
to add another name
to our witness list:
Alicia Florrick.
I have to
witness prep you.
They're coming
after you,
trying to get to Will
bribing judges another way.
I know.
F&E Construction.
What is it?
Why?
I found a check
in your file from Canada.
An un-cashed check from 2007.
Yeah. That-that shouldn't
be there.
That should be
in my personal file.
It's for $21,000.
That would go a long way
to pay your tax bill.
I know.
Do you have the check?
Thanks.
It's-it's complicated.
I called the number on it.
As part of your tax work,
I called employers
for updated checks.
When?
When did I call? Tuesday.
Did you speak to anyone?
Yes.
Who?
I don't know.
He wouldn't
give me his name.
He asked for the number
on your check.
Did you give it?
No.
Thanks.
He called me back.
What's going on, Kalinda?
It's just something
from an old thing.
"An old thing"?
Is it Lemond Bishop?
No. I'm gonna go
and take care of it.
Kalinda.
Yeah?
Nothing.
I'll be back.
I'm-I'm gonna go
take care of it.
That might be
too big for you.
I've got some lighter
ones around the corner.
No, this one's fine.
You sure?
You need anything else,
let me know.
♪ ♪
And it's not just
the sink, the shower, too.
Okay, I'll call down,
but we're probably on our own.
They go out of their
way not to fix things
when they're converting to
condos, so it forces you to buy.
Are you gonna?
Buy?
I don't know.
I like it here,
but maybe there's better.
Dad wants you
to buy the house.
- He...
- He told you
he wanted to sell it,
didn't he?
Would you?
- Buy the house?
- Yeah.
No.
Why not?
You were going to.
I know, but everything's
up in the air right now.
You got a raise.
Yes. But sometimes
getting a raise
means that you cost more,
so when they're looking
to downsize, it's easier to
fire you than someone cheaper.
And they're
looking to downsize?
No, but we're just going
through a bad spell.
You should move in.
We should all
live in one house.
What?
Not like you guys
are married.
Like a commune.
Hmm.
I've kind of grown
to like you.
Yeah? Not Zach?
No, not Zach.
He's getting too big.
Hey.
You shouldn't
answer it.
It's probably work.
They can't fire you
if they can't find you.
Very funny.
Hello?
AN:
Alicia Florrick?
Is it work?
No. Wrong number.
This is Kalinda.
Please leave a message.
You ready for this?
- I hope so.
- Don't worry, it'll all be about me.
Just tell the truth.
Have you seen Kalinda?
No, why?
She's not in today.
She's probably
just late.
You were second chair
on the Veriscene case,
right, Mrs. Florrick?
Yes.
Did you have
ex parte communication
with Judge Wynter
during the trial?
- No.
- And you have no personal
- relationship with Judge Wynter?
- That's correct.
But someone you know does?
You mean Will?
No.
I mean your husband.
Peter Florrick.
I-I have no idea.
You have no idea whether
your husband has a personal
relationship with Judge Wynter?
I mean, I know that
he knows him, but I don't know
the extent of
their relationship.
Did you know that your husband
met with Judge Wynter
three times
in the week leading up to
the Veriscene verdict?
- No.
- Really?
On the eve of Judge Wynter's
decision to award you
$25 million, your husband
met with him three times,
- and you had no idea?
- That's correct.
Are we working
off the assumption
they did, in fact, meet?
How do we know this?
Because we're going
to subpoena Peter Florrick.
You're going to
subpoena the state's attorney?
We already have.
Hold the door, please.
Thanks.
No problem. 28th?
Yeah.
So, you seeing Alicia?
Am I seeing Alicia?
No, actually, I'm being deposed.
Oh. Really?
Although it
occurred to me
I've never seen
where Alicia works.
Does she know
you're coming?
Not that it matters
either way.
I don't know.
So you must be looking forward
to getting back to the law, huh?
I am.
I think convicts
call it "short time."
Really?
I never did.
Well, hi.
Hi.
Look who I found.
Yes. Welcome.
I thought I would come
and meet you.
Which one?
You, Peter.
Thought you might want
to see my office.
-Hello, Eli.
- Yeah.
I...
Hi.
H-Hello, everyone.
Hi. I was just
showing Peter my office.
He's here
for a deposition.
Really?
Good. Great.
Cary.
- Hey, Cary.
- Hello.
Hello, Mr. Florrick.
How you doing?
- Hey, how you guys doing?
- Hi.
So how's it going here?
At Lockhart-Gardner? It's good.
I mean, I loved the state's
attorney's office,
but there's a lot
of smart people here, too.
One of our new
associates.
Hey, Kalinda.
It's a surprise
party for you.
I'm impressed.
What you have done
in three years is amazing.
Thank you.
Okay.
I guess I should go
meet my executioners.
Oh, Peter, you didn't
have to do this.
You could've blown it off.
It's a stupid nuisance suit.
I wanted to get out
and stretch my legs.
Hey. Come over tonight.
- I'll have to work.
- Just to see the house.
- Stay for five minutes, tops.
- I wish I could.
Peter?
Have you checked in
on Jackie lately?
Have I?
Yeah. Why?
I'm worried.
She seems confused.
She's getting older.
Hey...
congratulations.
You made it.
You need money?
Just an advance
on the work so far.
Why?
Kalinda, what's going on?
I-I have to go.
You have to... Why?
I thought you were
liking it here.
I am liking it here.
Okay, then you
would understand
my confusion.
Look...
we're in a bit of trouble.
We're short
on receivables.
Patric Edelstein
is delaying his monthly,
and we have some long-term suits
that haven't paid out yet.
I can get you some.
Not everything.
Okay.
This is good-bye?
Just for a little bit.
You're gonna make me cry.
I don't know.
It feels like things
are falling apart.
You'll build them up again,
that's what you do.
And you met with
Judge Wynter three times
before this last Thursday,
the day of the verdict?
Yes.
Is that a lot for you?
- Yeah  - In fact, before these
three meetings,
you had only
met him once...
in 2008
at a judge's lunch,
with 12 other judges.
Yeah, that sounds
about right.
So why' you meet with him?
Those three times?
I like him.
Did the subject
of your wife's lawsuit
come up
at these meetings?
- No.
- Really?
At the same time you were
meeting with this judge,
your wife had a suit
in front of him,
and the subject never came up?
- That's correct.
- This grand jury investigation
into Will Gardner's
supposed bribing
of three judges,
including Judge Wynters...
Objection.
We are not referring to the content
of that investigation,
just to Mr. Florrick's
supervision of it.
But just to correct you,
uh, Ms. Scott-Carr had
supervision over it. - Yes,
- until you removed her.
- I removed her
because the grand jury
had concluded.
But the state's attorney
can bring charges again?
He can. I chose not to.
You also chose not
to bring charges against
the three judges
involved in this bribery scheme.
The supposed
bribery scheme? Yes.
- Why not?
- I didn't want to.
I thought Ms. Scott-Carr
had gone beyond her directive.
So when you met
with Judge Wynter...
he owed you?
Did you not want to answer?
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't know
that was a question.
Didn't you ask
Judge Wynter to decide
this verdict for your wife
as a quid pro quo
- for dropping his investigation?
- No.
But isn't that
a fair conclusion?
- No.
- And how is that?
Because my wife
and I are separated.
Then I...
That is news to me.
Then what other reason
could there be
for these meetings?
His support for my campaign.
So I guess you could accuse me
of being corrupt for myself,
but not for my wife.
How's it going?
Good. You?
Good.
I have to head out.
I just wanted to say good night.
That man who called me,
F&E Construction,
he called me at home,
and he said my name.
- He said your name?
- Yes.
Did you give your name?
No.
Kalinda,
who is this man?
We said we would be up front
with each other.
I know.
Is this man dangerous?
Yeah.
Well, who is he?
He's my husband.
Come on.
You don't have anything.
The state's attorney
just told you
there's no way he could have
done this for his wife
because they're separated.
And he's done this with
some considerable expense
to his own political career...
because it's now in the record
that they've separated.
So, what do you have?
A passion to
see this through.
We take back our offer
to drop the class action.
You lost. Face it.
They're right.
We lost.
We should probably
just head out.
You think?
Here's the thing, though.
We were the distraction.
You were the distraction?
What does that mean?
Have you checked on your
top client, Patric Edelstein?
He's no longer your top client.
He's ours.
We just got the text.
He's been unhappy
with Will's suspension,
and with your distraction
with this lawsuit.
Sleight of hand.
You were watching the right,
you should've been
watching the left.
- Mommy!
- That's right,
we're done here.
Mommy's coming home.
After you.
No, no, after you.
Please.
- Mommy!
- Hello!
Let's go. Come on.
Oops.
And it's too late
to call him.
They planned
on that, too.
So...
tomorrow?
Tomorrow.
How you doing?
Me? I'm, uh...
okay.
You?
Same.
That was weird.
With Peter today?
Yes, it was.
Do you think it was a mistake?
No.
Good night, Alicia.
Good night, Will.
♪ In the hell ♪
♪ Beneath the stairs ♪
♪ There's someone ♪
♪ In that room ♪
♪ That frightens you ♪
♪ When they go boom ♪
♪ Boom, boom, boom ♪
♪ Boom, boom ♪
♪ Boom ♪
♪ Boom, boom, boom... ♪
Mom, my doorknob's
still broken.
How about some wine?
No, I have to get back.
They didn't change much.
The house? Yeah.
They tried to flip it,
but they didn't put
any work into it
so nobody wanted it.
Thanks for today.
I think you stopped
the suit.
I guess I just
told the truth.
That's bigger than you think.
Dad, the pizza's ready.
Okay.
- Pizza?
- No, I have to
get up early for work tomorrow.
Things are in flux.
When aren't things in flux?
Hey, come say good-bye
to your mom.
She's leaving.
♪ I... ♪
♪ Met you ♪
♪ Boom... ♪
I love you both.
I'll see you in
a few days.
Stay, Mom.
No one will think
it means anything.
Just...
have some pizza.
Then you can go.
You're getting big.
I love you.
Love you, too.
♪ Ooh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, ooh, oh ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ I... ♪
♪ Met you ♪
♪ I... met you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ ♪
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net
The best IPTV in the UK
WWW.ALLIN1BOX.CO.UK