Money.
How much money?
Twice what I'm making here.
- And all for the price of your soul.
- Not my whole soul,
just little pieces of it.
Anyway, I heard defense
attorneys have better sex.
If you like
coming from behind.
Oh, God...
- Okay, no.
- Oh, come on, Dana.
- We said no as long as we were coworkers.
- Yeah, we...
- we're still coworkers.
- Yeah,
for one more week.
Not to be too much of a pessimist,
but I don't think
you're gonna survive it.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah. You're like
a cop with one week
left on the job.
They all get shot.
Can't risk the wait.
Cary, I have
a boyfriend.
So do I.
Well, my guess
is my boyfriend's
- bigger than yours.
- Oh.
Okay.
These cases, I can't
finish in a week.
- I will them to you.
- Oh... great.
No sex and half your file work--
I really feel like I'm losing here.
Yeah, but you have one less body to
step over on your way to the top.
Must be your boyfriend.
Checking in on me.
Hello, dear.
How are you?
I'm good, Cary.
How about you?
I'm good, Matan.
Really? You and Matan?
I just got a call about
an ASA needed at a crime scene
for some kind of legal issue.
I was gonna head down,
but it turns out
Lockhart & Gardner
are the defense attorneys on it.
So lucky you.
What's the legal issue?
No idea.
This sounds like hazing.
It does, doesn't it?
Let me give you
the address, dear.
- And that's all I do?
- That's all you do.
Just hit the return key,
and it's on your
computer at work.
But why does it never
seem so simple?
Because you don't
trust technology.
Hey, you guys have all your
bags packed and ready, right?
Because Dad's gonna
be here any minute.
- Hey, Mom?
- Yes?
What do you do when
we're at Dad's?
What do I do?
Uh, not much.
I miss you two.
For about an hour.
And then I do
some laundry,
I read for work. Why?
Do you ever go out?
- Uh, for dinner? Sometimes.
- With friends?
Sometimes.
What friends?
Friends from work.
Or clients.
People we know?
No, I don't think you do.
We're just worried
about you, Mom.
Honey...
I'm fine. Really.
Mom, it's work.
Will Gardner.
Okay, thanks.
I-I'm gonna...
just take that in there.
Hang it up.
I was.
Sorry about
calling you at home.
No problem.
Everything all right?
Yes. Actually,
this is about work.
Oh. Good.
I mean, I'm here.
- Your new hire, the first-year?
- Caitlin.
Yes. A call came in about
the Jin-Pyn account.
She was the only one here.
She went out on it, but I think
she'll need some hand-holding.
Oh, o-okay.
Um, what's it about?
No idea. But the son seems to be
in some kind of legal trouble.
Mom! It's Dad!
I'll be right there.
Do you have the address?
Should have guessed.
What?
Booze cruise.
$50, all the beer
you can drink.
Down there.
You did that in college?
I did a lot of
things in college.
Only one band.
A seasickness band.
You wear them in pairs.
You're not gonna leave.
You're too
good at this.
That's what they say to the cop
with only one week left.
Five miles out
someone found the deceased,
a Maya Nichols, below deck,
called the police.
Witnesses say she was
getting unwanted attention
from two college kids.
We were just about to haul 'em
in for a suspect rape exam
when this joker showed up.
You are the authority here?
I am. What seems
to be the problem?
The problem is, Mr. Anders
is the son of a Dutch courier
at our embassy, and is therefore
covered by diplomatic immunity.
- I was not there! I was not!
- These are my papers,
and these are the papers
of Mr. Anders.
Who's that?
Uh, Jin-Pyn.
Supposedly, he's got
diplomatic immunity, too.
Chinese ambassador's
on his way.
Per the Viennese Convention
on Diplomatic Relations,
Mr. Anders is to
be treated...
Yes, I heard you.
- Thought there was some Lockhart/
- Yes.
Me. Here.
- I don't think I know you.
- You don't.
Caitlin D'Arcy.
I'm new as of last week.
Okay. Well, what do
you have to offer?
Nothing. I'm just taping
everything you do.
Well, uh...
I'm Cary Agos, and...
these two youths
are under investigation
for rape and murder.
- They have legal immunity.
- From prosecution, not investigation.
So unless they want to confess,
I'm investigating.
Go ahead, Detective,
take them in.
This is illegal.
- Now, who is your boss?
- The People of Illinois.
You want their number?
You feeling pretty
good about yourself?
Yeah, but how do I look?
The best IPTV in the UK
WWW.ALLIN1BOX.CO.UK
- Caitlin, what's going on?
- Mrs. Florrick, hello.
He's being accused
of rape and murder.
- Have you told him his rights?
- I was asked
to stand outside-- they're
doing a suspect exam.
Chen, my name is
Alicia Florrick.
I'm your parents' lawyer.
It is your right to have me
observe the suspect exam.
Do you approve?
I, uh... yeah.
Ma'am, please,
step back through.
It is his Sixth Amendment
right that I be here.
Chen, did they tell you you
had the right to remain silent?
- I didn't do it.
- I know.
I need you to only talk to me.
- Do you understand?
- I promised Dick
- I wouldn't talk.
- Here. Left earring stud.
Blond hair,
two inches long.
Mrs. Florrick?
I'm from the
Dutch embassy.
- I'm here to see Mr. Anders.
- We're getting everything sorted out, sir.
Who's the ASA?
I am. Who are you?
- Judge Winter.
- Oh.
- I'm-I'm sorry. I...
- Your Honor,
I represent
Mr. Chen Jin-Pyn.
He is the son of
a diplomatic translator,
and therefore
is guaranteed...
Yes, and that's why I was
yanked out of my house
in the middle of the night.
Where is he?
Your Honor, there is strong evidence
that these two men raped and killed...
I'm sorry to say
that's not relevant.
Given their immunity status,
you have no right to hold them.
This is a court order requiring
their immediate release.
Your Honor. Cary, you can
hold one of them. Taiwan.
Uh, Your Honor,
excuse me, I-I understand we
have to release Mr. Dick Anders,
given his status
as a Dutch citizen, but Jin-Pyn
is Taiwanese,
and Taiwan enjoys
no such diplomatic status.
How is that?
The One China rule.
The U.S. Government
extends diplomatic relations
to China but not Taiwan.
Your Honor, this is a gray area.
Not in matters
of diplomatic immunity.
Taiwan is the only nation
not accorded such rights.
Your Honor, this isn't
the United Nations.
You can't just keep one
and let the other go.
Actually, that's
exactly what I can do.
I order the release of
Mr. Anders but not Mr. Jin-Pyn.
That is unfair, Your Honor.
Good luck, buddy.
I'm out of here.
Of course it is.
When have you ever known
international politics
to be fair.
♪ The Good Wife 3x06 ♪
Affairs of State
Original Air Date on October 30, 2011
re-sync by elderman corrections by Alice
www.Addic7ed.com
Well, you really stirred up
the hornet's nest.
It was a rape-murder--
I held both suspects
- as long as I could.
- So, where are we?
No semen, but we believe
it was an attempted rape;
- She resisted; Chen killed her.
- Murder weapon?
None found.
Blunt head trauma.
What does the
client say happened?
Caitlin?
He says they both
flirted with the victim,
and then his friend Anders
went off with her.
But we can't get to Anders?
No, he was released.
Well, that's not good.
What else ties him to the girl?
The blond hair caught
in Chen's left earring stud.
- No pubic hair?
- None.
Oh, Dana, you're still here.
- Six more days of bliss.
- Any blood spatter?
- On Chen, no.
- What do you think the defense will be?
To blame the one that got away.
Too bad there's one
that got away.
And our strategy?
Connect Anders
to the rape.
Did the police
do a suspect exam?
On Anders, no.
He was released prior.
Hm. And what about
the blond hair on our guy?
- How does he explain that?
- Chen says they made out.
It was consensual.
Then Chen went to go
buy the victim a drink,
- and Anders took her below deck.
- A drink?
- I thought it was a booze cruise.
- Just beer and wine.
Hard alcohol,
you had to pay.
We have Chen's
credit card receipt
with the time on it,
so if they police can pinpoint
the time of the murder,
we can prove
that Chen was on the
other end of the boat.
Eli Gold, ladies and gentlemen.
You needed me?
You push this off on me and then
you criticize my handling of it?
I wasn't trying
to criticize you.
Did I give you
that impression?
You did.
My apologies.
What was that about?
We were trying to make you feel part
of the Lockhart/Gardner family.
Don't you want
to feel a part?
Oh. I'm okay.
What do you need?
Lobbying. The son
of a Taiwanese diplomat
is being denied immunity from
prosecution due to the One China rule.
- Oy. That thicket.
- Yep, that thicket.
I thought if you
could talk to someone
quietly, we could make this
go away without much fuss.
Know anyone in
the State Department?
Yes?
Nothing.
- How important is it?
- Well,
heading into the presidential
campaign, my guess is
Taiwan will be spending
a lot on U.S. lobbyists.
Could be lucrative...
for you.
Okay.
This is not going to be pretty.
Sorry you had to see that.
Definitely not my finest hour.
No, it's cool.
You were a good judge.
Okay, the less said
about that, the better.
Oh, Alicia, hey.
Mr. Gardner was a judge in my
intercollegiate moot court.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Till I was removed. Bias.
Yeah, they had, like,
some 60-year-old come in.
Anyway...
- Yeah. Caitlin.
- Oh, sorry.
- Orientation, right?
- Go get orientated.
So, this binder has all
your human resource forms,
a fax sheet on billing,
ABA, pro bono requirements.
Great, thanks.
- He's nice, isn't he?
- Who, Will Gardner?
Yes. So is Diane.
They're both also busy.
So if there's anything you
need, you come to me first.
- Oh, I'm sorry. Did I just embarrass myself?
- No, no, no, you did fine.
Oh, God, I did, didn't I?
Caitlin, you were fine.
Here, work over here.
Go ahead, start
filling these out.
Hello?
Thanks a lot.
Excuse me.
This is my office.
Then I guess you can do
whatever you want, can't you?
I...
May I help you?
Not anymore.
Next time you need help
with IT, call me.
You don't just do it
on your own.
Look at this. Look.
What did you do?
What did I do?
What did I...? Okay.
It's your cloud, lady.
Go live on it.
Right there. Her. Closer.
Hey, do you know how
I get to the zoo?
So you just troll along the
lakefront looking for ex-wives?
No, just you.
Your office
told me you'd be here.
So...
Wow, you're really slowing down,
aren't you?
I'll just be a minute.
How's the presidential
campaign going?
Why? What did you hear?
Oh, God, you're paranoid.
No, I'm a vegetarian.
Since when?
Since we divorced.
What do you need?
Who do you know at State?
A lot of people.
It's a Taiwan issue.
A poor, innocent kid's
been accused of...
something or other,
and they won't grant him
diplomatic immunity.
Do you want me to talk
to Doug Rothstein?
Yeah. Really?
That'd be great.
You're-you're looking
good, Vanessa.
Eli?
Your turn.
Do you know Kim Kesler?
Kim... Kesler?
Who's she?
He. A political op
out of California.
I thought you guys
were all staffed up.
- It's not for the president.
- Who then?
Me.
Seriously, Vanessa?
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
He-He approached me.
State Senate.
Oh, my God, you have
that wild look in your eye.
Rahm gets in,
and everybody thinks they can.
It's a good time
for a woman.
Is that what
Kim Kesler told you--
the man with a woman's name?
I need your help, Eli--
your professional opinion.
Meet us for dinner tonight.
Kim Kesler.
Kick his tires.
See if he's real, or if he's
selling me a bill of goods.
I can't believe
you're considering this.
I want to do
something with my life.
You always used to say that.
Well, now I mean it.
We're not having a moment.
No, no, we're not.
I'm-I'm going, I'm going.
Mrs. Florrick,
can I show you something?
What is it, Caitlin?
I'm a little busy.
It's probably
nothing, but I think
I have something on
the consensual. Chen.
We have to prove that he made
out with her consensually.
Oh. Sure.
Okay, so I was looking
at AfterDeathSpace for
Maya, the dead girl.
Oh, AfterDeathSpace.
You know, when
someone dies,
and everybody wants to
share stories and photos.
Okay.
And what was cool is,
everybody at the booze
cruise was tweeting photos.
And so look.
But what was even more cool
is... look.
The color of her cup-- red.
Okay.
It's a stoplight party,
not a spectrum party.
- A...?
- A stoplight party.
Oh, you carry a red cup
to say you're in a relationship,
a yellow cup
to say you're choosy,
and a green cup to
say you're open.
But see?
This one's from later--
an hour after the first pic.
And look at her cup.
Now it's green.
Well, maybe it's a mistake.
Take my word for it.
You know what cup
you're carrying
at a stoplight party.
So what made her switch
from a red cup to a green one?
Yeah, got it. Red to green.
Okay, listen,
I'll call you back.
- Hi.
- Hey.
So you're not
with the police?
No. You're Maya's
boyfriend, right?
Yeah. I was.
I already talked to the cops.
I wasn't there.
But you were on the phone
with her, right?
At the booze cruise.
She called you from it
the night she died.
So?
- Well, you broke up with
her on the phone. - No.
Listen, you're safe from arrest.
Just tell me the truth.
I am.
She broke up with me.
She said she
was tired of me
spending all my time
with this waitress
I know from Ra Sushi, but
she was this mother of three,
really nice, and I just like
talking to her, you know?
- Sure. Um... - And she wanted to
be a philosophy major, too,
back when she
was in college.
It's not like I'm a
philosophy major yet.
I'm still undecided
about my major.
Sure, look, don't worry about that.
I just like talking to her.
But you talked to her?
- Who, the waitress?
- No. Maya.
When she broke up with you,
you talked to her, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, no, no.
She, um...
She left me
a voice mail.
Do you have it?
You are so full of yourself.
You think
I can't do any guy here?
Can you e-mail me
that voice mail?
Yeah, sure.
Does it help?
Yeah, it does.
There's more if you want.
Your phone just
keeps cutting me off.
I just want... Hey!
I said, don't touch me.
What? I'm not touching you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Did you play that
for anyone else?
- Yeah.
- Who?
Hey! I said, don't touch me.
What? I'm not touching you.
That's Chen.
Sounds like
unwanted attention to me.
There goes consensual for them.
We should make an offer.
Life? No chance of parole?
Hey, Cary.
Sorry to interrupt.
We're gonna be shuffling
the offices around a bit,
so if you could get your stuff
together and be ready
in the next few days, okay?
Uh, this is from Peter?
Yup, he delegated to me.
What's going on there?
It's a guy thing.
Office jockeying.
I don't think they can put you
in any smaller of an office.
Oh, they can.
Hello.
Oh, my mom's just downstairs.
You're Zach, right?
I'm Will Gardner,
your mom's boss.
Oh.
Hey.
So, no school today, huh?
No, there was.
Oh, it's 4:00.
Helping Mom out?
Yeah.
Well...
keep on keepin' on.
You should know something
about your friend, Cary.
My friend, Cary?
Yeah, you should know something.
He has a thing
for ethnic women.
Oh. Really?
Yeah, it's pretty obvious.
Every black or Hispanic woman
through here.
Wow. Well, thank you
for the warning.
Got it working.
You did not.
I did. The IT guy put on
proprietary software,
so he could charge your firm
for every megabyte he stored.
That's why it rejected the
transferring of your files.
What? I don't understand.
It's really corrupt.
You don't need
to be paying to store files.
In fact, it slows
the system down.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Oh, your boss was in here. Will.
Yes, I-I saw.
Did you say hi?
I did.
All right, I better go.
Okay. I love you.
Love you, too.
Yeah?
I want a car.
It's like Moneyball.
Politics doesn't have
to be for the rich.
It's the true democratization
of power in this country.
You have citizen
engagement on one hand.
Megatrend, right?
I mean, everybody's
talking about it.
Mark Penn, so on,
and I'm not even
talking about RTR.
I mean, talk about
real Moneyball.
RTR?
Oh. Jeez.
Real-Time Response.
They hit Vanessa,
and bam, we hit back. Bam!
We hit back.
Through?
Micro-pockets
of committed,
citizen, online
journalist bloggers.
Each talking from a subset
of their own communities.
Let's say we have upstate
agricultural sections, right?
We also have the
urban cities, right?
We have activated
in there...
Well, that went well.
You're not going with him.
This was all a joke, right?
He was trying to impress you.
Oh, my God, Vanessa,
he is a clown.
Then help me.
You were never going with him?
Are you kidding?
Citizen engagement, RTR.
He just gave me the bug.
So this was all so I
would agree to help you?
I'm not going to be your
campaign manager, Vanessa.
I know.
Just get me started.
Do some polling.
See if there's any interest,
that's all.
- See if I have the stomach for this.
- You don't.
Well, then, it'll be over fast.
So, what happened with
the State Department?
Oh, yeah, good news.
Hello?
The State Department
screwed you.
They're pushing
for Chen's release.
They don't want
to isolate Taiwan.
There's a hearing tomorrow.
Damn it.
He's guilty.
We just... We just
got this voice mail.
It's a slam dunk.
Yeah. Too bad.
Good, you got
your stuff together.
I have another office
for you down the hall.
I extend my sincere gratitude
to each and every one of you
for being here tonight.
So he doesn't expect me?
No, but he's cool--
an old family friend.
Just don't get
rambly on him.
Uncle Dan.
- Hey,   - Dana.
- How you doing?
Look at you.
Dad told me you
were in town.
You've, uh,
caught me playing hooky.
The same stump speech
the 18th time,
and you're allowed
a little leeway.
Know what I mean?
Oh, this is,
this is Cary.
Uh, nice to meet you, sir.
Oh, ignore him-- he
calls everybody sir.
It's the straight,
suburban thing.
Uh-huh.
Uncle Daniel works
in the Obama State Department.
Well, that sounds
deathly formal.
So it's true--
you did break up with Jimi?
No, we're just...
It's complicated.
Uh-huh.
Anyway, Cary and
I work together
- at the state's attorney's office.
- Oh, yeah,
Peter-- how's he doing?
We worked together
a long time ago.
Good,
he's good,
he's good, but we're
working on a case
involving the
One China rule.
Really?
Well, that I have
to hear all about.
Good job.
Ah, thanks,
not too rambly?
Surprisingly not.
So Matan says that you have
a thing for ethnic women.
He what?
He says you have a
thing for ethnic women.
You just can't control
yourself around us.
Oh, I...
that's not true.
Unless that's
a good thing.
That depends.
On...?
I want you to vet
my ex-wife.
- Really?
- Yeah, I know
it sounds a bit weird, but
she's thinking of running
for state senate and
she wants me to vet her.
All right, well,
I have to do some work
on Taiwan first,
but then, sure.
How, how thorough
should I be?
As thorough
as her enemies would be.
Okay.
Um... this isn't
about something else?
You mean, am I jealous
of my wife
and want to see
who she's sleeping with?
No.
Okay.
Oh, come on!
So this is a hearing
into the status
of Mr. Jin-Pyn's
diplomatic...
status.
Don't worry, Chen,
you have the backing
of the state department.
Thank you.
I can't spend
another day in here.
I don't know, they're smiling
like they know something.
Now let's begin.
I understand the
defense has a witness.
Yes, Your Honor, it is our
contention that protections
of diplomatic immunity
were denied our client
due to the peculiarities
of Taiwan.
To that end,
we have asked a spokes...
Ma'am, there's a call
from the state department.
A Mr. Daniel Golden would like
to speak with you.
...a spokeswoman
at the state department...
Yes, Counselor?
Excuse me, Your Honor,
if we could delay...
As long as you want, Counselor.
Um, actually, Your Honor, we ask
the court that reasonable bail
be set,
and we would have
no objection to make
home confinement
a condition.
What happened?
State worried
that extending
diplomatic immunity to the kid
would be a slap
in the face to China.
Okay, we have
to get discovery.
None of your hair was
found on the body, Chen,
but we did just get
the lab report back
on the trace evidence.
There was a blond hair--
not Maya's, a man's--
on her collar.
They don't know
who it matches.
Anders.
That's what
we think,
but the police didn't
do his suspect exam,
so we have nothing
to match it to.
Do you have anything of his?
Anything that might have
one of his hairs on it--
a brush or an item of clothing?
I know his gym locker
combination at school.
My brother left
all my things
in his locker.
He gave me
the combination.
I'll be right in and out.
Thanks.
It's the other
seasickness band, Cary.
How do I know you didn't
plant it there, Kalinda?
Because I didn't.
Uh-huh, and you just
happened to know
the number
of Anders' locker?
No, I just happen to be
a very good investigator.
Look, check
if you don't believe me.
I'll get back to you.
Okay, whatever.
We're all having
to make sacrifices,
but you have a
window now at least.
That one.
The cubicle
in the middle.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Hi, uh, sorry
to keep you waiting.
No problem, I
keep myself busy.
You have a
pretty office.
Thank you.
Start of a campaign,
you work in Versailles.
By the end, you're in Motel 6--
not to disparage
Motel 6.
I'm a politician now.
So, uh, you, uh, married once
to Mr. Gold?
Four happy years, eight
medium ones, and two bad ones.
- I hope that doesn't preclude
me from running. - Actually,
I'm not here to make judgment,
just, just questions.
So why did you guys break up?
Uh, I think that was
in the divorce settlement.
Actually, it wasn't, just
"irreconcilable differences."
Ah, well, that's what it was.
Yeah, but I think
we'll need to go deeper.
Okay, uh, we were both
working too hard.
I was having to take a lot
of trips out of town.
Yeah, uh, Dubai,
three trips.
Yes.
At that time, I was doing
PR for an oil company.
And who did you
meet there?
Who did I meet?
I-- do you want
an itemized list?
Yeah.
Just write
down the ones
that you remember.
Are you looking
for anyone in particular?
Yeah, uh, Omar Tate.
You're doing
his dirty work for him,
aren't you?
Eli's dirty work.
- No.
- He told you
to ask me that.
No, my vetting is
independent of Mr. Gold.
- I don't believe you.
- I understand that,
but it's true.
It was a mistake,
Omar was a mistake.
Uh, how many times
did you meet?
Don't tell him.
I was young.
This is, this is merely
part of the vetting.
Don't tell him.
Please.
Yeah, I was
on the booze cruise, too,
but I just remember seeing
Maya by the bar.
Did you see her with this man?
No.
I mean, I saw him
in the newspaper,
but I didn't see
them leave together.
I mean, we were
both worried
about getting
disconnected at parties,
so we always
kept track.
How did you keep track?
Oh, you know,
that app.
What app?
The rape app?
Have you heard
of it?
No, show me.
We both had it installed
on our phones
so we could keep track
of each other.
See, the GPS shows you
where your friend is.
There's a panic button.
Yeah, I know.
That's what sucks.
The phone vibrated
when Maya pushed it,
but the music was so loud
and I was dancing,
so I didn't feel it.
What?
It has a history of when
Maya pushed the panic button.
Yeah, I know, but it
didn't show her location.
I know, but it shows what time
she pressed the button.
11:33.
Yeah, I do see it.
11:34 p.m.
Chen bought a mojito
at 11:34 p.m.
Why does that matter?
A rape app?
No, I've never heard
of that.
Okay,
well, if that's
probative,
then the state's
attorney's office
will question her, yep.
Ha-- no, no,
I think
it's a bit too early
to talk about release.
Yeah, okay,
thank you, bye.
What was that?
The defense attorneys.
They say they have
the time of death
via a friend
who received
a signal Maya sent on
something called a rape app.
Do you believe them?
I don't know.
Nice office.
Thanks.
I get a lot more air here.
Chen did it, he did it.
How do you know?
He's Taiwanese-- he would sign
his surname first.
Hey, Dick.
How's it going?
I hear you stopped going
to your anthropology class.
Listen, I don't have
to talk to you.
Actually, you do because
you stopped going
to your anthropology class.
What, what are you
talking about?
You haven't been
in six weeks.
Registrar officially
dropped you from the class,
so you're only taking
eight hours now.
Yeah, so, so what?
So diplomatic immunity applies
to diplomats' children
up to the age of 23,
provided they are
full-time students.
You aren't anymore.
I can bring charges against
you any time I want.
I didn't do it.
I believe you, but I think
you know what happened,
and I can make a case
that you were part of it.
Chen grabbed her seasickness
band when he killed her.
Didn't he? And then
he slipped it to you
to hide it, right? Okay.
That's your signature.
You used his credit
card to buy a drink,
and when you looked
up, Chen was gone.
He followed Maya below
deck where he killed her.
So...
it's your choice.
You want to be a witness
or an accomplice?
How much do you want me
to tell you?
Enough to know if
she should run or not.
She shouldn't run.
Okay. Why?
Well, she was
on the organizing board
for a fund-raiser
for Rod Blagojevich.
Old news. What else?
She's had relationships.
I figured. How many?
A few.
But not slut level?
No.
Then we shouldn't
have a problem.
Kalinda, we are doctors
discussing a patient.
What?
Well, one of them
in particular is problematic.
Omar Tate.
He's a financier
of high-end resorts.
What is it? Criminal past?
No.
No, he has a spotless record.
Perfect credit, actually.
Kalinda, you're being weird.
Well, Omar Tate
isn't his birth name.
It's Aarash...
bin Laden.
Come again?
It's Aarash bin Laden,
Osama's second cousin.
My ex-wife slept
with a bin Laden?
Listen, for what it's worth,
Aarash bin Laden
has never been linked
to terrorist activity
of any kind.
Oh, good. She banged
a nice bin Laden.
Uh...
This is absurd.
When was this?
And he has publicly denounced
the actions of al Qaeda.
Wait. When was this?
Uh, you know, I think
the details are in the file.
Kalinda, when was this?
2007.
She was married to me.
I'm sorry.
20 years, and that's my last,
best and final.
That leaves me
nowhere to go, Cary.
Go to your client.
Well, how do you know
Dick's story is reliable?
Nah, I don't have to make
my case to you, Alicia.
Take it or leave it.
But know that
it has a 24-hour clock.
Very impressive.
You heading out?
Yup. My last week here,
and I haven't been shot.
The day's young yet.
Do you think
Dick's telling the truth?
I think he's afraid
of prosecution,
so he'll say
whatever they want.
But it also could
be the truth.
Is that...?
That-That's him. Chen.
Call him.
Damn. It's Cary.
Hello?
Alicia, our office
was notified your client
just broke his electronic
perimeter. What's going on?
I-I'm not sure.
Alicia, if you know
your client is attempting
to flee the jurisdiction,
you have
a legal obligation
to report that.
I know my legal
obligations, Cary.
I have not been in touch
with my client.
I will call him
and get back to you.
Alicia...
Let me call him,
and I'll get back to you.
Wait. What are you doing?
We're not going
to know where he is.
I don't want to
know where he is.
Alicia?
I couldn't reach him.
Tread carefully here, Alicia,
because if you know something,
you're facing obstruction
of justice,
aiding and abetting...
I have not spoken to my client.
Do you know where he is?
Not for certain.
What do you know for certain?
I witnessed an Audi
with a driver
resembling my client
headed westbound on 90.
He's going to O'Hare.
Again, I do not know that
for certain.
I thought he was innocent.
I know.
Sometimes...
the guilty ones look
like the innocent ones.
Well, that's depressing.
So, what did she tell you?
I don't think you should run.
Why?
How... could you...
fund-raise
for Rod Blagojevich?
I know.
- It's dumb, huh?
- Yeah.
The voters don't know you.
That'll define you.
You don't think
you could leak it,
take the sting away?
No.
What else, Eli?
Isn't that enough?
No.
She told you?
I don't even know why I care.
The thought that my semen mixed
with bin Laden's.
Come on, Eli,
you know how this works.
The semen doesn't
just stay in us.
I thought we were happy in 2007.
We were.
It was a mistake.
I loved you, Vanessa.
We never talked.
We talked.
About work.
About politics.
My mother died, and...
This was a mistake.
Don't you dare say I
wasn't there for you.
I was there for you.
You were not!
You flew out.
I had to fly out.
You said it was fine.
- Because what could I say?
- That it wasn't fine.
But you were supposed
to know that it wasn't fine.
- How??  - Oh, God, it's like
we never left each other.
You know... thanks.
I just thought
I had done two years
of my life well,
that's all.
2006...
and seven.
You did do it well.
Sometimes it's too late.
♪ One, two, three, four... ♪.
How is she?
Not what I expected.
- Is that good?
- It is.
So... I met your son earlier.
I know. He said.
I was lame.
I was babbling.
He didn't say that.
I was.
So... do you want
me to meet them?
What?
No.
I mean, formally.
I know. No.
You sure?
Because I could probably make
a good impression.
That's okay.
Thanks.
I mean, really thanks, Will.
But it's not necessary.
Okay. Good.
Good. Good.
♪ Dog's got a bone ♪
♪ All on his own ♪
♪ Wednesday morning... ♪.
Mr. Gardner?
Excuse me.
I'm really sorry
about earlier.
For...?
Nothing.
I'm just figuring things
out here.
Good.
But why are you sorry?
I just didn't mean
to come to you first.
Alicia said if I had
any questions to come to her
and not to bother the partners.
No, you're not bothering us.
Don't worry about it.
- Are you sure?
- I'm positive.
Okay.
Thank you.
Everybody's so nice here.
Yeah. Lawyers.
The nicest people
in the world.
♪ Listen you will see,
coming on in to me ♪
♪ Listen you will see ♪
♪ Coming on in to me... ♪.
Oh, come on.
Hey!
One minute.
Where are you putting me
now, the parking garage?
- Excuse me?
- I won the Taiwan case.
The one that
you sloughed off on me.
We got Chen at the airport,
trying to flee.
- He's going away for life.
- I'm not moving you.
Peter's moving you.
Peter? Where?
There?
I guess you kiss
enough butts,
you eventually
kiss the right one.
re-sync by elderman corrections by Alice
www.Addic7ed.com
The best IPTV in the UK
WWW.ALLIN1BOX.CO.UK