Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SNAKE RATTLES)
(DOG BARKING)
Hey, boy.
Boy.
Where'd you come from?
CASEY: Blaise!
Blaise!
There you are. Come on.
Hi there.
Hi.
Thanks for finding him.
Yeah, no... he kinda found me.
We just moved in.
We're right back there.
Welcome.
Is that yours?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's mine.
I suppose that makes us neighbors.
All right, well, we oughta head home.
Come on, Blaise.
Hey, I'm... I'm Jonas.
Ford.
I'm Casey Caraway.
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
(COWS MOOING)
Where'd you go?
I found a buzztail in the barn.
Just walked out to the woods a bit.
I'll deal with this.
The check valve on the hose is leakin'.
We'll need to use
the kitchen pipes for today.
Mom's not gonna like that.
Hell, let's see how she likes it
when we can't afford her rum and smokes...
'cause we're too backed up.
Hey. You remember how I showed you.
Shut off that water supply and let
the pressure out. And Jonas?
When that snake finds it's way back...
you kill it.
(COWS MOOING)
(CAR DOOR SHUTS)
(STEPS APPROACHING)
Hey, boy.
- Mornin'.
- Morning.
Sleep okay?
CASEY: Yeah.
That coffee I'm smelling?
Yep.
Got some toast, too.
There's nothin' to put on it, though.
I'll leave you some cash.
Why don't you go into town today
and pick us up a few things?
How's that sound?
Sure.
Here.
You out did yourself, baby girl.
Are you nervous?
Nervous about what?
New station, new town.
Catching bad guys is your daddy's trade.
He can take it anywhere.
Why? Do I look nervous?
Come here.
Come on.
Let me have your hand.
You feel it?
Can't get any calmer than that.
Casey...
I'm sorry we had to move.
I'm proud of ya' for making the best of it.
I'll get us out of here as quick as I can.
Before you know it.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRILLING)
Blaise, come here.
(CICADAS BUZZING)
Hi, ma'am.
My name is Casey Caraway.
My daddy and I, we just moved
into the house down the road.
Um...
I met your son Jonas this morning.
Is he home by any chance?
What's your business with him?
There's no business.
I was just... I was about
to head into town...
No, no, no, Jonas...
he don't go to town.
So he can't show you nothin'
that you wouldn't see for yourself.
No, I...
I guess, I just mean the way
to get to know him a little.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(TRACTOR ENGINE TURNS OFF)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, cowboy.
I was lookin' for you.
I know.
Your mom...
Yeah, she's...
nah, she gets... sad...
sometimes.
You gonna be in trouble?
I don't care.
Uh... where you goin'?
Nowhere, really.
Do you wanna come?
Yeah.
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
Blaise, come on.
Come on.
So, how's the school here?
I start on Monday.
Oh, it's good, but I don't really go anymore.
Really?
Yeah.
And your parents are okay with that?
I hope so, it was their idea.
And here I thought I'd have
someone to cheat off of.
(LAUGHS)
Probably doing you a favor in that case.
Your family?
Why'd y'all move here?
Actually, my dad, he...
he grew up, the next county over.
He says they need a lot of eyes and ears...
because of all of the dirty trading
coming through town.
And your mom?
She okay with the move?
My mom's dead.
When I was a baby.
Cancer.
I'm sorry.
Can't miss what you never had.
Does that smell right to you?
Yeah.
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
There you are, baby girl.
Beginning to worry about you a bit.
Hi, Daddy.
This is our neighbor, Jonas.
Mr. Caraway.
So that's your old ranch
down the road, is it?
Yes, sir.
Not many ranchers around here
still see worth it to stick it out.
Something to admire there.
Can't be easy living.
Nah... ain't so bad, sir.
I hope you're hungry.
Got some steaks.
That-a-girl.
Let me take that bag off ya.
I'll go on back and fire up the grill.
I take it your mama's
got a nice dinner waiting for you.
That right?
Yes, sir.
Call me Wayne.
Casey, you come in soon now.
Mm-hm.
Come on, Blaise!
Well... thanks for showing me around.
Yeah.
Sorry if I might've spoiled
any other things...
Nah, nah, you... you didn't spoil nothin'.
Good.
And where the hell you been?
Was just... showing Casey around town.
Being friendly. That's what neighbors
oughta be, ought they?
Now you tuck in that lip. And you are not
to just run on out of here without notice.
Hell, I wouldn't have had to if Ma
didn't slam the door on her face.
Hey, you left me high and dry today, son.
I fell behind a great deal
'cause of your selfishness.
Pa... I ain't selfish.
Okay, I work just as hard
as any ranch hand that gets paid...
and I don't complain or ask for nothing.
I'm sorry for runnin' out on you.
I'm gonna finish chopping up that wood...
I rounded up this morning, then reinforce
the pen, all like I was suppose to.
Uh, Jonas?
Forget the pen.
It'll be there tomorrow.
I know... but I got plans tomorrow.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Do you know people can see
for three miles on flat land?
JONAS: That's pretty far.
It's not far enough.
It's always been my dream
to see the ocean one day.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
My mom used to say
how beautiful the coast is.
Said she felt trapped by the land.
Told me the ocean is freedom.
Thought you said your mama died
when you were a baby.
That was a lie.
Why?
Guess it...
just hurts too much to remember her.
You, uh...
You lie a lot?
All the time.
You don't think about...
God, or...
I think God's also a lie.
Just something someone made up
to keep people from being bad.
Like Santa Claus for grown ups.
But I don't need to lie with you.
Not anymore.
Ask me anything...
and I'll tell you the truth.
You, uh...
wanna be my girlfriend?
Yeah.
Hey, I... got you something.
There's two of them,
the other one's back at my house.
Now if we need to talk
to each other... we can.
I love it.
Good.
- So I was thinking maybe tomorrow...
- She's busy.
Why are you hiding, Daddy?
- I ain't hidin', I'm waitin'.
- It's my fault she's late, sir, I took us...
Head on home.
It's my time with my daughter now.
Um...
guess I'll come by tomorrow, probably...
You got shit in your ears, boy?
CASEY: Come on, Blaise.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Wanted to celebrate
with my baby girl tonight.
I made spaghetti Bolognese, your favorite.
I'm not hungry.
Good thing I tossed it, then.
I wouldn't get too attached to that boy.
Looks like we're gonna get out of
this shit hole sooner than I thought.
That's too bad.
'Cause I was starting to like it here.
Stop.
Come down.
You look like her.
You talk like her.
Look at me.
Don't be like her.
You're my blood. You're a Caraway.
It's you and me, Casey.
Say it.
It's you and me.
Wait.
I said wait, goddammit!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Come on, boy! You wanna
fuck around with my daughter, huh?
You wanna do that?
Come on! Oh, hell yeah!
You ever bob for apples?
Oh, hell yeah!
CASEY: Daddy! Daddy, stop it!
Daddy, stop it, please!
Dad, stop! Let him go!
Back up!
Stop!
Daddy, stop!
- Daddy, please!
- You see?
(CHOKING)
Daddy, please stop it! That's enough now!
You're all right, boy.
Daddy, that's enough, now!
Big breath, now.
No, Dad, stop! Please, stop it!
- Quiet!
- Stop!
It's you and me, Dad! It's you and me!
Please, stop it!
Dad, please!
(COUGHING)
Next time I see you around my house...
around my daughter...
I'll hold you under for good.
WAYNE: Casey, get in the house!
I said, get in the house!
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
CASEY: (OVER WALKIE TALKIE)
Jonas? Jonas, are you there?
Yeah, I'm here.
CASEY: Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine. You?
CASEY: I'm so sorry.
You didn't do nothin'.
You shouldn't be there with him.
It ain't right.
No, Jonas, you don't understand.
My dad...
I ain't afraid of him.
You should be.
(LIGHT CLICKS OFF)
Didn't see you in there today, Mr. Ford.
Quite a sermon you missed.
Need to talk to you
about one of your officers, sir.
Uh-huh.
Mr. Caraway.
Well, go on then.
He's no good... sir.
Gonna need more than that.
No good, how?
It's how he treats his daughter.
I understand the two of you
have become pretty close, am I correct?
Yes, sir.
And this complaint of yours, it wouldn't have
anything to do with a potential complaint...
of his about you spending all day
and night with her would it?
No.
But he has made such an objection?
Hm.
I saw him beat her.
And he went on afterward
to drown me half to death.
Well, that doesn't sound quite right.
But what puzzles me about this, you see...
is that kids are a product of their parents.
Now, Casey's about the sweetest...
happiest little girl these
old eyes ever seen.
And considerin' her mama
ain't been around for some time...
I credit Sergeant Caraway...
with the type of young lady she's become.
Now, regardin' all this hittin'
and drownin'...
I'll surely look into it,
'cause that's my job...
but I will tell you this...
you ain't Casey's family.
You might share spit and secrets
but the two of you's don't share blood.
And the only business you have with her
is what her father says so.
Now, you go on, now.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Well, hell, boy.
I was on the fence about you,
but it's official now...
I like you.
You got a pretty good pair...
considerin' they ain't dropped yet.
Of course, that being said...
get off my property.
You ain't welcome.
You're a bad man.
Oh, is that so?
And what's your idea
of a good man, your daddy?
Huh?
Some hard bum who keeps
his family locked up on his ranch...
like it's a damn tomb.
He don't beat on us.
Never laid a finger.
That's 'cause he's a coward.
You don't know nothin' about him.
Oh... that's where you're wrong, son.
You see...
there's only two kinds of men
in this world...
your daddy... and me.
Now, the way I see it...
you got two options...
and I'm sorry to say
that not either of 'em...
involves you having a friendship
with my baby girl.
Option number one...
we be civil, as all neighbors oughta be.
We see each other in town...
we nod, smile...
be on our respective ways.
Option number two...
I make life for your family a living hell.
One little phone call about
violated regulations and I'll have...
land inspectors so far up your daddy's ass...
the cattle will be impressed
how hard he shits.
You keep coming around here,
doing what you do...
and I'll know which option
you've chosen for yourself.
And your family.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTING)
(INDISTINCT TV CHATTER)
Hey, Pa?
Yeah?
Shh.
Don't shush me.
Damn it, Elbert,
I'm right in the middle of this thing.
You're always in the middle...
- Pa?
- What?
Can I talk to you?
Porch.
(INDISTINCT TV CHATTER)
Well?
It's Mr. Caraway, sir.
Casey's daddy.
What about him?
I saw him hit Casey.
And when I tried to protect her...
he dragged me outside
and he held my head in a basin.
What do you mean...
when you tried to protect her?
I ran inside and I...
tried to protect her.
Well, that was a pretty damn
foolish thing to do, now, wasn't it?
What the hell was I supposed to do, Pa?
Just watch him beat on her?
Now it probably wasn't like that.
He's a man of the law.
I ain't sayin' that makes him a saint...
I'm sayin' it ain't up to us to judge.
You need to be smart in this life, son.
Think before you act!
You don't go running into a man's house
uninvited and start attacking him!
And a police officer, no less!
You have any idea the reign of shit
that man could bring down on this family!
She needs help... Pa.
Gotta do somethin'.
Like what?
Run over there throwin' punches?
The only thing that'll do...
is wind me up in the drunk tank
with a court date.
You are a coward.
Yeah.
You know...
you and your mama...
oughta take a little trip sometime.
'Cause this world will eat you up whole.
And I'll tell you something else...
you ever talk to me like this...
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
JONAS: (OVER WALKIE) Hey, Casey?
Casey, you there?
Casey?
Casey, are you there?
I know damn well, you're awake.
Casey?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(WALKIE TALKIE STATIC)
Dipshit.
(ENGINE STARTING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(ENGINE TURNS OFF)
(TRUCK DOOR OPENS)
(TRUCK DOOR CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(TAILGATE OPENING)
(MOTORCYCLES APPROACHING)
(ENGINES TURN OFF)
WAYNE: Hey... evening.
Found the place alright?
BIKER: Let's get this over with.
WAYNE: Where's the fire? You just got here.
BIKER: Let's go then.
WAYNE: I'll tell you what.
You set your bag down in between us...
and I'll throw mine over.
WAYNE: There now. That's more like it.
(GUNSHOT)
(MULTIPLE GUNSHOTS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
Fuck!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Something was taken
out of my truck while I was here.
This was the only place
it could've been taken. Speak!
There was a boy.
- A boy?
- I saw a boy.
He was hiding outside before. He had a...
He had a bag with him.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(MUSIC CHANGES)
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(ENGINE STALLING)
Casey!
Casey! Casey!
Casey... come back!
Casey!
What's in the bag?
You took this from my dad?
Who'd he take it from?
I don't know.
But he killed 'em for it.
What were you thinking?
That home ain't safe for you.
We had to get you outta there.
And now 'cause of this money, we can.
Where we gonna go?
WAYNE: (OVER WALKIE) Jonas, you there?
You can still get out of this, son.
WAYNE: (OVER WALKIE)
I'll make a deal with you.
Bring my daughter and my bag and...
that'll be the end of it. No harm, no foul.
Jonas...
if you don't return what's mine...
if you make me chase you...
it's gonna get mean...
and you're gonna wish I drowned your ass.
Fuck!
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(METAL CREAKING)
(WIND BLOWING)
Jonas?
Yeah?
You praying?
No.
(METAL CREAKING)
Now might be a good time.
(CAR HORN HONKS)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Come on, Jonas, hurry up.
Come on.
Let's go, Jonas.
Go, go, go, go.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Blaise! Blaise, come here!
JONAS: Sunday school.
Best place to be...
every Sunday morning.
All right.
I lost count twice...
but, I think I got around
four hundred and thirty thousand.
I've got about five hundred
and fifty thousand.
So that's...
nine hundred and eighty, total.
It's almost a million dollars.
- Do you know what that means?
- It means we're rich.
No, Jonas, this is not our money.
Hey, well, it ain't your pa's, neither.
I stole from him just like
he stole from them...
so we got as much right to it as he does.
We just deserve it... 'cause we're good.
It's only half.
And it's just a back up.
So, if ever we need more,
we'll come back and dig it up.
So where you wanna go?
The ocean.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
(RADIO PLAYING)
# I saw the light come shining #
# Shining all around #
# I saw that light come down #
Help you with something?
- Want a gun.
- (LAUGHING)
And I wanna retire.
Not old enough.
Maybe I can help with that.
Where'd you get that?
Does it matter?
Single action colt.
Thirty-eight.
It's an antique.
What's wrong with those?
Those are on the books.
It's this one... or nothing.
Does it work?
It works.
I'll take it then.
Some bullets, too.
What the hell you want with this, anyway?
Protect my family.
All of it.
You get the other half
when you show me how to use it.
(THUNDER ROLLING)
(RAIN FALLING)
Won't be much longer.
It doesn't hurt now, Jonas.
Stop worrying.
He's mean as hell.
Ain't he?
He never used to lay a hand on me.
But my mom...
He wasn't too concerned with beating her up.
He used to say she could take it.
I tried, you know, like...
I tried convincing her to run away with me.
She wouldn't leave him.
This one time...
he came to pick us up.
We were at the movies, me and my mom.
He... he had been drinking.
So... so, she got on his case
about it and started yelling.
He lost control...
and the car crashed.
I watched her die.
And then, uh... the cops came.
But they were his friends, you know, so...
they made sure nothing bad
would happen to him.
And then after that, I guess...
I guess I was the only one
around to get angry at.
He'd... he'd always feel bad the day after...
so he'd buy me a present.
A dress, some shoes... a puppy.
And every time, he promised...
he wouldn't lose control again.
But he's a liar... just like me.
No.
God made a mistake giving you to him.
You're good.
That's something you can trust.
Something else you can trust...
you ain't never gonna see him again.
(THUNDER CRASHING)
All right.
(SHOWER RUNNING)
Come on.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
You're so clean.
Yeah... yeah.
Kinda got... gotten used
to the fact of you smelling bad.
I thought that was you the whole time.
Hey!
You're freezing!
- Really?
- Yeah.
How about this one?
Yep, that's even worse!
Is this better than the tarp?
Yeah.
Have you ever kissed a girl, Jonas?
(BLOWING DOG WHISTLE)
(BLAISE BARKING)
Blaise!
JONAS: What's out there?
I don't see anything.
- Blaise, quiet.
- (BLAISE BARKING)
I don't know what's wrong with him.
(BLOWING DOG WHISTLE)
(BARKING CONTINUES)
We gotta go. Casey, We gotta go, now.
- (BLOWING DOG WHISTLE)
- (BLAISE BARKING)
Go, go, go.
(BLAISE BARKING)
(ENGINE STARTING)
Last time you hopped in the back...
of someone's car without them knowing...
it got you into some trouble, Mr. Ford.
Give me your gun.
Don't carry one.
Slow.
Put your hands on the wheel.
How'd you find us?
Got word of a report
from a pawnshop owner in town.
Said a young boy
tried to sell him an old pistol.
Says the boy was with a pretty
little blonde and a dog, too.
That got my attention,
even if the rest didn't quite add up.
Motel must've been mighty hard
to resist after a storm like that.
Havin' fun spendin' our money?
It ain't your money!
Drive.
(SIGHS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
You're gonna get that poor girl killed,
you know that, don't ya?
I'm saving her.
You're chin deep in shit here, son.
The longer you play this out,
the worse off you'll be.
So let's just put the gun down, go get Casey
and the money and be done with all this.
The money's gone.
We got mugged by a bum in Crow Lake.
You expect me to believe that?
Believe what you want, just keep driving.
What's in your head, boy?
How can you possibly think
you're gonna get away with this?
We just will.
We deserve to.
I hate to break the news to you, Mr. Ford...
but who deserves what don't mean
diddily in the real world.
One thing's for sure, you two sure left
a nice trail of bread crumbs behind ya.
Slow down.
Couple of runaways with travel
packs and a dopey old dog.
That's an image that tends
to linger in people's minds.
I said slow down!
You stole a lot of money, Mr. Ford.
When you steal from a man,
he doesn't stop looking for you.
It isn't just one day, decide to let it go.
- Slow down!
- God forgives, so we don't have to.
Look what you're making an old man do!
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Give me your wallet and phone.
(GROANING)
Son, you should get that checked.
You got shit in your ears?
Your hat, too.
You think I'm a bad man, Jonas?
I'm the tooth fairy compared
to what's comin'.
I ain't scared of him.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Casey!
- Jonas!
- Casey!
What happened? What happened?
How's it look?
Oh, this... this is bad.
You need... you need to go to the hospital.
No, no, no hospital.
They'll be waiting for us.
Here, just hold it there! Hold it there!
Ma'am, I... I need some things.
Nothing back here I'm allowed to sell you
without a parent and a prescription, hun.
I need disinfectant and stuff to numb pain.
Someone you know hurting?
Here just... take it.
Just give me what I need.
Please.
He's my friend, he...
he's bleeding and it's really bad.
Then you better get them to a hospital.
We can't.
I want to help you...
I can't just give you what you're asking.
I'm not asking.
Oh!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Jonas, come on, help me out.
- Ow!
- I'm sorry!
Okay. Come on.
Hold these, hold these. Come on.
Okay.
(HORN HONKING)
Keep pressing!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
Okay... okay.
Open, open, open.
Here.
Okay.
You're gonna need to keep still, okay?
Agh!
- Agh!
- I'm... I'm sorry.
Jonas, please, you gotta stop.
You gotta stop moving.
Okay, okay, okay.
You're doing really great.
Agh!
- Agh!
- I'm... I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Sorry... I'm so sorry.
Agh!
Hey, cowboy.
CASEY: How you feeling?
You saved me.
What do you think?
It's no ocean, but it's ours.
We need to rethink a few things.
I know.
We just need to figure out a way to...
cover a lot of ground... quickly.
That'll be tough with Blaise.
You looking for the gun?
Yeah.
It's gone.
What?
Got rid of it this morning...
while you were passed out.
Casey, why would you do that?
Because it scares me.
It scares me more to think about
what we're suppose to do without it.
Okay, that gun keeps us safe and you know it.
I don't want to be those kind of people.
What kind of people?
The kind that sticks a gun in someone's
face to get what they want.
Well, I don't want to be those
kind of people, either, Casey...
but we have to be realistic about this.
It's only a matter of time before someone
sees us with Blaise and puts it together.
He's gonna get us caught again and when
he does we need to be ready for it.
Casey... where is it?
I'm not saying.
We need it, Casey.
Just in case someone stronger
than me tries to hurt you.
No one's stronger than you, Jonas.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Hi, there.
Hi, sir.
FATHER: What can I help you with?
Where'd you go?
- Where's Blaise?
- He's gone!
- I gave him up, just like you wanted.
- Hey, Casey!
He was my only friend before you!
And I abandoned him to keep you safe!
Keep me safe?
What are you talking about, Casey?
This has all been to protect you.
That's the reason for my whole plan!
What plan? You didn't have a plan!
You barely gave it a thought!
There wasn't time for that, Casey!
I had to get you out of that house!
Why? Okay, why couldn't you
just leave me right where I was?
You stole the money! You had to leave!
Not me! Not Blaise!
Then why are you still here, then?
Huh? Why'd you even come?
Because you weren't leaving without me...
and he was coming after you.
That's why I left.
To get you out of there,
to protect you and I still am.
If my daddy finds us...
he'll beat me two inches from death...
but you...
he'll go all the way.
- Let's go get Blaise.
- No.
- Casey, we can make it work...
- It's done!
Let's pack, we're already behind.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
JONAS: You hate me?
CASEY: No...
I love you.
JONAS: I love you, too.
Just, um... could you wait one second?
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
ELBERT: (OVER PHONE) Hello?
Hello?
Jonas?
Son, is that you?
Pa?
Aw, Jonas...
Thank God, are... are you all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm all right.
Where are you?
Whatever we've done
to make you abandon us, I...
You didn't do nothin'.
Casey's dad's after us.
He's dangerous, Pa.
He's a thief and a killer.
The chief, too.
Well, co... come home then,
you'll be safe here.
Casey won't be.
JONAS: (OVER PHONE)
He'll come after us, take her away...
and there won't be anything
we can do about it.
Well, then, we'll go to the police
and tell them what you're telling me.
They are the police, Pa.
My word won't hold up against theirs.
- Son, listen to me...
- Tell Ma I love her...
and I'll be home in a little while.
I sent something in the post for you.
Jonas... don't you hang up now!
There's more comin'.
ELBERT: (OVER PHONE) Jonas!
Jo...
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(POLICE SIREN BLARES)
DRIVER: (OVER PA) Sorry, folks,
looks like we're bein' pulled over.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, my God, Jonas.
Let's get the bags ready.
JONAS: Sir?
DRIVER:
Son, I'm going to need you to keep your seat.
Sir, I'll pay you, okay,
I got a lot of money!
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- Listen, sir...
No, no, don't open the door, please!
- Son!
- Sir!
DRIVER: Good afternoon, officers!
Well, hey, boy... sure am glad to see you.
Step off the bus, Mr. Ford.
Hey!
Agh.
(CUFFS CLICKING)
There's my angel.
Everything's fine, folks. Police matter.
Casey?
Casey, let's go.
Goddamn, girl.
No, don't let him take us!
No!
Casey... it's time to go home, honey.
No...
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
That'll be all.
Where's the rest of it?
I told the sheriff.
I got mugged in Crow Lake.
That's all that's left.
Casey? The truth!
Right now!
Okay, we buried it!
That's a little vague.
No, back North!
Just in case we'd wanna come back.
Get your ass up.
Get back in the car!
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINE STARTING)
You did pretty good, considering.
You even let my daughter give up the thing...
she loves most in the whole world...
'cause you thought it'd set you free.
Pretty cold, Mr. Ford.
Funny thing is, abandoning
the dog is what got you caught.
I got a call from a vet in Hodgeville.
Someone brought him in to check his ID.
He had a microchip under his ear.
When you scan it, our info comes up.
We figured the only reason
to ditch the pup...
is you was aiming to take a bus.
Blaise is our dog, Casey.
Not everything's as simple
as it seems, when you're a kid.
It's a mean world and the angels
left us to fend for ourselves.
You gotta fight for whatever's yours...
however you know how.
You wouldn't know an angel,
if you were beatin' on one.
That's what you do, ain't it?
You beat on angels?
How we on gas?
Not in the red yet.
Take the next stop anyway.
These kids are probably hungry.
Why don't you let me take over?
These patties take two hands to eat.
If you insist.
(ENGINE STARTS)
What's happening?
Jonas?
He's all right.
A couple of crushed Valium
never hurt anybody.
What the hell are you doing?
This is as far as I go.
I'm taking my half of the money.
Your half, wherever it is, is your problem.
Your fault.
I'm done with this nonsense.
You fuck...
Sweet dreams, darlin'.
It's the least you deserve.
You really fucked me on this one, Wayne.
Goddamn it. Fuck!
Bitch.
(GAGS)
How much farther, Casey?
Casey?
It's fifty miles... maybe less.
(ENGINE STARTING)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
Up ahead... through that clearing.
WAYNE: I'd be sure, if I were you.
Come on, boy.
Yeah, come on! There ya go!
Casey.
Casey, what are you doing?
Casey... please.
Casey, please! Casey!
- Come on now, baby girl.
- Casey, please don't.
- Let's get this done.
- Casey!
Casey! Casey!
Casey!
All you had to do was mind your own business.
Let's go.
Casey! Casey!
Casey!
It's under here somewhere.
What are you waiting for, then?
I'll try that one.
No use stallin'.
Hey!
Whoa! Baby girl.
I'll kill you before I let you kill him.
Nobody's killin' anybody.
Put the gun down, Casey and we'll talk.
You shut up!
Casey, you're scaring me.
Okay, I admit it... I know I failed you.
I lost my heart, I lost my way.
But I swear on my soul,
on your mama's grave...
- I'll let him go.
- I don't believe you.
You know what happens
if you pull that trigger, don't you?
You'll be alone.
I know you're with Jonas now.
Pretty soon he's gonna get tired
and he's gonna wanna go home.
You'll see... one day he'll quit
on you, quick as light.
It's coming, I guarantee it.
Casey, you're my angel.
Baby girl, please.
It's you and me, right?
Say it.
Shut up.
It's you and...
(SOBBING)
(CHOKING)
(CRYING)
(ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
I'm sorry.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CHANGES)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org