Completely.
iEl amigo del cártel!
- [GUNFIRE]
- [INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
You hit?
You're in shock.
You're his wife,
and you got scared enough to talk to me.
Just tell me where you sent him.
I don't think so.
♪♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[LOLA MARSH'S "SOMETHING STUPID" PLAYS]
[HUMMING]
♪♪
[LIGHTER CLICKS]
[TAIL RATTLING, WATER BUBBLING]
♪♪
[FAUCET TURNS ON]
[FAUCET TURNS OFF]
♪♪
[SLURPS]
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[RINGING]
[CELLPHONE RINGING, VIBRATING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
Jimmy?
JIMMY: Yeah.
It's me.
[GASPS]
I'm okay.
[FLY BUZZES]
[CRYING]
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
♪♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[CAR DOORS CLOSING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[VEHICLE DEPARTS]
[FLY BUZZES]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[VEHICLE DOOR OPENS]
[VEHICLE DOOR CLOSES]
[VEHICLE DEPARTING]
TYRUS: You're sure?
Alright. Stay put, and call
me if there's a problem.
Doesn't look like anyone's
been down that road,
definitely no one official.
Bodies, trucks... it's all still there.
Couple of flatbeds headed their way.
They'll clear it all out.
Like it never happened.
And the one who followed you.
We'll be damn lucky if
we ever find that guy.
That'll have to do.
He's in the middle of nowhere.
Don't go to sleep yet.
We gotta work on your story.
Alright. Let's do it.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[DOOR CLOSES, BAGS THUD]
[BREATHING HEAVILY] De Guzman. Jorge.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
$7 million?
Yep.
[BAG THUDS]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[COUNTING MACHINES WHIRRING]
I'm fine.
$7 million.
Your client has $7 million.
Where'd it come from?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
It's not for me to ask where
a client gets his money.
And just who exactly is your client?
Jorge de Guzman.
[WHIRRING CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR WHOOSHES, CLOSES]
Yes, hello?
This is extra.
[SIGHS]
And now Mr. De Guzman?
[HORNS HONKING, SIRENS WAILING]
Well.
You must have a story.
Car trouble.
Ah, broke down about six
miles from the pick-up site.
Y'know there's no cell
reception out there, right?
Car trouble.
Yeah. Just kaput.
So, um...
why so long?
It's not that far back to the main road.
You didn't just hitchhike?
I thought of that, but, you know,
with $7 mil in cash,
I was kind of afraid
who might pick me up.
I didn't think it was worth the risk.
I walked north.
Probably not the smartest move,
but after a night lost in the desert,
I made it.
Well, that was the right call.
Hey, hey, you did good, eh?
[GROANS, INHALES SHARPLY]
Anyway, listen, I wouldn't be too happy.
The $7 mil... it...
it really sent up a huge flare.
They're looking into you.
I-I don't know how long
"Jorge de Guzman" is gonna hold up.
Hey, listen, by the time
these dipshits figure it out,
I will be long gone, man.
Back home in Mexico, y'know?
Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey, but don't worry.
You and me? We're not done.
We're gonna do things, big things.
"Friend of the cartel", right?
- Right.
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
So, hey, my, um... my cousins...
they pay you?
Uh... yep.
Perfecto.
So make sure you buy
something nice for the wife.
Man, she's a looker, huh?
Uh, my... my what?
Yeah! The abuela, man...
she came by to see me.
Hey, nice job, man.
I mean, for somebody who
marries that far up...
bien hecho, man.
Respect, you know?
Yeah.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
KIM: Let me help.
[WATER RUNNING]
Here.
[EXHALING SHARPLY]
Oh, my God, Jimmy.
You need to go to the emergency room.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
I cleaned it out real
good at the truck stop.
Alright, well, let's at least
just go get you an I.V., huh?
You're dehydrated.
No. I don't need an I.V.
I-I've been pounding
sports drinks nonstop.
I'm really o-okay.
Alright. Come on. You're
gonna get in this bath, though.
It'll help your skin.
[FAUCET SQUEALS, SHUTS OFF]
What is this, Cream of Wheat?
Oatmeal. It's an oatmeal bath.
Anti-inflammatory.
It'll help your sunburn.
[WATER SLOSHING]
[GROANING]
The temp okay?
Yeah. It's good. [INHALES SHARPLY]
You sure?
Yeah. [EXHALES HEAVILY]
Okay.
You don't want any food
or anything else to drink?
No. I'm good.
I just need to sit.
This is good.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[WATER DRIPPING]
I can't believe you walked
through the desert alone
for 36 hours.
I c... I can't even fathom it.
That's right.
All by myself.
[SCOFFS]
[WATER DRIPPING]
So...
is there anything you want to tell me?
- About... ?
- Lalo.
You saw Lalo?
Yeah.
Jimmy, short of going to the police,
Lalo was the only lead I had
to figure out what happened...
Kim, you have to stay
away from people like Lalo.
- Jimmy...
- You don't see Lalo.
I see Lalo. Okay?
I'm in the game. You're not in the game.
What... The game?
Listen, it was perfectly safe.
I was at the MDC, surrounded by guards,
like any lawyer visiting a client, okay?
But he's not your client.
He's my client, so
please just keep away.
Jimmy, I was worried about you.
And I'm worried about you.
Kim, when I was out there...
I didn't think I was gonna make it.
I thought I was...
done.
I was that close to giving up.
And the only thing that kept me going...
was knowing that you were here.
So...
Okay.
I won't see Lalo again.
Good.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[WATER DRIPPING]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
After all this...
was it worth it?
Go look in the bag.
The bag in the living room.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
It's on the chair.
It's a gray bag.
♪♪
You see it?
Yeah, Jimmy.
I see it.
♪♪
That's what it's all about.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
♪♪
MIKE: Six guys, three
vehicles, heavily armed.
My guess is
they followed the Salamanca
cousins up from Chihuahua,
trailing the money
but not wanting to
take these two guys on.
And I'm no expert, but they had tattoos,
same symbol I saw on a job back East.
A Colombian gang.
Draw it for me.
[SIGHS]
These men were hired.
By who?
[SCREEN BEEPING]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[CROWD GASPS]
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
Sí?
GUS: I trust you heard the good news.
Gustavo. Which good news is that?
Our colleague has been released
by the American authorities.
At a substantial price, but he's free.
And I'm told he will be returning home
to continue operations.
That is good news.
But coming south, you say?
That's correct.
Forfeiting bail is the only way
to assure he remains out of prison.
Well, then, all will
be returning to normal.
And, I trust, your run of
bad luck will be behind you.
Bad luck?
The DEA.
The fire.
The arrests.
My hope is that it's over.
Yes.
I believe the coming
weeks will be our best yet.
Excellent. I'll pass on the good news.
Buenas noches, Gustavo.
Thank you. Enjoy your evening.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I just spoke to the man
responsible for the attack.
Someone we need to worry about?
He was trying to protect
his own business...
by protecting our business.
If that's him trying to help...
He knows nothing of what
we are trying to accomplish.
Once Salamanca is south of the border,
our actions must be unimpeachable.
Any reflection on me
will not be greeted with kindness.
Alright.
Yes?
There's one other
thing we should discuss.
Nacho Varga.
He wants out.
He's done everything we asked.
He held up his end.
I think it's time we cut him loose.
I see no reason to give up an asset.
Once Salamanca's dealt with,
we have no use for Varga.
He's the only guy they
have running things up here.
He disappears,
Salamanca operation falls apart.
[SIGHS]
Varga stays.
Better to control the opposition
without their knowledge.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
You have a gun to his father's head.
That doesn't sit with me.
You want to keep Varga for the long run,
I don't think fear is a great motivator.
A dog who bites every owner he's had...
can only be disciplined
with a firm hand.
Or... put down.
[DOOR CREAKS]
He's taking care of business tonight.
Tomorrow morning he's
seeing Hector to say goodbye.
Um, after that, I drive him south.
He didn't tell me where.
All I know is I'm dropping him off
and somebody else is
taking him over the border.
TYRUS: That it?
Yeah. Hey, um...
[SIGHS] Once he's
down, that's it, right?
He's done?
Just do what you're told,
don't worry about it.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[COFFEE PERCOLATING]
Hey.
Hungry?
You good with cereal?
Or you want me to try an omelet?
Uh, cereal,
probably the safest
thing for my stomach.
- Okay.
- I'll get it.
No, no, no, no, no. I got it.
Just... Just relax.
[DRAWER OPENS AND CLOSES]
[SILVERWARE CLINKS]
You goin' in late today?
[REFRIGERATOR DOOR OPENS]
- Uh...
- [REFRIGERATOR DOOR CLOSES]
I just thought I'd stay home today.
Kim, I can take care of myself.
Well, I already called in sick,
so you're stuck with me.
[JUICER WHIRRING]
[JUICE GRINDING]
[ORANGE THUDS]
[JUICE SPLASHING, ORANGE THUDS]
[WHIRRING INTENSIFIES]
[ORANGE THUDS]
[JUICER GRINDING]
Oh! Damn it!
Shit.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
[WHIRRING STOPS]
I guess my stomach's just
not ready for this yet.
I-It's okay.
Not a big deal.
[PAPER TOWELS RUSTLING]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[GROANS LIGHTLY] Are you sure
you don't have to go into work?
Yeah, I'm sure. We both
need to take it easy.
How about a day without drama?
That sounds real good, actually.
- [CHUCKLES]
- WOMAN: Oh, hiya, Skinny.
- WOMAN #2: Hello, Ruth.
- Hello, Maisie.
- Well, look who's here.
- Hello, Hildy.
HILDY: How are you?
Tell me... is the lord
of the universe in?
Yes, he's in. In a bad humor.
Somebody must have
stolen the crown jewels.
- Shall we announce you?
- Oh, no, no.
I'll blow my own horn.
He's in. Bruce, you better wait here.
I'll be back in 10 minutes.
BRUCE: Even 10 minutes is a
long time to be away from you.
- What did you say?
- Huh?
Well... Go on.
- Aww...
- [CHUCKLES] Well, go ahead.
Well, I just said even 10 minutes
is a long time to be away from you.
I heard you the first time. I like it.
That's why I asked you to say it again.
I can stand being spoiled a little.
The gentleman I'm going in to
see did very little spoiling.
I'd like to spoil him just once.
You sure you don't
want me to go with you?
Oh, no, I can handle it.
Well, if things gets rough,
remember, I'm here.
[CELLPHONE VIBRATING LOUDLY]
MAN: Hi, Hildy! Welcome back!
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
I'm... I'm sorry.
No, today... uh, it's impossible today.
I-I can't help you.
[SIGHS] Yeah, that's right.
A little more around the chin, boss.
Uh, w-wait. What are they saying?
Uh, y... Just wait 45
minutes. I-I-I can be there.
- What? Jimmy, no.
- Yeah, you tell them I'm on my way.
- So, how's the big slot-machine king?
- [KEYPAD BEEPS]
- Oh, I ain't doing that no more.
- Jim... Jimmy.
- You can barely walk.
- What are you doing?
It's my client. He's in big trouble.
They're trying to kill his plea deal
because his buddy was carrying weed.
Well, okay.
So get a continuance.
You don't have to do this today.
No, this guy's scared out of his mind.
I-I wouldn't feel right
leaving him hanging.
[SIGHS]
Jimmy, look, I know you're lying.
And I know something terrible
happened in the desert.
This isn't about our deal.
I'm not insisting or
forcing you to tell me.
I just...
[SIGHS] want you to
know that I'm here...
for you.
And you can tell me, okay?
No judgments.
You're right.
Something did happen out there.
When I was in the desert...
[SIGHS] I had to drink my own pee.
I was out of water,
and, uh, in order to
survive, I had to drink pee.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Yeah, that's it, so...
And there you go.
Look...
I will recover,
and we never need to mention this again.
I'm gonna go get changed,
and I'm gonna get down there.
[FOOTSTEPS DEPART]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Kim.
- Feeling better?
- Oh, yeah.
Just a 24-hour thing. It passed.
Besides, I thought I should come in
and prep the Colorado meeting.
Oh, they moved that up to
this morning. Stef handled it.
There was no pushback
from Boulder city council?
Stef cleared up the
conditional use issue.
Everything's moving forward.
Wow. That's great.
Great.
Well, uh...
Okay.
You wanted to write letters
to the planning board in Broomfield.
Right. Yes, that's right.
I'll get started on that,
if you can just get me those names.
List is on your desk.
Of course. Great.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION,
TELEPHONE RINGING]
First letter is for Mr. Armand Bekaris,
Chairman of the Planning
and Zoning Commission,
and, uh, let's just c.c. the Vice Chair,
Elaine Perlman while we're at it.
"Dear Mr. Bekaris.
Mesa Verde Bank and
Trust respectfully submit
the following request
for your consideration.
In regards to the resolution
number PZ 2004-dash-36
Variance appeal to allow for
a six-and-one-half-foot
encroachment into the...
Into the minimum
required rear setback...
Um, minimum required rear setback
for a drive-through awning to allow..."
[SIGHS] Strike that.
"To facilitate...
access to...
the property at..."
[SUCKS TEETH]
"... 841 North".
[TAPE RECORDER CLICKS, THUDS]
So, can you call his assistant
and get some intel on
what he's into right now?
Kim.
They told me you were out sick today.
[STAMMERS] Yeah, no.
I, uh... Rich, you free to talk?
Yeah. Is everything okay?
Yeah.
I just need a minute.
Okay. Mm.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
So, what's up?
I, uh... I know this
is going to sound...
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
[TELEPHONES RINGING]
What?
I'm sorry that I can't
give you more notice...
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Marcie, uh, can you do me a favor?
Copy all the pro bono files
and send the originals to my place.
Also, it's no rush,
but box up my diplomas
and photos, please.
Are... we moving offices?
I don't want you to worry.
I talked to Rich.
You'll be reassigned to another partner.
Wait. Reassigned?
Oh, and they're gonna want these.
[KEYS JINGLING]
I'm parked in my usual spot.
If I left anything else in there,
just put it in the box.
Thank you, Marcie.
- Good luck.
- Kim?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[LALO SPEAKING SPANISH]
[BOTH LAUGH]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
NURSE: Hi there.
We're bringing birthday
cake out for Louise,
one of our residents.
Everyone's going to sing.
Hector really doesn't
like to miss these.
Yeah.
Could you give us a minute, please?
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[SMOOCHES]
[CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE]
[WHEELCHAIR SQUEAKING]
[LAUGHTER]
Okay, guys.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Louise ♪
[APPLAUSE]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Where to?
Go. The border.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Hey.
That was something [CHUCKLING]
what happened in there.
Hey, look, don't feel bad.
You can't win 'em all.
But that one? Jeesh!
I thought for sure I was gonna lose.
There wasn't a chance in hell
I was supposed to win that one.
But there you were.
Snatching defeat from
the jaws of victory.
[LAUGHS] Ball in your hand,
at the goal line, fumble!
Law students are gonna
review the "Goodman Debacle"
as a teachable moment, so
at least there's that. [CHUCKLES]
No, think of all the kids you'll
help learn "what not to do"
when faced with underwhelming odds.
So embarrassing.
You'll probably have to
change your name... again.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Hey, just so you know,
I don't think any less of you.
You're still, uh... a lawyer.
[LAUGHS]
[SIREN WAILING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
You can start talking any time.
You said this goes away.
So, what's the timeframe on that?
It's different for different people,
I suppose.
For me.
When will this be over for me?
Well, here's what's gonna happen.
One day...
one day you're gonna wake
up, eat your breakfast,
brush your teeth, go
about your business.
And sooner or later,
you're gonna realize you
haven't thought about it.
None of it.
And that's the moment.
You realize you can forget.
When you know that's possible,
it all gets easier.
But what about you?
Like, what happened out
there doesn't bother you?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Them wanting to steal the $7 million
didn't work for me.
Not to mention they wanted
to shoot you in the head.
It was them, or it was us.
Cut and dried.
- They were in the game.
- [EXHALES HEAVILY]
What about Fred?
From Travel Wire.
Was he in the game?
No.
There was a lot wrong
with what happened there.
Yeah. Lalo. [SIGHS]
Lalo killed that guy.
And for what?
He killed that guy,
and we're helping him.
[SIGHS]
All this shit just to...
so he can get out of
jail and just get away?
It's not the end of the story.
Wait a minute.
What does that mean, uh,
"not the end of the story"?
What... What are you saying?
Are you saying what
I think you're saying?
Is something gonna happen to Lalo?
I didn't say that.
Aw, Jesus. [STAMMERS]
What have I gotten
myself involved with here?
Look, just tell me. What
are you saying is gonna...
Look.
We all make our choices.
And those choices...
they put us on a road.
Sometimes those choices seem small,
but they put you on the road.
You think about getting off.
But eventually you're back on it.
And the road we're on
led us out to the desert
and everything that happened there
and straight back to
where we are right now.
And nothing...
nothing can be done about that.
Do you understand that?
I can't believe...
[SIGHS]
I can't believe there's, like,
over a billion people on this planet
and the only person I have
to talk about this to is you.
[CAR DOOR CREAKS]
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
You want me to wait?
Nah. They'll be here.
Really. Go.
You sure?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look, I'll be in touch, man.
Hey, that fire you did at Fring's...
that was good work, man.
We're gonna do more.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Sounds good.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES, ENGINE STARTS]
♪♪
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[KNOCK ON WINDOW]
Take me back up the road.
Slow.
♪♪
- What for?
- Just do it.
Six or seven miles back.
♪♪
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS]
What are we looking for?
Lawyer said his car broke down.
♪♪
Six miles from the pick-up.
Where is it?
♪♪
Ohh, let me out here. Let me out here.
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
♪♪
[GEARSHIFT CLICKS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
♪♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GRUNTING]
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Come.
Back to Albuquerque.
♪♪
What about Marco and Leonel?
What about them?
I'll get them a message. Let's go.
♪♪
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[ENGINE REVS, TIRES SCREECH]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[CAR DOOR OPENS, CREAKS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[KEYS JINGLING]
[KEYS CLATTER]
Jimmy?
You okay?
[EXHALES HEAVILY, INHALES SHARPLY]
Yeah, what time is it?
- It's 6:30.
- [EXHALES HEAVILY]
I'm sorry.
You want to go back to sleep?
No. I-I'm up.
[SIGHS]
You can still go to a doctor, you know.
No harm in getting checked out.
I'm fine.
I, uh, think I just need food.
I haven't eaten since, um...
well, really before everything.
Okay.
Maybe go easy, just some soup at first.
I'm okay, Kim, really.
I know.
Good.
Good. [EXHALES HEAVILY]
What about you?
You seem, uh...
worried, maybe?
No, no, no.
It's just...
I have news, but it can wait.
Let's get some food in you first.
What news?
What kind of news?
Nothing bad.
So, tha... that means it's good news?
Yeah. I think so. [CHUCKLES]
Great. Lemme hear it.
I, uh...
quit Schweikart and Cokely.
And I gave up Mesa Verde.
How 'bout we get some food together?
Wait.
What happened?
Did somebody say something
about what we did?
- No, no.
- Was it Rich?
Nobody said anything.
Uh... It just... It... It felt right.
- It felt right? What... How?
- I...
I-I just...
I keep pushing Mesa Verde
away to do my pro bono work,
and then when you were gone,
I didn't know what happened.
I mean, I...
I thought you were dead.
So...
that was, um...
all of it helped me to see
what's important and what isn't.
[CELLPHONE VIBRATES, RINGS]
So you're just gonna throw it all away?
I mean, you busted
your ass for all of it.
I'm not throwing it away.
I did S&C. I did Mesa Verde.
I-I achieved that.
I had that experience, but...
it doesn't make me happy.
Look, it's been a rough couple of days,
so why don't you just hold
off on a final decision?
Call Rich. Tell him
you're thinking it over.
I already talked to Rich.
And I called Paige.
We had a nice, very long conversation.
- It's done.
- [SILVERWARE CLATTERS]
Then I spent the
afternoon at the courthouse
with pro bono clients
without Mesa Verde hanging over my head.
Best afternoon I've had in a long time.
Alright, "pro bono" is wonderful.
It is, but "pro bono" means no money.
So, what's the plan here?
I don't know. But I'll figure it out.
Okay.
Leaving Schweikart... I get that.
It's a bunch of stuffed shirts.
But, uh, Mesa Verde?
Hey, that's like leaving the Yankees
to play amateur ring toss.
No, it's not.
I'm... I'm leaving something that makes
zero difference in the world
to help people who are actually in need.
This is a bad idea.
- What?
- [GLASS THUDS]
Look, we all make choices, right?
And those choices...
they put us on a road.
And the road has good choices,
and it has bad choices.
And this is a bad choice road.
- What are you even talking about?
- I'm...
[CELLPHONE VIBRATES, RINGS]
... saying that bad
choices lead to bad roads
that lead to bad places.
When you decided to be "Saul Goodman",
I didn't get it, still don't, really,
but I stood by your decision.
And I'm not changing my identity.
I'm just leaving a job.
What I did was completely different!
- How?
- 'Cause I was leaving failure for success!
It's not different.
You believed it was right for you.
Give me the courtesy
of believing this is right for me.
And I'm giving you a reality check.
This is too far, too fast.
This is really none
of your damn business.
[WINCES]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[CELLPHONE VIBRATES, RINGS]
[SIGHS]
Yeah?
MIKE: Listen to me.
Put your phone down.
Leave it on so I can hear.
So you can hear? Hear what?
Do what I said right now.
Put it down, somewhere it can't be seen.
Jimmy.
Hey, guys!
I come in?
Lalo.
Thought you'd be down South,
enjoying your freedom.
Yeah, well...
had some business to attend to.
Told you he'd be back.
Nice! I like it.
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
Hey, look, you want a drink?
Uh, we got some beer in the fridge.
Unless you're not staying that...
[TAPS ON TANK]
You shouldn't... I'm sorry. Um...
- [TAPPING ON TANK]
- Sorry.
Y-You shouldn't, uh, do that.
It upsets the fish.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
Look, you want to talk, we can talk,
but, uh, Kim was just
stepping out, so...
LALO: Nah. She can stay.
I mean, she is part of
the "legal team", right?
Hey, relax.
Sit down. We're just gonna talk.
C'mon.
Sit!
Okay.
So...
Tell me what happened.
What happened?
Yeah, when, uh... when
you picked up the money.
Just... walk me through it.
What I told you already?
Yes.
Fine.
Uh, I-I picked up the
money from your cousins.
It was right where you
told me it would be.
Driving back, my car crapped out
about six or seven miles
from the pick-up site.
There's no phone service,
so I walked north through
the desert all night.
Well, I slept a little,
but then in the morning,
I walked again until I
made it to a truck stop.
I went into the bathroom and cleaned up.
I bought some clothes,
and I... I called a cab.
I delivered the money.
Took 'em a couple hours to
count it, usual rigmarole,
and then I... then I saw you.
Tell me again.
What?
Tell. Me. Again.
♪♪
[BREATHING SHALLOWLY]
I picked up the money
from those two, uh, fine gentlemen.
My car broke down
after about, well, just 10 minutes.
There was no phone service,
and I was afraid to hitchhike
'cause of how much money it was.
And, uh, I ran out of water.
So I had to drink my own pee.
- Ugh!
- A lot of it.
So, you wanted details, there you go.
And then I, uh, finally
made it to a truck stop,
I called a cab.
And I waited,
and then he took me
directly to the courthouse.
I paid your bail, and I gotchu out.
I'm... I'm not sure what
you're looking for here,
but there... there you go.
♪♪
I just want to hear the story.
Lalo, this is exactly what he told me,
- so if you could just...
- Shh.
♪♪
I just like to hear the story.
I mean...
I paid a lot of money for that story.
So I think I can hear
it as much as I want.
♪♪
[TAPPING ON TANK]
So...
tell me again.
♪♪
I picked up two big bags of money.
$7 million.
Two heavy, heavy bags
that you paid me to get.
I put 'em in the trunk of my car.
Then about, uh, 10 minutes later,
my car's engine went.
Um, I tried to fix it,
but it was overheated or something.
So I walked north through the desert.
I walked and I walked and I walked
with those heavy, heavy bags.
and I finally made it to a truck stop.
And I went right to the bathroom
and I stuck my head under the faucet
and I bought a giant
pack of energy drinks.
And I called a taxi, and I waited.
I don't know what the problem is,
but can she leave here?
She doesn't need to be here.
She had nothing to do with it.
It was me.
It was all me.
It was all you, huh?
Yeah.
♪♪
What'd you do, Saul, hmm?
Whatever you think I did,
I don't really know.
I just... She just...
I saw your car.
♪♪
Okay?
You push it in a ditch?
I, what?
Did you push it in a ditch?
♪♪
- I don't think so.
- You don't think so?!
Well, I mean, you
either did or you didn't.
So, um, which one is it?
♪♪
[SIGHS] I don't know what you want.
Do you want the money back?
'Cause it's... it's in a bag in
the other room. You can take it.
I just want what happened.
I-I told you what happened.
Did you?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Look, okay, I...
Geez. Are you... Are
you kidding me with this?
Kim, really...
Do you know what he did for you?
$7 million of your money.
He hauled it across a goddamn desert
without one penny missing.
And he got you out of
jail for a murder that,
let's face it, you're
definitely guilty of.
He did everything you asked
and went way beyond what any
other lawyer would ever do.
So what, exactly, is it
that you're getting at?
What do you want?
♪♪
I found his car in a ravine.
Bullet holes on the side.
So...
I'm just waiting to
hear how that happened.
♪♪
Bullet holes.
That's it?
[STAMMERS]
Look, I don't know what
it's like where you're from,
but here in New Mexico,
you leave a soda can out,
someone's taking a shot at it.
That... That... That's
what you're on about?
You don't think it's possible
a couple of yahoos with guns
shot up a piece-of-junk car,
then rolled it down in
a ditch, end of story?
What kind of operation
are you running, anyway?
Tell me.
'Cause I think I know why
you sent him to do this job.
It's obvious.
You have no one else you can trust.
Right?
So you sent some lawyer
through the desert with your...
with your 7 million bucks?
That... I... No offense,
but you need to get your house in order.
[CHUCKLES] Really?
Yeah, really.
If you don't trust your
men with your money,
you have bigger problems than
if you trust Saul Goodman.
♪♪
And for the record, he doesn't lie,
not to me, not to his clients.
He's telling you the truth.
But next time you have a bunch of money
and no one you can trust,
leave him out of it, okay?
Try a... a wire transfer.
Try a... a shell company or... or...
You've heard of the Cayman
Islands, right? Jesus.
Get your shit together and
stop torturing the one man
who went through hell to save your ass.
♪♪
[DOOR OPENS, CREAKS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[EXHALING SHARPLY]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
What now?
Mexíco.
Back to the same place?
No. Change of plans.
Come on, Ignacio. Go.
We got a long way ahead of us.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]