Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hey, Gene.
Thanks, Jimmy.
- Trina.
- Hey, Jimmy.
Got a package, Dan.
How's it going?
What's up?
- Hey.
- Hey, yourself.
Jimmy, I'm really slammed.
Just tell me what you need.
What is it?
I can't open it.
So, what does it say?
I must call to your attention
the newly passed Environmental Impact
and Sustainability Assurance Act,
a statute that, as you
know, went into effect
without any ex post
facto provisions in place.
You got a second, Chuck?
Um, not really. I'm I'm kind of...
It'll just take two seconds. I promise.
All right.
What's this?
Is this a joke?
No. No joke.
You... you passed the bar?
Yeah. I did.
I... I thought if Kim could do
it, maybe I can, too, you know?
So I got my last few credits for undergrad
from a community college.
I mean, they're not just for draft Dodgers
and yoga classes, all right?
Then I found a law school
that would accept me.
You know, wasn't Georgetown
or anything, but...
The University of American Samoa.
Oh. Correspondence school.
Well, I wasn't gonna quit work, right?
Day... nights, weekends, you know?
They call it "distance learning" nowadays.
But they're accredited. Go, land crabs.
So, you know, I did that.
And, um, the bar exam's a mother.
I mean, for me it was.
I failed it the first two times,
but I guess it's like
losing your virginity...
third time's the charm.
How... this must have taken you years.
And you kept it a secret all this time.
Why? You didn't come to me for help?
Jesus, Chuck, you're
the busiest guy I know.
I mean, you're doing important shit.
Wow!
I don't know what to say.
Well, are you proud of me?
Hmm? Oh... Yes!
- Absolutely.
- Thanks.
Chuck, that means a lot.
Oh, hey.
I was hoping, you know, if
you think it's appropriate,
um, once I get sworn in and everything...
Consider hiring me?
As what?
Oh. A... a lawyer.
Obviously. Yeah.
Well, that's a question
I'm gonna have to take up
with Howard and the other partners.
Uh, you know, it's not my decision alone.
But how could they say no?
So much drive.
Jimmy, look what you've done here.
- _
- Oh, yeah! Whoo!
- Oh, man. I told those guys devil's food.
- All right, all right!
Yeah. Well, I will sue the store for you.
Good. Just remember us when
you're all big-time, huh?
I don't remember you now, Burt.
You're representing mail room,
so you show those upstairs
jackholes how it gets...
Hey.
What are you folks up to? Having a party?
Just a little celebration
on behalf of New Mexico's newest attorney.
I heard. Jesus, Jimmy, you're
a regular Charlie Hustle.
- Congratulations, my friend.
- Oh, thank you. Thanks.
Uh, would you like some cake?
Oh, here. Uh, don't mind if I do.
Really, really impressive, Jimmy.
We're all proud of you.
Hey, I hate to interrupt.
But could you guys give
Jimmy and me a moment?
- Sure.
- Yeah, absolutely.
Please, sit down.
Uh, let's reassess in six months.
Thanks for understanding, Jimmy.
Uh, you want the door open or closed?
Closed.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
_
How's it going?
Uh, settling back in.
Great.
So, apparently, they are ready for us.
Oh, thanks, but I want to
get a couple things done
before lunch, and I'm
still trying to settle...
Come on, Kim. You deserve this.
Come bask in the glow.
Thank you all for coming.
I appreciate you making time
in the middle of your busy days.
I'm pleased to announce
that working closely
with the Bernalillo County
district attorney's office,
we have reached a plea agreement
for former treasurer Craig Kettleman.
We believe this is a just and fair outcome
and brings to a close
an incident Mr. Kettleman deeply regrets.
He is committed to making
amends for his mistakes...
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm here to see Mrs. Landry.
Oh.
Sign in right here, please.
Are you a relative?
Lawyer.
But I treat my clients like family.
Oh. Uh, y... you know where to find her?
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Ah.
Hey.
Good morning, folks. Hi.
Jimmy McGill. I... oh.
Hey, pick a card, any card.
All right. How's it going there?
Good. Whoa! Not so t...
Oh. Shh.
Little surprise from the card fairy.
Give me back squeeze.
Squeeze whatever you got
that's below the water
that I can't see.
Oh, yeah.
All right, Mrs. Landry,
just a few more signatures,
and, uh thy will be done.
Would you like another hydrox?
No, thank you. I'm all hydrox'd out.
Well, please help yourself
if you change your mind.
All right. That one.
Okay. And that one.
And that is it.
What a relief.
I should have done this years ago.
Well, people do tend to put it off.
- Hmm.
- But everybody should have a will.
Please tell your friends.
And that comes to $140.
And I'm happy to take, uh,
cash or a check or, uh... cash.
O... one moment.
Could you write me a check?
Well, it's been so long,
I... I... I really don't know
if I have enough in my account.
I am so sorry.
Thi... this is awful, but...
... All I have is $43.
Okay.
Now, I could ask for an advance.
I... I... I am so sorry.
It's fine.
I... I don't know what
to say. This is awful.
Uh, oh, you could keep the
will until I get my allowance,
and... and that should only
be until the end of next week.
Okay, that's not necessary.
Here's my address.
Just mail it to me when
you've got it, all right?
And why don't we, uh... we'll
just make it an even $120.
All right?
Oh. Oh. Thank you.
You have a nice day.
Excuse me. Allowance?
Your family has you on an allowance?
Oh, no, no. It's... it's my money.
I just get it from Sandpiper Crossing.
$500 a month...
I don't understand.
You should have social security checks...
... Plus that pension we talked about.
So how are you on an allowance?
Well, the checks go to Sandpiper,
and then they take out my
fees and... and my expenses.
Why don't you just come on in?
I'm afraid I'm not explaining it very well.
I... I have statements here... somewhere.
Somewhere. Okay. Here...
So your pension and social security
goes straight to the Sandpiper people?
They take out... they
take out what they need,
and then... and then I get my allowance.
Here.
And... and all the rest
goes into my savings account.
It's really all very above-board.
A lot of places do it this way.
This is how they do it
for everybody around here?
Well, yes, they... they try
to make everything easy for us.
Mrs. Landry, are any of your friends around
who I could talk to?
I see you spent... now, I
don't know if you noticed...
$187.50 on 4-10-12.
Do you know what 4-10-12 is?
No. In order to find out,
you have to look on the back.
Okay? And see this key.
I see you have reading glasses.
Can I borrow your glasses?
Yes. Thank you.
Oh, these are gonna help me,
but I don't know if they'll do the trick.
So tiny.
4-10-12...
I think it might be Q-tips. I can't tell.
It's probably an accident,
but we should look into it.
don't you think?
They're not doing this intentionally.
Okay? This could be a mistake.
But if we correct the mistake,
then you'll get some money
back, and it'll be fair.
Hey, Chuck.
My boxes, the ones I left...
Oh.
Sandpiper Crossing...
Did you do my wills?
Yes, I did.
Hey. Would you look at that?
- Thank you.
- Don't thank me.
This was a one-time thing,
and don't think I don't see
what you were doing here.
You wanted to play Tom Sawyer,
wanted me to paint the fence,
and god help me, it worked.
You need help?
Hire a paralegal, stand
on your own two feet.
Yeah. Sure. I'll do that.
You're not even listening to me.
No, I... I hear you, Chuck, okay?
Self-reliance. It's great
stuff. Would you look at this?
What did I just say?
Ta... take a look, okay? Just right here.
Do you see what I see?
All I'm asking is for you
to take a look. Please?
"Sandpiper Crossing... "
It's a retirement home, assisted living.
It's... this is one of
their monthly invoices
they send their residents.
What exactly am I looking for?
It's nothing earth-shaking.
Just little things, little things like...
like this right here.
$14 for code 118-62. What's 118-62?
I wonder.
How could you even read
this? It's like microfilm.
118-62 is facial tissue.
14 bucks for a box of Kleenex.
Yeah, I found others.
There's $3.50 for a single
roll of toilet paper,
22 bucks for a bottle of aspirin.
It's a clear pattern of overcharging.
Nothing huge, but it adds up to real money.
I mean, here, look.
This woman... she got soaked
for like 400 bucks last month.
And there's a pretty solid attempt
at concealment of that fact,
which to my way of thinking, makes it...
Fraud. This was in work I did?
Yeah, you must have missed it.
Um, look, Chuck, I got lucky, right?
Even a stopped clock is right twice a day.
And this is no mom-and-pop outfit, okay?
I dug around a little.
They're owned by some kind of
real-estate investment trust.
I'm working at getting more
info, but this could be big.
I mean, this could be a big case, right?
Well... if it's more
than a few errant billings
and if it's systematic and
you establish a pattern,
it could be class-action.
What do I do now? I mean, what next?
Well, you're gonna need more information.
You don't want to go off half-cocked.
Full cock. Okay.
No, I... I'm gonna head back there.
Thank you. You're the best.
Back to see Mrs. Landry.
Okay. What gives?
Sorry, sir. New policy.
We're concerned about
solicitation on premises.
I'm not a gigolo, if
that's what you're implying.
Legal solicitation.
We are obligated to protect our
residents from being harassed,
and we have the right to refuse entry.
I have clients in there.
Now, they have the legal
right to meet with me.
Well, you'll just have to
arrange to meet them elsewhere.
Oh, come on, guys. Seriously?
What, are you making
soylent green back there?
It's... all right, okay.
I... I'm backing away. Yeah?
You know what? Uh... This...
Hey, this has gotten me a
little bit stirred up down there.
Can I use your restroom?
Please, it's... I've got I.B.S.
Go ahead.
"To Sandpiper Crossing...
... clients of James M. McGill...
This is to inform you to stay...
Sir? Are you all right in there?
"We believe that... breach of contract... "
Come on, now, sir. I've been very patient.
"... clear pattern of malfeasance...
This is a negligent infliction
of emotional distress."
Sir, I really need you to
finish up and come out now.
"... contact by the end of the week
or I will be forced to move forward."
- Sir, I need you to finish up...
- This is a demand letter informing Sandpiper Crossing
of pending litigation
for defrauding my clients
through systematic overcharging.
You're shredding in there! I'm not deaf!
I can hear you! Stop right now!
This here... this makes it official, right?
If you don't stop shredding right now,
that's destruction of
evidence... spoliation!
That's what it's called, and it's a felony!
So call your lawyers right now
and tell them I said that...
me... James McGill esquire!
I'm telling you guys, big mistake! Aah!
Hey.
Am I calling at a bad time?
No, not at all.
How you doing?
Uh, pretty good. Getting by.
How about you?
Getting by.
It's good to hear from you.
Yeah. I... I've been...
there's been a lot going on.
You know how it is.
Yeah, I know.
Uh, listen.
I was... was hoping maybe
you could do me a favor.
Do you think you could watch Kaylee?
It'd be during my shift
the day after tomorrow.
Look, I hate to ask, but
my regular sitter's down...
anything you need, I'll be there.
You can get off work? I don't
want to impose or anything.
No. Anytime.
It's not an imposition.
Thanks. Appreciate it.
Yeah, no problem.
At a quarter to 2:00?
I'll see you then.
Okay.
Ohh! Jesus!
Aah.
Come on.
Where is it?
Oh.
Oh!
Oh! God damn it!
And it didn't even make it fit.
And I'm like, "it's not like
we're close to being done."
I mean, can't you get
somebody else to do it?"
Right.
They don't pay any of
us enough for this shit.
You know what? And it's
going on and on and on.
And so I'm like,
"why are you making your
problems my problems?"
Right. Like you don't have
enough problems of your own.
Exactly! That's exactly what I'm saying.
Thank you. But he just...
James McGill.
Mr. McGill,
Rich Schweikart of Schweikart and Cokely.
We're the law firm representing
Sandpiper Crossing assisted living.
How are you this evening?
Quite well, thank you. How are you?
Doing fine. Doing fine.
I'm sorry to call so late.
Did I catch you at a bad time?
No, no. No, it's fine.
It's just that you're whispering.
I'm at the opera.
Oh. What opera?
"Magic Flute."
Mozart! Lovely.
Well, I'll try not to keep you.
We received... something from you today,
and we're not quite sure what.
It's a demand letter.
Ah.
Well, it was a little confusing
'cause it was written on, uh...
Well, I had to write it quickly
because your clients were in the
process of destroying evidence.
Mr. McGill, if you're talking
about shredding documents,
that's neither irregular nor illegal.
Every business in America does it.
You say potato, I say spoliation.
Mm-hmm.
Maybe you should walk me through
what you're alleging here.
I believe it's all in the letter.
Uh, uh, I... I'm not saying it's not,
but it's a bit hard to read.
Next time, I'd use double-ply.
Let's not fixate on the medium, okay?
Let's look at the message.
Now, your clients are facing
multiple counts of elder abuse
and... and fraud and deceptive
and unfair trade practices,
and that's just the start, okay?
I'm not a betting man, but I
bet the farm I'll find more.
Mr. McGill, are you
related to Charles McGill?
He's my brother.
Yeah? How's he doing these days?
I... I fail to see the relevance of this.
Frankly, the only reason
that I made this phone call
was out of respect for Charles
on the off chance that you
might be related to him.
My partner suggested that the best response
would be to send a rule 11
letter and have you sanctioned,
but I didn't want to jump
to that immediate length.
Hey, how about you stop
trying to rattle my cage
and just, you know, respond to the merits?
This is my response, Mr. McGill...
you have no good-faith basis
to threaten any litigation.
This is a shakedown, and we both know it.
Now, if you push this any
further, my hands will be tied.
Sorry for interrupting your evening.
Enjoy "The Magic Flute."
Blow my magic flute.
Aah!
Son of a bitch!
Jimmy, what are you doing here?
Oh, uh, Chuck, um...
Sorry to... show up like this.
I just needed space to work.
What is all this?
What have you done to my dining room?
They were spoliating, the Sandpiper people.
They wouldn't let me in,
and I could see that they were shredding.
I wrote them a demand
letter, and I gave it to them.
- You broke in to a nursing home?
- Assisted living.
And you stole their garbage.
My god. No, it was in public.
There was no lock, no nothing.
I just lifted the lid, and there it was.
There's no reasonable
expectation of privacy
in that situation, is there?
You can't say it's private if
a hobo can use it as a wigwam.
That's... that's the standard, right?
If animals or vagrants can get in?
More or less, yes.
Okay, so this is all legal.
I mean, it's completely
above-the-belt legal.
I just need to figure out what
they're trying to cover up.
You know, you don't shred like this
unless you got something
to hide, am I right?
- Not necessarily.
- Oh, come on, Chuck.
A lawyer shows up,
starts figuring out their
little scheme, and suddenly this?
No, it's not a coincidence. It's in here.
Well, at least it's not crosscut.
Look, you won't even know I'm here, okay?
I just need some space and some quiet,
and I'll be out of your
hair as soon as I c...
Stop, stop. It's okay. You can work here.
Thanks.
I don't mind the company.
You look like you could
use a cup of coffee.
Good god, yes.
I'll put it on.
Up, up. Up.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
God's sweet sake.
Yeah.
Oh, good. You're up.
Well, Jesus, Chuck, how
long have I been asleep?
Chuck, how did you... ?
I... I can't believe this. Uh...
Uh, thank you. This is a huge help.
I felt like I was shoveling
snow in a blizzard.
Well, it gets better.
What's this?
It's your smoking gun.
It's a, uh... invoice for syringes.
Yes. From?
Morrissey Medical Supply Lincoln, Nebraska.
- So?
- Trust me.
Meanwhile, we need to
start pulling case law...
any precedent dealing
with 18 U.S.C. 1961 to '68.
Probably not a bad idea to pull 30.47.1
from NMSA... Uh, 1978.
I don't think that's gonna play, really,
but it's a good opening salvo for us.
Wait, "us"?
We're working together on this?
Mm. That's up to you, Jimmy.
'Cause...
Well...
All right.
All right. All right. Let's get to work.
- Kim Wexler.
- Hey, gorgeous.
Oh, man. Sweet-talking
right out of the gate?
You want something. Make it fast.
- I want to go home.
- Okay, okay.
Will you look something
up for me on Westlaw?
Please?
You're lucky I'm a pushover.
All right. Hit me.
Thank you.
Uh, anything on Sedima v. Imrex,
Slesinger v. Disney, Holmes v. S.I.P.C...
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Slow
down, slow down. V. Disney.
Holmes v. S.I...
D.C., yeah.
And, uh, anything on
57.12.1-24 NMSA, 1978.
Uh, okay.
It would help if I knew what
you were looking for here.
Anything, everything.
What? You want me to just read
you the head notes or something?
No, no, print it... full cases,
and any cases that cite to those cases.
Shepardize like the wolf's at the door.
Jesus, Jimmy, that's gonna
be thousands of pages.
Pretty please with sugar on top?
Come on. You owe me one.
Yes, I do, but this is gonna take hours.
- And who do I bill it to?
- Bill it to Howard.
I still remember his code...
1933, same year Hitler came to power.
You're not funny. I'm
not billing it to my boss.
How about yours? I'll pay you back.
Jimmy, this is 300, 400
bucks worth of printing.
The accountants will find
it and I'll get fired,
which sounds fun and all, but no.
Okay. Hold on a sec.
Hey.
Uh, Kim can't print without a code.
Should I go over there,
take notes, and come back?
No, no, no. It would take too long.
Use mine... 1868.
Yeah.
1868. Use that. It's Chuck's.
You're using Chuck's number?
Does Chuck know you're
using Chuck's number?
We're working on something together.
And bring it over to his place after.
- You're a lifesaver.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
You're working a case together?
Yeah. Keep this under your
hat, but it's gonna be huge...
maybe a class-action, even.
We think it'll settle for
$1 million, maybe $2 million.
How does that work?
- Chuck's a partner at HHM.
- So what?
Look, I know Chuck's partnership
agreement chapter and verse.
He can work with outside parties.
That clause is intended
for small-time stuff,
pro bono cases.
So? I'm bono. I'm very bono.
Chuck's a rock star,
okay? They'll work it out.
And Chuck can handle this?
Last time I saw him, he was...
Last time you saw him,
he wasn't himself, okay?
This is good for him.
Okay.
What?
I don't know. I'm just...
Whatever. I'll see you in a couple hours.
Okay. We're ordering a pizza, okay?
I'll save you a slice.
Now, you know, if you don't separate those,
you're gonna end up with brown.
Hello?
Hey.
We're in here.
We're playing sculptor.
She's Michelangelina. How's work?
Eh, you know... work. How did it go?
Kid's a dream. She's easy.
And you better stay that way.
How you doing, sweetie? Huh?
Hmm?
Well, I better be going.
Oh, wait. Hang on a sec, would you?
I want to talk to you about something.
What's up?
I want to know what I should do with this.
I've been carrying it around for weeks,
like holding on to it.
Every place I put it feels wrong.
I thought about putting it in
the collection plate, but...
It seemed... I don't know.
Look, with Matty gone, I have expenses,
and the death benefit helped, but...
What I want to ask you is...
... Can I spend this?
Stace, if this money helps you and Kaylee,
if it does a single
good thing in this world,
then you spend every penny.
That's a relief. It'll help a lot.
Of course, it's only a drop in the bucket.
I swear, everyone I know
has had problems with them.
I had one. The computer in the engine...
it locked in the middle of the Rockies.
Yeah, it decided I was
overheating, and that was it.
Yeah. I couldn't get it
fixed for a hundred miles.
I had to have it towed to Telluride.
It was unbelievable.
Huh.
No, it's... it's the
chip. It's the little...
Yeah, it's like 800 bucks, not counting...
Labor.
Hey, Mel, can I call you back?
Chuck, the Sandpiper has landed.
Gentlemen, I'm Jimmy McGill.
- Welcome.
- Rich Schweikart.
This is Alvin Reese. Phil Jergens.
Thanks for coming.
Oh, whoa. I have to ask you.
Uh, please leave electronics in the car...
laptops, blackberries,
palm pilots, watches.
If you lick it and it
goes bzzt, leave it here.
Why?
My brother Chuck has a certain sensitivity.
It's a medical condition.
This is the price of admission.
Yeah, I heard about this.
Go ahead. It's fine.
Here you go.
Make yourselves comfortable, gentlemen.
I'll be right back.
All right.
Chuck. Come on, buddy.
I...
I don't... I don't know if I can do this.
You... oh, you can do this, all right?
These guys...
Those guys... they're nothing. Okay?
They're the Pistons, and you're the Bulls.
All right?
All you got to do is sit
there and look intimidating.
They're scared of you
already, and they should be.
You're Charles McGill.
Let's go. Let's go get 'em.
Ah.
Hey.
Do you remember me, Charles?
We were on a co-defense...
Church's Donuts v. Amendola?
Oh.
It was... Jesus 9, 10 years ago.
Yeah.
Oh, our guys were suing the other guys,
and they were suing us right back,
and the city had some
grievance with everyone,
so we had to bundle like
four actions together,
and I was sure that we were sunk.
But you... you quoted... what was it?
Huh? Addyston Pipe & Steel.
You turned it all antitrust,
and the whole thing went
away in summary judgment.
It was amazing. It was amazing.
I figured you'd be arguing
in front of the Supreme Court someday.
Well, it's, uh, good to see you.
Yeah.
All right, well, let's get started.
Um, we've read your revised demand.
It's, uh, quite a laundry
list. Very creative.
Yeah, creative, like the way
your clients have been billing my clients.
'Cause that's like Salvador Dal× creative.
That's cute. Y... you know,
you're not gonna make this stick.
Setting aside evidentiary concerns...
whoa, whoa. Your guys couldn't
afford 10 bucks for a padlock?
That's on them. Public property.
Maybe a judge sees that
your way, maybe he doesn't.
But the damages for elder abuse?
The statute requires proof that
there was some undo influence...
someone threatening the
residents of Sandpiper Crossing.
As far as I understand it, no one
has claimed there's a guy with a knife
telling them to hand
over their lunch money.
There are a lot of
assisted-living facilities
out there that may be disreputable,
but that's not the case with
our client, not even close.
All their facilities all 12 of them...
every single one, five-star rated.
You go to any one of them right now,
and you know what you'll see?
You'll see happy, healthy residents.
Sandpiper takes care of these people.
They don't bilk them.
But we looked into it,
and some of your clients
have, in fact, been overbilled.
It's... it's an accounting error.
It doesn't rise to the level
of fraud, not even close.
We've calculated the damages.
All told, it's $46,320.
Mm-hmm, so here's what
we're prepared to do.
We're gonna make your clients whole...
a check for the $46,000
and change right now.
And on top of that,
we'll give you another
$46k to cover your expenses.
So what's that? $92,000?
Let's call it $100,000 even.
We admit to no wrongdoing,
and your clients release all claims.
I think you're gonna need
to do better than that.
Ah, this was in your demand letter.
They're syringes. So?
I... I don't know if you know this,
but that's a pretty standard item
in an assisted-living facility.
Correct. But it's not
what it is that matters.
It's where it's from.
Lincoln, Nebraska.
Go, cornhuskers.
Well, since you're not picking
up what I'm putting down,
I'll explain it to you.
Um, Nebraska, although they
both begin with the letter "N,"
actually turns out to be a
different state than New Mexico.
So your client accepted shipments
across state lines for its enterprise.
I... in the U.S. mail, no less.
Are you trying to make this a RICO case?
Like our client is John Gotti or something?
Well, you know as well as I do
RICO's used mostly for business beefs.
Sedima establishes a pretty low threshold
for RICO provisions to kick in.
Interstate commerce is a bitch, huh?
As soon as we establish a pattern to...
what was your word? Uh, "overbillings"?
I prefer the classic term of "fraud."
You're looking at treble damages.
So your 100 grand... I think
you know where you can stick it.
Will you give us a moment?
Well...
What number exactly did you have in mind?
$20 million.
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.
Oh, you can't expect...
$20 million.
Or we'll see you in court.
Hmm.
$20 million?
Didn't you hear them?
This is a big company.
12 separate facilities.
They can't possibly all be in New Mexico.
This is potentially a multi-state
federal class-action lawsuit
with a RICO kicker at the penalty phase.
$20 million? That's conservative.
Now, class cert... that's where we start.
I'll draft our complaint, try
to get us a conditional one.
They'll try to pierce it,
but it should hold long
enough to start discovery.
And we need to get you back on the grounds,
quash this prohibition against you.
Uh, some injunctive relief. Maybe a T.R.O.
Jimmy?
Do you want to get started on the T.R.O.?
Yeah. Yes.
It looks good. No heartworm, no mange.
- Where did you get her?
- Shelter.
Good. There's too many
puppy mills out there.
I had a dachsie in the other day.
Some douche bred her so much, poor thing,
she just had one giant hernia for a belly.
Couldn't even walk.
Those people can go straight to hell,
as far as I'm concerned.
Anything else I can do for you?
You still in touch with your people?
Depends on the type of
work you're looking for...
your dos, your don'ts,
your wills, your won'ts.
Well, if you tell me what you've got,
I'll tell you what I'll do.
I signed up three more
clients at the mall today.
Jesus, those mall walkers...
Those geezers are faster than you think.
I could sleep for a decade.
Did you get what I asked?
- The, uh, code provisions?
- Ohh.
Shit.
Uh, it's in the car.
Just give me a minute. I'll, uh...
I'll go.
Where's the...
Chuck? Hey.
Chuck?
Yeah.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/jnqg
Help other users to choose the best subtitles