There's been a development
I'd like to make you aware of.
We've found samples of Hannah's DNA
in the boot of your grandfather's car.
What do you remember, Shaun?
Charlie? Have you seen Hannah?
I thought she was with you.
CAREY: Did you lose control?
What happened between you
and Hannah Roberts?
When I think about it,
when I close my eyes,
I've started seeing Hannah
on the video.
- Why is it happening? - Normally I can
see it coming something like that.
If we need you testify, Becky,
just stick to the facts.
Why don't you tell me
where Hannah is,
before your friend starts
dropping digits.
I don't know where she is!!
I've been trying to find out what
happened to her, where she's gone.
I would've got somewhere if one
of your guys hadn't turned up.
The hell you talking about?
The guy I was following!
We have the support of SO15'S
finest, led by DSU Garland.
Sorry, Sir. DSU...? Garland.
Gemma.
Taxi turning into Eaton Square,
Belgravia.
Ma'am, we're in position.
Eaton Square, Belgravia.
We do not have eyes on Shaun Emery.
- I can see him.
- Get tactical in here now.
HERE! I'M DOWN HERE!
House search complete.
No contact.
I'm starting to think that
Shaun Emery is telling the truth.
Except that I can prove he isn't.
Hannah Roberts did not
get on that bus.
If I wanted to hide
an edit in this scene,
I'd use something crossing
the frame blocking the action.
It doesn't have to be a bus.
I understand you have this drive
to get to the very heart of things.
But accepting you can rarely
see the whole picture...
...is part of the job.
I'm heading down there.
All units in pursuit,
suspect vehicle
on the Venners Farm North Road.
Suspect is currently on foot.
Stationary.
PHILIPS: What's he doing?
Us a favour? Nothing like
a full frontal for clarity.
Can't beat it.
Hello, mate. Now send us a swab
of your DNA and we're done.
RADIO: Echo Nine approaching
Venners Farm.
GARLAND: Bring him in.
SIRENS APPROACH
Stay on him.
Oi!
HE STRUGGLES
HE SCREAMS
HE RETCHES
HE PANTS
HE SCREAMS
SIRENS BLARE
RADIO: Echo Nine to Control.
Medical assistance required.
Target is not contained.
Repeat. Target is not contained.
Coverage?
- Blind spot.
- Find him.
NADIA: Echo One, arrival
at Venners Farm.
Nadia, leave Uniform to go
after the suspect.
You and Flynn secure that vehicle.
Understood.
SOCO and coroner's officer.
Female victim.
Patrick?
Official identification
notwithstanding...
...yeah, it's Hannah Roberts, yes.
- Where is he?
- No visual. It's a flippin' camera desert.
What's on the other side
of that wasteland?
Borders the A113 slip road.
RADIO: All units, be advised -
suspect may be headed towards
the A113 Westbound slip road.
SIREN BLARES, TYRES SCREECH
HE STRUGGLES
SIRENS APPROACH, HE PANTS
HELICOPTER BLADES
Shaun!
Shaun, it's DI Carey.
It's over. Let me bring you in.
I'll listen to you, Shaun.
She's dead!
You're not going to listen to me.
No-one is.
Look, I lied to you, Shaun.
We never found Hannah's DNA
in the car, I was bluffing.
The only thing
we have on you is that video.
HE SNIFFS
HE COUGHS
Marcus Levy came to see me.
He can explain it. Your CCTV.
He said it was all in my head. No.
He's got a new theory.
You should hear it.
Come with me
and we can talk it through.
HE GROANS
You've been sprayed with CS?
Open your eyes
and put your face into the wind.
It's the only way to get rid of it.
Look, I saw something.
I saw you taken to a house
in Eaton Square.
Only no-one else saw it.
And now they think I'm mad!
I am going to have to arrest you
in order to bring you in.
You know that, right?
You're going to have to
trust me, though.
I want you to stand up, slowly.
Take one step towards the curb
and put your hands behind your back.
Shaun Emery, I am arresting
you on suspicion of murder.
I'm sorry. You do not... Fuck!
If they don't believe you,
they ain't going to believe me.
Gastor Square. What?
That's where they took me.
Fuck.
Shaun! Shaun, wait!
Shaun, Stop!
TYRES SCREECH, SIREN APPROACHES
Shit!
Straight on! That way!
HE COUGHS AND STRAINS
Come again, Detective?
Suspect has my vehicle, Ma'am.
I was overpowered.
Are you hurt?
Negative.
RADIO: Control to all units.
Suspect is now driving
a police-issue, unmarked Volvo V40.
TYRES SCREECH
HE GROANS
TYRES SQUEAL
- Are you all right, Ma'am?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Emery? - Uniform are still looking.
- You're lucky he didn't hurt you.
There's no obvious wounds
or marks on the body.
And no rigour.
Reckon she's been dead
hours, not days.
She must have been held alive
until earlier today.
The people who put a delay
on this case have got
a hell of a lot to answer for.
OFFICER: Delta One to Westminster,
ETA ten minutes.
- You are going to Croydon coroner's?
- Westminster.
We're SCD. OK? We're Lambeth.
Dispatch went through Vauxhall,
so this is us.
Nadia, follow them to the mortuary,
tell the coroner
we need the postmortem done
in the next 24 hours. Ma'am.
Patrick, I need you to do
something for me.
Run a check on all the properties
in Gastor Square.
- Meet me there in an hour's time.
- Gastor Square?
- Emery mentioned it to me.
- What, when he nicked your motor?
Yes.
Patrick, do you mind
if I take yours?
SHE SIGHS
PHONE RINGS OUT
- Rach. -You picked up.
I need to see you. It's work.
Yes...
...I need to see you too.
Shaun?
HE LOCKS AND BOLTS DOOR
Tell me about Shaun.
DEVICE BEEPS
IT BEEPS QUICKER
HE COUGHS
Easy, Shaun.
I don't want to use the Taser,
but, if I have to, I will.
We were waiting for you to stumble
into a blind spot all night.
I didn't expect you to stumble
into the road. My apologies.
Steady!
You've probably broken some ribs.
I need to take a look at your shoes.
Pass them to me, please.
You'll get them back.
Kenny! Stop the van!
Kenny! Jesus Christ!
- Sh. You stay fucking back.
- We're trying to HELP you!
- Don't fucking move.
- Wait! Look inside your shoe!
You've got a tracker!
If I may?
Why do you think
they always know where to find you?
Those fucking...
I'm meeting people
for dinner at nine.
- Work people or wife people?
- Wife people.
Pretentious wife people who think
food tastes better at 1,000 feet.
The Shard?
That'll put a dent in your wallet.
Paying for the view
and I don't like heights.
- BARTENDER: Anything for you, madam?
- Just water, please.
So, I hear you've had a result.
You stuck with it. You were right.
Why is the woman who redacted
the evidence now running the case?
Gemma Garland.
She's SO15, apparently.
Whatever she is, she's making
a mockery of your department.
How do you mean?
I raised a serious concern with her,
and she dismissed it.
Concern?
I think someone's interfering
with our feeds,
tampering with evidence.
I'm listening.
Take this video.
There's a chance it may have been
manipulated
while it was being monitored.
Live? It's possible that someone
hacked the feed, put a delay on it,
then used this bus to mask an edit.
Switching from a real event
to a fake one.
What, and then magic
all of this stuff up?
Who's your suspect,
Steven Spielberg?
It reminded me of something.
From Operation Sycamore.
This was key, wasn't it?
We knew the three Potters
were in contact with the arms dealer
but we had no evidence
to connect them.
Right, until your CCTV trawl
uncovered this meeting.
Look at it.
A truck goes past
just before they meet.
I'm sorry. Is that it? A truck
goes past? A bus goes past?
For someone extolling the virtues
of hard evidence,
you don't exactly have very much.
Listen, Rachel, the reason
I wanted to see you is this...
...thing has to stop.
Thing?
Us. It has stopped. I stopped it.
Every step of the way
you're coming to me...
I called you because I thought
you'd want to know there's a chance
the bloody camera network's
been compromised!
Or did you already know?
- I can't get into this.
- Did you... already know?
You've had a shock tonight, Rachel.
Why don't you get some rest.
MOBILE RINGS
Mr Levy, it's Detective Carey.
If you could give me a call back
on this number when you get this,
I'd really appreciate it, thank you.
TV: The body has been identified
as that of missing barrister
Hannah Roberts. The cause of death
has not yet been determined.
But police have confirmed that
Shaun Emery, who remains at large,
is now wanted on suspicion
of murder.
This van is hot now. All that
swerving around in range.
He can't be in here.
What is that?
A map of blind spots.
Where the cameras can't see.
If you're careful, you can get
across town without being watched.
If they can track a shoe,
they can track a phone, no?
Not that phone.
There's another spot in 100 metres.
Who are you? Alma.
No, who ARE you?
All in good time.
TYRES SQUEAL
Here.
Quick.
They should fit.
Do you want to go around in what
the police saw you wearing,
and get arrested,
or do you want to put those on?
VAN DOORS SLAM
Alma's in charge. You touch her,
I'll chew your face off.
Shadow me, please.
It's important we stick together.
SHE SIGHS
This is what you're up against.
If you want a way out of this,
you need to follow me.
Come on.
You're with the good guys now.
PHONE BUZZES
Nadia.
The mortuary reckon the postmortem
isn't due till Monday.
- Says who?
- Garland authorised it.
Call Croydon and tell them
we're doing the postmortem there.
- What? Move the body?
- Can you do that?
I'm the SIO, aren't I?
Ma'am.
PHONE RINGS OFF
PHONE BUZZES
I was wondering when you'd call.
Toy Soldier's tracker
was removed in a blind spot.
Leave this to me.
We're running face-match on him
as we speak.
I know you are.
You know when you saw Emery
in Eaton Square,
do you think you might have got
the wrong address?
They all look the bloody same.
Not exactly the same.
What's the easiest way
to tell a lie, Patrick?
Stick as closely to
the truth as possible.
Look.
Photoshop the door number,
and what have you got?
This house.
This is the house
we should have raided.
Come on.
What, now?
Just us?
Look - there's a new one,
not mapped.
Good job it's facing away.
But that's not a police camera.
It's a private one, no?
Six million CCTV cameras in the UK.
Almost all of them are online.
- And if they're online...
- They can be hacked?
Doesn't seem like any of this
bothers you. It don't surprise me.
Big Brother's watching us.
He's not just watching.
Go on.
We need to keep moving.
Wait a second.
Does that thing make
untraceable phone calls?
PHONE BUZZES
Hello? Don't hang up.
It's not true what
they're saying on the TV.
You know I didn't hurt her.
You know I couldn't.
Will you... will you do me a favour?
Will you tell Jaycee that
when she goes to school tomorrow?
No matter what anyone says...
...to remember that I didn't do it.
The police came here...
...asking about you.
And?
They wanted to know
if you'd ever been violent.
Shaun?
What do you want from us?
I want you to believe me.
She will.
Sure you want to do this, Ma'am?
Sir?
It's not the fig leaf.
Detective Carey,
Homicide and Serious Crime.
I'd like a word with
the occupants of the property.
The occupants are overseas.
What a surprise.
I'm afraid I'm going to
have to ask you to move.
It's all right.
Let them in.
Please.
You sure you're not thirsty?
No. Thank you, Mr Napier.
Frank.
We're sorry to drag you
from your work.
It was our suspect, Shaun Emery,
who pointed us in your direction.
He mentioned this address when
I spoke to him earlier this evening.
You spoke to Shaun Emery tonight?
Briefly.
I didn't manage to get
the significance of it.
Perhaps you could shed some light?
Siege of Petersburg, 1865.
Lincoln may have won
the hearts and minds...
...but if General Grant hadn't
butchered the Confederacy...
...that war probably would have
gone the other way.
I don't want to insult
your intelligence, Detective Carey,
and I hope you don't insult mine.
But the work we do here
is very sensitive.
If I were to give you any details,
without the warrantry
of your Government or mine,
that would constitute
an unauthorised sharing
of intelligence.
Heck, protocol dictates I can't
even acknowledge this address.
This address? Where we're sitting
now? You can't acknowledge it?
It seems...
...Detective Flynn is not
hip to the quirks of our trade.
But you, on other hand...
...you weren't always in Homicide,
were you?
I transferred from CT.
Why in the world would you
do a thing like that?
It's making more and more sense.
Can I ask a question?
If you're not able to share
anything, why meet us at all?
So he can gather intelligence on us.
Old habits.
Well...
...I should get back to work.
Perhaps we'll get that warrantry.
I wish you all
the luck in the world.
But shouldn't you be
hunting your murder suspect?
We are.
Still thinking
about your girlfriend?
She's my ex.
When all this is resolved,
you'll feel a great weight lifted.
Yeah, what makes you sure
it's going to be resolved?
Trust me.
My barrister, my friend is dead.
The police think I done it.
My ex thinks I done it.
And between, you and me, there
are moments I'm scared I done it.
So, if you know I didn't do it,
maybe you could explain it to me.
Cos I'd like to find
the people that did.
They call it "correction".
When they take something that
they don't like and they change it.
Who?
Alma. Who?
I will tell you.
But you need to be patient.
Right now, I just need you
to concentrate.
And help me over this wall.
PHONE BUZZES
SHE SIGHS
I can't keep taking calls, Frank.
When I find him, you'll find him.
I just thought you should know,
your Detective Inspector
came knocking on my front door.
Carey?
Bright girl.
Too bright?
It's tricky, politically.
She's a bit of a mascot around here.
I'm sure you'll find a way.
- Found it. - Found what?
- That photo in his office.
General Ulysses S Grant
at City Point. What about it?
It claims to be from 1865.
But experts now believe
it was created in 1902.
The background is from
a different battle.
And the body's from
a different general.
It's one of the earliest
examples of faked photography.
Frank Napier is flaunting it
in our face.
You know that "sensitive work"
he mentioned?
They're hacking our CCTV.
Tampering with evidence.
I just... I just don't have evidence.
I think I owe you an apology.
- For? - I should have been
talking more to you and Latif,
instead of leaning on 15
all the time.
Guess I'd have known better
if I hadn't "practically skipped
my stint in Uniform".
HE LAUGHS WRYLY
I didn't mean to take the mick.
What's wrong? I'm just hoping
Marcus Levy might have
called me back.
Who? He's the video expert.
He knows how Emery's footage
might have been faked.
Ma'am, I don't trust
these people one bit.
But Shaun Emery's video
can't be fake.
We've got the body!
And the double-decker?
We know Hannah didn't get in
that bus like Emery claimed.
I mean, you saw the footage!
We're not just talking about
one video, either.
What about his whole journey?
To the river. Back home.
Levy said it's simpler
than you might think.
All the hard work could have been
done beforehand.
Then the fakery spliced
with the real.
Yes, I know how it sounds.
But he's the expert.
It's not that.
Just something Becky said.
Becky?
At first, his shoulders are relaxed.
He doesn't put his hands up,
then, when he does,
they're open, defensive.
And then he changed.
You say it's unusual, then,
Becky, not to see the signs?
We can always tell when something's
going to kick off.
So, how do you explain this one?
He's a psycho. Can't predict that.
I'd have called in sooner, if I had.
If there was nothing
suspicious about it,
just out of interest,
why were you monitoring it
in the first place?
That's what we do. We watch.
But out of everything that's
happening in the borough? Well...
He's... not a bad looking bloke,
is he? And...
...I just thought it was romantic.
His behaviour changes completely.
And it changes right after the bus.
What, all this is made up
on a computer, like Toy Story?
Marcus Levy said the hard work
could've been done in advance.
And how could they know where
these two would end up standing?
Er... what are you talking about?
Yeah, what about Toy Story?
We just need to analyse
the footage, that's all.
Make sure it all stands up.
You can't argue with this.
No, of course.
Thank you.
Sorry, I shouldn't have
said all that.
Not in front of the children.
See, even that makes sense.
What does?
If you wanted to pass
fake footage off as real,
you'd want someone naive to find it.
What? Rachel?
You said you'd talk to me
and Nads from now on?
Team Homicide?
This isn't about Homicide.
Call it a night, Patrick.
You're going to have come up with a
better name for our team than that.
PHONE BUZZES
Mr Levy, thanks for calling me back.
I'm afraid it's not Mr Levy.
It's DC Taylor
from Stoke Newington CID.
According to his
Mr Levy's phone,
yours was the last number he called.
Neighbours discovered him
unconscious
on his living room floor
this evening. He's in a coma.
Treat it as suspicious.
There's no sign of force.
The front door was left open.
They wanted him found.
Have you any idea why Mr Levy
might have been targeted?
Did you get him down all right?
- HE CHUCKLES
- Good.
My bus will be here
in three minutes.
Don't go to bed! I'll be home
before you know it!
- DS Flynn, please leave a message.
- Patrick, it's Rachel.
Just be vigilant on
your way home, please.
I'll explain later,
but just make sure you're safe.
And your family.
Are you serious?
This is where you've brought me?
What about all these fucking people?
Don't worry, they'll all be too
off their heads to recognise you.
- And these cameras?
- They're offline. They're secure.
I know this place.
What are you doing?
Come on.
You said you wanted to know
about "correction".
We can talk in there.
LOUD HOUSE MUSIC PLAYS
All right, listen, I've got to go.
I'll grab a bottle of red
from the offie.
I'm on my way.
Taxi!
CAR ALARM BEEPS
VEHICLE APPROACHES
DI Carey.
I'm sure you're busy trying to
locate your suspect
but I need a moment of your time.
It's come to my attention
that, earlier this evening,
you instructed DS Latif to arrange
the removal of a victim's
remains from Lambeth Coroner's.
Any attempt to move such an article
during an ongoing investigation
should be considered a breech
in the chain of evidence. This is
a homicide investigation that began
at SCD. The autopsy should
have been carried out at
Croydon Coroner's Office.
...the body was rightfully
registered at Lambeth Coroner's
and I can only conclude that your intention
was to pervert the course of justice.
I'm perverting the course of justice!
This is not the first transgression
you've made during the course
of this investigation.
I also have reason to believe
you conspired to publish classified
CCTV evidence online in an effort to
undermine your superiors and unduly
influence police operations.
These incidents will be reviewed
by a disciplinary board to determine
if action or criminal charges
should be taken against you.
Until then,
I am left with no alternative
but to suspend you from duty
with immediate effect.
Get some rest, Rachel.
Hopefully, when you return,
the decision will go your way.
Be a huge loss to the force
if you were to go.
I never said anything
about the evidence.
But I couldn't move the body.
I'd be suspended.
Ma'am?
I'm sorry.
I'm meant to take the car.
You sure this can't wait till
the day shift? Sorry, fella.
The coffees are on me.
WOMAN LAUGHS LOUDLY
Chestnut.
- Chestnut? Is this a joke?
- It is a joke!
THEY LAUGH
Guv? I thought it was you!
Sorry, am I interrupting?
No...
DI Carey, this is my wife, Elaine.
This is Dee.
Too many names.
Hi! I'm Rachel.
You two work together?
- We did. I got moved. - Promoted.
- Technically.
So, who's looking after
the kids tonight?
We just let them
walk the streets, don't we?
- Whereabouts are you sitting?
- Oh. I'm not with anyone, actually.
I got stood up.
ALL: Aw.
Come and sit down.
Let's get the girl a drink!
You're on a big case though,
at the moment, aren't you?
No, I got suspended.
I had no idea.
Sounds like you really do
need a drink!
Excuse me?
Could we get another drinks menu?
That's really kind,
but it's been a weird day.
I think I'll just go up to the
top floor and jump out the window.
I think you'll find the windows
don't open. Try the roof.
Daniel?
It's fine. Detective's humour.
It was so lovely to meet you.
Guv'.
CHATTER RECOMMENCES
Just going to the little boys' room.
Shaun?
Shaun!
Come on, Carey, pick up!
Where are you?
PHONE BUZZES
I'll talk to them about the
suspension but you need to go.
I remembered something else
about Sycamore.
I wasn't meant to be
on CCTV watch that day.
I was re-assigned that morning,
told to help with the trawl.
Perfect, wasn't I! Fast-track girl,
hungry for promotion.
- I can speak later. - I was used to
find something planted for me
and surely you remember it
because you were the one
that re-assigned me! And THAT -
that's what got me promoted!
So, my career's a fucking lie.
You were even going to put me
forward for a commendation,
- for a case won on false evidence!
- Keep your voice down.
Why is this happening? How many
other suspects have we fitted up?
Answer me...
...or, so help me, I will march over
there and I will tell your wife
about us in every, intimate detail.
If you knew what was at stake,
you'd walk away
and pretend this never happened.
I do know the stakes.
- I know what happened to Marcus Levy.
- Who?
He's lying unconscious in A&E.
For what?
For figuring out what
they did to Shaun?
Is that what they'll do to me?
I don't know what you're
talking about. Shaun Emery!
You faked his video evidence, too.
Why? Rachel, I...
And if Shaun didn't kill
Hannah Roberts...
...then who did?
Your wife must be wondering
where you've got to.
I'll tell you this.
The soldier and the silly bitch,
if that video was faked,
I swear on my children,
it wasn't anyone we know.
Why would you call her that?
How far did you even
look into the victim, Detective?
Ask yourself this...
...when did you last hear
of a human rights lawyer
defending a British soldier?
This is Detective Inspector
Rachel Carey.
Please leave a message.
Ma'am? Call me back!
If there was a delay
on the video feed,
Latif would've checked
the wrong bus.
I've been going through CCTV
on the previous bus that night.
She's there. Hannah Roberts.
She got on the bus
just like Emery said.
Shaun!
VOICE TALKS SOFTLY
...though she with giants fight.
She will make good her right
to be a pilgrim.
A pilgrim of justice.
ALL: Pilgrim of justice.
I'm sorry.
He wouldn't wait.
That's understandable.
Charlie.
I imagine you'd like to know
what the fuck is going on.