I’m Simone.
I’m his sister.
You've put me in the shit.
They’ll be coming.
Until they get what they want.
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
We’ve got new orders.
And an additional order saying.
Avoid combat situations.
- What?
- Abort attack.
Five of our subs
are counting on us.
Tell the men to stand down!
Aye, sir.
You will liaise with a vessel
and effect an exchange.
It's man.
Mr Samuel Greenwood.
Plane!
Two U-boats...
That’s 100 dead comrades.
All because we aborted
the attack.
And now this poor sod.
Being killed in combat
is one thing...
but dying because we’ve taken
a passenger on board...
a foreigner...
That’s... a disgrace.
With you in command it
would have been different,
First Watch Officer.
Unfortunately I don’t have
a father to make me a captain.
Although...
Hoffmann senior would have
attacked the convoy on his own.
He wouldn’t have given a damn
about orders from HQ.
“Imbued with the determination
to win and unrelenting
towards himself.”
Junior doesn’t understand
the meaning of this sentence.
If you don’t like my cooking,
leave it.
I won’t be offended.
I’ll leave it out for you
in case you get hungry later.
- What do you want?
- I’m looking for Nathalie.
I must to speak to her.
Let her in.
Sit down.
Bיatrice takes care of Anna
when l’m at work.
After a German officer
got shot in Nantes,
they decided to
register us all.
As a reprisal.
I fled.
I got the job
at the Cheval Blanc.
I never worked
upstairs, you know.
I’m a barmaid.
What’s the best place to hide
from the Germans for Jewish girl?
Amongst German soldiers.
I didn’t know that Frank...
He didn’t tell me.
I know.
With your brother,
it just happened like that.
Jazz brought us together.
Louis Armstrong.
The pregnancy wasn’t planned.
I asked him for money
for an abortion.
He didn’t want that.
He wanted to keep it.
He wanted to be a father.
That’s when I told him
everything...
That I’m Jewish.
He didn’t care at all.
He couldn’t understand
why I hadn’t told him.
Frank...
wanted to buy passports.
Yes...
America...
It was just an idea, a dream.
They’re too expensive
on the black market anyway.
He wanted to pay with this.
He wanted me to give it to
a woman.
In exchange for passports, I...
Do you know what this is?
No,
all I can tell you is that...
he talked more
and more about leaving.
He said that he may have
found a way out.
If you knew what I’ve done...
Would you like to hold her?
Yes.
Anna...
that’s your Aunt Simone.
She likes you.
I... must go.
Is that your girl?
Yes.
Show me.
Pretty.
Is she French?
Yes.
Tell me, Frank,
you speak English, right?
Is it true that the
guy’s name is Greenwood?
Sam Greenwood?
Grnholz.
Samuel Grnholz.
At home, someone with
that name scrubs the road.
With a toothbrush.
Do we have a fucking Jew
on board?
I can smell them 10 miles
upwind, I swear.
Ralf...
Any of that dried meat left?
The last bit?
It’s okay.
- Serves you right.
- What do you mean?
You told Lutz about it.
- Change of watch.
- So?
One look at his dumb,
fat face is enough.
He can’t keep a secret.
- You could have told me.
- You’re a big boy.
Arsehole.
We’ll be a laughing stock back
on shore.
We’re traitors.
So who the fuck is this
arsehole?
Maybe a POW.
Or a spy.
Maybe he knows something that
could help us win the war.
Was that in your book?
- He could be Irish.
- What?
I knew a guy, planesman on U-65.
Dead now.
He told me they once had
a special mission
to take two Irishmen from
Wilhelmshaven back to Dublin.
IRA men, freedom fighters
against the Tommies.
The Micks know a thing
or two about potatoes.
Thorsten finally made a joke.
Well done, kiddo!
Whoever he is, he’s bad luck.
Why bad luck?
Best peel them to the right
or none of us will go home.
Another stupid comment like
that and I’ll kill you.
I promise.
That thing about the captain...
You heard it too?
About the U-boats?
Of course.
Not that.
Something about
his last mission.
But I couldn’t believe it.
Not at first.
Then I heard it from
a couple of others.
What?
Come on, tell me.
Only if you won’t tell anyone.
A damaged U-boat is
making a stop here
for repairs before
carrying on to Lorient.
It's Schulz’s boat..
- The Shulz?
- Yes.
They've been at sea
for ten weeks.
and they'll be wanting to
let off steam.
Berlin wants a fuss made
of them for the cameras.
We'll have to make
it look really good.
There ould even be some locals.
But no one who fought in the
Spanish Civil War,
and for the wrong side.
I can reassure you.
The death of that woman
is unfortunate.
It’s not like you.
It’s the fault of
the local police.
- Was she from around here?
- Probably not.
- Nobody reported her missing.
- What does that mean?
- I'm working on it.
- Do that, Forster.
You know how much I rely
on the French workers.
I can’t afford to jeopardise
the peace on the base.
- What now?
- What do you mean?
We didn’t get it so
the Brits won’t help us.
And?
- How are you?
- Hello...
- Did you have a nice evening?
- Yes, thanks. And you?
It was fine, thanks.
See you later...
Good morning,
Inspector Forster.
Just call me Mr Forster.
Oh, no thank you.
Miss Simone,
I have a serious problem.
- With the prisioner?
- Why do you say that?
Don’t worry, she’s
been relocated.
She’s not our problem now.
There are more pressing matters.
A parade for King Kong.
- Who?
- His real name is Schulz.
A homecoming U-boat captain.
Gluck asked me to ensure
the event goes smoothly.
I wondering if I could talk
you into a short outing.
Maybe tomorrow?
I’d like to show you
something very dear to me.
Yes.
I’m glad, Miss Simone.
Are you sure?
Yes, I swear.
He shot him.
In cold blood.
- Did you hear about Hoffmann?
- No, tell me.
He told the firing
squad to stand down
so he could shoot
the kid himself.
You made that up.
He shot him right in the face.
Twice, the cowardly bastard.
- Hoffmann?
- Of course. Who else?
We should sail due north
to avoid further air attacks,
then swing west here.
Can we still make
the rendezvous?
Yes. If we cross these Allied
shipping lanes diagonally.
What distance are
we talking about?
About 30 nautical miles.
We could dive underneath
the convoy route.
Is that technically feasible?
If the batteries
are fully charged
and we squeeze every last
milliamp out of them... yes.
Very well.
We’ll follow the chief
engineer’s advice.
If you need me,
I’ll be on the bridge.
Have you heard the rumour
that our passenger is a Jew?
I’m not interested in rumours,
Strelitz.
Take him back before
I lose my temper.
Tennstedt!
I was only notifying
the passenger
that he is not at
liberty to walk around.
The name of the prisoner
was Jacqueline Rossignol.
How do we know it’s her?
Description matches,
and distinguishing features...
the Republican tattoo,
left breast...
Fighter in the
Spanish Civil War...
and a communist.
Rounded up entering
France in 1940,
sent to the camp at Vernet.
Transferred to a camp
in Brittany six months ago
but escaped in the company
of another inmate
who sustained multiple bullet
wounds.
That’s why the morphine.
- Her name?
- Carla Monroe.
The second person you saw at
the church was a woman, right?
We need a picture of her.
Can I help you?
Maybe.
Here you are, gentlemen.
Enioy your meal.
Just a moment, did
I understand right?
You saw the designs?
Tell me, Ralf, do you know
the cucumber shooting game?
- No.
- You don’t?
Are you deaf?
He just said he didn’t.
Okay, listen.
Two whores are laid on their
backs on the floor.
Each of them gets a cucumber
shoved up her pussy.
Then the shooter slaps
his whore on the belly
and the one who shoots his
cucumber the furthest has won.
Can’t you shut your
fucking trap for once?
- Beginner’s luck.
- No such thing.
- Another hand?
- Of course.
Guys, don’t you get bored
with gambling?
More bored than cruising
around playing taxi?
What a shitty trip.
Watch out, boys,
here comes the Frenchman.
Frenchman?
- Yeah, he’s not a real German.
- A Frenchman?
And someone from Africa.
What kind of crew is this?
Strasser, you know you
make noises in your sleep?
Squealing noises.
High-pitched little squeals.
Strange squeals.
Piggy squeals.
You’ve got to be wary of him.
He got his CO
court-martialled.
Don’t talk crap.
Did they sentence
Heinz, yes or no?
It was a disgrace.
He sank a hospital ship.
But I didn’t squeal.
Of course you did.
I’m wondering if it runs
in your family.
Chubby says you saw your sister
before we sailed.
I’ll pay her a visit.
Maybe she’ll squeal too
if I give it to her from behind.
No, Frank!
Strasser! What the hell
is wrong with you?
Nothing, Captain.
Get up.
Just a misunderstanding.
Extra watch duties
for both of you.
Starting now for you.
Come on, move it.
And you, get cleaned up.
You look like shit.
Everyone in the office
is really excited
about the parade tomorrow.
You too?
I won’t attend.
I don’t approve of granstanders
like Schulz.
As if he has done
any better than
those who are still out there.
I’m sorry.
I’m sure your brother
will come back unharmed.
I look forward to meeting him.
- If tou please...
- Thank you.
So?
What do you think.
It's beautiful.
Very big.
Yes.
I've just bought it.
I intend to stay here, Simone.
In France.
Once we’ve won the war.
Come on in.
A little snack is
waiting for us.
Civilisation and its Discontents
by Sigmund Freud
Freud.
My psychology professor
was profoundly influenced
by his theses.
Jewish, yes.
But he had some interesting
ideas.
One day nobody will care that it
was written by a Jew.
Nobody will remember
what a Jew was.
A Chגteaux Grand Cיroux.
We should really
let it breathe, but...
Cheers.
I'm pleased you accepted
my invitation.
Gladly.
It’s beautiful.
Yes, I can see a future
for myself here.
And an easy life.
Once we’ve got rid of
a few pockets of resistance.
What resistance?
Nothing major.
Just a few small cells.
And what do you mean by cells?
It’s usually five
or six people,
they are decentralised,
mainly criminals.
But you’ve seen yourself
how aggressive they can be.
By the way, the prisoner
had a female accomplice.
In his book,
Freud describes very well
how some people only follow
their destrutive impulses.
Unfortunately we don’t have
a photo yet,
but this could be her.
I need that translated.
Miss Simone,
I have a favour to ask.
Would you teach me French?
My language skills are
unfortunately very mauvaise.
Yes...
And it would be "mauvais".
“Language skills”
are masculine in French.
There you have it.
I’ve always dreamed of that...
A strict teacher
with your looks.
Come on, let’s go.
Where are we up to?
Almost done.
I’m sorry, sir.
I lost control.
You and Maas were on the same
the same sub?
U-311.
Hinz’s sub.
Don’t worry, Strasser.
Is it true that two
of our U-boats are missing?
From the pack that
attacked the convoy?
- Who says that?
- The first watch officer.
The second watch officer
heard it on the supply ship.
The scout U-boat
is always under attack.
The other one was probably
blasted by the destroyers.
Sir, we’re approaching
the Allied convoy route.
Conning tower hatch closed.
Prepare to dive.
Rig buoyancy vents.
Two U-boats
and you don’t say a word?
I thought the second watch officer
had already told you.
It is your duty to report to me.
Anything else is an act of
insubordination, Tennstedt.
You can go.
The second watch officer
will take over.
Dive!
Dive to 40 metres.
15 degrees down
on the bow planes.
Stern, zero.
Did you know
about the two subs?
Yes, but I thought they’d...
Second watch officer
in control room.
Have you ever played this?
Never.
- Want to learn?
- Sure, why not?
It’s about getting the king.
You use various
pieces to do that.
Have you heard the saying...
“You can’t do in war what you
haven’t learnt in peacetime.”
- What?
- You know all kinds of shit.
I knew a first watch officer
who used to say it.
Odd guy, had a glass eye
which had turned yellow.
Oh no, they’re mouldy.
It’s going to be stew, then.
Just tell me where you heard it.
It’s on the wall in the lobby.
At Mrwik.
Mrwik?
The officers’ college?
Yeah, where else?
Stop talking to the passenger.
The passports...
Take the baby and leave.
I didn't think anything good
ould ever happen to me again.
Frank will join you later.
Do you have money?
Enough for the...
the crossing.
- And you know where to go?
- To Lisbon, I think.
I’ll let him know.
He will join you there.
And you?
What will you do?
Make sure you get
enough vitamins.
We’re already getting
the first sniffles, sir.
I almost forgot...
- Your apple.
- Thank you.
Sir, I was able to plot
our position by the stars.
We’re north of the
convoy route, as planned.
You remember the reason
for the war?
Air to breathe without Jews
and Bolsheviks.
And now we’re transporting
a bloody Yid.
Are you sure of that?
The guy is circumcised.
90% of the Yanks are circumcised
so that they wank less.
It’s true.
Ship ahead!
Now, now.
Slowly.
And be quiet.
Distance 3 km.
She’s heaving to.
She’s got it in for us.
Alarm!
Corvette at zero-zero-five!
Wake up, arseholes!
Put the bunks away.
Flood tubes 1 to 4!
- Hatch is closed.
- Dive!
Dive to periscope depth.
15 degrees down on bow planes,
stern zero.
An American Corvette.
They’ve detected us.
Do we try to avoid them?
If they alert other escorts,
we could come under
sustained attack.
We can’t chicken out again.
Not this time.
Battle stations.
Aye, sir.
Battle stations!
Open outer doors.
Distance 2000.
Angle-on-the-bow, starboard 30.
Torpedo speed 30,
running depth 4.
Right full rudder.
New course zero-four-five.
In three minutes,
angle-on-the-bow, starboard 45.
Our best shot.
Today we’re in luck.
Corvette now at
three-four-zero.
Angle-on-the-bow, starboard 40.
Make ready tubes 1 and 2
for submerged firing.
Forward room, make ready tubes
1 and 2 for submerged firing.
Tubes 1 and 2 ready
for submerged firing.
Go on, Tiger.
Your turn today.
Maintain periscope depth.
One metre up.
Five degrees up on bow planes.
Torpedo speed 30.
Enemy speed 15,
angle-on-the-bow,
starboard 45.
Distance 1700.
Is there a problem,
First Watch Officer?
No problem, sir.
Torpedo speed 30.
Enemy speed 15,
angle-on-the-bow, starboard 45.
Distance 1700.
Fire one.
Fire two.
- Fire one. Fire two.
- Fire torpedoes!
Four... five...
six... seven... eight...
Safety released!
Move it!
Secure!
- Secured!
- Now push it in.
21... 22...
23... 24...
Pull it back!
Help me.
Lift him. Fucking hell!
Jesus Christ.
We need a belt, quick.
Rig for surfacing.
I’m sorry, but
you can’t keep it.
We need to amputate.
Hold him down, okay?
Really hard.
Grab hold of his arm.
Tight.
Now we start to cut, okay?
You ready?
You can do it, buddy.
You can do it.
That’s your responsibility.
We survive air raids
and destroyer attacks
then something like
this happens here!
You have slight concussion.
This will help with headaches.
Get some rest.
Hey, can you get me more wine?
A bottle of wine, please.
Pour it.
Hey, has one of you
ever fucked her?
No.
But she’s pretty.
Way prettier than yours.
You’re right.
All right, let’s go upstairs.
No, I just work at the bar.
What?
She says she only works down
here and doesn’t fuck.
Girl, that feels as wrong as
a bomb going off
in a safe harbour.
Are you trying to run?
If you won’t come upstairs,
we’ll do it right here.
Fucking French whore!
Do as you’re told!
Fuck her! Fuck her! Fuck her!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org