Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app
Okay, you're good.
...last night.
Here's more of that terrifying
video from our news crew.
Rioters
are storming parts of the city,
looting stores
and setting buildings on fire.
The National Guard fire into the crowd.
I mean, this violence is endemic.
It's like a disease that's
infecting a growing area...
Jay.
You can't stay inside all day.
It stinks out there.
Dylan's taking Bobby out on the tractor.
Dylan stinks.
I'm getting eaten alive today.
Wow.
These are amazing.
You want me to send this one to your dad?
Okay.
But you got to do
one thing for me.
Look. I'm not driving.
Oh, well, now, somebody's got to drive.
- Somebody's got to drive.
- I'll drive it.
- Careful.
- All right, where are we going now, Dylan?
This is Mission Control to Jay.
Sorry I haven't written to you
for a while.
I've been away from
civilization for a few weeks.
How's Bobby?
He still farting in his sleep?
Hope you two are getting along.
Miss you both so much.
I can't believe it's been
two years since I saw you last.
I want to come see you,
but I need to keep fighting.
I'm heading out on another secret mission,
but I promise, when it's over,
I'll come and visit.
I know it's hard not seeing
each other, but remember,
everything I do is to protect you.
Did you know that Bobby practically
drove the tractor all by himself today?
I was just staying on his lap,
and I was doing all the steering.
Oh, okay. And could you reach
the steering wheel from where you were?
Yeah.
- No joke.
- No joke?
I asked him if he had a
license, and he said he did.
Right?
I-I said I did not.
Oh, I didn't hear the "not" part.
Is Mom gonna be okay?
It's just a bug. Don't worry about it.
Wow, Jay.
That is an awesome picture.
We should try to frame that.
Frame it now.
Go to bed.
Now.
So, Dylan, want me to help you
get it back all together
so we can frame it?
Hey.
Wakey, wakey, Jay.
Dad?
You're back.
Come here. Come here.
I'm sorry it took so long.
I missed you so much.
I missed you, too.
I got to check something.
Keep your eyes open.
It's all good. Just relax.
Okay, you're good.
Hey. Jay.
I'm taking you on a road trip.
How's that sound?
- Now? Let's do it.
- Huh?
- You good to go?
- Yeah.
- Ready for action?
- Uh-huh.
- Bobby!
- Calm down. Calm down.
- Wake up, dumbass. Dad's back.
- Calm down.
Go get ready.
Little man.
Come give me a hug, little man.
- Daddy's back.
- Dad?
Yeah, it's me.
- Remember me?
- Mm-hmm.
You look different.
Yeah, I look a little different.
- Hey, you look different, too.
- Hmm.
Come on, come here, give me a hug.
Give me a hug. Huh?
Come on, give me a hug, give me a hug.
Give me a real hug. Come on.
Yeah, that's right.
Look over there. Okay.
Keep looking up. Don't blink.
Don't...
I said don't blink. Hey.
Hey, quit cheating.
Okay. Who wants to play a game?
- I like playing games.
- Okay, the game is called
"get in the car as fast
as humanly possible."
You gonna let him beat you?
Okay, let's go. Let's get going.
You with me?
- Yeah.
- Then let's play.
- Okay, who's gonna win?
- Come on, slowpoke.
Three, two... Car's out this way.
One. One second, liftoff.
Let's go.
All good? Good job.
- Okay, so who won?
- I won.
- I got in the car first.
- But I leapt in first.
- Yeah?
- No, that's not fair.
- Shut up, fart breath.
- Oh, yeah? You shut up then.
Yo, seat belts on.
Listen, Dad, I got to the car first.
Dad?
Can you tell us a war story?
Like, all the battles you've been in?
And have you ever jumped out
of a helicopter?
You want to be a Marine, huh?
- Maybe.
- Okay.
Why didn't Mom tell us we were
going on this road trip?
Because she wanted it
to be a big surprise.
Where are we going?
Mm, it... it's a surprise.
Disneyland?
No, we're not going to Disneyland.
- Why?
- 'Cause it's, uh...
Dude, it's dangerous there.
You didn't hear what happened?
- No.
- Dude.
I mean, a-a ride broke down.
A bunch of kids died.
Jay, you hear about that?
Why aren't Mom and Dylan going?
Dude, they're going
on their own vacation.
They're going skiing.
In Canada.
I want to go skiing.
Oh, really? You want to go
freeze your ass off
on top of a mountain? Huh?
With Mr. Stick Up His Butt?
Hmm?
Or you want to go on
a road trip with your old man?
Number two, please.
Okay. Well, then here it goes.
Okay, we're going on
a Special Operations road trip.
Is y'all with me?
- Yeah.
- Well, check it out.
There's no bedtimes.
You can go to sleep whenever you want.
You get to eat candy whenever you want.
If you follow the rules,
I'll let you fire my gun.
- Sound like fun?
- Yeah.
Okay. Rule number one: I don't want y'all
talking to anybody out here.
Lot of weirdos on the open road.
Okay? Okay, rule number two:
I want y'all to stay covered in this.
- Mine. Mine!
- It's mine.
J-Jay, use some, and then
give it to your brother, okay?
Yeah. What is it?
It's, uh, bug spray, okay?
Yeah, you dumbass. What'd you think?
Y'all get down. Get down now.
Okay, good job, everybody. Get up.
How about a team fist bump?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- Boom.
- Yeah? Okay.
Okay. I'm gonna get
some supplies, fill up.
I'll be right back.
Can we come with you?
Yeah, please, please, please.
Please.
Well...
well, you could come with me, or...
you could stay here
and open your presents.
- Presents! We got presents!
- No way.
We got presents!
All right, all right. I love presents.
Okay, lock the doors.
Thanks, Dad.
Jay, what did you get?
- Pens. Cool.
- I got an action figure.
Better than your stupid pens, Jay.
My sketchbook.
"Hello. My name is Muscleman."
I'm Bobby. "Hi, Bobby.
Oh, cool. Bobby is a cool name."
This is Mission Control to Jay.
Uh, we need a copilot up here.
Uh, okay.
Little man's out cold.
Yeah.
Hey, you kept all my letters, huh?
I kept all your drawings, too.
And some days, I thought
I'd never make it back,
that's what kept me going.
Dad?
Why do you have pictures of monsters?
You going through my stuff?
Huh? You're not supposed to do that.
Yeah, well, that wasn't a rule.
Well, it's a rule now, okay?
Rule number three:
Don't go through my stuff.
Hey.
They're not monsters. They're parasites.
It's just a tiny organism that
lives inside another creature.
Inside humans?
Hey, don't worry about it.
Why don't you get some sleep?
We can talk in the morning, okay?
I just got to go pee.
Yeah, no peeing on this road trip.
I already told you.
That's-that's the next rule.
But that wasn't a rule, though.
No, that's it... you got to pee
your pants. That's all.
Come on, Dad. I need to go.
I can't hold it.
Okay, you covered in that spray?
Mm-hmm.
Just here. That's far enough.
So you got hair around your pecker yet?
Dad, shut up.
Dad.
Jay, get in the car.
It's okay.
All right.
Are we there yet?
Shut up.
Evening, Officer.
All right, that's enough right there.
Okay.
What's going on here?
On a road trip with my boys.
Little man needed to stop
for a toilet break.
Huh.
Didn't think to put your hazards on?
There was nobody on the road.
I was on the road.
You're right.
Yeah, my bad. I apologize.
So a little road trip, huh?
Uh-huh.
At 3:00 a.m.?
Yeah, you know, the early bird.
Sir, I want you to put your
hands on the back of that car.
Shit,
there ain't no need for that.
I got an "easy way or
a hard way" speech prepared,
if you really want to hear it.
Whoa.
Sir, do you have a permit
for this firearm?
Not on me.
That against the law?
It's a class A misdemeanor if it's loaded.
Sir, do you have any other
weapons in the vehicle?
No, sir.
Officer, I'm a Marine, special forces.
I just came back off deployment.
Just trying to see my kids, you know?
Going up camping in Tahoe.
I only got 'em for the weekend,
so that's why I'm driving at night.
Just trying to make up for time.
Turn around.
Real slow.
Let me get my I.D.
You can write me a ticket.
- I'll be on my way.
- Stop right now.
Put your hands behind your head
and get down on your knees.
Get your hands on your head
and get down on your knees now!
I don't want no trouble.
Stay down!
No, please, stop!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Sorry you had to see that, boys.
- I want to go home.
- I know, kid.
- I know.
- I want to go right now!
We can't go home, Bobby.
Why can't we go home?
Just breathe with me for a second, okay?
Can you help me out? Jay, you, too.
In and out.
We can't go home.
This ain't a road trip.
This is a rescue mission.
What do you mean?
Something's come to our planet.
Aliens?
Non-terrestrial microorganisms.
I haven't seen any aliens.
You have. You just don't know it.
They live inside of us.
They use us as hosts.
And that happens through insects.
That's why we use the bug spray.
We got to go back and save Mom.
What's wrong with Mom?
She's got one inside her.
She's alive. She's just not in control.
Hey, but I'm gonna save her.
Boys... first, I've got to get you safe.
That's why right now
I'm taking you to a base
that's still operational.
It's one of the only ones.
It's full of scientists...
they're working on a cure.
Hey.
Hey, take my hand.
Come on, Jay.
Y'all ever heard of the Three Musketeers?
No, never.
They were the three toughest
soldiers there ever was.
And they could survive anything
'cause they stuck together.
Now, you're telling me,
if we don't stand by each other,
we can't get through anything?
Yes.
I know we can.
Hey.
How'd you sleep?
I had a nightmare.
Hey, come on up.
You okay?
Yeah. What you reading?
I'm trying to become
a neuroparasitology expert.
What's this one?
Oh, this one's a nasty little dude.
It burrows its way
inside a fish's eyeball,
manipulates its behavior
so it gets eaten by a bird.
And then it reproduces
inside the bird's guts.
Crazy, huh?
Are aliens reproducing inside Mom's guts?
No.
Your mom's got guts to spare.
Okay? Believe me.
Hey, let me show you something else.
This is where we're headed.
It's in Nevada.
We should be there about noon tomorrow.
And...
and we came from up here in Oregon, right?
Yeah. You've got
yourself a job navigating.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Are these muscles?
What you doing growing up on me, huh?
You've got muscles now?
Show me what you're packing.
Ooh.
Oh, my God, put it away.
You're gonna get in trouble.
It's dangerous.
Dude.
Look at you, huh?
You grew up.
And Bobby, too.
Bobby, rise and shine!
Pancake time!
How many people have been infected?
Could be as much
as half the population.
Folks look normal, but inside they're not.
If you use that spray,
it's like a force field.
You're gonna be safe.
What happens if you get infected?
I won't let that happen.
Jay. Weren't you gonna draw me a picture?
Oh. Yeah.
Hey, Bobby.
Nothing bad's gonna happen
to you while I'm around, okay?
And besides, if this ain't
a hell of an adventure,
I don't know what is, dude.
I would've killed to do
something like this
when I was a kid.
Hey. When you get back to school,
can you imagine the crazy
stories you're gonna have?
Uh, can I tell them about the gun firing?
I mean, I'm not sure
if you can tell them that.
It's top secret, dude.
That's just for the crew.
That's just for the Musketeers.
But you can tell them you went on
a crazy road trip
with your cool-ass dad, okay?
Yeah, just smile.
Smiling's the best disguise.
Okay, that's a little bit
too much. It's scary.
Dude, you're looking like
an alien yourself now.
- Just smile normally.
- What if the trooper finds us?
There's no way he's gonna find us.
What do you mean?
'Cause we drove halfway
across California last night.
Here you go.
All right.
It's a little hot. Just be careful.
Get some of that.
You don't like maple syrup?
I'm not allowed.
Oh, Dylan says sugar makes him hyper.
You know, for once, Dylan is right.
Sugar does make you hyper.
That's why we like it.
Hey.
Don't run in the road.
You see that? You see what happened?
You got to stay close.
I got to go get some supplies.
You okay holding fort, watching Bobby?
Hey, it's a big responsibility.
It's kind of a promotion.
You up to it?
Yeah.
Okay. Here you go.
Stay in the car.
I'll be five minutes.
Okay.
Bobby.
You lay low, and I'll stand watch.
All right.
Hey, Jay, what do you think it's like
when there's an alien inside you?
I think it's like you can hear everything
and see everything,
but you just can't move
and you can't speak.
It's like being a prisoner
inside your own body.
You think the Red Sox are aliens?
- The Red Sox?
- Yeah.
Who cares?
Why do you even like them, anyway?
Well, like, Dylan says
they're gonna be the winner of the season.
You know what? If Dylan likes them,
then they're definitely aliens.
I think she saw me.
Shh. Stay down.
There's no more spray.
Bobby, stop. Stop.
Hey. Kids, you got ten dollars?
Bobby. Bobby.
Bobby, get back here!
Bobby!
Dad. Dad.
- What?
- I lost Bobby.
- There was an alien, and then
- I couldn't do anything.
- Shh. Calm down.
- Calm down. Calm down.
- And I tried to find him.
I'm so sorry, Dad.
I lost him.
Okay. Come with me.
Stay close.
Bobby, Bobby. What you doing, man?
What you doing running off like that?
I got scared.
That's not a goddamn excuse, okay?
You want to draw attention to us?
- No. No.
- Look at me.
You want to draw attention to us?
No.
Hey.
We're behind enemy lines here.
Okay? So if you want us
to make it out in one piece,
you got to learn to follow orders.
- Oh, you-you want these, huh?
- Yes.
Take this.
It's not okay.
Okay? This happens again,
we got a problem.
I mean it.
Why are you angry at me
when he's the dumb shit that ran off?
- I'm not a dumb shit! You are!
- Hey.
- Yes, you are.
- He is a kid.
I'm a kid, too.
No, you're not. No.
You're not a kid anymore.
You can't be. I'm sorry. I need you.
Hey, look at me. Look at me.
Families take care of each other.
- Is that clear?
- Yes.
Damn.
Scaring the hell out of me.
Hey, can we just try
and enjoy this road trip?
- What kind of candy you want?
- Starburst or Skittles.
Don't go easy on me this time.
I'll start the count.
One, two, three, four,
I declare a thumb war.
- One, two, three, four, I...
- How do you keep doing that?
I just won a thumb war.
How come Bobby gets to sit in the front?
Poo-poo, poo-poo, poo-poo head.
This is so fun, Dad.
Hey, Jay, you think this thing
could hit a hundred?
Yeah!
Want to find out? Yeah?
Let's see what this hunk of junk can do.
Come on!
Come on, Dad!
- Three, two... one!
- Go, Dad!
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, I need a nap.
- I just need a nap, okay?
- Dad? No, no, no.
- Dad, wake up! Wake up.
- No, no, no. No, no, no.
- Dad, Dad, wake up. Dad, wake up.
- Dad, wake up.
- Dad!
- Whoa. Whoa, whoa, wh-wh-whoa.
What-what'd I miss?
Who was driving?
No one.
You were kind of driving.
You were about to pull over.
We all friends again now?
Yeah.
Whoo!
Okay.
This is dumb.
You don't like this?
Heavy metal, dude.
Guns N' Roses, Iron Maiden, Megadeth?
Okay, what do you guys listen to?
K-pop.
That's why you're in the back.
Okay, what music do you like?
Barbra Streisand.
Well, it's official.
You're both infected.
Hey, boys, help me out.
Can I change this music now?
No way.
This is the best stuff.
Hey, Dad?
Yeah.
You think there was a part of
Mom that's still fighting it?
Yeah, that sounds like
your mom.
I think there was.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I mean, she'd been acting
all strange recently.
Like how?
Like barfing all the time.
You mean, like, in the mornings?
Yeah. And she's been eating
some weird stuff.
Like chocolate and mayonnaise.
And cottage cheese and onion.
What's up?
What's wrong?
One second. I need to think.
Dad, what's wrong?
Shh.
I got to call base.
Hello?
Hello, Hattie?
It's me, Malik.
Where the hell have you been?
- You didn't show up for work.
- Uh, I-I know.
You missed your psych eval.
Look, you want to go back to prison?
I thought we respected each other.
You gonna let me down like this?
Hattie, shut up and listen, okay?
I need you to go check on Piya.
Check on Piya?
I need you to tell me
exactly what's going on and where you are.
I went and got my kids.
What do you mean, got 'em?
I mean I went and got them.
They're with me now.
Christ, Malik. That's called kidnapping.
And if you... if you cross state lines,
it's a federal offense.
Hey, I did not... I did not kidnap them.
I saved them. Okay?
I can't explain it all right now,
but they're safe now...
they're safer here with me.
Okay, you need to stop talking.
Stop talking and tell me
exactly where you are right now.
I can't do that, Hattie.
Just go check on Piya.
Okay? She's in the garage with Dylan.
- Look, we can...
- Please, you're the only person I trust.
We can fix this, but you have to tell...
Ma-Malik? Malik? Malik?
Malik, please pick up.
You got me scared as hell.
If it's about visitation rights,
we can talk through it.
- Stop! Stop!
- You were showing
too much promise
to do something this stupid.
I'm not gonna give up on you.
I'm not gonna stop calling.
- You're on my side.
- Stop. No, get off.
You're on my side. You're on my side.
- Hey, stop!
- You are on my side.
Hey, quit it.
Are we there yet?
Bobby, I'm trying to think
right now, okay?
Just quietly let's enjoy the view.
♪ I'm going
all around the world, yeah ♪
Hey, can you pull your hand in?
- ♪ I'm off to save the world ♪
- You know, if you drop that,
we're not going back for it, okay?
- It slipped.
- You kidding me?
Well, I guess he's gonna
have to fend for himself now.
Turn around!
Welcome to the school of life, kid.
You fuck up, you pay the price.
- I want it back!
- Come on.
- What? No. Hey.
- Turn around!
Damn it! Hey!
Ah, get off me!
Bobby!
You okay?
What the hell is wrong with you, Bobby?
You almost got us killed.
When I tell you we're not
going back for a toy,
what do you think that means?
What do you think it means?
Huh?!
That we're not going back for the toy!
We've got people chasing us now!
You understand?
Jesus, Dad.
Leave him alone.
Hey.
- Sorry. I'm sorry.
- I hate you. I hate you!
- I'm sorry.
- I hate you!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I want to go back to Mom!
I'm sorry.
I miss Mom!
He s-said he just wanted to talk,
so I let him in, and then
he started acting really weird.
He shined a-a penlight in my eye.
Then he said...
he knew I was one of them.
O-One of what?
- I don't know.
- We don't know.
I don't know what that means.
Said he was gonna save the boys.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
I know this is difficult.
I don't...
They could be anywhere.
Hi.
I'm Malik's parole officer.
I called this in.
Your office said he missed a psych eval.
Yeah, I've been trying to track him down.
And you waited 24 hours?
Well, Malik wasn't deemed a flight risk.
Ma'am, if you don't mind
waiting over there,
we can talk when we're done here.
Thank you.
So, what is this...
what is this about a psych evaluation?
I'm Special Agent Lance Dunn
from the FBI Child Abduction
Rapid Deployment team.
Hattie Hayes, Shasta County Parole.
I'm just plain old Shep.
What sort of cases do you work, Hattie?
Uh, mostly drug and thug.
And, uh, what can you tell us
about our kidnapper?
He grew up in foster care,
not all of it good.
Uh, staff sergeant
in the Marine Raider Unit.
Did about ten tours in all.
He was court-martialed
for beating up his captain.
Broke the guy's jaw
into five pieces.
Had to be put in a medically
induced coma for a week.
Malik did two years, Leavenworth.
That's right.
And your experience with him?
He was... uh, he was very polite.
Called me "ma'am."
Not everybody does that.
But he...
he seemed like a good guy.
That's your assessment?
That he seemed like a good guy?
Excuse me. I'm a good judge of character.
Everybody thinks they're
a good judge of character.
Well, I turn over
about 120 clients a year.
Been doing this for 18 years.
So that's...
Well, that's a lot of cases.
And I have to look each and
every one of them in the eye
to see if I can find the good in 'em,
'cause that's what I do... that's my job.
I think it's very sweet
that you're one of those
"benefit of the doubt" POs,
but by not putting out
an arrest warrant straightaway,
you exponentially increased the risk
of these boys being hurt or killed.
Malik is not gonna hurt anyone,
least of all his boys.
Lance, you do us a favor
and, uh, check and see
if the tech's finished up.
We're gonna head out in five.
Mm.
What's up with Johnny Utah?
Hattie, we have, uh...
...strong reasons to believe
that Malik might be
a family annihilator.
- That's...
- I know what it is.
But you don't buy it.
Unfortunately, he checks
a lot of these boxes.
Separated from wife, isolated from kids.
Dishonorably discharged
from the one thing that he was good at.
He's got no benefits,
no health care, no pension.
Nothing.
Then you put him on the inside
for a couple of years
to ferment.
Resentment, rage.
You add PTSD into the mix,
what do you got?
A ticking time bomb.
He packed no clothes.
No toys for the kids.
Not even a toothbrush.
But you know what he did have?
He had a gun.
Now, what's a convicted felon doing
purchasing a firearm?
You're a parole officer.
But he loves his boys.
Practically all annihilators
are considered loving fathers.
That's why nobody sees it coming.
If we don't stop Malik,
he's gonna execute those boys.
And then he's gonna turn
the gun on himself.
Because that's the ultimate revenge.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Clip goes in.
Yep. Rack it.
Okay? It's ready to go.
Finger off the trigger.
You're gonna line up the target
between these two sights.
Squeeze.
How was that?
You're not scared of it.
You find something trying
to kill you, you kill it first.
Not that high.
Let it go.
Okay, Jay, let's go.
Spotted some aliens! Shoot! Get 'em!
This rescue operation
extends to all adjacent states.
You guys know what to do.
Make the calls.
Scan every pixel of CCTV
at every gas station and every ATM.
Now, it's likely that Malik
has manipulated his children
and they have no idea the kind
of danger that they're in.
In fact, they probably think
he's the greatest father in the world.
Now, we've put the Amber Alert out,
but Malik Khan has a 22-hour lead on us,
and that is a scary head start,
so we need to tighten the net real quick.
He is a desperate man,
and he's willing to take
desperate measures.
And he can turn on them at any moment.
Hey, baby.
Ma, you made it.
Sorry I'm late, baby. You winning?
- I got two strikes.
- Damn, girl.
Look at you, with your little
cute self. Go get 'em.
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
Don't worry, I've been
pretending to be you,
so we're actually doing pretty good.
Eh, you-you okay?
Who got on the wrong side of you today?
I'm the one on the wrong side.
I gave somebody the benefit of the doubt
that I shouldn't have.
Well, hey, you can't be right
all the time, baby.
Yeah, but...
this guy could be bad news.
Huh.
How bad?
As bad as they come.
Little dude is combustible,
just like me.
Not you, though. You're something else.
I'm not tough, if that's what you mean.
Yo.
Keeping a level head when
all hell's breaking loose...
that's a special kind of tough.
That's why we need you around.
I need you.
And you're humble, too.
And good-looking.
And the girls
are gonna love you.
Be chasing you around the playground.
Huh?
Dad?
Do you still love Mom?
Yeah.
Of course I do.
We had some good years
alongside those tough ones.
Hell...
I ever tell you first time we met?
No.
- Want to know?
- Yeah.
Okay, don't laugh at me.
Okay, I'll try not to.
Okay, screw it. You can laugh.
A buddy of mine wants
to take me to a dance.
Okay? I'd just come back off tour.
It's not gonna go well.
Uh...
- Dude, you suck at dancing.
- I know.
But I want to go, so I go
and I get all loaded up to loosen up.
Okay, but...
an hour later, I've sunk
about a dozen whiskeys.
And now I'm all in, dude.
I'm throwing all kinds of shapes.
I'm doing stuff you've never seen before.
Like what?
Well, they're brand-new.
They're copyrighted.
I can't tell you.
I get a little excited.
I decide to try a backflip.
I kick your mom in the head.
Dude, what?
I hit her right in the head,
dude, with my boot.
What is wrong with you?
I know.
Hey, hey, you see that?
What?
Meteors.
I don't see anything.
What, are you blind?
There must be a hundred of 'em.
It's beautiful.
Couple of hours, all that's
gonna be in the ecosystem.
Let's get back on the road.
You put that spray on, Jay.
You got to stay safe.
Yep. Let's get you inside.
- Dad.
- Yeah?
You kidding me?
You got a spare?
$500 cars don't come with spares.
Raúl?
Hattie.
Sorry I'm late.
You want something?
Th-They're about to close.
Whatever he's having.
- Thank you.
- Right.
Thanks for coming.
No problem.
So you said, uh...
Malik kidnapped his boys?
- Yeah.
- Here you go.
Thanks.
I'm just...
trying to figure out what triggered him.
You guys were close, right?
Yeah.
Very.
Been through hell and back together.
What kind of Marine was he?
Malik was a fucking badass.
But, uh, he also knew how to...
turn it on and off.
What about the assault?
That was completely out of character.
I mean, you got to take into account
what we were going through.
We'd been in three different
firefights that day.
We seen two of our buddies get ripped up.
It's 120 degrees out.
We're getting eaten alive by bugs.
The stress level's just...
Unimaginable.
Yeah, it was.
We found some children in the wreckage.
Then his whole fucking world
came tumbling down.
Uh, you mentioned some letters.
Yeah, about a year ago...
I got these.
He sent me hundreds and hundreds of them.
Pretty out there stuff.
Obviously, I thought he was
having some kind of breakdown.
Oh, my God.
You got to look for a motel.
You got to look for a service station.
You got to look for someplace
we can pull off, okay?
We're still a long way from base.
- Dad?
- Yeah.
If half the world are aliens,
how come nothing's been on TV?
You kidding me? They're not
there to tell us the truth.
So the government knows?
The government probably got turned first.
Think about it.
Has anyone else seen one of these meteors?
Like, wouldn't there be
videos of them online?
Wouldn't NASA know about them?
They take all that stuff down.
Why would they take it down?
You think I'm making it up.
No.
You don't seem so sure.
It's just a lot to take in.
Yeah...
I know it's a lot.
Open your eyes.
- Dad, stop.
- Open your eyes. Huh?
- Ow. Ah.
- Can you hold still?
- I'm trying to protect you.
- Stop.
Stop!
Stop hurting my brother.
Stay in the car. Pack up all the gear.
Yeah.
Easy, now.
Two boys, eight and ten.
A 38-year-old male, armed and dangerous,
driving a blue Cherokee
with California plates.
Our car broke down.
So you were fixing to take mine?
Not trying to hurt anybody.
That gun in your back pocket loaded?
Yeah.
So there's that.
Were you in the military?
Not the one you're talking about.
I did ten tours.
Yeah? Whose side were you on?
Side that gave me a Bronze Star.
Yeah, well, you can put
whiskers on a snake
and call it a kitty.
Don't mean it ain't gonna bite.
I could just leave, go ahead
and walk to the next town.
You could've done that,
but you chose to come in here,
onto my property.
And that's a hell of a mistake
when you've got a $10,000
reward on your head.
But then I don't hold much esteem
for the federal government.
So why don't you take a seat
at the table there,
and maybe there's a way we both
can come out of this on top.
You think Dad shot an alien?
What are you doing?
I'm calling base.
Malik?
It's Jay, his son.
Is this base?
Base? Uh, no.
I'm Hattie Hayes.
I'm your father's parole officer.
My dad was in prison?
Jay, honey, I need to know
exactly where you are.
We entered Nevada a few miles back.
How many miles was that?
How do I know you're not an alien?
Alien?
Okay, Jay, honey, uh, listen.
You've been kidnapped,
and your mom is-is terribly...
Is my mom okay?
Yes, your mom is fine, honey. She...
Come on, let's get in the car.
Come on, let's get in the car!
Did you shoot an alien?
Yeah, a big mean one.
Dad, are you okay?
It's just a flesh wound.
I'll clean it up later.
Think it's about time
you learned how to drive.
You can't fuck it up. It's automatic.
Okay, right is accelerate.
Left is brake.
"D" is drive.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa. Okay.
Now split the difference.
You're doing great, Jay.
Come on.
Jay, lay that down.
Dad, whose house is this?
I don't know, Jay. It's abandoned.
Lay down.
Go to sleep now.
Plain old Shep.
How you doing, Hattie?
How'd you get in the building?
I know people.
No need, really, to come all this way.
I mean, uh, thank you
for relaying the information, but...
I want to come with you.
Excuse me?
You can't come, Hattie.
Shep, please. I-I don't think
we're dealing with a family annihilator.
I think Malik might be suffering
from an undiagnosed psychotic disorder.
So you're a psychiatrist now.
No, but I spoke to his Marine buddy,
who was sent these.
Now, Malik's son asked me
if I was an alien.
Maybe Malik's not out to hurt his boys.
Maybe he thinks he's on some
sort of mission to save 'em.
Yeah, maybe, and maybe
makes him more dangerous.
I mean, what if Malik goes
into a 7-Eleven,
sees a cashier that's looking
at him a little funny,
shoots him 'cause he thinks he's an alien?
What if he thinks his boys
are aliens, shoots them?
It doesn't change what I have to do.
But, surely, it changes
how you engage him.
With all due respect, I've been
doing this for 20 years.
I know his profile.
I am not gonna antagonize the man.
Whoa, whoa. I'm not doubting
you know how to do your job,
but I am saying Malik called me
and his son called me,
so I'm an asset to you.
Why not bring me along just for the ride?
And if you need me, I'm there.
And if you don't,
I just sit in the back seat,
keep my mouth shut, learn from the best.
Oh, shit.
Whose piece-of-shit car
is that out front?
I don't know.
Dad?
Hurry up, man. Let's go.
Hey.
Dad?
Dad!
Oh, fuck.
Kurt, call an ambulance!
What are you doing just sitting there?
- Call an ambulance!
- Oh, my God.
Oh, Dad, Dad, Dad.
You okay?
Someone did this to you?
- Yeah.
- Who did it?
Is he turning into an alien?
It's just a flesh wound, Bobby.
He needs to rest.
Jay, where are we?
Don't know.
Come on.
You think the aliens ate our food?
Probably.
Aliens like Pop-Tarts?
Everyone likes Pop-Tarts, Bobby.
- Hey.
- I'm hungry.
I know.
Let's see if we can find
something to eat, yeah?
How?
Nice one.
Jay, do you think there was a war here?
Yeah.
I found a kitchen, Jay.
Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, what are you doing?
Gonna win! Gonna win!
Gonna win!
Hah, I won.
Ooh, you can go all the way up there?
Look. What do you think that is?
- That?
- Yeah.
Looks like an elephant
that just swallowed a duck.
Come on. Let's see
if there's a shop nearby.
What should we get?
Spaghetti and meatballs.
What do you think?
Uh, ice cream.
Salt and vinegar chips.
What about marshmallows?
You go buy us something to eat,
and I'll get some medicine for Dad.
You only got ten dollars, remember.
Come on, at least five bucks more.
Howdy.
Hey.
What can I do you for?
Well, my dad got bit by a dog,
and he has a tooth stuck in him.
That sounds kind of serious.
Do you want me to call you an ambulance?
No, no, it's not that bad.
Just...
medium bad.
He just needs something for the pain.
Well, if you say so.
$9.40.
Keep the change.
Well, I hope he feels...
...kidnapped his two boys.
A multiagency task force
is looking for them.
Malik Khan assaulted two men,
a state trooper in Northern California
and a man in Vulture, Nevada.
Both men are recovering in the hospital.
Khan served two years in prison,
and he is considered armed and dangerous.
It is believed Malik...
Hey.
You're not driving this, are you, son?
No. No, no way.
Kids can't drive.
I'm waiting on my brother.
Um, you're not in any kind
of trouble, are you, son?
No.
'Cause you can tell me if you are.
But I'm not.
Nice chatting with you.
Dex!
911. What's your emergency?
Hi. Uh, I've just had a child
walk into my pharmacy.
He, um... I think he's in danger.
He handed me money
with blood splattered over it.
Uh, he-he looked like
he wanted to say something
but didn't know how.
Okay.
He was sitting in the driver seat
of a burgundy car.
It's not real. It's not real.
It's not real.
That's Dad's fucking car.
Turn around!
Drive slow. We don't want them to see us.
You think Dad's gonna be okay?
Jay.
Listen, Bobby.
I think we need to call Mom.
But... but she's an alien.
What if Dad made it all up?
Think about it.
Aliens taking over the world?
You just said they ate our Pop-Tarts.
Do you think aliens eat Pop-Tarts?
Are you that stupid?
Get off me!
Ouch.
You okay, Bobby?
Bobby?
Bobby!
I hate you!
Bobby, I'm heading back.
I need to check on Dad.
Hey, Jay.
Where you been, buddy?
Bobby okay?
He's fine.
I got some things for you.
Look at you.
Driving all by yourself, huh?
You gonna be okay?
The bleeding stopped. I'll live.
Come here.
Hey. Come here.
I need to talk to you.
What's wrong?
I know you've been lying to us.
You weren't on a secret mission
all those years.
You were in prison.
You've been lying
about aliens coming down.
That's not the whole picture, okay?
Stay away from me.
Easy. Easy.
Easy.
I was in prison.
I hid that from you.
I was trying to make it easier on you.
Maybe I was trying
to make it easier on me, too.
I've been confused, Jay.
Up here.
You know?
I'm seeing things that's not there.
You're lying.
You've been lying this whole time!
Malik Khan!
We're here to arrest you
for the abduction of your two sons,
the assault of Grant Healy
and the theft of his motor vehicle!
Now, come out with your hands
above your head!
Down.
Fucking asshole!
You want to shoot a ten-year-old boy?
Now, stay put and watch my six.
Hey. Okay.
Get away from the window. Stay low.
Where's my gun?
In the car.
I want you to stay in here.
Stay low, okay?
Dwight!
Stop!
Sit down.
Okay. Wait here.
- How high can you count?
- 300.
Okay. I want you to count to 600.
I'll be back.
One, two, three,
four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten,
11, 12, 13,
14, 15, 16,
17, 18...
Drop it.
Drop it!
Get back in the house.
Step forward.
Why are you coming after me?
You attacked our dad.
He shot at me.
In his home.
Is that water?
Can I have some, please?
Easy. Easy.
I need you to take your shirt off.
384, 385,
386,
387...
388,
389,
390, 391, 392,
393, 394...
You okay?
Yeah.
I'm gonna make things right.
How do you like
these new wheels, boys?
Cool upgrade, huh?
Were they aliens?
Yeah, Bobby.
Mean, ugly ones.
Let me speak to them now.
Let me speak to my babies
to make sure they're...
I can't, Piya.
I can't. Not now.
No, you put them on the phone.
You got the address.
You'll see 'em soon.
What, you're going to
leave them there and drive...
I don't know, but I'm not
going back to prison.
What does that mean?
What does that even mean, Malik?
Piya, I got to go.
- I'm sorry.
- Do not hang up on me.
Don't you dare hang up on me.
Two buffalo burgers.
Okay, I got good news and bad news.
Want to hear the good news?
Mom and Dylan are cured.
They said they can't wait to see you
and they love you more
than anything in the world.
What's the bad news?
Bad news is I got to keep fighting.
Yeah.
Don't worry about it.
A buddy of mine works here.
He's undercover.
He's gonna keep an eye on y'all.
You just got to stay here, and
somebody's gonna come get you.
Can you do that?
We can do that.
I'm gonna miss you, Dad.
I'll miss you, too.
Three Musketeers.
Come on.
Go, man.
This is for ice cream.
You can have as much as you goddamn want.
- Do you really mean it, Dad?
- Yeah.
You earned it.
Hey.
Take care of your brother.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey.
Jay, I...
I told you to take care of your brother.
What the fuck, Jay?
He's not the one that needs looking after.
Oh, fuck.
Jay, get up here.
Does he have
the boy in the vehicle?
Yeah, he's in the vehicle.
Great. Keep that chopper close.
If he thinks about making a move,
I want to know about it.
He's following us.
Okay, hold on.
- Fuck!
- Dad, we need to stop.
I can't stop now, Jay.
Come get it!
Dad, stop!
- Whose side are you on?
- Yours, Dad.
Whoa!
Yeah!
Shep, do you need
a whole arsenal aimed at him?
It's standard procedure, Hattie.
He's an armed and dangerous individual.
There's a ten-year-old boy in there.
That's who I'm worried about.
- Shep...
- Let Shepard do his thing.
What?
I'm Special Agent Shepard West.
It's nice to meet you, sir.
Nice to meet you, too.
- What do you want?
- I just want you to know
that I'm here to try to help you
and get this situation resolved
as peacefully as possible.
Now, there's no media here.
It's not looking too peaceful
pointing all that hardware at my boy.
So how about you take a look
at that first?
Okay, I'll do that.
Everybody, guns down!
- I said stand down! Weapons down!
- Weapons down.
It's okay.
I'm sorry about that, Malik,
but I'm gonna need you
to do the same thing for me.
If you could surrender your weapon and...
Hey, hey, hey.
You try and insult my intelligence again,
I'm gonna do something real fucking stupid
in your direction, you understand me?
Trust me, I just don't want
anyone to get hurt.
Why the fuck should I trust you, huh?
We're done.
Okay, who do you trust?
Do you trust your PO?
My... What, Hattie?
Yeah. She's standing by.
Well, then, asshole, put her on.
Okay, I'm gonna do that now.
Malik?
Oh, Hattie.
Came all this way for me, huh?
I fucked up, Hattie.
I dug myself in pretty deep.
I, uh...
I can see that.
But there's still a way out.
Ah, not for me.
- I deserve what's coming.
- I have to disagree with you.
Your mind has played
a horrible trick on you, Malik,
and everybody's gonna take that
into account, okay?
Everybody's gonna take that into account.
See, there are some things
going on in your head
that you're not in control of.
But, Malik, your boys need you
now more than ever, okay?
If we do this thing right...
Listen to me.
If we do this thing right,
you will always be a hero to your sons.
- Move in, move in.
- No! No!
Go, go!
You trying to fuck me, Hattie?
- No, Malik...
- Huh? You trying to fuck me?!
You're trying to fuck me.
Hold your positions!
Malik! Let Jay out of
the car so we can resolve this.
You've got one more minute.
Hey, Jay.
Thank you for coming out here
to take care of me.
You did a good job, okay?
You did great.
I need you to run off now.
Hmm.
Get out of the car.
Get out of the car!
I'm not going without you.
Families take care of each other.
I didn't take care of you.
I put you in danger.
You put your trust in me.
And I lied to you.
Look where I got us to.
And it weren't you
that did those bad things.
It was the demons inside of you.
But you're a hero to me, Dad.
Charlie
Six, you're green. Move in.
Get back!
Kid's got a gun.
Kid's got a gun. Put it down!
Don't shoot.
- Do not fucking shoot.
- Hey!
Hey, hey, hey! Hey, over here!
Over here!
Get back!
Put it down! Get back!
Over here! I'm over here!
Put it down!
Kid's armed.
- Drop it.
- Get back!
Back up! Put it down!
- Jay!
- They're gonna shoot you!
Not if you're here with me, they won't.
Put it down, Jay.
Look at me. Look at me.
Come here.
Come here, baby. Come here.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/9cjb6
Help other users to choose the best subtitles