( theme music playing )
OpenSubtitles recommends using PureVPN
From 1.99 USD/Month -> bit.ly/getpvpn
( phone ringing )
THE "BOUQUET" RESIDENCE,
THE LADY OF THE HOUSE SPEAKING.
DO I SOUND
LIKE A CHINESE TAKE-AWAY?
I AM A HIGHLY DESIRABLE
PRIVATE RESIDENCE
IN AN AREA OF OUTSTANDING
NATURAL PROPERTY VALUES.
AND I'M WAITING
FOR YOUR APOLOGY,
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
THE THOUGHT OF BEAN SHOOTS
AND CRISPY WON TON
HAVE TOTALLY STIR-FRIED
YOUR BASIC GOOD MANNERS.
NOW, KINDLY
CLEAR THIS LINE.
THERE ARE PEOPLE OF SUBSTANCE
IN THIS COMMUNITY
WHO ARE PROBABLY QUEUING
TO RING ME AT THIS VERY MOMENT.
YOUR SUGGESTION
IS NOTED,
BUT I SEE LITTLE
PRACTICAL MERIT
IN HAVING THE TELEPHONE
UP MY JUMPER.
I'VE JUST BEEN INSULTED
ON MY OWN TELEPHONE.
I EXPECT
THE OPPORTUNITIES ARE RARE
OF BEING INSULTED
ON OTHER PEOPLE'S.
I THINK
IT'S TIME, RICHARD,
THAT YOU COMPLAINED.
ABOUT WHAT?
ABOUT THESE WRONG NUMBERS
FOR THE CHINESE TAKE-AWAY.
YOU MUST RING
THE AMBASSADOR.
WHAT AMBASSADOR?
THE CHINESE, OF COURSE.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S REALLY HIS PROVINCE.
- THEN WHAT'S HE HERE FOR?
- PROBABLY FOR MORE THAN THAT.
THEY'RE A VERY
ANCIENT CIVILIZATION.
OH, RICHARD,
DON'T JUST SIT THERE,
GET DIRECTORY
INQUIRIES.
THAT'S IT!
FINISHED!
NO MORE MEN.
ENOUGH'S ENOUGH.
IN THE END,
THEY ALL DECEIVE YOU.
AFTER ALL I'VE
DONE FOR THAT SWINE,
TO LEAVE ME
FOR ANOTHER WOMAN,
I DON'T CARE
IF SHE IS HIS WIFE.
WELL, IT'S OVER.
I'VE LEARNED MY LESSON.
I ONLY WANT ONE.
I WISH YOU'D
FIND YOURSELF
A NICE STEADY BLOKE.
GIVE YOUR HORMONES
A CHANCE TO SETTLE.
STOP LIVING
ON YOUR NERVES...
AND MY FAGS.
MY HORMONES
HAVE SETTLED!
I'VE FINISHED--
NO MORE MEN!
THE SWINE!
HE SWORE HE'D LOVE ME
TILL THE END OF TIME!
I DIDN'T REALIZE
HE MEANT CLOSING TIME.
GO ON THEN,
READ ME SOME BOOK.
"'I LOVE YOU'
HE SAID,
LIFTING HER GENTLY
ONTO THE BALCONY.
'OH, JEREMY,'
SHE SAID."
OH, CHUFFIN' HECK.
HELLO!
GOOD MORNING,
MR. PENWORTHY.
MRS. BUCKET.
- "BOUQUET."
- WERE YOU GOING TOO FAST?
IT'S THE MODERN DISEASE.
HAVE YOU HURT YOURSELF?
I DO HOPE YOU'VE SUSTAINED
NO INJURY.
NO, THANK YOU,
I'M FINE.
YOUR WAVING
DISTRACTED ME.
REALLY?
I'D ASK YOU IN,
ONLY MY HUSBAND'S BUSY
ON THE TELEPHONE
WITH THE CHINESE AMBASSADOR.
I WONDER IF I
MIGHT ASK YOU
NOT TO COUGH
OR SNEEZE TOO LOUDLY.
MY HUSBAND'S ON THE TELEPHONE
WITH THE CHINESE AMBASSADOR.
THEY'RE A VERY ANCIENT
CIVILIZATION.
WELL,
WHAT DID HE SAY?
I HAD TO LEAVE A MESSAGE.
IT WAS AN ANSWERING MACHINE.
OH, WAS IT
A CULTURED VOICE?
- YES.
- WELL, THAT'S IT, THEN.
YOU'VE BEEN SPEAKING
TO THE AMBASSADOR.
I HARDLY THINK SO.
NOW, DON'T CONTRADICT ME,
RICHARD,
IT'S VERY TIRING.
YOU OUGHT TO BE
VERY PLEASED
THAT YOU'RE
ON CHATTING TERMS
WITH THE CHINESE
AMBASSADOR.
- WHO IS?
- WE ARE.
YOU LEFT A MESSAGE
ON HIS MACHINE,
THEREFORE,
HE WILL RING US BACK.
I MUST TELL
MY SHERIDAN.
NO SIGN OF HER.
LET'S GET IN THE CAR
AND AWAY
BEFORE SHE SPOTS US.
YOU'RE GETTING PARANOID
ABOUT HYACINTH.
WHICH SEEMS A VERY
SENSIBLE WAY TO BE.
- NOT SO LOUD.
- EMMET, I'M AT MY OWN HOME
IN BROAD DAYLIGHT.
I SEE NO REASON
TO CREEP ABOUT.
I CAN GIVE YOU
ONE DAMN GOOD REASON
TO CREEP ABOUT.
NO, I'VE GOT
A BETTER IDEA.
LET'S FREEWHEEL
DOWN THE DRIVE
AND START THE CAR
IN THE STREET.
- THERE ISN'T ANY SLOPE.
- I'LL GIVE YOU A PUSH.
- EMMET!
- IT'S WORTH IT, LIZ!
BELIEVE ME,
IT'S WORTH IT.
IF SHE SPOTS US SHE'LL WANT
TO KNOW WHERE WE'RE GOING.
YOU'LL TELL HER
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T LIE.
WHY IS IT?
YOU'RE A GROWN WOMAN
AND YOU CAN'T LIE?
HAVING TROUBLE
WITH THE CAR?
I'LL GET RICHARD
TO GIVE YOU A HAND.
THAT'S IF HE'S FINISHED
HIS DIPLOMATIC CALL.
IT'S ALL RIGHT,
HYACINTH, HONESTLY.
NO, I WON'T
BE DISSUADED.
THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS
ARE FOR.
* PEOPLE,
PEOPLE WHO NEED PEOPLE *
* ARE THE LUCKIEST
PEOPLE... *
QUICK,
START THE CAR!
IT'S TOO LATE NOW.  WE'LL HAVE
TO GO THROUGH WITH IT.
I'LL GO WHERE THERE
ARE NO MEN.
I'LL EMIGRATE
SOMEWHERE DESOLATE,
WITH NONE
OF THE CREATURE COMFORTS
SCRUB THAT,
TOO MUCH LIKE HOME.
MEN!
HOW CAN YOU GO ON
READING ROMANTIC DRIVEL
WHEN YOU KNOW
WHAT MEN ARE LIKE?
IN THIS BOOK,
THEY'RE TERRIFIC.
JEREMY HAS HAIR
LIKE GOLDEN CORN.
HE'S TALL
AND SLENDER,
A MAGNIFICENT FIGURE
ON A HORSE.
SO HOW COME I'M STILL
IN LOVE WITH ONSLOW?
YOU MUST BE COMING
UNGLUED IN THE HEAD.
- ANY MORE CRISPS?
- GET 'EM YOURSELF.
IT'S ALL RIGHT,
I'LL GET THEM.
YOU'D THINK HIS HAIR
WAS LIKE GOLDEN CORN.
SMOKEY BACON FLAVOR.
THERE'S NO SMOKEY
BACON FLAVOR LEFT!
OH, NICE.
IT COULD BE
THE ALTERNATOR.
RIGHT.
TRY NOW, LIZ.
( engine starts )
- WELL DONE, RICHARD.
- YES, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I DIDN'T
DO MUCH, REALLY.
DON'T BE SO MODEST.
IT WAS VERY
KIND OF YOU.
- I DON'T THINK I DID ANYTHING.
- YOU DID ENOUGH, DEAR.
AND NOW ELIZABETH
AND EMMET
CAN BE OFF TO WHERE
THEY'RE GOING.
WHEREVER THAT IS.
- ARE YOU GOING FAR?
- NO, NOT FAR.
WELL, THAT'S VERY
MYSTERIOUS.
IS IT A VERY
INTERESTING "NOT FAR"?
IT'S JUST
THE CHURCH HALL,
HYACINTH.
OH, THE CHURCH HALL.
I DIDN'T KNOW
THERE WAS A FUNCTION.
NO, NO, NO,
NOT A FUNCTION, REALLY.
AH--
THE VICAR ASKED EMMET
IF HE'D JUST--
J-JUST A BIT MUSIC
FOR FULL-GROWN PEOPLE.
OH, EMMET,
WHAT A GOOD IDEA.
RICHARD,
WE'D BETTER GET ALONG.
MUSTN'T DELAY
THESE PEOPLE.
I THOUGHT SHE'D
PUSH HER WAY IN.
I COULD HAVE SWORN
SHE'D WANT TO SING.
WELL, THERE YOU ARE.
YOU'RE BEING UNFAIR TO HER.
I'VE JUST HAD
A WONDERFUL IDEA!
WHY DON'T
I JOIN YOU?
YOU PLAY
AND I'LL SING.
FOR THE OLD PEOPLE,
BLESS THEM.
HOW THEY'LL ENJOY IT.
I'LL RING
THE VICAR NOW
AND I'LL SEE YOU
AT THE CHURCH HALL.
( humming )
* LA-DEE-DAH-- *
OH, MAY I SPEAK
TO THE VICAR, PLEASE?
NOT AVAILABLE,
IS HE BUSY?
OH, RINGING THE BELLS,
OH.
RINGS HIS OWN BELLS,
HOW DEMOCRATIC.
OH, I CAN JUST PICTURE
THE VICAR AT THE END
OF HIS ROPE.
NOW, I ASSUME I'M SPEAKING
TO THE VICAR'S WIFE.
YES, YOU REMEMBER ME,
DEAR?
HYACINTH "BOUQUET."
THAT IS A BAD COUGH, DEAR.
HAS SOMETHING
GONE DOWN THE WRONG WAY?
I WANT YOU TO PASS
A LITTLE MESSAGE
TO THE VICAR,
HE'LL BE THRILLED.
WE HAVE A SURPRISE
FOR THE OLD PEOPLE'S
ENTERTAINMENT.
TELL THE VICAR THAT IT
WON'T JUST BE PIANOFORTE,
I'VE VOLUNTEERED
MY SERVICES TO SING.
YOU MUST TAKE SOMETHING
FOR THAT COUGH, DEAR.
THE BUCKET WOMAN!
( gasps )
HE'LL GO MAD
WHEN I TELL HIM
IT'S THE BUCKET WOMAN.
( bells ringing )
THE BUCKET WOMAN!
( bells jangle )
( Hyacinth humming )
* LA-- *
WHICH SHALL I WEAR, DEAR?
OH, I WISH YOU
WOULDN'T GIVE ME THAT KIND
OF RESPONSIBILITY.
YOU KNOW I VALUE
YOUR OPINION, RICHARD.
SINCE WHEN?
- I'LL WEAR THIS ONE.
- GLAD I SORTED THAT
OUT FOR YOU.
- AH, I'LL ANSWER IT.
* LA-LA-DA-DEE *
* LA-DOE-DA-DEE. *
THE "BOUQUET" RESIDENCE,
THE LADY OF THE HOUSE SPEAKING.
RICHARD?
OH YES, HE'S HERE.
SHE'LL FIND OUT
SOONER OR LATER.
- WHY DID YOU TELL HER?
- I HAD TO TELL HER.
I MEAN,
YOU WERE THERE.
SHE PRACTICALLY
DRAGGED IT OUT OF ME.
ONE MORE HESITATION,
SHE'D HAVE TORN OUT
MY FINGERNAILS.
YOU COULD HAVE LIED.
WELL, YOU KNOW HOW BAD
I AM AT LYING.
I'LL TEACH YOU.
OH, EMMET,
JUST MAKE THE BEST OF IT.
IT'S FOR THE OLD PEOPLE.
OF WHOM I'M GOING TO BE ONE
BEFORE THIS IS OVER.
WELL, BE FAIR TO HER.
SHE'S GOT A RICH
STRONG VOICE.
IT'S NOT THE VOICE,
IT'S WHO'S
IN CHARGE OF IT.
( humming )
OH, WHO WAS IT,
DEAR?
IT WAS THE HEAD
OF MY DEPARTMENT.
OH, THAT'S NICE, DEAR.
THEY'RE THINKING
OF OFFERING
- SOME PEOPLE
EARLY RETIREMENT.
- HMM?
HE WANTS TO KNOW
HOW I FEEL
ABOUT EARLY
RETIREMENT.
OH, RICHARD!
THAT MEANS WE'D BE TOGETHER
ALL DAY AND EVERY DAY!
( singing )
( dramatic music playing
on television )
WELL,
HOW DO I LOOK?
GREAT.
- HOW DO I LOOK?
- FINE.
THERE'S ONLY THE DOG
PAYING ANY ATTENTION.
DID SOMEBODY
TURN THE SET OFF?
ROSE TURNED
THE SET OFF.
THANK GOD FOR THAT,
I THOUGHT I'D GONE BLIND.
COULD YOU SPARE ME
ONE MOMENT OF YOUR TIME?
IT'S IMPORTANT
TO ME.
HOW DO I LOOK?
FIGURE IN BLACK.
I'VE SEEN IT SOMEWHERE.
WEREN'T YOU IN FRANKENSTEIN'S
HOUSE OF HORRORS?
( TV playing )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
ALL DRESSED IN BLACK?
PRACTICING.
I'M TAKING THE VEIL,
I'M GOING
TO BE A NUN.
YOUR SKIRT'S
TOO SHORT.
I'LL HAVE IT
LENGTHENED.
TALK ABOUT POACHER
TURNING GAMEKEEPER,
THEY'LL NEVER
TAKE YOU FOR A NUN.
THEY MIGHT
IF I CAN GET
A RECOMMENDATION
FROM A CLERGYMAN.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
A CLERGYMAN.
OH, I MET THAT DISHY VICAR
AT OUR HYACINTH'S.
THEY WAY YOU THREW
YOURSELF AT HIM,
HE'LL NEVER RECOMMEND
YOU FOR A NUN.
YOU'RE TOO EMOTIONAL,
OUR ROSE.
OH, I'VE TAKEN CARE
OF THAT.
I'VE TAKEN
A TRANQUILIZER.
IT SHOULD
SLOW ME DOWN
TO A MORE
RELIGIOUS SPEED.
I HOPE YOUR BRAKES
DON'T FAIL IN FRONT
OF THAT VICAR.
EARLY RETIREMENT...
RICHARD,
THE DOOR.
NO, DEAR,
THIS DOOR.
RICHARD, WHAT ON EARTH'S
THE MATTER WITH YOU, DEAR?
THE MATTER WITH ME?
NOTHING.
WHY SHOULD ANYTHING
BE THE MATTER?
( horn blares )
I SHALL START WITH A FEW
OF THE OLD FAVORITES.
THEY LOVE
THE OLD FAVORITES.
SHERIDAN ALWAYS LOVED
WE HAVE TO HAVE
A TALK, HYACINTH,
ABOUT EARLY
RETIREMENT.
AND FOR A FINALE
I THINK A MEDLEY
FROM "THE SOUND
OF MUSIC."
TURN LEFT HERE,
RICHARD.
FOR THAT I SHALL WEAR
MY AUSTRIAN HAT--
THE ONE
WITH THE FEATHER.
I WONDER IF EMMET
HAS ANY LEATHER SHORTS.
A TALK, I MEAN WITH ME
TALKING, TOO.
HE COULD HAVE,
YOU KNOW.
ANYONE WHO'S IN
AN OPERATIC SOCIETY
SHOULD HAVE
SOME LEATHER SHORTS.
OF COURSE HE'S PROBABLY
LEFT THEM BEHIND.
YOU COULD GO AND FETCH
THEM FOR HIM, RICHARD.
TURN LEFT, DEAR.
YOU'RE GOING TO PROMISE ME
THAT WHEN WE HAVE OUR TALK,
THAT YOU'LL MAKE AN EFFORT
AND TRY TO LISTEN
WHEN YOU'RE NOT ACTUALLY
SAYING ANYTHING.
RICHARD, ARE YOU LISTENING?
ARE YOU PAYING ATTENTION?
- YOU'VE NOT BEEN LISTENING.
- TURN RIGHT, DEAR.
WHAT ARE WE
DOING HERE?
YOU SAID
TURN RIGHT.
I MEANT RIGHT
AT THE NEXT JUNCTION.
YOU WERE GOING TO ALLOW ME
TO GO ALL THAT WAY
WITHOUT FURTHER
INSTRUCTIONS.
I WANT YOU TO START
REVERSING NOW, RICHARD.
THIS IS NOT
THE KIND OF AREA
IN WHICH I WISH
TO BE SEEN PARKING.
Vicar:
RIGHT, I'M OFF.
- DON'T I GET A KISS?
- OF COURSE YOU GET A KISS.
KEEP AWAY
FROM THE LADIES.
NOW, HOW CAN I
KEEP AWAY FROM THE LADIES?
98.5% OF MY CONGREGATION
ARE LADIES.
AND THEY ALL ADORE YOU.
INCLUDING ME.
- YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS.
- OF COURSE I'M JEALOUS.
KEEP AWAY
FROM THE LADIES.
I MUST GO.
AH!
NOW WHERE ARE THOSE
DATES FOR THE YOUTH CLUB?
WHY THE VICARAGE?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SINGING
AT THE CHURCH HALL.
WELL, I THOUGHT
I'D ASK THE VICAR
IF THERE WERE ANY LITTLE
FAVORITES HE WISHES ME
TO INCLUDE.
IT'S THE SORT OF COURTESY
HE WOULD EXPECT FROM ME.
( groans )
HAVEN'T YOU FORGOTTEN
SOMETHING, DEAR?
- HMM?
- THE DOOR.
EARLY RETIREMENT.
HMM?
OH, THAT WAS QUICK.
YOU SAID,
"KEEP AWAY FROM THE LADIES."
OH, I SEE.
I MEANT KEEP AWAY
FROM ALL OF THEM,
NOT JUST THAT ONE.
TELL HER I'VE BEEN
CALLED AWAY.
- WHERE TO?
- VLADIVOSTOK.
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER,
RICHARD.
WHATEVER'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
REALLYWANT TO KNOW?
OF COURSE
I WANT TO KNOW.
WHATEVER CONCERNS YOU
CONCERNS ME.
VERY WELL THEN,
I'LL TELL YOU.
THE THING THAT'S
BOTHERING ME--
YOU SEE HOW MUCH
BETTER IT IS WHEN WE
TALK THESE THINGS OUT.
I HAVEN'T STARTED YET.
THAT'S WHAT WIVES
ARE FOR--
TO LISTEN.
WELL,
YOU THINK OF ALL THE TERRIBLE
THINGS THAT CAN HAPPEN TO YOU
( bells ringing )
OH, MY GOODNESS,
LOOK AT THE TIME.
WE MUSTN'T KEEP EMMET WAITING,
HE'LL WANT TO REHEARSE.
I'LL TALK
TO THE VICAR LATER.
WE MUST GO STRAIGHT
TO THE CHURCH HALL!
* DO-DO-DO-DOOT-- *
YOU CAN'T HIDE
THERE ALL DAY.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
I'D BE SAFER IN THE KITCHEN.
I'LL HAVE ANOTHER
CUP OF COFFEE.
JUDGING BY THE LENGTH
OF HER SKIRT,
IT MUST BE ROSE
UNDERNEATH THAT VEIL.
WHAT WOULD ROSE
BE DOING HERE?
WOBBLING AS IF SHE'S
BEEN DRINKING,
WELL, SHE CAN WOBBLE OFF
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
I WILL NOT HAVE
A SISTER IN BLACK
WOBBLING
INTO OUR CHURCH.
ROSE!
INCREDIBLE.
YOU LOOK EXACTLY LIKE
MY SISTER HYACINTH.
ROSE, HAVE YOU
BEEN DRINKING?
I HAVEN'T
BEEN DRINKING.
I TOOK A PILL--
AND IT SEEMS TO HAVE GONE
STRAIGHT TO MY KNEES.
I WISH WE COULD SAY
THE SAME ABOUT YOUR SKIRT.
- WHY ARE YOU HERE?!
- I WANT TO SEE THE VICAR.
YOU'RE IN NO CONDITION
TO SEE THE VICAR.
I WANT TO BE A NUN.
PUT ME DOWN!
- I WANT TO BE A NUN!
- RICHARD, GIVE ME A HAND.
FUNNY HOW YOU
MISHEAR THINGS.
I COULD HAVE SWORN SHE SAID
SHE WANTED TO BE A NUN.
- I DO!  I DO!
- WE'LL HAVE TO
TAKE HER HOME.
THERE'S NO TIME.
OH, RICHARD,
DO REMEMBER WHERE YOU ARE.
WE HAVE TO HIDE HER
IN THE HALL UNTIL SHE
PULLS HERSELF TOGETHER.
PULL MYSELF TOGETHER?
GOOD GRIEF,
OUR HYACINTH,
YOU'RE NOT
EVEN SATISFIED
WHEN A PERSON
WANTS TO BE A NUN.
HOW TOGETHER
DO YOU HAVE TO GET?
Hyacinth:
NO, DON'T GET
IN THE WAY, RICHARD.
OH, MIND WHAT
YOU'RE DOING, DEAR!
ROSE!
I KNOW IT'S BEEN
A LIFETIME'S DEDICATION,
BUT I WISH YOU'D TRY
TO BREAK THIS HABIT
OF WANTING
TO LIE DOWN EVERYWHERE.
DO TRY AND STAY
ON YOUR FEET.
KNEES!
IF I'M GOING TO BE A NUN
I SHOULD BE ON MY KNEES.
IT'S ME THAT WILL
BE ON MY KNEES.
OH, RICHARD WANTS
TO BE A NUN, TOO.
SHE'S SURPRISINGLY
HEAVY
FOR A SHORT-SKIRTED
PERSON.
UHH!
HOW MANY PILLS
DID SHE TAKE?
( giggling )
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING,
THIS BEING A NUN
MAKES YOU FEEL REALLY GOOD.
I FEEL UPLIFTED!
( giggling )
LOOK, POP HER
IN THE STORE CUPBOARD,
UNTIL SHE GETS BACK
THE USE OF HER LEGS.
I CAN'T HAVE
HER SEEN LIKE THIS.
OH, DEAR.
OH, HYACINTH!
ELIZABETH, DEAR,
ABOUT OUR
LITTLE CONCERT,
I THOUGHT I'D BEGIN
WITH SOMETHING CLASSICAL.
I THINK EMMET'S ALREADY
GOT A PROGRAM IN MIND.
OH GOOD, AND THEN A SELECTION
FROM "THE SOUND OF MUSIC"
AND FINISH WITH
"ANNIE, GET YOUR GUN."
I'M NOT SURE
THAT EMMET WAS
QUITE THINKING
ALONG THOSE LINES.
OH, HE'LL LOVE IT.
EVERYBODY LOVES
MY ANNIE OAKLEY.
I THINK I'D BETTER
WARN HIM--
TELL HIM.
RICHARD,
HOW DO I LOOK, DEAR?
I KEEP SEEING YOU AS
A KIND OF RECURRING MOTIF
RUNNING THROUGH
MY EARLY RETIREMENT.
THAT'S NICE, DEAR.
- AND THE HAT,
HOW'S THE HAT?
- YES, THAT, TOO.
SHE'S GONE!
SHE WAS HERE.
SHE WAS HEADING THIS WAY,
AND NOW SHE'S GONE.
AND STILL THERE ARE PEOPLE
WHO REFUSE
TO BELIEVE
IN THE POWER OF PRAYER.
OFF YOU GO,
THEN.
AND KEEP AWAY
FROM THE LADIES.
( off-key )
* WITH A GUN *
NO, NO!
LOOK, SUPPORT ME, LOUDER.
PLUS FORTE!
* WITH A GUN *
* WITH A GUN-- *
NO, IT'S TOO LOUD, NOW.
PIANISSIMO.
* OH, YOU CAN'T
GET A MAN *
* A MAN--
A MAN-- *
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE
PLAYING THE RIGHT NOTE?
I SUPPOSE IRVING
KNEW WHAT HE WAS DOING.
* IF I WENT
TO BATTLE *
* WITH SOMEONE'S
HERD OF CATTLE *
* THERE'D BE ST-- *
NO!
HAVE YOU LOST
YOUR PLACE AGAIN?
I THOUGHT YOU HAD.
FROM THE BEGINNING.
* IF I WENT TO BATTLE *
* WITH SOMEONE'S HERD-- *
KEEP IT GOING!  FASTER!
* WHEN IT WAS DONE *
* THAT IF I SHOT THE HERDER
I'D HOLLER BLOODY MURDER-- *
LOOK, YOU TOLD ME
HE'D BEEN CERTIFICATED.
DA CAPO,
BACK TO THE BEGINNING,
PLEASE.
NO, NO!
ENOUGH!
THAT'S IT!
I'M ONLY FLESH AND BLOOD.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANY LONGER!
PSST!
WHAT IS IT HE CAN'T
TAKE ANY LONGER?
THE CHAIR.  HE'S GOT
THE WRONG SIZE CHAIR?
HE'S VERY PARTICULAR
ABOUT HIS CHAIR.
IT AFFECTS THE STYLE
OF HIS PLAYING.
WHY DON'T YOU GET
ANOTHER TYPE OF CHAIR.
( whispering )
TAKE A WALK OUTSIDE.
YES.
YES, I'LL--
I'LL GET
ANOTHER CHAIR!
OH, SHUT UP!
I'M SO SORRY ABOUT
THE INTERRUPTION,
HYACINTH.
OH, NO APOLOGY
NECESSARY.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO EXPLAIN TO ME
ABOUT THE LITTLE ERUPTIONS
OF THE ARTISTIC TEMPERAMENT.
I'M THE FIRST TO UNDERSTAND
ABOUT THE ARTISTIC TEMPERAMENT.
RICHARD WAS SAYING SO,
ONLY THIS MORNING
TO THE CHINESE
AMBASSADOR.
- ( giggling )
- ROSE!
SHE WAS IN THE ROOM
WITH THE CHAIRS!
( screams )
ROSE!  PUT MY ACCOMPANIST
DOWN AT ONCE!
THIS IS NO WAY
TO BEGIN YOUR VOCATION!
THE BUCKET WOMAN!
AH, VICAR!
VICAR, MY SISTER'S
HAD A CONVERSION,
PROFOUNDLY.
WHY DON'T YOU PLAY
"MISTY" FOR ME?
LET'S PUT HER BACK
IN THE CUPBOARD,AGAIN,
SHE CAN MEDITATE
IN THERE FOR A WHILE.
HAS ANYONE SEEN MY HUSBAND?
HE'S WANTED ON THE PHONE.
( crashing, clanking )
OH, VICAR!
EXCUSE ME!
WELL!
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO BE
A NUN.
( theme music playing )
OpenSubtitles recommends using PureVPN
From 1.99 USD/Month -> bit.ly/getpvpn