Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
When I was a little girl,
my understanding of revenge
was as simple
as the Sunday school proverbs
it hid behind.
Neat little morality slogans,
like "do unto others"
and "two wrongs
don't make a right."
♪ if you love me ♪
{Fireworks
popping and whistling}
But two wrongs
can never make a right
because two wrongs
can never equal each other.
{Whistling and popping
continues}
♪
For the truly wronged...
Real satisfaction
can only be found
in one of two places...
Absolute forgiveness...
Or mortal vindication.
♪
This is not a story
about forgiveness.
Emily.
♪
I've been looking for you.
Where's Daniel?
Uh, he's walking the beach.
We're having a thing.
Same thing
or different thing?
Same thing. But don't worry.
He's right behind me.
It's my job to worry.
Your job is to enjoy yourself.
It's your engagement party.
Can someone get me a 20
on Daniel Grayson?
Hey, congrats, Emily.
Thank you.
♪
Nice night for it.
Nice night for what,
Nolan?
Celebrating.
You shouldn't be here.
That makes two of us.
Emily,
where have you been hiding?
Come on.
Let's see that ring, girl.
Hi.
{Indistinct conversations
continue}
♪
I feel like a jackass
in this tux.
Well, stop acting like one,
and you'll stop
feeling like one.
Trust me. If your friends
could see you now...
I'd probably get jumped.
Mm.
♪
Hey, you really want
outta that tux?
{Indistinct conversations
continue}
♪
Come on.
We'll run away together.
You're slow.
I'm going. I'm going.
Little too much food
lately.
Come on.
Maybe not.
Where are we going?
You ask
too many questions.
Show me
what you got, bad boy.
Here. Let me help you.
I got it. I got it.
Fire and ice...
When we first sat down
to discuss tonight's occasion,
I was immediately taken
with the idea
of an evening inspired
by primal bookends...
fire and ice...
Beginnings and endings...
And the love between
a man and a woman.
Yo. Yo, 8 mile,
private party here!
{Woman speaking indistinctly,
amplified voice}
...A starry evening.
That creep better not
be taking pictures.
Hey!
You got a problem?!
{Woman continues speaking
indistinctly, amplified voice}
Tonight not only
marks the final weekend
of a remarkable summer
in the Hamptons,
it is also the celebration
of my son Daniel's engagement...
To the lovely and beguiling
Ms. Emily Thorne.
And though we've only known her
for a few short months,
Emily already feels like
the piece of the family puzzle
we never even knew
was missing.
Aw.
In a word,
I approve.
And as anyone can tell you,
approval is not something
I give away freely.
Where the hell
is my son?
Charlotte.
Oh, my God.
Mom!
My brother...
Somebody come here!
Come here!
Mom!
Daniel!
Get away from my son!
Daniel, please!
No!
Daniel!
I can't tell you
what a rare opportunity
you have here, Ms. Thorne.
The current owners live
in the city, of course,
but they've been
loyal hamptonites for years.
Perhaps if Mr. Davis had been
a bit more loyal to his wife,
they wouldn't be renting out
this season.
Word has it, he dumped her
for a girl half his age.
Men.
You mind if I look around
a bit?
That's what we're here for.
♪ Here I go ♪
Dad?
♪ I'll tell you ♪
Hey, kiddo.
You having fun exploring?
We really get to spend
the whole summer here?
And every summer
after that.
What do you think?
I think
mom would've loved it.
Hey, you know how much
I love you, Amanda?
Infinity?
Well, infinity...
♪ With all of your heart ♪
Times infinity.
♪ If you love me ♪
Ms. Thorne?
Now you have to imagine,
it's Memorial Day weekend,
75 and sunny,
all those boys of summer
wondering who the new girl is.
And that's Grayson manor.
You won't find
a better address than this.
I'll take it.
Oh. Wonderful.
I'll get the contract.
♪ Shining your light ♪
♪ my way ♪
♪ say la, la, la,
la, la, la, la, la ♪
Hello, hello.
Ashley, hey.
Hey.
What do you think?
Are you kidding?
Look at this place.
I want your life.
You love your life.
Yeah, you're right.
I just want your money.
What's mine is yours.
Should I get us some glasses?
I wish.
It's for Victoria Grayson.
Who?
You are hopeless.
Victoria Grayson...
reigning queen
of the Hamptons.
Not to mention,
your new next door neighbor.
Queen Victoria?
Mm. Believe me,
she's earned the title.
My boss has me handling
the guest list
for her Memorial Day party.
Mm.
If I screw this up, I might
as well move back to Croydon.
Well, how much
are the tickets?
10,000 a pop.
Count me in for one.
Are you sure?
It's for a good cause,
right?
Yeah, my career.
Thank you.
You want to get drunk
on cheap Margaritas later?
With or without you.
Good luck with her highness.
Bye.
Let's dump our long position
on 5- and 10-year treasuries
before the fed
stops buying them up.
And, uh, get us into some of
those low-rated tech bonds.
Thanks.
Looks like Lydia and Michael's
new renter is settling in.
Lucky
girl, scoring that property.
Pretty one, too,
even from up here.
I guess that makes her
doubly lucky.
I don't believe in luck.
I thought you were taking
the weekend off.
Mm.
Hey.
Ew. Get a room,
you guys.
Oh, I'm sorry, Charlie.
I didn't see you sneaking in.
Didn't see you sneaking out
last night, either, Charlotte.
I went over to Tracey's.
Told you I was going
before you went to bed.
No, you didn't.
Mom, you're too young and too
pretty to be this senile.
Hmm.
{Tv continues playing
indistinctly}
Remind me to buy her
a cat bell.
Aw, let her have
a little fun.
She got straight a's
this year.
No one's accusing her
of being stupid.
♪
Don't think
I didn't see you eyeballing
that case of beer, dec.
Our dad owns a bar, dumbass.
I can get as much beer
as I want.
All right.
Well, in that case,
I'll just have to make sure
dad double-checks the inventory
while I'm gone.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Why don't you tell me
another hundred times, huh?
Did you already wash
those garbage bins out back?
Beats uploading
this future shipwreck.
♪
Ahoy! Captain Porter.
Welcome back, Nolan.
What can I do for you?
Need a boat for the summer.
This one will do.
It's not for rent.
Who said anything
about renting?
How much you want for...
"Amanda"?
It's not for sale, either.
♪
I'm taking it down to Haiti
next week.
I thought you hated
the ocean.
Well, I-I spent a lot of time
and money
working through that,
amongst other things.
So...
I'm buying a boat.
Right.
Just not this one.
Amanda must be
some special girl.
Can I help you
with something?
You don't like me much,
do you?
One more thing for you
to work through, I guess.
{People continue
speaking indistinctly}
♪
The response to your
"in with the new"
Memorial Day party
has been overwhelming,
Mrs. Grayson.
The party is at 90% capacity...
And the "regrets" web site's
already collected
nearly $50,000,
for everything from
domestic violence prevention
to cancer awareness.
Some of these regrets
wouldn't wipe their noses
with $50,000, dear.
If we're going to set a more
generous tone for the summer,
it's clear I'm going to
have to do something fresh
and provocative, so...
I've decided
to auction off a piece
from my personal art collection.
What a wild idea,
Victoria.
Well, I don't care
how good the cause is,
if you put up the Van Gogh
that Michael and I gave you...
I'll kill myself.
The Van Gogh is off limits
for sentimental reasons.
Please.
Okay.
Ashley, would you please add
the new announcement
to the web site, see if we can't
drum up some more business?
And, ladies, thanks again.
Lydia...
We were all so sorry
to hear about you and Michael
this winter.
You were one of those couples
everyone roots for.
I have no doubt.
How are you holding up?
Michael's threatening to put
the beach house on the market
if I don't release my claim
on the West Side walk-up.
It's bad enough, having
some stranger renting it out.
I can't bear the thought
of losing it
to one of the she-wolves.
Mm. Well, then don't let them
see your weakness.
It's the first thing
they'll use against you.
{Women continue speaking
indistinctly}
All right?
Mm-hmm. Thank you.
{Angus & Julia Stone's "Hold on"
playing}
{Indistinct conversations
continue}
♪ And I'm waiting for the day ♪
♪ I know you've got your part ♪
Hey, you want to know a trick?
Yeah.
You plant your feet
in the sand
and you stand still through
the whole first wave. Okay.
Then the next wave's
gonna feel warmer. Okay.
And then the one after that's
gonna feel warmer still.
Finally, you're barely gonna
notice the cold at all.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Here it comes.
Okay. Aah!
You must come from
a family of polar bears.
That water is ice cold.
Only at first.
After a while,
you can't feel anything.
Sounds like my marriage.
You must be the new renter.
Emily Thorne.
Word gets around fast.
Like lightning.
I'm Lydia Davis.
My husband and I own
the house you're staying in.
Oh.
Oh, wow.
It's so nice to meet you.
I can't tell you
how much I love it.
Me, too.
Some good memories
were made there.
Well, hopefully I can make
some of my own.
So long as we don't have to take
it out of your damage deposit.
Welcome to the Hamptons.
♪ What do you take me for? ♪
♪ hold on ♪
♪ what did you say that for? ♪
Federal prosecutors
wrapped up their case
for treason
against disgraced hedge fund
executive David Clarke.
Hedge fund
Taking the stand
was Clarke's secretary,
Lydia Davis,
whose testimony supported
the damning allegations
made by Clarke's former boss,
Conrad Grayson.
Grayson's testimony
detailed the scheme
Clarke used to channel money
to the terrorists
responsible for the downing
of flight 1-9-7.
All 246 Americans onboard
that flight were killed.
What do you
like better, dad,
sea glass or starfish?
Dad?
Starfish, definitely.
Here you go.
Thank you.
David, it's Victoria.
Hey, do you mind going
and looking after Sammy for me?
Sure.
David, are you there?
What's the matter, Sammy?
Hey, everything okay?
Whatcha doin'?
Daddy!
Whoa, whoa. What's going on?
Hands up so I can see 'em.
What's going on?
You're making a mis... wait!
You're making a mistake!
Get your hands off my daughter!
Aah! No!
Amanda! Let her go!
Amanda! Amanda!
Aah!
David Clarke
had everyone fooled,
including me.
I'm just glad I can help put
that monster away.
No one is to approach
the head table
unless they're escorted by
either myself or Mrs. Grayson.
I cannot stress how important
that seating chart is.
Got it?
I got it.
Good.
At 2:00,
security will be delivering
Mrs. Grayson's manet
to be set up for auction
in the main cabin.
Okay?
Jenkins.
Ems, please don't kill me.
Well, that depends.
What am I
not killing you for?
Standing you up
this afternoon.
I have a million-dollar
art auction to deal with.
Oh,
there's no pressure there.
You want me to pick up
your dress for you?
Oh, you're a lifesaver.
Oh, please. I'm sightseeing.
You're working.
I got you covered.
Thank you.
Bye.
{Indistinct conversations
continue}
More tea?
Please.
Do you think I'm tan enough
for my first day on the beach
or do I need another spray?
What you need
is another bathing suit.
Compared to what the rest
of my friends are wearing,
this is practically
a burka.
Unlike the
rest of your friends...
It's important
to me that you don't end up
on "page six" at one of
Diddy's hot tub parties.
Danny's home.
Ooh, Danny!
Ah.
How you doing?
Oh.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm so glad to see you.
What's going on, a fire sale?
Charity stunt.
Welcome home, Daniel.
Hi, mom.
I'm headed down
to the beach.
Okay.
She's growing up fast.
Too fast.
You hungry?
You know,
I'm a little wiped out.
I think I'll just
lay down for a bit.
Yeah, you look a little tired.
Well, studying
will do that to a guy.
Mm. So will partying.
Mom, I just got here.
Give me a break.
Where's dad, golfing?
Where else?
Yep. Where else?
Now...
It feels like summer.
Champagne?
You have to ask?
Oh.
Mm.
Ah.
Ah...
Conrad?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Conrad.
Oh, God.
♪
All right, so the first thing
you do is enter the code.
It's not exactly...
Ooh.
Then you swipe the card.
Then the amount.
Are we eating in here?
Uh, yeah.
I'm afraid so.
Dec.
Yeah, yeah, I got it. Uh,
card, swipe, amount, right?
Code, swipe, amount.
Jack, will you take care
of the mean girls' table?
It's too early in the season
for me to start making enemies.
Why should this year
be any different?
Because you're sailing off
to save the world,
and this place can't afford
bad press.
Yeah, yeah, I, uh,
I got it. Okay?
Hi. Help you?
Um, are you the owner?
Hopefully not for another
30 years or so.
You're looking for my dad.
Some suit's
looking for you.
You are?
Um, Doug Reid
with first federal.
Oh, Mr. Reid.
I'll take care of him, Jack.
Hey, Mr. Reid.
Carl Porter.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks for coming down.
Why don't you follow me
to my office?
I know you like him.
Here he comes.
Ladies.
We'll take
three rum and diets.
Uh, gonna need to see ID's.
Um, we left our ID's
at the beach,
but we have plenty of money.
Yeah.
Sorry. I'm not interested
in your money.
Are you interested
in my phone number?
{Indistinct conversations
continue}
It looks like a stemi.
We need to get him in quick.
What does that mean?
Is he gonna be okay?
Ma'am, I need you
to step back, please.
Where are you taking him?
Southfork hospital.
Lydia. Lydia.
Nice and easy, on my count.
One, two...
Emily Thorne.
Three. My... my God.
Is this your husband?
Do you need a ride to the hospital?
No, I don't. I...
{Paramedics continue
speaking indistinctly}
{Emergency radio chatter
continues}
...And an EKG.
As soon as we get there.
♪
Sammy.
The whole point of fetch
is to bring the stick back
when I throw it.
I really gotta
explain this again?
Come here.
Come here, Sammy.
I found a stick for you.
What's his name?
Sam.
He sure likes sticks.
Fetch it, Sammy.
Nice throw.
Thanks.
I'm Jack.
I'm Amanda.
Come on, Sammy.
Pick up the stick.
Where you going?
Get back here.
What are you doing?
Sammy.
Sam?
Barks.
Sammy!
Sammy! Get down.
What's the matter with you?
I'm sorry.
He's not normally
this friendly.
He's kind of an old grump,
actually.
Mm.
Oh, he got mud
on your dress.
Oh, that's no big deal.
There's an Earl and Emma's
dry cleaners
right around the corner.
I'll walk you over.
Oh, that's okay.
Um, I got it.
Thanks.
Well, hey.
Uh, tell Earl and Emma
that you're a friend
of Jack Porter's.
My family owns the tavern down
by the docks, the stowaway.
What's... what's your name?
I'll... put you on
the official comp list.
You don't have to do that.
Well, I'm not picking up
the tab. Sammy is.
He feels terrible.
Don't you?
Thanks anyway.
All righty, then.
You have a great summer.
{Woman speaking indistinctly
over PA.}
Hey.
Oh, my God, Conrad.
I thought I was going to find you dead.
I'm fine.
What happened?
Acute abdominal dyspepsia.
The remorse
of a guilty stomach.
Your staff made it sound as if
he was having a heart attack.
Well,
depending on the severity,
the symptoms
can be identical.
As far as I can tell,
your husband's
as healthy
as a thoroughbred.
But I do suggest
that he stay away
from the Southfork Inn's
spicy bisque for a while.
The Southfork Inn?
Yeah.
I thought you went golfing.
Yeah, I did, earlier.
Southfork is a half-hour
in the opposite direction.
I'm aware of that.
Excuse me.
Come on. You know
I just get in the way
when you're planning
one of your parties.
I just thought
I would go for a drive
and stay out of your hair for a while.
And I'm sorry
that I scared you.
Don't do it again.
♪
Emily.
Hey.
You look amazing.
I look amazing? Look at you.
Look at this party.
Congratulations.
Well, it's too early for that.
Haven't you seen "Titanic"?
So how well
do you know these people?
Well enough to know
who to keep away from
and who to snuggle up to.
Mm. Quick tutorial?
Okay.
The girl in the orange
Escada dress?
Mm-hmm.
That's
Mayor Bloomberg's niece.
And the woman
she's talking to,
now this one is important...
Megan Foster.
Shoe buyer
for Barneys of New York.
Ooh.
♪
Gray suit boy
is kinda cute.
That's Daniel Grayson,
Victoria's
tragically privileged spawn.
Daniel wrapped his convertible
around a tree last summer
after one too many.
Didn't hurt his face much.
Yeah, it didn't work out
quite as well
for the waitress
he was shagging.
His parents paid off
everyone and their mother
to keep him out of jail.
And the plot thickens.
Who's that?  You
ever been on a private jet?
Nolan Ross.
I've got two.
Former tech boom whiz kid
and perennial
pain in the ass.
If you emptied the bank accounts
of everyone at this party,
it wouldn't add up to the interest...
There he is...
His makes in a week.
Old blue eyes.
Nolan...
And that
is queen Victoria.
Wow.
Hello, Nolan.
Hello, Victoria.
How are you?
I think she spotted you.
Good.
Introduce us.
♪
Hey, how about
that stock split, huh?
What'd I tell you?
Turned out great.
Conrad.
Yeah.
We weren't sure we were going
to see you this afternoon.
Huh?
Rumor had it that you, uh,
really dodged a bullet
yesterday.
Oh, well, I'm happy to report
that the rumors of my demise
are greatly exaggerated.
Oh. Well, I'm thrilled
to hear it.
I'll be sure
to spread the word.
Oh, I'm sure you will.
Lydia.
♪
I just...
Karrie, you look like
you could use another drink.
Darling, would you please
show her the way to the bar?
Sure.
Lydia.
Where have you
been hiding yourself?
I left three messages
for you.
Mrs. Grayson,
forgive me for interrupting.
I just wanted to introduce you
to a dear friend of mine.
Victoria Grayson,
Emily Thorne.
Hello, Mrs. Grayson.
Ah, Ms. Thorne.
I was wondering
who the late entry was
on the guest roster.
Well, Emily's new
to the Hamptons,
but she really wanted to
take part in your fund-raiser.
Oh. How do you two
know each other?
We volunteered together
at the met this winter.
Mm. Apparently being
a sustaining patron
just wasn't enough
for Emily.
Mm. I try to give back
as much as I can.
Lydia. Hi.
Oh, don't tell me
you've taken up volunteering
at the met as well.
Emily's renting my house
for the summer.
Ah.
We met briefly on the beach.
And then yesterday
at the Southfork Inn.
I hope your husband's
feeling better.
♪
Mm.
{Indistinct conversations
continue}
♪
Victoria, wait.
{Indistinct conversations
continue}
Everyone, listen up, please.
I just want to thank you all
for helping the stowaway
kick off the season right.
You're welcome!
Where were you people
all winter?
Tomorrow my son Jack
is setting sail for Haiti
to pitch in with the red cross.
Good luck, Jack!
He wanted to go
right after the quake,
but I convinced him to
stick around an extra year
to help me out.
Almost two, actually,
but who's counting?
Was it two?
Yeah.
It was two.
{Door closes,
bell on door jingles}
Good going, Jack.
To Jack!
I'm gonna miss you, son.
I'm gonna miss you, too.
Yeah, baby!
Mr. Porter,
do you have a moment?
Sure.
Right this way.
{Indistinct conversations
continue}
The bank is not going to
approve any further extensions.
But business is back.
All's I need is 30 more days.
I am sorry.
It's out of my hands.
{Playing up-tempo
instrumental music}
Here we go round again,
Danny boy,
summertime in the Hamptons.
Yep.
Same people,
same parties...
Same everything.
{Indistinct conversations
continue}
Where do you want
to discuss it?
Yo, man.
Want to bump it up
a notch?
Oh, my God!
Wow.
I'm so sorry.
God, I'm such an idiot.
No, don't worry about it.
It's, uh,
probably the universe
telling me
I need a costume change.
Uh... I'm Daniel.
Emily.
How about I get you
a dry Martini?
Twice the alcohol,
half the stain potential.
Sure. I'm sorry.
No, no. It's okay.
Now wait right here.
{Music and indistinct
conversations continue}
♪
How much does he owe?
I'm sorry. That's between
your dad and the bank.
Come on. He's owned
the place 30 years.
How bad is it?
The bank's gonna foreclose
at the end of the month.
The only way to stop it now
is full payment on arrears.
I am sorry.
There's nothing I can do.
♪
{Indistinct conversations
continue}
♪
Good afternoon, everyone,
and happy Memorial Day.
I wanted the theme
of today's party
to signify a fresh start
for all of us.
As difficult as
the last few years have been,
they have been devastating
on our charities.
But now, as things are
beginning to turn around,
I'm looking forward
to giving back,
and I know
that all of you are, too.
{Guests laughing
and shouting indistinctly}
So to start things off right,
I'd like to announce the winner
of the art auction,
my dear friend...
Lydia Davis...
Oh!
Congratulations.
Who won't be going home
with the manet this evening,
but with the treasured van gogh
that hangs in my living room.
{Guests gasping
and speaking indistinctly}
But I thought the van gogh was
a gift from Lydia and Michael.
Have Ms. Davis
escorted off the boat.
And in related news,
Lydia has asked me
to announce that the beach house
she shared with her husband
is officially on the market.
Ms. Davis...
I'm afraid this will be
her final weekend
in the Hamptons.
So call your realtors,
ladies and gentlemen,
because this one's
going to go fast.
And, Lydia...
Wherever you end up,
I hope that the van gogh
is a constant reminder
of the friendship we shared.
{Guests continue
speaking indistinctly}
Get
your hands off my daughter!
I
want that kid outta here. Now!
Give her to social services!
Daddy!
Amanda!
Settle down!
Where are you taking her?!
No! Daddy!
Amanda! No!
She's really something,
isn't she?
My mother.
She sure is.
- A big thank-you also...
- To chance meetings.
To an unforgettable summer.
How many Harvard men
does it take
to screw in a lightbulb?
I don't know. How many?
One, and the whole world
just revolves around him.
One more?
Drink or joke?
Either. Both.
Mm. Neither.
I am just buzzed enough
to find that last joke funny.
One more, and I might think
that you meant it.
But don't let me stop you.
Oh, no, no. I've had about
all the club soda I can take.
You don't drink?
Used to...
Epically.
Hmm.
I gotta admit, it's...
it's nice meeting someone
who never knew the old me.
Yeah.
I know the feeling.
♪
Double infinity.
Something like that.
That's a long time.
Daniel...
Your father and I
are leaving.
Thank you for a lovely party,
Mrs. Grayson.
It was great
meeting both of you.
Well, now that you've
moved in next door,
I suppose we'll be seeing
a lot of you this summer.
♪
I'll expect you shortly,
Daniel.
♪
{Indistinct conversations
and laughter}
Don't let my mom
rattle you.
Intimidation is practically
a sign of endearment with her.
I'd hate to be
on her bad side.
Yes, you would.
I should go.
Uh, I'm headed your way.
You need a ride?
No, thanks.
Maybe next time.
Till next time.
♪
You didn't
have to exile her.
Oh, what I did was cruel?
You could have had anyone,
and you knew she was
my closest friend.
It was never meant
to be an affair.
Oh, it just happened?
Are you physically incapable
of taking responsibility
for your actions?
There is a problem
we seem to share.
If you'll remember,
I gave up everything once
to prove how much I love you.
I returned the favor.
I helped you destroy a man.
Oh, no, no, no. That was
your idea, not mine.
You did what you did to save
yourself as much as me.
A compromise I'm reminded of
every day.
You got plenty
in the bargain.
Oh...
These guys really put the "suck"
in seersucker.
Want to bump it up
a notch?
What a waste of humanity.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
God, I'm such an idiot.
No, don't worry about it.
With whom do I have the
pleasure of speaking? Hey.
It's, uh...
It's Jack Porter.
Listen, if you still
want to buy my boat,
bring a check down to the docks
first thing in the morning.
Okay?
There's nothing
I'd like to do more.
All right.
See you then.
♪
Welcome home, Amanda.
I nearly didn't
recognize you today,
but that's the whole point,
isn't it?
Oh! Ugh! Uhh!
Do you know how easy it would be
for me to crush your windpipe?
I don't think
your father would approve.
Amanda...
Oh...
Your father trusted me.
My father trusted everybody.
Ugh! What are you
doing here, Nolan?
Don't worry. Don't worry.
Your secret's safe.
No one wants
this imperious cadre
of toxic phonies to eat it
more than yours truly.
So how can I be of service?
You can't.
You're not a part of this.
Yes, I am.
Remember,
I witnessed firsthand
what these people did
to your father.
They're hard-core.
I can handle them.
And I have no problem
taking you down, too,
if you get in my way.
I-I don't want
to get in your way.
I want to help you.
You can't help me, Nolan.
Suit yourself.
But I can be
just as powerful an enemy
as any one of them.
Just sayin'.
Oh...
You might be interested
to know,
I had a nice chat
with Jack Porter tonight.
Guess who's still
carrying a torch
for little Amanda Clarke.
Amanda Clarke
no longer exists.
{Angus & Julia Stone's
"For you" playing}
♪ If I talk real slow ♪
Clarke, Happy Birthday.
You've been emancipated.
♪ If I try real hard ♪
♪ To make my point ♪
♪ Dear ♪
♪ That you ♪
♪ have my heart ♪
♪ Here ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ go ♪
♪ I'll tell you ♪
♪ what you already know ♪
Amanda Clarke.
Who are you?
Nolan Ross.
Friend of your father's.
You're not exactly
the little angel he described.
♪ I'll tell you ♪
My father hasn't seen me
in ten years.
♪ ...Know ♪
♪ if you love... ♪
I'm sorry to be
the one to tell you.
He passed away...
Six weeks ago.
♪ ...Heart ♪
He wanted you
to have something.
Whatever that is,
I don't want it.
Oh, no, no, no, trust me.
You definitely do.
My father was a murderer
and a liar.
So why would I trust you,
huh?
'Cause that's just what
they want you to believe.
Forget everything that
you think you know, Amanda.
Your dad was protecting you.
From what?
Open the box.
Find out.
♪
Your father was the first person
to believe in me.
He invested in my company
when no one else would.
That key, it opens
a lock box in Zurich.
Now that you're 18,
you're officially 49% owner
of my company.
Board meetings are
every other Wednesday, but...
You don't have to show up.
I never do.
"My dear Amanda...
"If you're reading this,
"then two things
have come to pass,
"I am finally able
to provide you the life
"you were unjustly denied,
"and sadly,
I won't be able
"to share
that life with you.
"I hope these journals
provide answers
"to the questions you've had
all these years.
"I am not the man
they say I am
and I did not do
the things they say I did."
♪
"All I ask is that you promise
to do the one thing
that's been so hard
for me to do."
♪
"Forgive."
But that was a promise
I couldn't keep.
When deception cuts this deep,
someone has to pay.
My father's chance
to bring justice
to the truly guilty
was stolen from him.
His only option
was to forgive.
I have others.
♪
Would you set it up
by the windows, please?
You don't understand.
I want the beach house.
He hasn't even been out...
And I'd like some, uh,
pepper in my bisque.
They say vengeance is a dish...
Best served cold.
But sometimes it's as warm
as a bowl of soup.
♪ ...Already know ♪
My father...
Died an innocent man,
betrayed by the woman
he loved.
♪ I'll tell you ♪
♪ what you already know ♪
♪ if you love me ♪
♪ with all of your heart ♪
When everything you love
has been stolen from you...
Sometimes all you have left
is revenge.
Like I said...
♪ I'll make you a star ♪
This is not a story
about forgiveness.
Yes?
I want you to find out
everything you can
about a young woman
named Emily Thorne.
Emily Thorne?
That's right.
♪ Shining your light ♪
♪ my way ♪
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-