- Guys.
- Hey, Vocabulary.
Guys...
Here to inspect the sugar factory?
We adulterate it, only 25% is shit.
That's better than the rest.
Some people even put rat poison in it,
but we are purists.
- Only phenacetin.
- This is good stuff.
The market agrees with you.
- Do you hear that?
- We're working our asses off.
- We're done. Let's go, I'm starving.
- You always want to eat.
- Enzo, what's the matter?
- Nothing, we have to go.
- Come with me.
- Keep it up, guys.
- Carmela, how are you?
- Fine.
- Was the camera turned on?
- Yes, the police took the footage.
- Did you see who it was?
- No, I couldn't see his face.
The police said it was a warning.
It wasn't a big bomb.
- But the next time it's serious.
- What did you tell them?
If they do their job, like I do
every night, there will be no next time.
I'll see you later.
This bomb is from the Federation,
I'm sure of it.
But they can't think we're afraid now.
We can't stop now,
we almost have them.
We have to kill 'em
and roll 'em up in bags.
We have to hit them now,
it doesn't matter who.
We just need to kill one now.
- Speak to me, Ciro.
- I just got the news.
- I need to see you right away.
- Where?
- I'll meet you at the warehouse.
- Okay.
We are your brothers.
We're done here.
Come with me.
What did he say?
Nothing.
But I know him well.
In is heart, he's furious.
Then that bomb can work in our favor.
Are you sure?
If they go nuts at the Federation now,
they'll do a lot of damage.
Unless they crash into a tree
and the Federation stays intact.
I turned Enzo into a soldier...
but now he has to become a capo.
He has to learn
to think before he shoots.
Only then we can win this.
If you're 20 years old,
shooting is easier than thinking.
I know.
That's why I have to talk to him.
Alone.
Translated by: NederSubs
Do you know why the Federation
planted that bomb?
They think we're nobody,
but that isn't true.
But they have to keep thinking that.
We must keep our nerve.
When we're done,
we're going to kill them.
Do you mean I shouldn't do anything?
You do as I say, when I say it.
First, you have to reorganize your men.
How do you mean?
It won't work if everyone thinks
they're the boss.
If you want to win the war,
there can only be one leader.
And that's you.
Let me ask you something.
Shoot.
What's in this for you?
- 20 percent, as always.
- That's not much.
If everything goes well, I'll get Forcella.
What are you doing this for?
I'm doing the only thing I'm good at.
But whatever I do,
the spirits won't leave me alone.
- Guys, we need to get ready.
- We'll destroy them.
Yes, we will.
- But it's not that straightforward.
- How do you mean?
I have a plan.
We must weaken the Federation first.
If you follow my lead,
we can wipe them away.
And then we're the boss
in our own neighborhood.
Sounds good, but I think
we no longer decide together.
You are the boss now, aren't you?
We're sailing towards the storm.
There is only one captain on the ship.
That was the case for the generation
before us. My dad died for it.
But we see things differently.
We don't let anyone tell us what to do.
To win the war,
we'll have to change things.
And when we change things, we'll win.
I promise.
So you are Enzo Blue Blood.
Do you have that name for me?
This is from Gennaro.
This is the contact, we already
talked to him. He's expecting your call.
But you have to give him something.
That's not a problem.
I still don't know your name.
Patrizia.
It was a pleasure, Patrì.
Leave it to me.
Good.
And?
- The kid showed up.
- Great.
Something else: tell Cianel
to spend all her cash on weapons.
Is this a joke?
Should I hypnotize her, or what?
She's not a part of your war.
Make it clear
she's either for or against me.
And what if she's against you?
What do I do?
Then you let her pay the price.
This is not acceptable, clear?
Or should I cram you in it?
And now get the hell out.
What a mistake to hire those losers.
They work hard
and they don't bother us...
but this is about decency.
How the hell can I bury someone
in a red-lined coffin?
It's a matter of respect.
What is it?
The war Genny wants to wage
with those people from downtown...
That's not a joke.
It's real, and he's going to start now.
What do you think of it?
They called us monkeys.
It's time to show them
nobody puts these monkeys in a cage.
They should wash out their mouths
with soap before they can talk to you.
Well said.
Come in.
This is a gift for you.
- Hello, Cocò.
- How are you, Catenella?
- Not bad, and you?
- Okay. I have some good stuff for you.
Good stuff, great class.
Your Myriam would love it.
And the price is really good.
If it's good and cheap stuff,
I can't refuse.
- Do I see you in half an hour?
- I never turn down a great deal...
but half an hour is too short.
I have to discuss with Myriam first.
They want money straightaway.
That's why the price is so reasonable.
Okay, I'm on my way.
I'll surprise Myriam with it.
Well done.
He's on his way.
Don't move.
Let me go.
Stand up.
Sit still, for fuck's sake.
Don't move.
Piece of shit.
We know you're buying weapons
for the Federation.
We want to know where you store them.
What are you doing?
You are puppies
challenging Neapolitan Mastiffs.
They'll tear you apart alive.
He's like an old washing machine:
hit it a few times and it works again.
We are not puppies, you are.
You have a boss.
Kill me.
Kill me, but I can't tell you.
- Ronni, everything alright?
- Certainly.
Look who's here.
I'm looking at his daughter Myriam.
She doesn't look like her father,
a real sweetie.
And that kid is also cute.
I'll show him to you.
Do you see that kid on that bike?
And that's his mother.
I wouldn't like to hurt her...
What do you think?
See? Puppies bite as well.
Please...
My family has nothing to do with this.
You can decide that yourself.
And? What should I tell my buddy?
What do I say to him?
There are three stashes.
The hotel near the train station...
the cemetery in Chiaiano...
and the flag factory in Via Marina.
Well done.
You did the right thing.
Are you coming along?
We know where the weapons are.
Good. Then we can start biting.
Are we going to screw over
that asshole Arenella right away?
Arenella is a real son of a bitch,
but he is cold-blooded.
We better go for Crazy.
He's stupid, and very short-tempered.
And the Capaccios have too few men
to defend their place.
We hit them at a place
where they can't hit us back right away.
Then we do real damage.
To bite hard, we need teeth.
And we're short of those.
You don't have to worry about that.
I have a present for you.
You made the right choice, Blue Blood.
There was no other choice.
Tell me, kiddo...
Can you handle these toys?
Don't you worry.
I will get you many customers.
Hopefully we aren't leaving these toys
in the hands of children.
Do you know why they call Ciro
the Immortal?
Because he survived three wars?
When he was 21 days old,
his parents died in an earthquake.
He was the only survivor
of the 30 residents.
If you think you are the earthquake
that will kill him, I'll find you.
Like yourself, I'm a son of a king...
but just like Ciro,
I grew up being an orphan.
We are sons of spirits,
our fathers were slaughtered,
and the Federation didn't even
give us back their bodies.
So you only want revenge?
I want what they took away from us
and what I deserve:
I want Forcella.
Then you'll get Forcella.
But if you get hungry afterwards...
I'll rip your heart out.
As far as I'm concerned, he's your
responsibility, because he chose you.
Everything that happens to him
should also happen to you. Clear?
Hurry up.
Lift it off.
And this one too.
Put it against the wall.
Dig in.
- Holy shit.
- Santa has come.
You know what to do.
- Have you ever had a weapon?
- No.
Take this one.
Who are you again?
The people who are letting you live.
- Get lost, this is not your terrain.
- You didn't understand.
You're a herding dog now
and I'm the shepherd.
Goodbye.
Guys, let's move on.
Alright. Bye.
Those beards took over
our parking lot and the Torri Bar.
We have to teach them a lesson.
- They must die.
- Wait.
Wait until
they've taken over everything?
Maybe they have a strategy.
- What do you mean?
- Why do you never think?
They've done this right under our noses.
So they're either really stupid...
or they're keeping us on a leash.
We are not dogs,
we're strong enough to destroy them.
Pick up the weapons.
I'll see you in an hour. Hurry up.
- What's taking them so long?
- No idea.
We've been here for two hours.
There they are.
Where are they going?
- Wait.
- Where did he go?
Now.
Close it.
We have them.
Come on, hurry up.
Hurry up.
Drive.
Quiet, don't move.
There's nobody here.
Are they dead?
What are you talking about? Come on.
Take this.
Stop dreaming, come with me.
Hand it to me.
They have all weapons
and almost all lives.
We have to call the Slave for weapons.
And new men, Romeo must help us.
He also benefits from this.
They'll go after him as well.
We'll give 5000 euros
to everyone who joins us.
We form an army, cut off their dicks
and cram them in their mouths.
That requires more than just an army.
Don't you see what happened?
We had more people and weapons
and it still happened.
What should we do then,
according to you?
We let them believe that they have won,
that they're stronger.
That we're shitting ourselves
and don't fight back.
We wait a few hours so they'll relax...
and then we'll send them to God
to ask for forgiveness.
What's going on? Where is Enzo?
Don't worry, Enzo knows what he's doing.
- Everything okay?
- It's suspiciously quiet.
What do we do now?
We go home,
but first we send a message.
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
- Maria saw strangers in our neighborhood.
- What do we do?
Go and see, Valerio.
You wanted to see me?
I heard your boys have been busy.
- What do you think?
- You know what you're doing.
You gave me this business
and I work hard.
If you join me,
this is only the beginning.
- But now I need something else from you.
- What?
30 percent of your revenue.
I need it to win this war.
I'll make sure you'll get back
three times the amount.
Do you see this coffin?
Nice, huh? I keep him for myself.
But I only go in when I'm very old.
Whatever you want. But in the meantime,
we scored big points with the angels.
What do you mean?
You want the Capaccio's place?
After this war, it's yours.
We'll build a beautiful statue there.
Do you know what they say?
The biggest whore
is the one who gives you lice
and then fucks you again.
You do that too.
Excuse me, I'm lost.
How do I get to Via Foria?
Fuck off back to Vomero.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
You said you'd only look.
You take this.
Come on, we have to go.
Put this on.
Hurry up.
Go on.
Done?
We have to split up.
Go home.
- Everything okay?
- Everything okay.
- Go to bed.
- Take care.
Bye, sweetie.
- How are you?
- I'm still alive. What's up?
Maria told me who your new friend
from Secondigliano is.
Where are you going?
Look at me.
Was that friend with you tonight?
- Was he with you?
- No.
Why not?
He supplies the weapons and the drugs.
Thanks to him,
those assholes are now afraid.
I get it.
He is the choreographer and you dance.
If something goes wrong,
they'll come for you.
That's not how it went.
And if we win this war, then what?
Does he get paid for the choreography,
or does he buy the whole theater?
He's my brother.
I'll tell you what I told everyone:
If you're not for me, you're against me.
I've heard about your exam.
Valerio, you can do whatever you want...
but you have to get your diploma.
- What do we do?
- Inform the families, we'll go on tomorrow.
They are the devil.
What are you laughing at?
They're destroying us,
what's so funny about that?
Yes, laugh.
They're stone cold.
We can do two things:
We can exterminate them,
or we can invite them over.
Either way, it will be fun.
NEXT TIME