- Come on.
- I'm ready.
Drive.
Translated by: NederSubs
I did everything they asked.
But Azzurra and Pietro
are still with that asshole.
Despite all the fuss,
we haven't made any progress.
That's not true.
Just think about it.
Along the way you met many friends.
Old and new ones.
There is something else you can
give them, just think about it.
What, then?
The blood of your friends.
This is Patrizia.
She is the intermediary
Gennaro has chosen for the exchange.
We're here together, with the
souls in Purgatory as witnesses,
to give him our answer.
You'll speak first, Giuseppe.
Do you want to give your daughter
and grandson to Gennaro
in exchange for Blue Blood?
I don't agree with it.
I'm fine with it.
I think it's in everyone's interest
if we trade Enzo Villa for his family.
Are you sure?
We've already destroyed Genny.
And he no longer has a grip on
Enzo and his mates.
- That monkey has a double advantage.
- But we also benefit from it.
We're rid of those guys
and we can take back Forcella.
Don Ruggiero, may I say something?
Patrizia, what does Ciro di Marzio
say about Gennaro's proposal?
I don't know.
But until now,
Ciro has always stood behind Genny.
I think he would even
follow Genny to hell.
And we make sure he'll never resurface.
Without Ciro di Marzio,
Gennaro Savastano is nobody.
- Freeze. Quiet.
- What are you doing?
Asshole.
Let's go.
Give it to me.
Are you here to work?
Do you have the money with you?
Step back, you need to wait.
- Gennaro?
- He's in the back.
Your security was no good.
That's the problem.
Hence all those robberies in your store.
But rest assured, we're here now.
You're in good hands.
Sign here.
- Did you see it?
- What is this place?
- A new business.
- Private security?
Everyone has something valuable
that they want to protect at all costs.
- Remember, Rosario.
- Everything is alright.
And nobody can protect them
as well as I do.
Did you talk to them?
What did they say?
They agree with the exchange,
including Don Avitabile.
But there's a problem.
He thinks your offer is not enough.
What does he want?
He also wants Ciro.
- Gennaro has accepted everything.
- He accepted it? Good.
As long as I'm the intermediary,
he agrees with everything.
Do you want to tell me something else?
He wants to speak to you.
Does he want to make me an offer?
He's really at rock bottom.
He wants to stop the war
and continue dealing.
But he's afraid of how you'd react.
Without your support,
Secondigliano will revolt,
and then he's lost that business as well.
Good, let him be afraid.
The moment has come
to crush Genny for good.
Think twice about it.
Before the exchange,
there's still time to hurt him even more.
I told him to make you a proposal,
to keep you happy.
A room has been prepared
for you and Pietro.
Gennaro is in the back.
Hello, Gennaro.
And, do you like it?
I've always hated guards.
Even if they work for you?
You were on my side when I needed you.
And I never forget anything.
I thought you'd want to be
my partner in this business.
Wow, thanks.
First grave digger, and now a guard.
I'd rather have that statue
in Piazza Garibaldi you promised me.
- We can forget about downtown.
- Really?
I can't take any more risks.
And we can walk into Secondigliano
without risking our lives
or jail time.
I knew you were unfit for the System.
It's nothing for you.
I'll tell you what we do.
We'll both go our separate ways.
But I want the money back I gave you.
As soon as I make a profit again.
There's no time for that.
Do you know what I think, Gennaro?
If all these businesses were mine,
I'd forget about downtown in a heartbeat.
Stay strong.
Your father wants to see you.
- Hello?
- Do you recognize the place where you are?
No.
I used to take you here as a child,
in the summer.
You were just as little
as Pietro is now.
He loves you very much.
He would do everything to get you back.
"Do you want this? Then you'll get this."
Look around you, Azzurra.
The things you see
are not only your past.
They will also be your future.
Did it go as I thought?
He also wants your head.
Cianel.
You know this is very risky, right?
Our life is one big risk.
- What does Enzo think?
- He already said yes.
Enzo is on our side.
Tomorrow at three o'clock, you have to be
at the crockery warehouse. Enzo stays there.
Charming's men will only come
when I've seen Azzurra and Pietro.
What is it?
It was nice to walk together a bit.
- Our ways won't part.
- That is not important.
What happens, happens.
I stay where I am.
Is this the revenue?
- And? What do you think?
- These are good businesses.
- Gennaro is giving you a gem.
- Poor Gennaro.
He worked his ass off
to bring in those people,
and now all the money is for me.
I knew you were good,
but you're really great.
First, you took everything away from him.
Now, you're pushing him to the graveyard.
Why the long face?
I never forget my friends.
When I become a queen,
you'll be the prince.
Here is the money you asked for.
Thanks.
If everything goes well,
I'll give it back to you tomorrow.
And otherwise I have to think about
Maria and Cosimo.
He's with family for the time being.
Are you afraid?
If you were, I'd understand.
I've lost so much.
And now I want to take revenge.
And that can kill me.
You won't die.
You'll grow stronger, I promise you.
What do your buddies say?
We can count on everyone.
Great.
We meet tomorrow, here.
What's with that bag?
For you and Cosimo,
if I don't come back.
What? Do you know
what I'm going to do with that money?
I'll buy a hot air balloon. At the wedding,
we'll fly to the reception.
That's what I'm going to do
with this money.
They're there.
If anything happens to me, you have to
take care of Azzurra and Pietro.
I will.
Come here, sweetie.
They're going to San Giovanni a Teduccio,
the exact location follows. Come on.
Remember, Patrizia.
Our fate is now in your hands.
We're heading for him now.
So it's true?
- Are you ready?
I'll do everything you say,
but I want to tell you one thing:
I understand
that you want to take revenge.
But Ciro asks you to risk your life
for Savastano's son.
And I don't understand
why you risk so much for him.
We're not doing this for Gennaro,
but for us. To settle the score.
And without his drugs, we'll become
what we were before all this: street boys.
Would that be so bad?
Right now it would.
If something happens to you, anything...
I will kill them all.
Wait here.
Go.
After the railway bridge,
the crockery warehouse in San Giovanni.
A crockery warehouse,
after the railway bridge.
What's the matter? Isn't Ciro there?
He didn't show up.
Then we'll let you die alone.
- Stop.
- Weapons down.
- Throw away your gun.
- Put it down, assholes.
Freeze, or I'll kill you.
I'm going to kill you.
- Freeze, motherfucker.
- Put it down.
On the ground.
On the ground, now.
I'm not alone.
Call him and tell him
everything is alright.
Do you want to be a hero?
Any more heroes?
Starting tomorrow,
your neighborhood is ours.
Everyone gets a job, a house and a car.
And our respect.
Call him.
Tell him Ciro and I are dead,
and he is too.
Where is Patrizia?
Come on, we have to go.
Come to daddy.
We have to leave here.
What is it?
Did you think I betrayed you?
They're back.
That's Ciro.
NEXT TIME