With that amount of good stuff,
no one can beat us.
But we will attract attention.
And Blue Blood?
He had to prove himself, you said.
He did.
He killed a stranger to keep you happy.
You know that too.
But now the real killing
will commence...
and if they catch him or his men, I don't
know how he'll react. You don't either.
Before he met me, he was a nobody.
He hadn't done anything
like what he's doing now.
He knows he'll be nowhere without us.
But Enzo isn't stupid.
That's why I chose him.
I thought I could cross Avitabile...
but he crossed me.
Now I don't even trust myself anymore.
But I trust you.
Translated by: NederSubs
I get you, Gennaro...
but I don't understand
how you can trust Ciro.
Only when they touch your family,
you show who you really are.
And I saw Ciro di Marzio.
And he saw me.
That's how it always has been.
And now he's more than family to me.
You also left your family
to protect my dad, right?
My father thought he had the best
soldier on his side, and he did.
I saw something else as well:
It's not over yet.
What do you mean?
Let me know
when you arrive where you want to be.
- Welcome.
- Hey, kid.
- This is Ciro.
- Valerio, a pleasure.
Enzo said good things about you.
You know this is serious, right?
Of course.
Come in, our host expects us.
Wait a second.
Before we go in,
I want to know where the stuff is going.
The client is a partner in a large company
in London. That's where the coke is going.
And how does he get it there?
With a diplomatic passport.
His dad works at the Italian consulate.
What do you get from it?
Your respect and friendship,
and a share from the client.
- Take me to him.
- Come with me.
Antonello Rodi, a pleasure.
I heard you're looking for something,
is that right?
Valerio said I could talk to you
about a big order.
- How much?
- 200,000.
Where's the money?
Antonello...
We have to agree on a price.
I heard 43,000 euros per kilo
is a reasonable price.
Can I expect a volume discount?
We're not going under 40.
Then it will be five kilos,
that sounds good.
When is the delivery?
- Now, if you want.
- Give me your key, I'll go.
This car will draw too much attention.
If you stay below 300 km/h,
no cop will pull over a car like this.
You're coming with me.
That friend of yours thinks he's God.
He is not a god,
but he does open doors.
To him, we are that car,
going at 300 km/h.
But at the first sign of trouble,
he switches cars.
That car is not his.
What am I to you?
You're like how I was 10 years ago.
I was angry, hungry,
as ambitious as a young dog.
I felt I was the strongest of all.
But not anymore?
That was a different life.
And yet you're joining us. Why?
I couldn't take it anymore,
being in hell on my own.
This is a kilo.
You bought five of these packages.
Tell your friend he'll receive a gift
if this continues.
Guys, police.
- Where?
- At gate 9.
- How many cars?
- One, but they sniff around everywhere.
- I'll go.
- Everything loaded up? Hurry then.
Faster. Close it down.
- Hurry up.
- Close it down.
Get out of the car.
On your knees. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Face down.
Can we trust your friend
if they catch him?
We'll have to see.
I think he's got balls.
Quite a big amount.
And it's still bricks.
That's a lot of work.
- We've grown out of this place.
- Then we'll find another.
- Enzo, what's up?
- Hey, Don Saverio.
- I have a proposal for you.
- Come in.
When do you need it?
Immediately.
If everything goes well,
you'll get twice the amount next month.
Really?
Really.
- How much junk does that guy have?
- Let's throw everything away.
Except for Padre Pio.
Hey, you're free.
- And? What did they ask you?
- I said I wanted to test drive the car.
- And then?
- Nothing, Antonello confirmed it.
I got a reprimand from the commissioner,
and that's it.
Yes, because you're from Posillipo.
- We would've been in prison.
- That's why I lured them away.
Goliat, prepare the coke for his friend.
Come with me.
- You should've seen Ciro's face.
- Was he surprised?
So you see, yuppies also have balls.
- Ours are bigger.
- Your words.
I'll show you out.
Check if it works.
Looks good, man.
Two and five.
- Where do all those people come from?
- They're friends of Valerio.
- This stuff is flying off the shelf.
- It does.
Hey, Mullet. And?
Hey, guys. They're ready.
- Now they'll fly.
- You're the man.
- Bye, buddy.
- Bye, guys.
- You were great.
- Assholes.
Sir, there's a delivery for you.
This package is for room 412.
Goodbye.
Here you go.
- 50,000, and we've just started.
- And nobody notices.
- Those assholes wanted to cross us.
- But we crossed them.
Soon, there will be nothing left of them.
Carmela, I'm here.
What did you want to tell me?
I know everything, Enzo.
You're going against people who've
been in this profession for 50 years.
In those 50 years on the streets,
they only suffered colds.
- You're in over your head.
- Don't worry.
They know
you have nothing to do with it.
- You kept your word.
- I don't want to cry about you.
I know you very well.
Tell me, honestly, have you never
wanted to kill those thugs?
I dreamed about it every night.
Now it's no longer a dream.
This is our moment.
- Are you coming, Enzo?
- I'm coming.
Did you see that car?
- What about it?
- It was parked out front.
I saw it on the monitor.
We have to be careful, they found us.
Are you coming along?
Close the door.
And?
Blue Blood is the reason
our revenue has dropped.
Come here.
How is it possible that a couple of brats
with no pubic hair can screw us over?
You are surrounded by idiots. Get out.
They were able to do this
because they know us.
But we didn't know them, that's why
we didn't pay attention to them.
Fine.
- We have to get rid of him.
- Okay.
Wait, come here. Come here.
I want to look that scumbag in the eye
before he dies.
I know something. We'll bring him to you,
and then you can handle it yourself.
Fine, you do that.
What's this?
The gift I promised.
Pay me if you sell it.
I would only get it
if we continued our partnership.
You saved Valerio from the police,
a brother.
So hereby our partnership is continued.
We can no longer condone this business.
We have to get rid of him.
That makes sense.
I know only one thing:
You only get rid of someone
if there's no other solution.
I respect that idea...
but he has the same blood
as his grandfather.
Leave this to me, Ruggero.
I'll finish it.
How can such a brave kid
suddenly have so much big talk?
What do you mean?
Blue Blood is backed by someone higher up.
That's the person we have to deal with.
- Who can that be?
- I don't know.
If I knew, he would be the first one
I would get rid of.
We need to find out
who our real enemy is.
- You must talk to Blue Blood.
- I should talk to him?
- Do you really mean that?
- It's your zone, Eduardo.
Donna Carmela.
Can we talk for a second?
Where in the world
should we talk about?
Kids these days.
These children are born smart,
but they know nothing about life.
If you want to learn, you find someone
higher than you. No idiots.
For that, you'll need
people with experience.
And we have enough of those.
Don Eduardo...
Could you get to the point?
Enzo has to stay below us.
We have a good proposal for him.
Talk him into it. He'll listen to you.
What you're saying makes sense...
to a family member.
But I think we've never been family.
So what, Donna Carmela?
We can always become family.
- Forget about the past, see the future.
- The past teaches you how to live.
That's what my father once said.
Of course.
That's why I sit here at your table.
Other people
wouldn't have come here to talk.
I won't waste any more of your time.
Good evening.
Room 4.
- One?
- Yes.
Sweetheart.
- You're so beautiful.
- I can't take it anymore.
I missed you, you know?
I'll come back.
I'm conquering it piece by piece.
I don't want you to worry about me.
And Pietro?
He's doing fine.
I often tell him about you,
I say that Dad will come home soon.
You only have to think about him.
- He is the most important.
- I know.
Great.
I'm working on that, Gennaro.
Azzurra, is everything alright?
Yes, Mom, I'm coming.
Do you remember your father?
Not really.
He was always in a hurry.
He once went to buy a present with me,
at Christmas.
How was he?
I don't remember.
He left when he was 35
and then he was in jail for 20 years.
He spent more time in jail than outside.
According to Carmela, your dad would
certainly take the deal they'll offer you.
Time will tell.
But what do you think?
I'm going to talk to Arenella.
You don't know me that well.
I'm always to the point.
Fine, then let's not
waste each other's time.
Stregone is your grandfather's brother,
your blood is in his heart.
That's why he asked me
to also see your side of things.
I won't kill you now, this is not the time.
But don't forget this.
If that time comes,
we'll see who's still standing.
Okay. I'll give you two zones. What your
father always wanted, but never received.
Via Cicerone and Via Plinio, two streets
where you can make a lot of money.
- What do you want in return?
- What you're taking away from us.
We have our own channels.
You'll have to silence them,
and tell me who they are.
I've never betrayed my brothers.
Poor kid...
You are no more than a rascal.
You only have to tell me
who's behind you.
Your days are numbered.
Watch your back.
That applies to everyone, Don Eduardo.
Come on, guys.
- Who's there?
- It's me.
Come in.
Why are you here?
You are no longer alone in hell.
I also bought a ticket.
What do you mean?
I told them no.
No to what?
Ciro, I'm under no illusions.
I know it's every man for himself...
but sometimes it's better
to invest in people rather than things.
Maybe, but that never happened to me.
Nor to me, until now.
Today, life surprised me.
They offered me the world and I said no.
You know what the price was?
You would've had to die.
The war is about to begin.
Enzo is ready.
What happened?
They offered him
everything his father died for.
He said no.
He had to choose and he chose us.
He chose you.
That's why you're so happy.
What is it?
I've never hated someone
as much as you.
But we're finally on the same side...
and I don't want to end up alone.
NEXT TIME