Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Severe until you reach the sky
mix incense and candles
honest, lighter
Hug my necklace and showed me
But you can not delete anything
Please speak it to him, Brother
Worshipped if the police kill me
I love to be hated...
What is it?
Did not you hear the text? Do you think
I need to hear it?
Are you worried about it with Conte?
Do you think that Salvatore Conte
looking forward to meeting me?
He was waiting for me with open arms.
He probably forgot that I
set fire to his mother's apartment.
Yes, I'm concerned.
Also, because I leave you alone here.
Do not worry about it.
Get an agreement with Conte.
When you return,
it will be us who is in charge here.
- Can I turn on the music again?
- Hurry, otherwise the plane.
Here you go. This way.
Wait.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
- Can I meet Don Salvatore now?
- I drive you to the hotel.
- To the hotel?
- Those are my orders.
On Sunday are elections in Catalonia.
The favorite, Javier Lozano Iglesias,
supports the independence project.
Eulalia Cases y Santos is a sure winner.
5.4 million Catalans
must choose 135 MPs.
Selection premises are open
CET. 8:00 to 20:00.
Here is nice.
- It is at your disposal.
- What do we do now?
- You rest. I'll call you later.
Hola. My room is not good.
No, it's not good. Switch.
Another room, yes.
Gracias.
Fuck you.
Has he arrived? Yes.
I give Don Salvatore message.
Fine. Give him another room.
- Who is it?
- It's me.
We put it away.
Yes!
Your mobile phone is switched off.
I need to talk to you.
Hurry, time is pressing. Hurry!
Wait a second.
Our contact has sent a message.
The money has arrived, and I
has determined that you have to do it.
If Ciro solve it with Conte,
everything falls into place.
- But where is Honduras?
- Close to Mexico and Guatemala.
- Why me?
- It's the start.
We must turn our name stuck.
This is bigger than all the rest.
If it works out, all come
to us, and no one could touch us.
It is also for you. Everyone will
understand who called the shots.
Everyone will finally understand
you're the boss.
Well, mom. I'll do it.
I is a Savastano. I'll do it.
Then we will be the biggest.
Where are you going? Come here.
No one knows anything about it.
What about Noemi?
- Say you'll be traveling.
But do not know where you're going.
It only works if no
know nothing about it. Got it?
- Fine.
- Not even Ciro.
Not even Ciro.
- Hello?
- We do not do anything today.
What the hell do you mean?
What the hell am I supposed to do?
What do I know?
Do as you will. See you tomorrow.
Wait. Come here. Wait, honey!
What am I waiting for?
That I'll be back.
So it will be us who decide.
You promise a lot,
but you never keep your promises.
I was supposed to be a queen.
Looks like it might castle?
And now I also
waiting for you. Why?
- Because when I come back...
- "When I come back ..."
Are you coming back? Is it safe?
Yes.
Give me proof.
- Proof?
A proof of your love.
It does not matter.
I was still tired of it.
You're a loser, Genna!
You let others control over you.
You're a loser.
You're just a poor fool!
Shit! The son of a bitch.
The son of a bitch.
Fucking pigs...
- Who is it?
- Breakfast, sir.
Good day.
The phone is broken. Kaput.
- Someone is waiting for you.
What do you say?
Someone is waiting for you in the lobby.
Yes, sir.
Good morning. The car stops outside.
I want to thank him for last night.
Can you see that?
Part of it is his.
He is also behind this. 25 floors.
This is the most important thing: a casino.
- Pull over.
Why?
- I have to pee.
Here?
If you do not stop, I pee in the car.
Sightseeing tour is over now.
Take me to Conte!
- I have orders to...
- I will not give a shit. Call him.
Pick up the phone,
otherwise I'll kill you. Hurry!
Call him! Call him!
That's me.
We have a problem with the guest.
We are on the way.
It was good.
Are you faithful?
It's important.
A believer is never alone.
One is not afraid of anything.
Without my faith
I would never have achieved anything.
And I have only
one person to thank for that.
The person taught me
what it means to be a believer.
The person is my mother.
Have you met my mother?
It you are.
You even know where she lives.
Like it?
I really like it.
You either hear or see anything.
Excuse me, Don Salvatore,
but when can we talk?
What is it? Is it urgent?
I would have taken care of everything,
so I can go home.
You little shit!
You even came armed.
You came armed.
I know it was you.
Who set fire to the mother's apartment?
- That's an order!
- An order from another asshole!
And now you must die.
Where the hell are you going?
Fucking bastard!
We buy it all, Genna.
100, 200, 300 kilos.
We take everything they have.
But you have to put the price.
You must be crafty.
Start with 1.20
and not more than 1.40.
- I get it. A maximum of 1.40.
- Good.
We sell it to the dealers for 30
and they sell it on for 50
Then we have control over.
There will be no one else left.
Do not do more. Let me know
When you're done, so I'm taking over.
What happens then?
- Nothing. You need to be there.
For when the load is sent away,
money is sent from here-
And when they arrive,
you can travel back to Naples.
Why should I wait?
- You are a guarantee. You are Savastano.
If you are there when the money forward.
When they do, you can go home.
- Fine.
- This is the contact.
But learn the number by heart.
Leaflet must be destroyed.
Good travel.
May Our Lady be with you.
- Goodbye, Baroncino.
- Goodbye, Gennaro.
- Donna Imma...
- Goodbye, Baroncino.
What is it?
You look like your father.
- I need to learn the number by heart.
- Good.
Call can not be answered right now.
Please call back later.
Come here. Up you go.
That's it.
There is someone who will talk to you.
- Hello?
We can talk tonight.
They pick you up at. 22.00.
Are you in? Hello?
Roger that.
- Now we are almost even.
- Almost?
Yes. In order to get rid
I ought to get your mother to cry.
I do not have a mother.
Sit down.
I prefer
my own home in the evening-
- But I have invested in this
and wanted to see the place. Like it?
Yes. Even though this is pretty empty.
It is early. We are in Spain.
People still have not eaten dinner.
Don Salvatore, we'll have it all sorted.
Of course.
Now that marokkaneren is mine,
will fix it all.
Pietro Savastano has treated me
as a loser, but I buy them all.
There are changes coming.
New winds are blowing.
Maybe you're new to win?
Yes, but above all, son.
The fat one? Nonsense!
He only has a head
to keep the ears separated.
But he's a good boy,
and he listens to advice.
Mother?
I've tried to call Ciro
all day, but he does not answer.
- The mobile phone is switched off.
What do you want Ciro?
I just wanted to say hi.
- Are you scared?
- No.
Not for my own sake.
For you.
I leave here.
We do not know where Ciro's.
If only Ciro?
There are a lot of others here.
So, Gennaro.
Go to bed. It's late.
You're leaving in four hours.
- Mother?
- Yes.
The girl, Noemi...
I broke up with her.
You were right.
She was not for me.
Good. You did right in.
- Mother?
- Yes? What is it?
- Are you going to miss me a little?
- Oh, Gennaro...
Of course I'll do it.
- You give me a kiss?
You're getting too big for that.
I miss you already.
Do you understand that?
If something happens to you,
I will come right away. Got it?
Some petrol stations, and others oil.
I have the oil, but we have gasoline tanks.
We must be a little better friends.
Do I look to suffer Without your fuel tanks?
- I Missing something?
- They do not lack anything.
But at our house
we are the best. You know this.
They just consider it.
Would you consider it?
Yes, I will. I assume
and urinating and considering it.
Jeremenko is very angry with you.
You play for high stakes.
Hey... Hey!
Can not you see I'm busy?
There is a piece of shit that followed
Don Salvatore into the toilet.
- Do not come here again.
- Don Salvatore! Is there something wrong?
The ride is threatening me on my area.
Where the hell have you been?
Watch. There are also here rats. Russians.
Tell me who it was,
we should be careful with?
Jeremenko.
He is very big and you...
Is small.
Do you know what the difference between us?
You can tell your boss that.
Do not move!
Go away.
Go and tell your boss.
The fucking Russians
is extremely rich and vicious.
If they think
that is enough to become leaders...
Then they are mistaken.
You need it here.
They still have a lot to learn.
Excuse me, Don Salvatore.
What about my suggestion?
They still have not said
what you think of it.
I still have not understood
who your boss is.
I can say, I have some influence.
And if we make a deal
you will have only one problem.
To count our money.
Don Salvatore! Don Salvatore.
- We must get away from here.
- It hurts!
Behave nicely.
Yes, Rome is perfect.
However, it must be
with the first flight. Gracias.
You can kiss my ass, everybody.
Hola
We take such good care of you,
and then you will already home.
Wait a minute.
It is never wise to be impulsive.
Come down here.
There is a stretch of coastline north.
They would buy it and make money
on it with their own private harbor.
But why leave it to them?
I bought it, Then the Russians fuck.
It was a mistake.
Now we are enemies-
And I have a pinched vertebra
and a dog collar around his neck.
We can not kill them.
We have to negotiate with them.
I've thought about it.
Do you want to make peace with me?
Do you want my Moroccan?
Then you need to negotiate with the Russians.
And when it's all right,
I can do business with you.
It's your case.
Let's not waste time, Ciro.
You can not say no.
If you want to return home,
you must seek Jeremenko-
And say that we can share it.
60% to me and 40% of them.
As for me?
It's the pity.
Russians are really angry now
And I can not risk
to lose one of my men. Are you in?
Yes, I am with.
- 60% To you and 40% to the Russians.
- Good.
I would have had greater chances out to sea.
Now you underestimate yourself.
Relax. He comes
and pick you up later.
Take care, Ciro.
REGIONAL ELECTIONS
- Do you have paper and pen?
- Yes.
Give it to me. Hurry.
Hurry! Give it to me.
Good evening.
This way.
S'il vous plait.
Vitalij Jeremenko.
Speak up.
Signor Conte
would like to solve the problem.
Leaving he tell us?
No.
So he will not solve the problem.
He wants to do business with you.
Jeremenko never share his stuff with anyone.
What will he do with his stuff?
The system has a major impact here.
It is easier to work with us.
There is enough for everyone. Is better
to be friends than to be enemies.
- What is it?
- The winners of the next municipal elections.
They determine
what needs to be built and by whom.
And the technicians from the housing
commission and those who make concessions.
We know them. We pay them.
With them are all projects approved.
Without them you can buy
all the reasons you want.
It will not take
a building permit after 10 years.
Fifty fifty.
Our friendships here will also be yours.
Do you like to play games with people?
They are only candidates.
No one knows who wins.
But it is true that I have
more friends here than we have.
It is important to have friends.
- Friends.
We share it.
Fifty fifty.
Jeremenko also likes to play tricks.
Russian roulette.
Do you know what it is?
But this is Jeremenkos variant of it.
I is part of the system.
If I disappear,
it means that we were not in agreement.
Those who sent you, know
that you may not return.
You are not
particularly important for those Ciro.
Half the chances are better than no chance.
Fifty-fifty.
- Do it.
Look into the light.
When it is turned on, you shoot.
Friends.
- I said 60% to me, 40% of them.
- Salvatore.
However, 50 and 50 is better than nothing.
Now you must keep your word.
We forget about the past,
and marokkaneren is ours.
I have a better suggestion.
If you go over to me, your life will change.
I'm honored.
But I already have my own.
And I decide.
Do you really?
Why did they send you saw it,
where you risked to die?
It is, as it is.
I'm fine where I am.
I hope that it will always be that way.
- Hello, lawyer.
- Hello, donna Imma.
Why the urgency?
Has there been Pietro something?
Your husband is furious.
Ciro in Spain and Gennaro
South America was not his orders.
Wait a minute.
- I forgot something.
- I'll wait here.
What do you mean? Is Gennaro here?
- He's gone.
- Where is he?
I do not know. Only donna Imma
and Baroncino know where he is.
- Hurry.
What are we?
We're going home to Savastano.
- Are you okay?
- Cut the crap, Imma.
You must explain to me
what the hell is going on.
What is it you want to say?
I have always stood by your side.
Now you're not here.
But I'm still here.
IN THE NEXT SECTION
translation by rdgh
- www.addic7ed.com -
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app