There is a place not far from here
where you could be feared and respected.
Eight men who support
Hamund. You said it yourself.
We kill him, they all
become threats to both of us.
They disappear all at once tonight.
Between you and Flint, I'm not
certain who I should be more afraid of.
- Leave with me.
- I've spent my life trying to build something here.
- (sobbing)
- What if I forgo payment for the schedule
in exchange for my share of the prize?
When the time comes for me
to reveal the last piece,
I will be right by your side.
It wasn't Singleton that stole the page.
- It was him.
- You're lying to them.
If no one knows, everyone wins.
I believe in this place.
If there's anyone who can do
what's necessary to make it
something better, it's you.
Once we have the money, Flint dies.
- No argument.
- Not from me.
(theme music playing)
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
(rattling)
(music playing)
(thumping, squeaking)
(thunder rumbling)
ַa va?
Mr. Rackham, a word.
I've been expecting you, please Sit.
Won't you tell me what you
think of our little production?
The theme is "Evenings in Paris."
I'll give you three
guesses whose idea it was.
Mr. Rackham, I just saw the bursar.
He says I'm no longer to
receive my distribution
of the house's profits. Your instruction?
Yes, I did some rough
calculations to figure the amount
you've been skimming from the take
since we first began this arrangement.
It only seems fair to garnish
your proceeds to account for it.
(laughs) Mr. Rackham, I
understand your new friend
has helped to bring the girls into line,
has them reporting their
income in a most honest fashion.
That must be very nice for you.
But let us get something very straight.
I'm not one of the girls.
I will have my cut
or everyone in this street will
know what became of Mr. Noonan.
- You would do that?
- Don't you dare doubt it.
Well, Mrs. Mapleton, that sounds
like gross insubordination to me.
That, coupled with the graft
you've been responsible for,
leaves me with no choice but to
terminate your employment here.
- What?
- You're dismissed.
Thank you for your service.
Pardon me, but have you lost your mind?
Not that I'm aware of, no.
I just told you that I am fully willing
to inform every merchant in Nassau
that you murdered your way
into ownership of this place.
They will band together to see you hanged.
Which ones exactly?
Which merchants will
see Mr. Rackham hanged?
Mr. Connors the wheelwright?
(laughing)
Or perhaps Mr. Peterson the butcher.
Maybe Mr. Rusch the lapidary?
They all have enjoyed
steep discounts here lately.
Affordable now that the
books are in good order.
I wonder, given their fondness
for the new management,
which one of them would much care
what you think happened to Mr. Noonan?
You forgot the only
name that matters, dear.
The lady across the street.
She finds out about this...
Oh, Madam Guthrie knows.
She's fine with it.
But by all means, go ahead, tell her
again. I can't see any harm in it.
You will regret this, sir.
I'm sure I won't. Au revoir.
(thunder rumbles)
(chuckles)
Please don't judge me,
but I really enjoyed that.
You do not believe she will
attempt to strike back at you?
I wouldn't put it past her.
But at the moment I'll live with
the potential for future trouble
over the certainty of actual
trouble she was causing.
To a profitable venture.
And a partner significantly
more pleasing to the eye.
(wind whistling)
(crewmen yelling)
(music playing)
(men chatting)
What am I supposed to do with this?
If he's to continue on the ship, the
crutch is too much of an impediment.
He shall have to wear this
whether he likes it or not.
Come on, Randall.
Dr. Howell made this 'specially for you.
Help you move around better.
Perhaps you'll even be able to visit the
shitter once in a while without needing my help.
Whoa, easy there.
You're responsible for him.
You figure it out.
"Oh, Mr. Silver."
How can I ever thank you?
First you save me from ending up as
a stain on the Walrus's underside.
Then you secured my position on the crew
on the verge of an historic haul.
And if that weren't enough,
you're still trying to
find something comfortable
to put at the end of my stump.
"From the bottom of my heart, thank you."
You're welcome.
(thumps)
(thunder crackles)
Launch from the Ranger.
Captain Gates is coming over.
Crazy bastard.
What could be so fucking important
that he has to row through
all that shit out there?
(thunder crackles)
(grunting)
We make landfall in the morning.
The last part of the
schedule if you don't mind.
What's that?
My own reconnaissance.
There are a dozen bays and inlets
within a day's journey from here
that will make reasonable locations
for the Urca to take on water.
If the course you write
down leads to one of them,
odds are that your information is accurate.
And if it doesn't?
(thunder crackles)
Division Bay.
The course leads to Division Bay.
Shoals on the eastern shore,
but if we approach from the windward,
we should be able to take
up a strong opening position.
Take this to Mr. De Groot.
Tell him to adjust our course accordingly
and set up our final
approach for the morning.
Something else?
Well, now that I've fulfilled
my end of the bargain,
I'm just wondering where you and I stand.
Keep wondering.
I best be getting back.
Let's not tempt fate.
Talbot Rhodes. Private stock.
I've been waiting for an occasion.
My reckoning is tomorrow
we'll either be able to
afford a lot more of it or...
We'll be too dead to care.
(clucking)
(music continues)
(retching)
(knocking)
Captain asked me to pass these to you.
A new course.
The captain accepted the last
segment of the Urca route as valid?
One thing you should not doubt.
Certainty is not a word
I throw around lightly.
Now this information, I am
quite certain I have it right.
(door opens, closes)
That man has a strange way of handling
the prospect of imminent
wealth beyond reason.
Ma'am.
What are you doing here?
Captain Hornigold asked me to sit in
on Captain Lawrence's final
preparations before departure.
They're just finishing upstairs.
Mm.
I'm fine.
Believe it or not, this
place didn't collapse
the moment you walked out the door.
You really believe my
concern is for this place?
It's a ship killer out there.
I can't even imagine what
it's like further north.
You'd been opposed to hunting
the Urca from the beginning.
Perhaps God's on your side of this one.
I just think of all the trouble
that fucking schedule caused.
The trouble it caused Max and I.
Caused you and I.
The thought that it could all
end up being for nothing...
Perhaps the trouble was
going to happen anyway.
Schedule or no.
Perhaps.
Tomorrow a thing that you conceived
out of thin air becomes real.
A thing that will give this place
a chance to find some
small measure of peace.
That is not nothing.
(thunder rumbles)
Henderson?
It wasn't Henderson.
It was something like
Henderson. Harrison? Harvey?
I don't know who the
fuck you're talking about.
The man that nicked that
bottle was called Cregg.
Cregg! That's him. Cregg.
Mr. Cregg. Carpenter's mate.
Had a nose for sniffing out booze
on a prize ship like a fucking bloodhound.
Oh, Cregg. I remember
walking in on him once,
digging through a stash on a prize.
(laughs) He...
he found this bottle of
booze behind a baseboard.
Now he's convinced that the prize
captain's been hiding his best liquor.
So he pops the cork and takes this big swig
in front of all of us.
- And it was piss.
- It was piss.
(both laughing)
Aye, Cregg.
- Oh, God.
- Flint: Oh, Cregg.
I brought him over with me, you know.
We served together under
Avery when we was kids.
Huh. He was my first bunkmate.
For years he went on how he'd got this
huge stash hidden away.
And I should live to survive him
because one day I will be a rich man.
As you know, we lost him on the Pembroke.
So I open his locker and what do I find?
12 pesos, a busted pocket watch,
and a letter with instructions
to deliver it to his sister in New York.
Lying sack of shit
was Mr. Cregg.
So I bought the boys
a round with the pesos,
traded the pocket watch for a bit of tail,
and spent two weeks that winter in New York
trying to deliver that
fucking letter to his sister.
Looked high and low.
Never found her.
So on the way home,
I waited till we were in open water
and I could see no land in any direction,
and I dropped it over the side.
Returned to the sea.
There are no legacies
in this life, are there?
No monuments. No history.
Just the water.
It pays us
and then it claims us.
Swallows us whole.
As if we'd never been here at all.
Well...
I better be getting back.
(door creaks, closes)
(children talking)
(men grunting)
How the fuck can you cut Mapleton
loose without even telling me?
I'm sorry. I wasn't aware you
were her attorney in this matter.
She'll run her mouth all over
the fucking island about Noonan.
Who cares? The only people who
could conceivably make trouble for us
are currently elbow deep in
free prostitute downstairs.
What's worse, you keep
counsel with a whore about it.
Wait, what?
You think you can trust her, you dumb shit?
That's what this is about? Max?
You fucked her, didn't you?
Jesus H. Christ. I can't win with you.
She's in the camp with the
men and it's, "Come on, Jack",
let's go kill everybody and see
if we can't get her out of there.
"Hope you don't mind. Made
that decision on your behalf."
And now she's out, making us
a small fortune, by the way,
and you're pissed off about that, too.
Might you consider making up your
fucking mind about it, please?
- Fuck you, Jack.
- "Fuck you, Jack."
Yes, I know. Fuck me.
(door slams)
Listen here!
When we crest the point ahead
and spot the Urca in anchor,
we'll begin our final run at her.
- Take it.
- The Spanish banner may earn us a few hundred yards
of confusion before the captain
identifies us and opens fire.
So we'll close fast on her,
hammer her well with our guns,
and then take the fight to her decks.
That fight will be the fight of our lives,
make no mistake.
But on the other side
lies paradise.
(cheering)
I'll see you there. Mr. De Groot?
A full complement, if you please.
- (whistles)
- Signal the Ranger.
- Aye, captain.
- Full sail, final approach.
Check our position.
- This is the course.
- Well, check it again.
Captain, this is the
location you requested.
Your true manifest. Your false manifest.
And, most importantly, your bribe money.
Godspeed, Captain.
Perhaps we should go over
the details one more time.
The harbormaster's name is Singer.
The foreman's name is Smith.
The warehouse manager's Clay,
and the customs man is Kent.
Now if you don't let me board my ship
and leave this place,
none of it will matter
as the goods in my hold will
be rotten by the time I arrive.
- Goodbye.
- Godspeed.
I have to hand it to you,
you said you'd rebuild things
here without your father,
and damned if you didn't do just that.
Still one step yet to accomplish.
Removing my father entirely.
Excuse me?
I know he's out in the Underhill estate.
If you think he isn't
scheming to undo everything
we've done here, you're kidding yourself.
You are truly amazing.
In a moment when stability is at
hand and the world is at your feet,
your first instinct is to go out
in search of someone new to fight.
Captain, a moment.
God.
Can't believe you left
me for that old lady.
Captain Hornigold is right.
(cannon fire blasts)
What the fuck?
- Where did that come from?
- (Cannon fire rumbles)
Jesus Christ, Ben, why are your
men firing on their own ship?
My men aren't the ones doing the firing.
(cannon fire continues)
We need to get you off the beach now.
Is someone shooting the guns off out here?
What the hell is going on?
Someone has taken over the fort.
(cannon fire continues)
Captain, after an inventory of our stores,
the men have assented to your plan.
Provided we find a suitable
place to land the Walrus,
you'll have two days to send out scouts
and hopefully locate the Urca.
Given their mood, I'd say we
were lucky to get that long.
Do it, then.
- What?
- It's Mr. De Groot.
He's put his foot down.
Once we make landfall, he
wants Flint tried immediately.
Oh, Jesus.
He's bitter about the fact that we
didn't listen to him regarding the cook.
He says there's no Urca out here
and that justice has
been delayed long enough.
That's not gonna happen,
so let's discuss reality.
He said that you'd say that.
And after all your talk,
you're just protecting Flint.
I'm protecting all of us.
These men are right on the edge
and he wants to rile them up more
by talking about a lying, thieving captain,
then stand on a deserted beach
and talk about an election.
Before you know it, half a dozen men
will have laid claim to the captaincy.
Camps will divide.
It won't be dark yet
before the fighting starts.
We're gonna see Flint pay for his crimes.
But we'll do it at home
and we'll do it like civilized men.
That's how we avoid the abyss.
We knew you spent the
night drinking together.
How can we take you at your word?
You don't have to take my word.
Good enough for you?
Mr. Gates...
Logan: Sails!
To the south!
Is it the Urca?
Captain, is it her?
Captain, is it the Urca?
Man-of-war! She's a man-of-war!
Spanish banners!
In less than half an hour,
she'll be right on top of us.
Get orders to the Ranger.
Tell her to raise the black
and fire two shots over our bow.
- Mr. De Groot.
- Captain?
Rig a spring to the forward
anchor, then drop her immediately.
Drop anchor?
You mean to fight her?
You all have your orders!
Captain, join me.
- We don't have time.
- Make time.
If he engages that ship
in battle, we're dead.
- I know.
- I know you know.
But does Mr. Gates?
I can't let you go down this road.
As far that man-of-war knows,
we're Spanish merchantmen
under attack by pirate raiders.
We order the Ranger to flee,
the Spaniard passes us to give chase,
and before she realizes her
error, we've got her trapped.
She's got 100 guns.
We do this properly, she'll
never get a chance to use them.
We'll rake her stern to bow,
the Ranger will rake her bow to stern.
With a little luck, we'll
hammer her into submission
before she can bring
her broadsides to bear.
To accomplish what, exactly?
The Urca. She's here. Can't you see that?
All I can see is an empty bay,
a guardacosta warship,
and a captain that's lost
his fucking grip on reality.
Guardacosta? You think
that ship's here on patrol?
That she just happened by
this place at this time?
That ship is an escort.
It's the only explanation.
The Urca has no escort.
Was that not the justification
for this entire endeavor?
They altered their plans.
Found a ship they could spare.
I'm taking the Ranger and I'm leaving.
What did you just say?
I'm gonna weigh anchor and
I'm gonna make a run for it.
If I can keep ahead of it before dark,
there's just a chance we can slip away.
Without the Ranger, I have
no chance against that ship.
I know.
So you're deliberately
challenging my authority here?
Deliberately violating your duty?
My duty?
My duty is to them, not to you.
Although I have violated it more times
than I can remember in your defense.
Helped you deceive good men
who put their trust in
me because I was convinced
they would be better off for it.
Well, not here. Not this.
This is fucking madness.
Mr. Gates, if you walk through that door
with the intent of subverting my plans,
I will have no alternative but to
interpret that as an incitement of mutiny.
You think I'm inciting mutiny?
- You are inciting mutiny.
- I'm managing one!
There are men out there right now
that know about Singleton,
the book, the cook, all of it.
They know. And they mean
to see you hanged for it.
You told them?
After Billy, I just...
I didn't want to believe you could be
capable of doing something like that.
But I couldn't convince
myself that you weren't.
That's when I realized,
this has got to end.
So what, then?
You preside over a trial
that sees me hanged?
No.
We're going to go home
and I will see you and
Mrs. Barlow secreted away
before anybody knows you're gone.
You're gonna go to Boston.
You're gonna take the pardon
that she's offered you.
And that is the last that you
and I will ever see of each other.
Please.
Please, don't do this.
I'm sorry.
Take a moment.
I'll deal with them.
(door opens)
(choking)
This is not what I wanted.
(whimpers) I'm sorry.
(cracks)
I'm sorry.
(sobbing) I'm sorry.
(sobs)
I'm sorry.
(door creaks)
I came to lend credence to your case
that the Urca is still to be won.
What the fuck are you doing to him?
- Making sure there's nothing incriminating...
- Stop. Stop.
There's no way out of this.
Take it from me,
there's always a way.
Sir.
- What is it?
- A small band of men were seen approaching the fort
from the west this morning. No
one's been able to identify them.
Are all the home crews accounted for?
Aye. Every one. They had
nothing to do with this.
Naft: Could this be a first move
by England to reclaim the island?
Frasier: Without a single ship involved?
This does not have the air of a
state move. This is something else.
Captain, how easily are the great guns
- on the fort repositioned?
- What difference does that make?
He's asking if the fort
can turn her guns around
and bring them to bear
on the street... on us.
Let's hope whomever's up there is
not mad enough to consider that.
That's less than confidence-inspiring.
I have lieutenants calling in favors
from the crews of the
Colonial Dawn and the Medusa.
I'll have 250 men assembled and ready
to storm the fort in a matter of hours.
By first light tomorrow,
I'll be back in my chair
and whoever did this will
be hanging by his goddamn...
- What is it?
- Quick, you all need to see this.
Man: Go back inside.
Miss Guthrie.
I think it's time we talked.
Mr. Gates's heart has given out.
He's dead?
Mr. Logan.
Signal Mr. Thompson on the Ranger.
Inform him he's now in command.
His orders are to sail north.
When we fire on the target, he's to
tack hard to port and do the same.
Hoist the signals from the
foremast below the yard.
Get 'em up and down quickly
before the Spaniard sees them.
(door closes)
The question you need to ask yourself
is "What good can I do?"
You can call this murder.
A number of the men might even believe you,
but will that be enough
to stop this fight that is about to happen?
Because if it's not, a fight we might win
becomes a battle we are doomed to lose.
Because the men went into it
infected with your suspicions,
with your doubts.
So, Mr. Quartermaster,
is that truly what's
in their best interests?
St. Augustine.
Beg pardon?
When the warship draws close,
she'll ask our last port of call.
St. Augustine's the closest.
And as she's likely a customs ship,
we must identify our cargo
as anything but tobacco.
Seville regulates the trade heavily.
Thank you, Mr. Dufresne.
What the fuck did you do?
Spend enough time on an island,
begin to forget there's
a whole world out there.
A world where the rules are different.
I went out there, found men
who don't know the rules here
and who don't much care to learn them.
They helped me surprise
Captain Hornigold's men,
we took his fort, and not
once were any of them burdened
with the thought, "What if this
were to upset Eleanor Guthrie?"
Well, they're about to
learn the rules, Charles.
The hard way. You think
I'm gonna let this stand?
That Hornigold will? We have men lining up
in droves to back us in retaking it.
I'd expect nothing less.
Just out of curiosity,
how long do you think that's gonna take?
Can you take back that fort before...
I sink another ship in the bay?
Three more?
All of them?
Who knows?
If my men hold out long enough,
we may just decide to sink the Walrus
when she returns with
your precious Spanish gold
just out of spite.
So that's what this is.
You're annoyed at me, so you're
gonna destroy everything I've built.
Never said I wanted to destroy anything.
Then what do you want?
Hornigold controlled the fort.
The fort controls the bay.
The bay controls commerce.
That meant he was your partner.
Now, I control the fort.
So I will be your partner.
You are kidding me.
I was a tenant in this
place for a long time.
Didn't work out so well.
Now I'd like a stake.
You've absolutely lost your mind.
I remember the first time I saw you.
You were about 13.
You'd snuck down to the beach
despite Mr. Scott's rules forbidding it.
A girl that age
looking like you did.
And you just walked up
and down between the camps
like you owned the place.
Fearless.
Then you saw me watching
you and you didn't look away.
Didn't cower.
You just gave me this look...
this little smile...
that said you refused to be afraid of me.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I know you.
Better than your father, better than Scott.
Maybe better than anyone.
You don't give a shit
about money or respect.
Or the things you've built here.
I think you're just tired of fathers
telling you what to do.
And so I'm offering you
a life free from them.
With me in that fort, you do as you like.
As long as it doesn't cross me,
you'll hear no complaints.
You know I have no choice but to say yes.
But before I do, know this,
you'll sit in that fort for a
while. You'll get comfortable.
And that's the day I'm
gonna push you and your men
right into the fucking sea.
God, I missed that look.
Ben.
What the hell did he say?
He wants your seat on the
consortium. To be a partner to us.
Well, I have 300 men out there
more than happy to deny him.
- You can't, Ben.
- Oh, watch me.
I told him about the tunnels.
The tunnels that you would use to
launch a surprise attack into the fort.
- I told him.
- Jesus!
You told me to keep emotion
from clouding judgment.
To act in everyone's best interest.
I believe that's what I'm doing.
This is not the end of this.
Captain. Welcome back.
I hear congratulations are in order.
Steward of the fort. Stroke of pure genius.
In some ways, Jack, it had to come to this.
- Don't you think?
- Come to what?
Me deciding if you live or die.
Captain, I don't know what you've heard...
Hamund pulls you out of bed...
marches you down to the wrecks
to look for a stash of stolen pearls.
And somehow, only you and
your dog make it back alive.
- (sighs)
- Quite a moment.
Jack Rackham with nothing to say.
Had I a shrewd quartermaster right now,
he would tell me that I
can't let what you did stand.
He would say an offense like that
demanded an example be made of both of you.
The bloodier the better.
But today, I'm a little less worried
about perception than I used to be.
As long as I hold that fort,
doesn't really matter.
So the street will know what you did.
They will know you betrayed
your brothers for a woman.
That story will spread far and wide
and you'll never sail
beneath the black again.
You'll sit in this place and rot
with the rest of the whores.
Something tells me that'll
sting worse than dying.
Loyalty, Jack.
It's supposed to mean something.
It does to me, anyway.
Oh.
Love what you've done with the place.
(speaking Spanish)
Here she comes.
Cazadora. Marco Fernandez, captain.
Cazadora. Marco Fernandez, capitבn.
(speaking Spanish)
St, Augustine. Tobacco trade.
If I'm not mistaken,
you told him to name us
anything but a tobacco trader, did you not?
I did.
He means to prove that that
ship is not guardacosta.
That it's here for the same reason we are.
The Urca.
That ship lets us pass,
he will have managed to both
renew the men's lust for gold
and their faith in his judgment.
(speaking Spanish)
Hello.
All hands to their stations.
Quietly, if you please.
At 300 yards, we open fire.
Time and again he gambles with our lives.
That is, when he's not
taking them in cold blood.
And once more his influence grows.
And we're at his mercy with
no way to challenge him.
No, sir.
It only looks that way.
Turn us around slowly, boys.
They need to think we're just drifting.
Range?
Hundred yards, Captain.
- Open.
- Crewman: Open.
(men shouting)
- Come right a few degrees.
- Aye, Captain.
We only get one shot at
this. We miss, we die.
- Clear, tack hull.
- Range?
Approaching 200 yards, Captain.
All crews, fire on my mark.
Steady.
Almost there.
Captain Flint.
As quartermaster, I hereby accuse you
of tyrannical crimes against your crew.
All crews, fire!
Dufresne: Belay that order!
Your duties as a member of
this crew have reached an end.
Take a seat.
Beginning with the
murders of Mr. Singleton,
Billy Bones, and Mr. Gates.
What exactly do you hope
to accomplish by doing this?
In your case, Mr. Silver, justice.
Once Dufresne exposes Flint's
lies in their totality,
the crew are gonna want
answers from you, too.
And as I explained to Mr. Dufresne,
it's his word against Flint's.
Why would anyone believe him?
I hold in my hand a letter
written by Mr. Gates
confessing his knowledge
and complicity in the
captain's myriad crimes.
We're going to lose them.
We don't have time for this.
As well as his knowledge of the
captain's continued treachery
up to and including his plan to steal
a portion of the treasure
fleet proceeds for himself.
I gave you all an order! Fire!
Fire!
Mr. Logan.
It's in Mr. Gates's hand.
Where are you going?
- (gunshot flashes)
- (Grunts)
(groans)
(grunting)
Justice, thief.
This time there's no escaping it.
You're welcome.
Raise the sails. We're going home.
Who's shooting?!
Sorry.
Had to be done.
There's no running now.
Logan: The Ranger's coming about.
The Spaniards have got men in the rigging.
Fire, Mr. Dufresne. Everything you've got.
Don't waste this moment.
(cannon fire blasts)
All cannons, open fire!
Open fire!
(cheering)
(shouting) Reload!
Gunner: Ready with this cannon!
Fire!
The Ranger's opened fire!
Again!
Fire!
She's coming about!
Below!
To your stations!
(cannon fire roars)
(screams)
Set sail!
(men shouting, screaming)
(screams)
Doctor! Doctor!
(screams fade)
- (men screaming)
- (Gasps)
Max: No-man's-land.
There was a time when stopping
halfway across this bridge
would have been unthinkable to you.
How things change.
I can see that.
Max, I know we haven't spoken,
but I just want you to
know how sorry I am...
Don't.
You have nothing to be sorry about.
I was standing between you
and your dreams for this place.
You did what you had to do.
I thought you said this
place was just sand.
Sand has its virtues.
On sand, nothing is fixed.
Nothing is permanent.
And fates change so quickly.
Yesterday Captain Hornigold
was immovable from that fort
and Captain Vane was a beggar.
Now look at them today.
Yesterday I was a whore
of little consequence,
easily dismissed,
easily forgotten.
Today I am a madam
with an income and allies
and a woman who has learned
the most important of lessons.
Never let anyone stand in
between you and your ambitions.
Thank you for teaching it to me.
Ma'am, they're ready.
Congratulations on the launch
of your endeavor, by the way.
Today you have everything
you have ever wanted.
I suppose we can only guess
what tomorrow will bring.
(coughing)
They think it'll be a while
before she sails again.
In the meantime, you
and I have been charged
with provoking this whole mess.
Why am I still alive?
Why didn't you kill me?
Get him up.
(groans)
Told you I was certain about my
information regarding the Urca.
Unfortunately, you and I failed
to take into account the weather.
The Urca de Lima wrecked at sea last night.
Dashed by the storm.
(theme music playing)
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN