SILVER: Dobbs assaulted him,
and he believes him responsible
for choosing the men to
be interrogated by them.
But it's been sorted.
I had three men hold him down
while Dooley and Wayne
administered a beating.
ELLERS: The governor in Nassau
hanged a pirate in the square.
The pirate was Charles Vane.
What do you want to do about it?
BILLY: He knew it was the
only way to start it.
Start what?
The resistance in Nassau
is now under way.
QUEEN: How long before
their force arrives?
A week.
Then we have much preparation
to do and little time to do it.
Captain Hornigold will be sailing
in consort with you.
I know this enemy.
He took that cache with
the express purpose
of compelling us to commit your force
to a battlefield of his choosing.
If you allow him to dictate
the terms of battle,
you court a disastrous outcome.
[theme music playing]
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
[crickets chirping] [shoveling]
[shoveling]
SILVER: You sure this is wise?
At the end of the day,
secrets among friends
are the source of all
good things gone wrong.
Is that what we are now?
Friends?
RACKHAM: He wasn't talking about you.
He's talking about our
hostess, the queen.
That said, you're wrong. He's right.
The safest place for
this isn't behind walls
or guarded with guns.
The safest place lives outside the realm
of anyone's awareness.
If the English can't find it,
they can't take it.
I told them we were taking
it, just not where.
She agreed it was best for all
for its whereabouts to remain unknown,
provided that you were among the circle
that knew of it.
You they trust above any of us
not to betray for money.
The irony wasn't lost on either of us.
Well, now that you've been fetched,
much to do.
A war to plan for.
I've heard you use that
word a thousand times.
A war against England,
now a war to reclaim Nassau.
But hearing him use it just now,
so near the actual arrival of it,
it sounds different.
It feels different.
Not far from here, the
fortifications are already built
from which in a few days' time
you'll look out and stare
down King George's navy.
Are you having second thoughts?
Aren't you?
All of the blood that's
about to be spilt,
all the things about to
be lost... aren't you?
Well, I wish it wasn't necessary,
if that's what you're asking.
[grunts]
When we were becalmed,
I told Billy I believed
your darkest thoughts
somehow had the ability
to manifest themselves upon our reality.
That your anger over the
murder of Mrs. Barlow
became the storm into
which we all battled.
That your despair over her death
became the doldrums
into which we all sank.
In my defense, I hadn't had anything
to eat or drink in a while.
But the truth of it,
I'm not sure it was that far off.
Your demons are a part of our reality.
Such is the nature of the
influence you wield.
Some of those demands
I've come to know...
but the one in whose name
this war is to be fought...
it is still a stranger to me.
Before this war actually begins,
I'm asking where it actually began.
Will you tell me?
[cannons firing]
[men shouting]
[shouting continues]
[cannon fire continues]
[shouting]
[cannonball whistling] [screams]
[screams, groaning]
[men shouting]
[cannon fire continues]
[ship's bell ringing]
Oh, Jesus.
They are not fucking around, are they?
We're supposed to sail into that?
One ship against their entire fleet?
A favorable wind.
We'll be upon them quickly.
We'll take fire, obviously.
If we can just get our vanguard
aboard one of their ships,
we could disrupt their entire line.
Do not look at me like that.
This is the plan.
Harass their line.
We create uncertainty
in the minds of their
soldiers on the ground
and undermine their
confidence in their command.
Yeah, and I know how they'll feel.
MAN: Sails! East-southeast!
East?
Six ships. British colors.
Who the fuck is that?
Reinforcements, likely.
It seems Governor Rogers
was able to enlist
the aid of one of his colleagues.
I'll put a launch in the water now.
What for?
To inform Captain Flint
- so he can make his retreat.
- [chuckles]
There could be hundreds of
soldiers aboard those ships.
The captain's battle plan
does not take into account
a force that large.
Captain Flint's battle plan
does not take into account his retreat.
There is nowhere to retreat to.
And given how much we have
sacrificed to earn this battle,
how can we do anything
other than see it through?
My friend may have given his
life to earn this battle.
I understand the obligation
you are feeling to succeed,
but there comes a certain point
where one must accept what
is painfully obvious.
- How many ships?
- What?
The second fleet...
How many ships?
MAN: Six sets of sails!
Describe them, please.
What difference does it make?
Shut up.
The flotilla...
Describe them.
Three tall ships!
Two sloop!
- One man of war.
- And one man of war.
Make a course for that
second flotilla, please.
You're going to attack them?
Time is short, please.
Get us under way.
Get us under way!
[shouting]
[shouting continues]
MAN: Right flank, kneel!
Fire!
[man shouting]
[gunfire, shouting continues]
[grunts]
MAN: Reload!
MAN: Bring the mortars forward!
- Mortars.
- Mortars!
Concentrate on the mortars!
[screaming]
[screams]
MAN: Reload!
MAN #2: Three paces forward!
Present!
Fire!
Company, form into two ranks!
Now!
Second cannons!
MAN: Take cover!
[shouting continues]
MAN: Fire!
Mortars in position!
Fire!
[screams]
Captain, it's time!
- Not yet.
- Fire!
MAN #3: Two inches! Two inches!
Fire!
[gunshots, cannon fire echoing]
Captain, we need to fall back.
Fire!
[yelps]
Smoke!
- MAN: Smoke!
- MAN #2: Smoke!
MAN: Form into two ranks!
Formation forward!
- Fall back!
- MAN: Fall back!
- MAN #2: Retreat!
- FLINT: Fall back!
[shouting continues]
MAN: Hold your fire!
- MAN #2: Hold your fire!
- First company, prepare to move out!
I wouldn't do that.
Beg your pardon?
MAN: Stand easy!
He asked for this fight, Major.
He didn't do so without a plan.
And I promise you,
bumbling into a hasty retreat
wasn't a part of it.
Bumbling?
They were overwhelmed
by a superior force.
He wants us to pursue him.
He wants you to pursue him.
A tactical withdrawal to
guide us into an ambush.
Am I to believe he sacrificed
over 50 of his men,
led them into a massacre deliberately,
just to entice us to chase him?
You don't know that
man, Major, but I do.
He's quite capable of what
you suggest and more.
[chattering]
[murmuring]
Reflected there.
Is everything all right?
Show her what you showed to me.
"To the first to betray,
I offer the first chance to repent.
Remove the captain.
You have until nightfall."
Where did you get this?
It was sitting at the foot of my bed
when I woke this morning.
Someone left it while I slept.
The message, it would seem, is clear.
There is a voice out there
yet to identify itself
that wants to see Captain Vane's remains
removed from the gibbet in the square.
Why does it look like this?
An old wives' tale. Pirate lore.
Avery's maiden crew
was said to deliver the black spot
as a warning to wayward crew members.
Ignored on pain of death.
MORTON: I knew men when I was
young who sailed with Avery.
It was a bullshit story then,
and it's no less a bullshit story now.
Ma'am, cowards send notes.
The form of the threat may
not rightly be the issue.
We are aware there is
dissent on the street.
Perhaps removing the gibbet
would go a long way towards settling
whatever unrest may be brewing.
SOAMES: You're suggesting
that the governor comply
with an anonymous threat?
I am suggesting the gibbet
could be seen by some
to be inflammatory.
The point has been made.
The law has been satisfied.
It is a well-settled
statement of resolve
to maintain the display.
If it is removed in the
light of this threat,
in the light of Captain
Flint's standing ultimatum
against the use of it, would it not
worry you that it might appear weak?
It certainly worries me
to make self-defeating mistakes
out of fear of appearing weak.
ELEANOR: No, he's right.
He's right.
It gives me no pleasure having it there,
no matter what the street may say.
But to remove it in this moment
threatens to undermine confidence
in the governor's leadership.
That said, at the end
of three days' time,
I want it down and gone,
not a minute longer.
If you would like me
to form a small detail
to offer you protection
in the meantime...
If anyone has a problem with
my allegiance to the Crown,
my men and I are happy
to address it with them.
Ma'am?
Excuse me.
[murmuring]
You should be in bed.
I've spent enough time in bed.
I did what I did.
I know how it seems,
to the street, to you,
but please understand...
It seems...
as though a very difficult
thing was done.
It seems as though I am fortunate
you had the courage to do it.
You have enemies here.
Then let them be my enemies as well.
Any and all of them.
And let them come.
[birds squawking]
[wood creaking]
MAN: As you were.
[men chattering]
Six ships...
Two sloops, man of war...
It's a familiar combination.
I once had a fleet of that makeup.
MAN: Get her cleaned up, boy!
[men shouting indistinctly]
I came looking for Flint, not you.
Where is he?
He's currently being pummeled
by half the British navy
just beyond the horizon.
The navy?
The war to reclaim Nassau
began here about an hour ago.
The entirety of the British fleet
under the command of
Governor Rogers is in play.
I'd like to think that you're
here to join our effort,
but I fear the reason for your arrival
is something other than that.
Charles is dead.
The governor in Nassau
hung him in the square.
On the island I helped build,
he thought he could do that
and face no consequences.
He failed to account for me.
British law sentenced him,
but I think you and I
both know who it was
that fashioned that noose,
and it was no "he."
I look forward to seeing
Miss Guthrie again
and settling Charles' account with her.
But there is no victory over her
without a victory here today.
That much is clear.
Will you help us find it?
FLINT: Madness is such a
hard thing to define,
which makes it such an easy label
to affix to one's enemies.
Once it had been applied to Thomas,
once our relationship had been exposed,
defiled, scandalized...
everything ended.
There were times that I was persuaded
to sue for peace since then,
but that was the day
that on some level I knew...
that England was broken...
and that sooner or later a
good man must resist it.
I don't know what to say.
You don't need to say anything.
You asked me where I began,
and I felt that you were
entitled to an answer...
To the truth.
I appreciate that.
And I am genuinely sorry.
But you can see how this
might be of particular
and immediate concern for me.
I can?
Well, before today I knew of two people
who managed to truly know you,
to gain your trust, to be your partner,
and they both ended up dead
while playing the role.
- Now, wait a minute...
- Now you're telling me
there's a third member of this class,
making it even less credible
to characterize Mr. Gates'
and Mrs. Barlow's deaths as bad luck.
It would seem that those
closest to you meet their end
not just during their relationship,
but because of it.
And as I sit here, I'm acutely aware
there may be no one closer to you
in the world right now than I.
What exactly are you saying?
That I've somehow sought
out my own tragedies?
Did you not tell me that
our darkest motives
will conceal themselves from us?
Cloak themselves in whatever they must
in order to move us to action?
And even if that's not true,
a pattern is a pattern,
and only a fool ignores one
because he does not care
for the implications.
So you see yourself as a potential
fourth member of this class,
concerned that your association with me
will lead to your end.
My association with you
began out of necessity,
but I've come to find
a great deal of respect for you.
Perhaps even friendship.
Hmm.
Which is why I find myself
unnerved by the thought
that when this pattern
applies itself to you and I...
that I will be the end of you.
Is that so?
Well, the three who preceded me
all had one thing in common.
They were vulnerable to you.
Had more to lose than you,
less means with which to
protect themselves than you.
Until recently, I thought
that was me as well,
but now...
I don't know that it is anymore.
It is natural for men new to power
to assume that it has no limits.
Trust me. It does.
We agreed that I would select a man
to be responsible for
making a direct move
against Captain Hornigold
once the battle begins.
I chose Mr. Dobbs.
You chose Dobbs?
Why the fuck would you do that?
It's a dangerous errand...
It's more than dangerous.
The entirety of our plan
rests on its success.
Why would you assign it to a man
harboring who knows what sort
of resentment against you?
Because it isn't resentment.
If you had disciplined him,
he would resent you for it,
but towards me...
I don't believe he feels resentment.
I believe he feels shame
for having disappointed me
and a great need to redeem
himself in my eyes.
Send someone else.
It's done.
He knows.
Were I to replace him now,
it might provoke the
response you wish to avoid.
If you're wrong,
if Mr. Dobbs takes this
opportunity to betray you...
to betray us...
this battle will be over
before it ever begins.
Flint sent you to kill me,
yet instead, you surrendered.
Why?
I sailed with that crew for months.
Then they take the side
of those fucking savages
over a man who was supposed
to have been their brother.
Truth is, they didn't
give a shit about me
except that I did their bidding,
so now I'm ready to see it end,
and I can help you end it.
ROLLINS: Says he knows where
the slave camp is located.
Says the cache with the
gems is hidden nearby.
Mr. Carter, please bring
me that man there.
Unfortunately, I've known too
many men from Nassau in my life,
and it's so very hard to know
which can be taken at their word.
Show me that you truly intend
to leave Captain Flint
and your life with him behind you.
Oh, that man will meet the same end
whether you shoot him or
some other man hangs him,
but I'd like to be quite certain
your intentions are true.
[gunshot]
Major, prepare your men.
Sir.
Lieutenant, prepare the men.
Make sure they have plenty of supplies,
water, and ammunition.
We're heading into the forest.
[chattering]
[speaking softly in native language]
[gasps, speaks in native language]
MADI: He was hiding by the water.
Otherwise, everyone is accounted
for and where they belong.
All but you.
You do not feel you
are where you belong.
The men above would fight to protect us.
I should be among them.
If we are to lead them into this war,
we ought to show that we are
willing to lead them through it.
♪
You have protected me for so very long.
It is time I did the same for you.
Did he get it?
Your black spot was delivered, yeah.
- But?
- I saw him.
He was in the tavern
drinking with his men.
They were in high spirits.
And the gibbet remains?
Yeah.
I think it's going to take
more than a note to frighten him.
Of course it is.
It was Mr. Gates who first
told me about the spot.
It kept him awake for three nights.
It wasn't the note or the threat.
It was the idea of Avery himself,
just the awareness that
someone so terrible
- knew your name.
- [chuckles]
I have no doubt that
Captain Throckmorton
is currently unconcerned
with our threat.
We have only just begun
to tell our story.
We haven't yet introduced the villain.
It's been a few days since I told you
of my suspicions about Idelle,
her role in the attack on
the governor's caravan.
One can only assume she
did not act alone,
but had partners in this endeavor.
You did not report this
news to the governor
nor to Miss Guthrie.
Nor did you take any action
to discover who the partners might be.
Until I know how this game will unfold,
I choose to allow the players
to reveal themselves to me
lest I make an enemy out of someone
I may one day wish to call a friend.
- [coat whooshes]
- [gasps]
[women gasping]
This way.
Is it possible one of the governor's
calls for assistance was heard?
- Reinforcements from a sister colony?
- [men chattering]
Flint gave you command of his ship.
Yes.
You can count the things that Flint
and I agree upon on one hand.
But among them is the sincere confusion
as to why Charles invested
any time and energy in you.
I suppose Flint's come to
see that there might be
some capacity in you after all.
And?
And what?
"And" as in it sounded
as if there was more to that thought.
That you might see yourself
agreeing with him again...
about my capacity.
There wasn't any more to
that thought, was there?
MAN: Signal!
On the flagship's mainmast!
[men shouting]
They're showing her
fleet identification,
asking us to verify who we are.
Get my log from below.
You have the proper codes to respond?
I do.
Don't.
Raise the black instead.
♪
Raise the black?
He believes we are beneath him,
tactically incompetent.
Why give him any reason to doubt it?
To be underestimated
is an incredible gift.
Signal the line. Divide the gun crews
and prepare the larboard batteries.
Sir.
Prepare the larboard batteries!
MAN: Prepare the larboard batteries!
[men shouting]
[men chattering]
And did she fight it?
Your mother.
Did she resist your being here?
I believe she wanted to.
I believe every part of her
being was calling out for it.
Then why didn't she?
She has spent so many years
protecting our people,
protecting me.
To put it all in danger now...
it is a necessary sacrifice
if this war is to be won.
But it violates everything she
understands herself to be.
She let me go because she knows
that if we survive this battle today,
she will likely need to step aside
and make room for someone better suited
to do what must be done.
It's a hard thing to look
your successor in the eye
and know that their time is nearing
while yours is almost through.
But as far as successors go,
your mother could do far worse.
[dog barks and howls]
Ma'am!
[barking continues]
- [gunshot]
- Aah!
[groaning]
DOBBS: They'll fight to
the death to defend it.
There's only 100 men, more or less,
left behind to guard it.
The rest are women and children.
And the cache? It's being
guarded there as well?
It's nearby. Buried.
But the one of them who
knows where to find it
is inside that camp,
and he cannot run away.
Get a message to the major.
Tell him he can deploy his
men to this position.
Let's finish this as
quickly as possible.
[chattering]
BONNY: Do you trust him?
What's that?
A few weeks ago, we had a
chance to sail with him.
You said you'd always be
looking over your shoulder,
worried he'd fuck us the
first chance he got.
I will say this for him.
In recent weeks,
among the disturbing number of people
who've tried to kill
one or the both of us,
he is not among them.
Charles was, in some
sense, a son to him,
and Charles was, in some
sense, a brother to us.
I couldn't tell you what
that makes us to him,
but something, perhaps.
Gun crews at the ready!
MAN: Gun crews at the ready!
See you on the other side.
♪
Always.
[men shouting]
Does he actually mean to
exchange broadsides with us?
Pass word up the line.
All ships may fire at will.
Yes, sir.
Gun crews, prepare to engage!
Larboard batteries may fire at will!
[cannon fire continues]
MAN: Open the ports!
Open the ports!
♪
Company, present!
Fire!
Aah!
[gunfire continues]
Defenders across the water
have been rendered largely ineffective.
With any luck, we'll have a
beachhead established in an hour,
find Mr. Silver, the
fugitive Mr. Rackham,
and have the cache in our
possession before the sun sets.
- [gunfire continues]
- Sir.
[clicks tongue] Come.
[men shouting]
[shouting continues]
I once thought that to
lead men in this world,
to be liked was just as good as feared,
and that may very well be true.
But to be both liked
and feared all at once
is an entirely different
state of being...
in which, I believe, at
this moment, I exist alone.
The men need to know they're
in good favor with me.
They need it,
and there is nothing they won't do
to make sure they have it.
Mr. Dobbs will do what I ask of him.
MAN: Fire!
Pull everyone back.
- Sir?
- Pull them back, now!
SILVER: He will lead Captain Hornigold
exactly where I ask him to,
of this I'm sure.
[trumpeting]
But from there, it's up to you.
[grunts]
[shouting]
MAN: We're being ambushed!
[shouting, screaming]
[shouting, screaming continues]
MAN: Company, withdrawal!
[grunts]
[gasping]
[whinnies]
Fire!
[screams]
What the hell is he doing?
Could he mean to board us?
Order the larboard batteries to
concentrate their fire on that ship.
And send word to the
Orion to do the same.
Yes, sir.
All crews, larboard batteries,
target the lead ship!
[men shout] What...?
[men shouting]
Fire! MAN: Fire!
Aim ahead a little more!
MAN: Fire!
- Lead him!
- [grunts]
Aah!
Get to the stern chasers! Now!
Fire!
[screaming]
[cannon fire continues]
[chuckles]
Sir! It's the Orion!
She's been overrun!
Get the gun crews to resume firing.
[men shouting]
How, sir?
Sir?
Shall we prepare to repel boarders?
Cut our...
Our anchor cables
and signal the line to retreat.
[men shouting, screaming]
[grunting]
[spits]
[whinnies]
Come on!
- [whinnies]
- Aah!
♪
[shouts, screams echoing]
[gurgles]
[exhales]
MAN: Company, retreat!
MAN #2: Back! Fall back!
MAN #3: Company, retreat!
Retreat!
Tell your governor!
You tell him I'm coming!
Let us say there is some
merit to your argument.
Let us say that Mr. Dobbs
will do as you ask of him.
I would have to admit in that case
that the world has
shifted beneath our feet
in a most startling way.
But in terms of our future
and the danger that you
believe you may pose to me,
bear this in mind.
I have survived starvation,
a tempest,
pirate hunters,
jealous captains, mutinous crews,
angry lords,
a queen, a king,
and the goddamn British navy.
So to whatever extent
you may be concerned
that some day we will clash,
worried that though today we be friends,
some day you will have no
choice but to be my end,
I wouldn't worry too much.
GARRETT: They call him John the Giant.
They say that he's seven foot tall.
They say that he moves
better on that leg
than most do with the
ones that God gave them.
Why would they say that?
A man walks into a tavern
out of the dead of night,
threatens the entirety of the island,
and then proceeds to remove a
man's head with a metal shoe.
I say that's a story that
stands a strong chance
of seeing itself embellished.
Do we care that it isn't remotely true?
Doesn't matter what's true.
Not now, at any rate.
We're creating the appearance
of a man out of nothing.
The appearance of a man that the
resistance against the English
feels compelled to rally around.
We'll introduce him.
We'll put flesh on him.
We'll give him a soul.
But if the street wants to invest him
with more than we can on our own,
I won't fight them about it.
But hat name isn't
doing anything for us.
We'll have to see about that.
For those of you who have not heard,
the governor has imposed martial law
upon all of Nassau Town in response to
the murder of Captain Throckmorton.
He asks that I convey to
the rest of his council
the contents of the letter
left for him today,
taking responsibility for
Captain Throckmorton's murder.
"I was no one,
and then you came, and my island fell,
and I became something else."
Why not Flint?
Flint?
You want to put a man forward
as the face of our efforts
to oust the English from the island,
why not use Flint?
They all know him already.
They all fear him already.
I've lived too long dependent upon Flint
to be the one to hold
our ranks together.
It's time we finally had an alternative.
"On the night I confiscated
the pardon rolls,
the night I started becoming,
I made clear my position
that there would be two sorts of men
on the island going forward...
Those like Captain Vane,
determined to stand by their
oath to the very end,
and those like Captain Throckmorton,
happy to be the first to betray it.
And thus, as always, to traitors..."
Does he even know?
Mr. Silver?
Does he have any idea
you're using his name?
What flows forth from this house,
starting tonight,
is a new story for Nassau.
I've watched her follow mad men.
I've watched her follow rich men.
I've watched her bow before tyrants.
But now it's time she had a king.
When we're ready, when he's ready,
he'll step into the role
we've created for him...
and lead an impossible army
into an unwinnable war...
and win it.
"Captain Throckmorton's black spot
will not be the last.
Ignore it, and join him.
Heed it, and reclaim
your place amongst us.
Until then, I remain...
Long John Silver."
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
Watch Movies, Series & LiveTV
www.flixify.app