CAR RADIO PLAYS
MAN: Are you happy to be back?
WOMAN: Yes, I am, yup.
Thank God they've done a good job.
Thank you, Robert.
And thank Mark. Thank Mark!
Take care of yourselves,
take care of your neighbours
and take extra care on the roads.
MUSIC: It Won't Always Be Like This
by Inhaler
# Girl, you know this ain't love
# I'm just a bad old beggar
with nothing to do
# It's on you
# And, oh, what else can I do?
# You say that you're not around
# And you don't wanna be found
# Well, I wanna be the best
at what I do
# Oh, what about you?
What about you?
# Play me like a record, baby
# Spin me around,
turn me upside down
# And you don't want me to
# I'll pull the covers
right up over your head
# You're in my head
# It won't always be like this,
be like this
# I'm dead, honey, I'll be dead
# It won't always be like this
# Always be like this... #
MUSIC CONTAINS IN VENUE
HUBBUB
Daddy!
Oh!
You found it.
There was an element of luck.
Come meet Larry.
Are you ready for this?
Can I kill him if I don't like him?
Larry, this is my dad.
Yes, hi, Mr... Mr Brannick.
For God's sake, Larry, it's Tom.
Call me Mr Brannick,
I'll be looking over my
shoulder for my old man.
Good to meet you.
He's a nice lad. Really?
You like him? I do.
Oh!
A little something.
Can I open it now? Mm-hm.
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
Daddy, this is yours.
Your mum and I both had one.
I know.
But you can't give me this.
I want to.
Your mum used to say
it helped her see in the dark.
Thank you.
I love it.
Happy birthday, sweetheart.
PHONE VIBRATES
HE GROANS
Hello.
How long ago?
OK. I'll be there in an hour.
I've got to go to work.
OK.
POLICE CHATTER OVER RADIO
Make and model of the car
match those of Pat Keenan.
Nobody saw it being dumped.
The ferry crew were
the first to notice it
on their way to work at around 7am.
Then the call to us to say he'd been
kidnapped came in at around 7:30.
Confirming it's his vehicle will
take a little longer without
the numberplates. No bodies,
explosives? Divers found nothing.
Let's listen to the phone call.
WOMAN: Police emergency.
MAN: I've taken Pat Keenan.
This is Major White.
HE HANGS UP
Sir! It is his, sir!
Patrick Jarlath Keenan!
Let's issue a missing
person's report.
And his address is flagged
in the system. Sure. Sir.
Sir?
Make sure everyone
has a photo of Keenan.
Something wrong?
Bring everyone over.
All right, everybody!
Pat Keenan, 48,
married, three children,
runs a successful haulage business.
He also has a past as a senior
member of the IRA.
His disappearance
could well be political.
It could also be gang-related.
Keenan is known to have
connections in organised crime.
Could they not just be joyriders?
If the call was wee lads?
They used a paramilitary
authenticating code
which makes that unlikely.
We're looking into it.
Make no mistake - the people Keenan
was associated with in the past
and the ones he's involved
with now are an unsavoury bunch.
I shouldn't need to remind you
that the lines between gang-related
activities and political
paramilitaries are blurred at best,
so tread carefully.
Whoever his associates are,
we'd expect them
to be looking for him already.
No. Hold tight on that.
Take his life apart.
See what you can find
that might point to this.
Phone, financial records, personal
life, work. OK? All right!
Birdy, go down the shops
and houses and see
if there's any CCTV
over the road into the village.
Is there something you're not
telling me?
Yes. Carry on.
PHONE RINGS
DCS Twomey.
Jesus Christ!
Tom Brannick!
Talk about a blast
from the proverbial!
I can indeed.
I'll see you there.
SHIP'S HORN BLASTS IN DISTANCE
Come here!
How's Izzy?
She's third year medicine
at Queen's.
You've done a grand job.
I drove past 19 pubs on the way in,
why'd you want to meet here?
The postcard was taped inside the
wing mirror of Pat Keenan's car.
WOMAN: Police emergency.
MAN: I've taken Pat Keenan.
This is Major White.
Major White? It's in the form
of a loyalist Parliamentary code.
We're looking into it.
It was never proved
but God help us if it's Goliath.
Who else has seen the postcard?
Niamh, and the CSIs
at the scene. Niamh?
My DS, Niamh McGovern.
We have to look into it.
It's more complicated than that.
Why?
The fact that Pat Keenan
is your missing person...
You were on the Goliath case before.
The senior shut you down,
now you're one of the seniors.
You can go after it! Tom, you know
yourself, as soon as word gets out
that an ex-IRA man's gone missing,
all hell could break loose.
You start adding all this,
you'll start a war!
It's in the past.
Best left there.
Not for me.
Life must go on, Tom.
Nothing's going to bring her back.
Think of Izzy.
You've raised her in a world
without all this.
Just...
..find Pat Keenan.
Don't go down any other roads.
You don't know where they lead.
Just his car in the water
and no sign of him? No, ma'am.
Nothing else?
There was a postcard
taped to the wing mirror.
No message.
Does this postcard have a picture?
The cranes of Harland & Wolff.
I've been there to check it out
but nothing.
But the fact that the numberplates
are missing as well, ma'am,
we're into something here,
we just don't know what it is yet.
So what do you want to do next?
Go see the wife, Claire Keenan.
Has she reported him missing?
Not yet.
I suppose even if she wanted to,
she wouldn't report it to us,
she'd go to her own people.
I agree, ma'am,
but we still need to find out
what we can from her. I know.
We need to mind
what we're walking into.
We have a side of our community
that looks at us as the enemy
and the Keenans are right
at the very heart of that.
When did you last see him?
Yesterday. Morning.
Are there any witnesses to that?
I'm his wife. Mrs Keenan...
Sorry, do we need witnesses now
to married life? Mrs Keenan...
Or maybe it's just
the Catholics that do.
Has anyone contacted you
about your husband? No.
What was his car doing in the water?
We don't know that yet.
Is he dead?
We can't speculate.
Well, what CAN you do?
Right, I am not waiting
for you lot to solve this.
You have a much better chance with
us than you do with anyone else.
Mrs Keenan, in cases such as these,
it's best not to tell anyone.
People could take the law
into their own hands,
we risk a much more
volatile situation.
And you could put your husband
in more danger.
Um...
..do you have a toilet?
No, we shit in our hands.
Outside, under the block.
He went up yesterday morning.
For a conference.
And he sent me a text in
the afternoon to say that
something had come up and he was
going to be staying in Belfast.
Did he say where?
The Europa.
Is your husband the type
of man to keep secrets?
In what way? I mean...
..secrets that might
be about his past?
Other women... No.
It could be just the smallest...
I said no.
DRAWERS SLAM
What you doing?
Niamh.
HE WHISPERS
WHISPERS: I fucking knew it.
I couldn't trust youse as far as
I could throw youse. Get out. Out!
Mrs Keenan... Both of you! Now!
She'd never tell if her husband
was up to something.
Pat had a hospital appointment
at noon yesterday. The Royal.
LINE RINGS
We're making enquiries about
a patient called Patrick Keenan.
He was referred by his GP
for blurred vision. Certainly.
Take a seat.
PHONE NOTIFICATION
Got a message from a friend
in a local policing team.
Apparently, Keenan has a bit of
a reputation in the area. For?
Word is he's a bit of a ladies' man.
Sometimes he pays for it.
No surprise.
THUNDER RUMBLES
Yes, this is DCS Twomey.
Our people down at Dunfolan
have a missing-persons case -
a Pat or a Patrick Keenan.
Yeah, could I get everything on
that as soon as possible, please?
Thanks.
Well, that was a waste of time.
Whoever invented
patient confidentiality
wasn't in the police.
"Causes of blurred vision."
Astigmatism. Pr...presbyopia?
What's that?
Something to do with Presbyterians?
SHE CHUCKLES
It can also be caused by
dry eyes, pregnancy, migraines.
How do we get
out of this place, then?
Down here?
Will this lift get us out?
Aye, it will.
You visiting? Er, no, we're police.
Just asking a few questions.
Oh, police? I apologise in advance.
Probably come across a few of
my students. Are you at Queen's?
Just starting, God help me.
My daughter's third-year medicine.
What's her name?
And I'll keep an eye out for her.
Izzy Brannick. She'll be the one
chewing your ear off.
Here we are now.
Let me ask you something.
Why would somebody - er, a
middle-aged man, say -
a ladies' man...
Why would they be suffering
from blurred vision?
It's not really
my area of expertise.
I mean, I'm a trauma consultant.
But a ladies' man?
Sure he doesn't have syphilis?
I mean, he could also be
taking too much Viagra.
That affects your eyesight?
Let that be a warning to you.
Thank you.
GATES CREAK
SIREN WAILS
Jambo bastard! Shit!
Fucking Prod!
Uniform from Sierra Romeo 45.
Sitrep Dunfolan Police Station.
Attack, two petrol bombs,
two male...
Some help here!
..running towards New Street.
It's going to be OK. I've got you.
SHOUTING
Some help here!
You're all right,
you're all right. Up, up, up.
Let's clear that away
as quickly as possible.
I want a TST on standby
in case of any follow-up.
Get him inside.
Niamh, grab Birdy, set up a room
with some privacy.
Let's get to work, OK?
Tom? Ma'am. You saw it happen?
Yeah. Because of us.
It's because we went to see
Mrs Keenan. How do you know?
She convinced herself that we've
no interest in finding her husband.
She's managed to convince
the lot that did this, too.
What are you doing about it? We're
pursuing the leads that we do have.
Nothing concrete yet. All right,
Tom. Get on with it. Ma'am.
I need two more over here now!
That's good. Good.
Keep on going, keep on going!
ON PHONE: Police emergency.
I've taken Pat Keenan.
This is Major White.
Major White was a code used by
loyalist paramilitaries
in the early '90s.
The last person to use it
is long since dead, and the kid
whose voice we can hear was no doubt
slipped a 20 to make the call.
The handset was wiped clean. There's
nothing on it that we can use.
Keenan told his wife he was staying
in a hotel in Belfast. And?
He never booked it.
We have a copy of his joint account
statement, his personal account.
Nothing of note.
We know that he was IRA
over 20 years ago,
but there's been
no overt activity since.
Most of his contacts from those days
have moved into
"legit" businesses, anyway.
Int Hub have confirmed
he's not on their radar.
Birdy, any CCTV into the village?
Nothing.
And his hospital appointment raises
the possibility that he has
an illicit sex life.
That guy?
He's known to pay for it.
How much?
He gets it half-price
with his tenth cup of coffee.
CHUCKLING
I don't know, Birdy! Right, you lot,
you know what you need to do.
Piss off and do it.
Potentially, it could all relate
to his personal life.
Going on what we know,
it's possible.
But I think it goes
much deeper than that.
How does the postcard fit?
I need to know what you're not
telling me. If it's anything to do
with that postcard, I want you
to bring me up to speed.
It's nothing you need to
worry about.
Understood.
Where are you going, DS McGovern?
To ask McCallister to take me
off this investigation.
Don't.
Just, er...
In the early part of 1998,
in the months leading up
to the Peace Agreement...
..a handful of us
were made aware of...
..a possible assassin
who, it seemed,
had access to police intelligence.
He was never identified,
but the suspicion was...
..that it could only have been
an inside man.
We called him Goliath,
after the crane.
So you think he's still out there?
You think Keenan's dead?
In '98, the thing that linked
Goliath's victims was that
each one of them was made to look
as if they'd done a runner.
Fear, debt, reputation - they all
had a credible reason to leave.
And that's the version of events
that everyone chose to accept.
How many targets?
Four.
So Goliath's a serial killer.
That makes it sound indiscriminate.
These were targeted assassinations.
Peace was on the table. If word got
out that a member of the police was
picking off targets at will, it
would destroy that, just like now.
It would risk a return
to all-out war.
REPORTER: Reports are coming in that
the petrol bombing of PSNI Dunfolan
is directly linked
to the disappearance
of former IRA man Pat Keenan.
Police have faced heavy criticism
of their handling of the case.
MLA for Dunfolan Aiden O'Neill
had this to say earlier.
Naturally, I condemn the petrol
bombing of Dunfolan Police Station.
No-one wants to go back
to those days
of running battles in the streets.
But a member of my community
is missing, and so far the police
appear to have no answers regarding
his whereabouts or a possible
motive behind his disappearance.
What am I to say to the poor man's
wife when I believe,
as she does, that the police are
failing our community once again?
HE DIALS
LINE RINGS
Sir? Get me the ACC District
Policing Command.
These are the original
Goliath disappearances,
the ones who preceded Keenan.
David Corry.
Joe Harkin.
And Father Simon Quinlan.
A priest?
And an IRA arms dealer.
Joe Harkin was an IRA quartermaster.
And Corry, he was
from the other side.
He was a Protestant
paramilitary godfather.
That's what made it all the more
puzzling - it wasn't one side or
the other. His targets were people
who were a threat to
the peace process on both sides.
He kept it even-handed.
You said there were four targets.
Mm-hm.
He also murdered my wife.
Why is your wife not in the files?
Cos her disappearance
is not official.
Was she a threat to the peace?
She was military intelligence.
The nature of her job.
At the time, they said
that her cover had been blown,
she went to ground.
But that's not what happened.
She was kidnapped.
Same as Keenan.
If we find the files
of the original victims,
we can compare them
to the Keenan case.
When Joe Harkin went missing,
the investigation said it was
because he owed money
all around the country.
There was a list of all
the people he was thought to have
owed on that file.
I remember seeing it.
Keenan's name was on the list and
maybe our potential Goliath, too.
When did you say?
Last week of February '98.
There's nothing here.
There has to be!
Joe Harkin is the name
you're looking for.
He was the first of them
to disappear.
I'm telling you, there's nothing,
so there's not.
Something's going on. Goliath was a
name known only inside the police,
and now these files have upped
and vanished. There's someone...
..someone who doesn't want us
to get to the truth about
the Goliath disappearances.
We can't hold back, ma'am.
So don't. Find Pat Keenan.
That way, we can unlock Goliath.
Use whatever resources you need.
Pull people from other jobs,
if you have to. You have my backing.
Now get this done.
Keenan's disappearance
is similar to David Corry.
He was a prominent
Loyalist paramilitary
involved in numerous attacks
on the Catholic community.
Nasty piece of work.
He has a brother, Adam.
Lives out on the Cumber Road.
Adam never bought the official
version of what happened.
He's spent years
trying to disprove it.
And if we're short of information,
he could be the one
to fill in the blanks.
All right, then, let's go.
Jesus, that smells like
you're a 50-a-day man.
Aye, well, the lining's
burnt to shite,
but the money I paid for it,
there's no way I'm not wearing it.
Every pound's a prisoner, eh?
As Pat Keenan and David Corry
were paramilitaries,
was Adam a paramilitary, too?
No.
He was never one for violence.
Much happier up here.
He ran a bakery in the local
village. But he loved his brother.
He's dedicated the last 22 years
of his life trying to find him.
Tom Brannick.
That's right, Mr Corry.
HE BREATHES UNSTEADILY
You've still got a good boot on you?
I don't play any more.
Best out-half these parts have seen.
Rugby.
If youse want a cup of tea...
..you should've had it
before you came.
We're grand, thanks, Mr Corry.
Do you, er...
Do you mind if I record this? No.
The others that went missing
at the same time as your brother...
Joe Harkin. Simon Quinlan.
Your wi... Aye.
We're following
a new line of inquiry.
HE LAUGHS
A "new" line of inquiry?
HE COUGHS
My God. After 22 years!
You lot move with some urgency...!
Mr Corry, you don't believe
the verdict,
that your brother ran, just like
the others. He ran from nothing.
It was only because of the ceasefire
that everyone swallowed that shite.
And youse were all so drunk
on the idea of peace,
youse stopped doing your jobs.
Look what the peace has brought us.
Unanswered questions!
Where's my brother? His wife?
What peace do you think
he's known all these years, huh?
That's enough.
We think the connection between each
of the 1998 missing persons -
including your brother -
is credible.
But we're short some information.
All right.
Jesus.
Well!
You have a system?
Of course I've got a bloody system!
I'm not daft.
So we're looking for
the last week of February 1998,
anything relating to that.
Joe Harkin, particularly.
When I called for police help,
your lot treated me like I was
sitting in a press
with a tinfoil hat...
..telling them all that the...
..little green men
were footering up the path.
I-I don't have a great deal
on Joe Harkin. That much is true.
But, er...
They don't like a man like me
snooping around his neighbourhood.
No, Mr Corry, this is April '98.
Huh!
The peace deal was struck
on the 10th of April.
Then, the 11th of April...
..a woman reports suspicious
activity on an island in the lough.
She says it happened
the end of February,
around the time that Joe Harkin
went off the map.
The bodies could be out there
on that island.
Why so long to report it?
Well, maybe she...
Maybe she was one of the few
who believed that this ceasefire
might actually hold.
Who did she report it to?
Your lot!
What, you didn't know?
Well, sure all I did was drink
what you boys were drinking.
Merely wigged on idle talk.
Well, here, I don't have
the actual statement.
I never did.
I just knew of its existence, like.
And I asked for it - many times.
MESSAGE OVER RADIO
SIRENS WAIL
Do you have ID, sir?
It's Jackie's car.
Boss?
You in charge now? I am.
McCallister was doing a good job.
It's a delicate situation
which has been mishandled.
That's not her fault. Yes, it is.
She's allowed you to run amok.
I'm looking for Pat Keenan.
You told me to focus on him.
Fuck up! I know perfectly well
what you're up to.
McCallister filled me in.
You're after Goliath.
It's connected to the Keenan case.
I told you to keep the peace.
Every hour that Pat Keenan
is missing
is another hour of problems for this
service. Have you seen outside?
We don't have time for flights
of fancy or going on a hunch.
It all makes sense now,
why you're here.
Given my knowledge of the area and
the fact that I previously worked...
No, no, no. You could have supported
McCallister from Belfast,
given her all the assistance
she needed,
but you had to come down here
yourself to stop me
investigating Goliath.
Don't talk shite.
I came here to make sure you find
Keenan and put a stop to the unrest.
And, obviously, as a senior Catholic
officer, they're more likely
to believe that I'll move
heaven and earth to find him.
Now, you can start by making peace
with his wife,
cos I can guarantee you,
all of this is
because she's taken
a dislike to you.
That means she'll put the word out
against the whole operation.
Can you do that?
I came to you because I needed
an old friend's support.
And you have it, Tom.
There's no reason
for you to doubt it.
That's it, then?
DCS Twomey's in charge?
Aye, come back to his old district
to sit on me. Ah.
I think I'll keep out of that.
What's that? The missing statement
Adam Corry was talking about.
Constable Scott found it
in the files for April '98.
The witness was Muriel Busby
of Deacon's Farm
on the Bannbracken Road.
She said she was out feeding
the cows on a clear night.
She saw activity on an island.
From that distance, she says,
it looked like digging.
She identifies the location as
being between a bothy and a tree.
Jesus.
Let's go take a look.
I don't think we can. The record
shows that it wasn't actioned.
They put it at the back of a file
and forgot about it.
If the Pat Keenan and Goliath cases
are linked, we have to go out there.
We have to!
WOMAN: Who's that, Izzy?
BABY CHUCKLES
Daddy? Could it be Daddy?
Where's Daddy?
Good girl!
BABY GIGGLES
DOG BARKS
Hello. Can I help you?
Hello, there. Uh-huh.
We're with the Police Service.
Is Mrs Busby here?
Ach, no.
She died maybe 12, 13 year ago.
Are you family? Nah.
This place was empty for
a wee while before we bought it.
Do you mind if we look around?
No, look away.
Gilder, if you need me, all right?
COWS LOW
There. Between the bothy
and the tree.
That's where she saw
someone digging.
We'll get a search team ready
to go out there on the morning tide.
Here.
KNOCKS ON DOOR
Yeah?
Sir, I've got TSG Ops
up on the phone.
They said more boats are available
if we still want them.
Boats?
HE SIGHS
MOTORBOAT APPROACHES
TWOMEY CRIES OUT
This fucking cunt!
You two! I want a word!
Does Claire Keenan have
a holiday home I don't know about?
Jackie... I told you to make peace
with the missing man's wife
so that we could find
the missing man.
Yet here we all are,
halfway to the Galapagos,
checking out a 20-year-old tip-off.
DS McGovern identified this
as an unactioned witness statement
and burial site, and I agreed to it.
You know about this place, sir?
Did he not tell you
I was stationed here?
I was leading
the investigation in '98.
One of my boys took her statement.
That farmhouse, over there.
Why didn't you tell me? Oh, come on,
Tom! The peace deal, of course!
And I knew you'd've torn the arse
out of the whole thing.
This has implications
for the Pat Keenan case, sir.
He could be buried here, too.
Remember the times
we were living in.
It wasn't my bloody choice!
Off limits then and off limits now.
His wife was taken, sir.
She could be here.
You could have been here
20 years ago.
Fuck!
Tom!
Boss...
What else did you keep from me?
Nothing.
You know, there was a part of me...
..didn't want to find the bodies.
I didn't want to see my dead...
But Goliath...
Goliath...
No!
I promise you, Tom...
..there's nothing else.
We're alive, man.
Being on this island is a waste
of time and resources.
You know that.
You've dug.
There's nothing here.
We need to shut it down.
DS McGovern...
..stay and make sure everyone
gets off this island.
You come back with me.
All right, come on,
let's get away back on the boats.
You coming?
Sarge?
Between the bothy and the tree.
There's another tree.
Look, Birdy, another tree. What?
We should have been here.
But I can't see the farmhouse.
What can you see?
Cow shed. Exactly.
She says in her statement
that she was out feeding the cows.
We... We were digging
in the wrong place?
Ask them if we can borrow their GPR.
Oh, but... Ach, come on, Birdy!
We owe it to the boss.
To the families!
All right.
Good morning.
I'm Tori Matthews. I'm a trauma
consultant over at the Royal,
and for some stupid reason
I've agreed to teach you lot
from time to time.
CHUCKLING
You won't be laughing
when you get to know me.
LAUGHTER
Right, let's get started, shall we?
What's he doing here?
Dunno.
Er, see you at the house? Yeah.
I was in the area,
just thought I'd pop by.
Mm...
You OK?
Fine.
Really?
Things are a bit difficult at work.
I just need a break.
Oh! Mm.
It's nice to see you wear it.
Course.
If you want it back... No!
SHE LAUGHS
I held on to it
for all this time because...
..I thought that one day,
you know, your mum and me...
..might still be reunited.
But it's not going to happen.
We move on.
It's important to me
that you have it.
PHONE RINGS
Hello.
Boss, it's Birdy. Keenan's...
OVER RADIO:
Suspect vehicle heading south.
All units be advised,
I am in pursuit with HMSU,
with Int Hub
overwatching UAV support.
Keenan's numberplates
were spotted at a petrol
station on the Dundrum Road,
just outside of Newcastle.
And we're sure it's them?
Absolutely.
Should be getting a visual
on them any time now.
And there they are.
The police were screwed on to
this red Peugeot 207, male driver.
We pulled a UAV from another job
and we're tracking him from the air.
Where's he going?
OVER RADIO: Vehicle still making
its way along Brianford Road.
Roger that.
He's turning off the road.
The sign at the gate
is for Mourne View Hotel.
Stand by. Stand by. Received.
MESSAGES OVER RADIO
Go. Go, go, go!
SIREN WAILS
SHOUTING
Hands in the air, now!
Keep your hands up!
Secured.
Go to the ground floor.
Go, go, go!
Who are you? Where's Pat Keenan?
My name is Ben McFarland.
I own this hotel.
Why are his numberplates
on your car?
I didn't even notice
they weren't mine. Hold him.
All the rooms are clear.
He says he's alone? Yeah.
KNOCK ON DOOR
Pat Keenan?
Don't come in!
I said do not come in! The door's
booby-trapped. I can see it.
The numberplates are bait.
Stay back. Fall back!
MACHINE WHINES
WHINING BECOMES LOUDER
MESSAGES OVER RADIO
I am putting a camera
under the door...now.
No! Get back!
Coming up under
the inside door handle.
I have the device, detonator.
It looks like a mechanical trigger
attached to the door handle.
Hang on.
This isn't right.
The trigger and the detonator
aren't connected.
I'm going through.
All clear. Device is a hoax.
OVER RADIO: All clear.
Device is a hoax.
Pat?
Pat? You're OK. I'm Detective
Chief Inspector Tom Brannick.
You're all right. You're safe now.
KEENAN STRUGGLES
Sir? Deep breaths.
LINE RINGS
Boss? Niamh.
We're still on the island. What?
We've found something.
This way, sir.
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN