- Are you sure about this?
I don't like this idea.
I mean, we're doing fine.
The bills--
the bills are getting paid.
- For now. For now.
I'm a 68-year-old man
working toward a retirement
that will not pay the bills.
That's why we're doing this.
- I don't like this idea.
- I know you--I know.
We've talked about this.
It's gonna be fine, all right?
- Okay.
Okay.
- Come here.
- All right. Be careful.
- All right.
♪ ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
- You! Over here!
Get your hands up!
- Security! Drop your--
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Don't shoot!
- Shut up! Everybody shut up!
Let's go! Move it!
Move it! Come on!
- One minute!
We gotta go! We gotta go!
- Come on! Let's go!
♪ ♪
- Oh, damn it.
I just realized
I forgot to file
the 302 report before
I clocked out last night.
- Oh, yeah,
I saw that on your screen.
I hit Send after you left.
It's in the file.
- Oh, great. Thank you.
- Yep.
- What can I get you?
- All right, coffee's on me
this morning.
What's good here?
- Everything, honestly.
- Okay, uh, let me get
four coffees,
three blueberry muffins,
two cheese danishes to go.
- You got it.
- I'm sorry, um,
are you all from the 1-6?
- Yeah.
- Do you know, um,
Sergeant Clark?
I used to work with him
in the 81st precinct.
- No kidding?
Yeah, Clark got me
onto the force.
Old buddy of my dad's.
- Small world.
I'm Tiffany Wallace; this is
my partner, Stuart Scola.
- Douglas Burke.
- Nina Lewis.
You're dressed pretty sharp
for a Fed.
Thought you all wore
the standard-issue G-man suit.
- Well, after five years
of wearing a uniform,
you gotta take the opportunity
to put your own spin on it,
right?
I don't blame you.
- Yo, don't worry about it.
Yeah, our money's no good here.
- He's right.
- It's all right.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- So what was that about?
- What?
- Paying for the coffee.
- It's bureau policy.
We can't accept--
- I know bureau policy,
but for goodness' sakes,
it was just a cup of coffee.
The guy was trying
to be friendly.
You embarrassed him.
Made him feel like an idiot.
- Well, that wasn't
my intention.
- Well, that was the result.
- What the hell?
- Okay, everyone.
This is a tough one.
You all know Howard Kirkland.
He worked security at 26 Fed
longer than any of us
have been agents.
He was also working
a second job
at a check cashing center
in Brooklyn.
- And this morning,
gunmen stormed that center,
and Howard was killed
defending the people inside.
- I just talked to him
last night.
He said that he was putting
his retirement off
for another year.
His wife had a stroke
last month.
Anybody spoken to her?
- NYPD has notified her.
She had just dropped him off.
- Okay, we're taking the case,
though, right?
- Damn right we are.
What do we know so far?
- MO matches
two other robberies
at check cashing stores
in Queens
over the past three weeks.
NYPD's Central Robbery Division
has been investigating, but--
- Right, but these guys
are pros.
They cover their tracks well.
- This is surveillance footage
from the first two robberies.
Our robbers
wear these animal masks
to conceal their identities--
a rat and a dog.
- The Rat controls the hostages
while the Dog makes quick work
of shooting out
security cameras.
- They're in and out in less
than four minutes every time.
- Which one shot Howard?
- According to witnesses,
the Rat.
- Yeah, and this is the
first time they've killed, too,
which means they're escalating.
They'll shoot and kill again.
- Do we have any information
to ID these guys?
- They've been careful,
managed to avoid
getting caught on street cams
so far.
The only thing
I've been able to find
is a tattoo.
Our robber in the dog mask
has a crescent moon
on his wrist,
but it's not popping
in the criminal database.
- Yeah. Yeah, that's something.
Let's reach out
to local tattoo artists.
Maybe someone'll
recognize something.
Everyone else,
let's pull footage
from the area
around the robbery.
See if we can catch these guys
coming or going.
- All right, you guys
head over to the scene.
Follow up with witnesses.
You guys collect any kind
of information
NYPD already has.
I want these guys
in custody fast.
- We'll take
witness interviews.
Why don't you guys talk
to the handling detectives,
see if there's anything new
to run on?
- We're on it.
- Hey, Tiff.
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- What's up?
- They got you
working this one?
- Yep.
Um, the victim's
actually one of ours.
He worked at 26 Fed.
- Yeah, we heard.
I'm sorry.
Frank Dixon.
This is my partner,
Roger Palmer.
Palmer, this is Tiffany Wallace
and, uh...
- Stuart Scola.
You two used to work together?
- Dixon was my
training officer.
- Yeah, you got
a good one here, Stuart.
- Yeah, we're lucky
to have her.
- So, um, catch us up.
What do we need to know?
- Well, for starters,
these guys are good.
They move fast,
don't leave a lot behind.
Made off with 40 grand
this time.
- Any actionable leads?
- No.
We've interviewed
almost 70 witnesses
since the first robbery;
nothing we can run on.
Look, I get that
you lost a colleague today,
but we've been working
around the clock on this.
Not sure it makes sense for you
to just take it from us.
- Well, we got resources
that you don't,
and like Tiff said,
he was one of ours.
- Yeah, well,
we're pretty invested
in this case, that's all,
so maybe we can
work this together, huh?
- Of course.
- Yeah, we'll see.
Can't make any promises
till we know
what we're working with.
♪ ♪
- Fair enough.
We'll get the files
over to you ASAP.
Good seeing you, Tiff.
- Yeah.
- What?
- Didn't have to be
so dismissive.
- I was just being realistic.
- More like arrogant.
You think you're better
than these guys.
You do.
- There's Betsy, Howard's wife.
I can't let you
over there right now.
No, no, no, no, no.
We can't do that, ma'am.
- My branch manager called me,
freaking out,
saying some guys
broke in with guns.
Was it, uh, the same ones
who hit those joints in Queens?
- You heard about them?
- Yeah.
Cops were in a few days ago,
giving me the heads up,
saying check cashing places
were suddenly popular targets.
Wait, who got shot?
- Howard Kirkland.
Your security guard.
He didn't make it.
- He was a good guy.
Helped me, uh,
beef up my security system.
Put in hidden cameras
and a silent alarm.
- You have hidden cameras
in here?
- Yeah, in the smoke detectors.
- We're gonna need to see
that footage immediately.
♪ ♪
- Hey, did you get
the security footage
OA sent over from the robbery?
- Yeah, Hobbs is
sifting through it now,
but we were just
scrubbing video
from the other two check
cashing stores that got hit.
- You got something?
- Think so.
- Goody. What is it?
- This is from the location
of the first robbery--
two days before
the robberies started.
- Okay.
- This woman just came in
and wandered around.
Never cashed a check,
never turned in a form.
- Okay, you think
she's casing the place.
- Not just casing--filming.
- We're pretty sure
this is a spy camera.
Cheap kind you get online.
- Hmm.
- We checked for her
at the second store.
She was there too.
- Okay.
- Two days before the place
was hit.
Same necklace, same routine.
- Yeah, yeah. You get an ID?
- Not yet.
We don't have
a clear enough angle
for facial rec
because of the sunglasses,
but I don't think
she's one of our robbers.
I did a height comparison.
She's too short.
- Okay, well,
she could still
be an accomplice,
a sister, a girlfriend.
We find her, we can find out
who she's working with.
- We got agents checking
with employees at each
of the centers, seeing if
anyone recognizes her.
- Hey, pause it.
Zoom into the pen there.
- Platinum Royale.
- Right.
That's a strip club
on the East Side.
I walk by the place sometimes
on my way to the subway.
Just send the photo over
to the manager.
See if she works there.
- I went in for a money order
and changed my mind.
Is that a crime?
- No.
Armed robbery is.
See, every time you go into
a check cashing center
and change your mind,
place gets robbed
two days later.
So you ask me,
that's a hell of a coincidence.
- I don't know
what to tell you.
- Is that your little girl?
You know, if you freeze us out
and we find out
that you're involved in this,
you're looking at 15, 20 years
on a second-degree
murder charge.
Are you sure you wanna
do that to her?
- What--murder?
What are you talking about?
- Your buddies shot a man
in Brooklyn this morning--
a friend of ours.
- I didn't have anything
to do with that.
I swear.
I don't even know the guy.
- Okay, well,
tell us what you do know.
Who paid you
to case those places?
- I don't know his name.
He came into the club
a few weeks ago,
I gave him a couple of dances,
and he offered me a job.
Said I could make
a lot of money.
- What did this guy look like?
- Uh, salt and pepper hair.
Average height.
5'10", I guess.
He had a tattoo of a moon
or something on his wrist.
- What did he ask you to do?
- He gave me a necklace
with the camera in it.
Told me to go to these
addresses in Queens,
all check cashing places,
walk around,
get as many angles as I could,
and I would send the video
to his phone.
I didn't know
anybody would get hurt.
♪ ♪
- We're gonna need
that cell phone number.
- It's in my phone.
Can I, uh--
- Yeah, go ahead.
We'll also need a list
of the check cashing places.
♪ ♪
Here's the list that he text.
Three addresses.
- He never had you scope out
a place in Brooklyn?
- No. Just those three.
- That means there's a place
in Queens
they had cased
that hasn't been hit yet.
We should set up
some surveillance.
Catch them in the act.
- All right,
so we can put cameras
on both sides of the building.
One in the parking lot.
- And inside if the manager's
willing to cooperate of course.
- Who's gonna say "no"
to free surveillance equipment?
Those are gunshots.
FBI!
Everybody, stay where you are!
- Stay down! Stay down!
Go.
Dispatch, we have shots fired
at 150 Roosevelt Avenue
in Queens.
Send backup immediately.
♪ ♪
- Suspect is male,
wearing a green hat,
carrying a black backpack,
heading south
down Forest Street.
- All right, people,
the Dog and the Rat
have struck again.
It's like a kid's book.
Two stores in one day.
Means they're getting greedy
and, hopefully, sloppy.
Let's use this
to our advantage.
So OA saw
one of the robbers fleeing.
Did not get a good look
at his face,
but said he was wearing
a green hat, a black backpack,
and he swung a left
on Forest Street.
Where are we
with the street cams?
- Pulled everything within
a three-block radius.
Caught this.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Green hat.
Can you zoom into his wrist,
maybe?
- Crescent tattoo.
That's our guy.
- Aha, boom. There it is.
- Pulled the cab's
medallion number.
Got access to the interior
camera footage.
- Okay, yeah,
that's a good shot.
Can we run that
through facial rec?
- Already on it.
- Of course you are.
There he is.
Justin Maynard.
41 years old, 5'11", 190.
- That makes him
a physical match
for the robber in the dog mask.
- Maynard's got
a pretty good rap sheet.
Armed robbery, violent assault.
Already been to prison
three times.
- Really?
You got a location on him?
- Parole records show he works
at a salvage yard in Queens.
- Yeah, looks like that's
where the cab dropped him off.
- Okay, let's bring him in.
♪ ♪
- What are they doing here?
- I called them.
- For what?
- It was their case
before we took it.
They deserve to be
part of the takedown.
- We're a go.
♪ ♪
Drop the weapon!
- Is anyone else
on the premises?
Go. I got this.
♪ ♪
- What the hell
are you thinking?
- What are you talking about?
He was shooting at us.
- I was in your line of fire,
Palmer.
You could've hit me.
- But I didn't, so relax.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey, guys.
Calm down.
We got the bad guy.
That's all that matters, okay?
- Playing games,
and you know it.
- He's got a lousy attitude.
- No, he's a good guy
and a good agent.
Just doesn't like bullets
whizzing by his head is all.
- Justin, we found the masks
and the money
at the salvage yard.
We're also 20 minutes away
from getting a ballistics match
on your gun.
This is your last shot
at any kind of leniency,
so you wanna tell us
your side of the story?
- I've got nothing
to say to you.
- You sure about that?
You really wanna
risk life without
for a murder
your partner, Chris, committed?
- What the hell
are you talking about?
- The guy your buddy shot
this morning in Brooklyn
was a federal employee.
That's not me.
- No?
Then who is it?
- I don't know,
but I've never been
to that store.
- So what, are you saying
that Chris
pulled this one off
without you?
- That's not Chris, either.
7:30 this morning,
we were at a diner in Queens
having breakfast.
♪ ♪
- You're not gonna
believe this.
Maynard's alibi checks out.
Both he and Chris Wilson
are on camera
at the Sunshine Diner
this morning.
They couldn't have been
at the robbery in Brooklyn.
- Yeah, well, ballistics
tells the same story.
The guns found
at the salvage yard
were not a match to the gun
that killed Howard,
but they were a match
to the bullets
recovered from the three
locations in Queens.
- But the guys
from this morning's robbery,
they had the same clothes,
the same animal masks,
even the same crescent tattoo
on the wrist.
- They're copycats.
- So these guys
who killed Howard
are still running around
out there.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
Two different sets of robbers.
- Maynard and Wilson
did not kill Howard.
- Okay, start looking
into people
with knowledge
of the robbers' MO.
- Yeah, already on it.
Got agents
talking to associates
of Maynard and Wilson.
- And we're
re-interviewing everybody
that was present
at the first two robberies.
- Okay, great.
- Hey, guys, I got something
you wanna see.
I think the copycats
may have just slipped up.
I went over
hidden camera video
from the Brooklyn robbery.
I found a detail that
doesn't fit the original MO.
- Well, wait a second.
That's acoustic tubing.
He's wearing an earpiece.
- Yeah, I think I know
what he's listening to.
These guys got out of there
right before
the cops showed up,
so I synced up the timecodes
to this audio.
- All units, be advised,
we've got a 10-30
on Jackson and 37th.
- That's police dispatch.
- 10-4, 15 Charlie responding.
We're one minute out.
- These guys
have a police scanner?
- Yeah, except that's
an encrypted channel.
You can't pick that up
on a regular old scanner.
You have to have
a dedicated police radio.
- Are you saying these guys
might be cops?
- That's a pretty serious
accusation.
Do we have any proof
beyond the theory
that they had access
to the robbery case files?
- Nothing specific.
- But if you think about it,
some of the details
of the prior robberies
were only known to the police.
- Okay, start checking
the logs.
Find out which cops had access
to the robbery case files.
Dig into each of them.
- Uh, should I loop in
Detective Dixon?
- No, let's keep this
internal for now.
If the cops are involved,
we don't wanna tip off
the wrong person.
We need to wall off NYPD
until we are
absolutely certain.
- That might be tough.
What do I tell the NYPD rep
in the JOC?
- Keep any reference
to cops
as suspects out of the JOC.
For now,
they are simply robbers
until we can prove otherwise.
- Right.
- Last thing we needed
was to give you
another reason to hate cops.
- I don't hate cops.
Seriously, I just
didn't wanna waste time
sharing info,
witness statements,
surveillance footage.
There's no point.
Look, I knew Howard well.
He was a good guy--
like, a really good guy--
so I wanna do him right, Tiff.
That's it.
That's my only agenda.
- All right, listen up,
everybody.
This is not over yet.
Howard Kirkland's killer
is still at large.
Now, our Brooklyn robbers
somehow knew
every detail
of the original crime,
so we need
to go over everything
from this morning's robbery
with fresh eyes--
witness statements,
street cams, 911 calls.
Look for anything
that stands out
from the three
Queens robberies.
Leave no stone unturned.
Hey, what about those masks?
Our copycats
had to get their hands
on the exact same ones, right?
- Uh, PD identified 14 shops
in the city that carry them,
but detectives
already canvassed them.
They didn't find anything.
- Right.
You know what,
send that list over
to Scola and Tiffany anyway.
Have them re-canvas.
Maybe PD missed something.
- This have to do
with those robberies
the cops are investigating
a couple weeks ago?
- We know you already spoke
to the police about this.
- Yeah, and like I told them,
I haven't sold
either of those masks
before those stores got robbed.
- But you sold them since?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
To who?
- One of the cops.
Came back,
bought both the masks.
Needed to "put it in the file"
or something like that.
- When was this?
- Three days ago.
Maybe four.
- Do you remember his name?
- No.
- Does this store have cameras?
We don't get a lot of people
stealing stuff here.
- Okay, what did this cop
look like?
- White guy.
Salt and pepper hair.
- How old was he?
- Maybe 40?
Had these pretty blue eyes.
♪ ♪
- Is that him?
- Yeah. That's the guy.
- Son of a bitch.
I knew I didn't like that guy,
Palmer.
- We don't know for sure yet.
- No wonder they wanted
to hold on to the case,
didn't want us digging
into their investigation.
- We don't know anything
for sure.
Not yet.
- Tiff, Palmer knew
every detail
of the robberies in Queens.
Then a few days before
the robberies in Brooklyn,
he bought the same exact masks
they were using.
Look, he's our guy.
I'm not sure what this means
about Dixon, but--
- No.
Dixon doesn't have anything
to do with this.
Regardless of what Palmer
may or may not have done.
- You don't know that, Tiff.
Why do you think
it's taken them so long
to solve this thing--
or not solve this thing?
I mean, we got
to Maynard and Wilson in a day.
- These guys are working
on 30 cases at a time
with a tenth of the resources.
- I know that
you're still a cop at heart.
Like, I get that.
But the facts
are the facts, Tiff,
so the sooner you get
on board here, the better.
- What the hell does that mean?
- I'm saying that I think
your relationship with Dixon
is clouding your judgement.
♪ ♪
- Thanks.
Property clerk in Queens
said that there was no mask
ever logged into evidence.
- Palmer never mentioned
that he went back
to the costume shop
in any of his reports.
- He bought the masks
after he became familiar
with the robbers' MO.
He's gotta be one of the perps.
- Yeah, but we can't
move on him
just because he bought
a couple of masks.
We need more evidence.
- I mean, we have evidence,
but it's circumstantial.
Look, Palmer's cell phone
was turned off
an hour before the robbery
until an hour afterwards.
Also, he's the exact
same build and height
as the copycat
in the rat mask--
the guy who shot Howard.
- Plus he's got four kids,
two ex-wives,
and a lot of debt.
- Yeah, that's probably
not enough for a warrant
on his house and locker,
but we can bring him in,
see if we can get him talking.
- Uh, one problem.
Palmer's got an alibi.
NYPD report
puts him across town
the time of the robbery.
Says he was
investigating a lead
with his partner,
Detective Frank Dixon.
- Yeah, we think Dixon
is the other copycat?
- No, no way.
I know Dixon.
He's a good man.
Real police.
- Uh, yeah, Tiffany's right.
He can't be the robber.
The heights don't match.
- It doesn't mean
that he's not involved.
He signed that report.
It means he's covering
for Palmer.
- Then he must've had
a good reason.
- All right, well,
let's bring him in
and see if we can get him
to bust a hole
in Palmer's alibi.
- Dixon's been on the force
a long time.
He's not gonna talk to us.
He'll plead the fifth,
ask for his PBA lawyer.
- Maybe we make up a story
and try to box him in.
- We could,
but it's not gonna work.
- Why not?
- Police don't trust the FBI.
They don't like 'em
too much either,
so whatever we concoct,
he's gonna see through it.
Just let me talk to him
off the record
as a friend.
See what I can learn.
- Yeah. Okay.
Take Scola with you.
And, Tiff, keep your cards
close to the vest.
If Dixon is involved,
we don't want him
to alert Palmer
that we're investigating,
yeah?
- Hey, Scola.
What the hell's going on?
- What are you talking about?
- You and Tiff.
It's clear you're not
on the same page.
- That obvious, huh?
She, uh,
she used to work with Dixon.
He was her training officer,
and she loves the guy, so...
- Hmm.
And you're not sold?
I mean, do you think
he might be involved?
- He seems like
a nice enough guy,
but you never know, right?
- You know, when it's personal,
it's easy to make a mistake
you can't walk back from.
Just keep an eye out for her.
Okay?
- Goes without saying.
- I know.
Wanted to say it anyway.
- Sorry to drop in
on you like this.
- Oh, you know
you're always welcome.
Y'all want some water
or something?
- No, we're good.
- Agent Scola, right?
- Uh, Stuart.
- Oh.
- You celebrating the arrest?
- No, my daughter
got into Harvard.
- What?
- Yeah.
- That's amazing. Congrats.
- Hey, full ride.
Yeah, all she gotta do
is show up.
Hey, I want to apologize
for my partner.
He can be a bit of a cowboy
sometimes,
so I get where
you're coming from.
I had a couple of his bullets
whiz past my ear too.
- Appreciate that.
- Mm-hmm.
- So about the arrests.
We were going over some of the
paperwork you guys sent over...
- Mm-hmm.
- And saw that
you followed up on a lead
this morning?
- Yeah, it didn't pan out.
Got a call on the tip line
to meet a potential witness
down at McCarren Park.
Come to find out the guy
just wanted a free cappuccino.
For real.
Just some idiot
looking for attention.
- Who got stuck paying?
You or Palmer?
- I did.
- You didn't, uh, log a name
for this potential witness.
Any reason for that?
- Like I said,
the guy was a nutjob.
- Well, even so, in case
there are discovery issues,
we should have it in the file,
so...
♪ ♪
Any chance maybe Palmer
got the guy's info
while you were
grabbing his coffee?
- No, he stayed in the car.
Hey, Tiff, this is me--
this is me you're talking to.
What the hell
is really going on here?
- All right, um, look, Dix--
- We cannot get into specifics
right now, but the report
that you filed is connected
to a pending matter.
- Pending matter?
What the hell does that mean?
Just talk to me, Tiff.
I'll try to be helpful.
- She can't.
Like I said,
we can't get into specifics.
- Tiffany!
- Hey.
Can we convince you
to stay for dinner?
Brianna would love to see you.
- I'm sorry, Tracy.
We gotta get back
to the office,
and, um, finish up
some paperwork,
but let Brianna know that
I said "congratulations,"
though.
- I will.
- Yeah?
All right.
Yo, what was that?
- I needed to see
if Dixon's involved.
- He's not.
I already told you that.
There's no way in hell
he's involved,
and there's no way
he would've covered for Palmer.
If you would've just let me
tell him what's up--
- He's lying, Tiff.
I just gave him a chance
to walk it back,
but he doubled down on his lie.
He said Palmer was in the car;
he wasn't.
He was robbing
a check cashing store,
shooting Howard Kirkland.
- You talked to him
like he was a suspect.
What cop in his right mind
is gonna lower his guard
when you put him
in a situation like that?
- I'm just trying
to get answers.
- So am I!
And the best way to do that
was to loop in Dixon,
but you don't trust him,
which means you don't trust me.
♪ ♪
- Dixon didn't budge.
Said Palmer was in the car
while he bought
the potential witness
a cappuccino.
- So he's involved.
- Not sure.
According to Tiff,
it's doubtful.
- More like impossible.
- So where are we
with the second copycat?
Any potential suspects?
- Yeah, we dug into everyone
who accessed
the robbery case file,
cross-referenced those names
with phone and GPS records,
and ruled everyone out
except a guy named Kyle Webb.
- Webb is a young detective
with the Bronx robbery crew.
He's the right height,
and his phone was turned off
during the robbery,
just like Palmer's.
- Did we find a connection
between these guys?
- Yes--Palmer worked with Webb
at Bronx Robbery
for four years before
he was promoted to Central.
- And we ran Webb's financials.
He's broke.
Just applied
for a second mortgage.
- Do we have any evidence
that actually
connects him to the crime?
- Uh, no, but he accessed
the robbery files
several times and wasn't even
working on the case.
- Look, I read his file.
He's not the smartest guy.
I mean, he failed
his entrance exam twice.
I think we can trip him up
and get him to talk.
♪ ♪
- Detective Webb?
- Yeah?
- Special Agent Scola.
This is Special Agent Wallace.
- What's this about?
- The robberies
at the check cashing centers.
- Not my case.
And I thought you already
caught those guys.
- We did, we're just
talking to anyone
who accessed the case files.
AUSA's gonna ask about
the chain of custody,
and we don't want any surprises
if the defense files
a discovery motion.
- Okay.
- Your name came up
on the log.
Can you tell us about
your interest in the case?
- I, uh, thought it might have
some overlap
with a case I caught
three days ago--
robbery of a cell phone store
over in Allerton.
Couple of the details
were similar.
- If you caught the case
three days ago,
why'd you check the file
five times before that?
- Curiosity, I guess.
That all?
- Should do it.
Thanks for taking the time.
- Yeah, no problem.
♪ ♪
- Webb just sent a text message
to a burner asking to meet
at Madison Square Park
at 1:00 p.m.
Says it's urgent.
- Right on cue.
Webb's spooked.
He's running to Palmer.
We need to set up surveillance
on that meet.
If Webb implicates himself,
I want it on video.
- Directional mic is hot.
- We've got our eye.
How's our ear?
- Audio's online.
♪ ♪
- Webb just arrived.
No sign of his contact.
- It's still early.
- Look, about last night--
it's not that
I don't trust you,
because I do.
But if it turns out that Dixon
isn't the guy
that you think he is,
I just don't wanna see that
blow back on you.
- I get that.
I just think we owe him
a chance to come clean.
If he knew Palmer was a suspect
in a robbery homicide,
he'd walk his alibi back
in a second.
Look, I know you
have your doubts, but I don't.
- I've got eyes on Palmer.
He's heading towards Webb now.
- All right, copy. Stay close.
♪ ♪
- What took you so long?
- What are you talking about?
It's 1:00.
What's going on?
- Feds came to the precinct.
They were asking
about the ro--
- It's too loud.
Can you get any closer?
- Yeah, I'll try.
♪ ♪
Hey.
- How're you doing?
- Uh, one of those, please.
Thanks.
- Then they knew
I checked the case file, man.
What do you want me to do?
- You need to calm down.
I have everything
under control.
Stop stressing yourself out.
- The feds--
- Don't know anything.
Come here.
- What?
- Closer.
- Oh, what,
you think I'm wired?
- No.
Not anymore, I don't.
Look, bro,
everything's gonna be fine.
Just keep your mouth shut.
- What if they check the melt?
- Go home, okay?
Shut your mouth and go home.
- "The melt."
What's that about?
- The destruction of evidence.
♪ ♪
- This is it?
These are all the guns
that were confiscated
the last two months?
- Yeah, we're shipping them
out of state
day after tomorrow
so they can be melted down
for scrap metal.
If you tell me
what you're looking for,
maybe I can help you find it.
- Uh, we appreciate the offer,
but we'll let you know
if we need help.
- Yeah, we're good. Thank you.
Well, it's a great place
to dump a weapon
if you wanna guarantee
it's never found.
- Yeah, I'll keep that in mind
next time I decide
to commit armed robbery.
I just don't understand
why these guys
would throw away their lives
for 40 grand.
It doesn't make any sense.
- Oh, I used to work
with guys like that
back in Indiana.
Always wanting more.
They'll think that the badge
gave them the power
to control the narrative.
Clearly, these guys
didn't think they'd get caught.
Totally arrogant.
- Mags.
- Mm-hmm.
- Sig Sauer .45--
same make and model
Webb used to shoot out
the security cameras.
No tag.
- There was another gun in here
that was missing a tag.
Got it.
Nine-millimeter Beretta.
- Same as the gun used
to kill Howard.
- Hey.
So ballistics just came back.
Guns were a match
to the weapons
used by the Brooklyn robbers,
and Webb's prints were on both.
- So there's no way
to connect them to Palmer.
- No, guy was smart.
Made Webb do the dirty work,
knowing he'd be on the hook
if anyone found the guns,
and you can't wear gloves
into an evidence locker
without drawing
lots of unwanted attention.
- Okay, so let's go hard
at Webb.
Convince him to roll on Palmer.
- Right.
- I'll reach out
to the Chief of Detectives,
let them know we're arresting
one of their own.
♪ ♪
- Teams check in with status.
- Team one at green.
- Team two at green.
- Prepare to execute.
- Hold. Hold.
- Hold the breach.
Hold the breach.
- Is someone in that gray SUV?
- Don't know.
- Maintain the perimeter.
♪ ♪
- Neighbors didn't notice
anything suspicious.
What'd you get from the M.E.?
- Nothing actionable.
Webb's injuries are consistent
with a self-inflicted
gunshot wound.
- So what do we got?
- Found blood spatter
on the passenger window--
blowback from
the entrance wound.
But see this defined edge here?
Indicates something
was between the victim
and the window
when the gun was fired.
- Like a person?
- It's possible.
- You find any other evidence
that someone else
was in the car?
- No.
So far, only prints
we're finding belong to Webb.
We'll let you know what we get
off the weapon, though.
- Thanks.
- Had to be Palmer, right?
Without Webb's testimony,
we can't tie him
to the robberies.
- We got Dixon.
I can get him to cooperate,
but you gotta let me
do it my way.
- Do I need a lawyer?
- You might.
But I'm hoping that
you'll level with us.
- Why don't you and I
just talk?
He can wait outside.
- No.
Anything you say to me,
you can say to him too.
Look, I know you're trying
to protect your partner,
but whatever you're trying
to cover for,
this is not that.
We have evidence that
Palmer's behind the robbery
in Brooklyn yesterday.
He killed that security guard,
Howard Kirkland,
and then he killed
his accomplice,
another cop named Kyle Webb.
- What the hell are you
talking about?
You have proof of this?
- But the feds--
- Don't know anything.
Come here. Closer.
- What, you think I'm wired?
- No.
Not anymore, I don't.
Look, bro,
everything's gonna be fine.
Just keep your mouth shut.
- What if they check the melt?
- Go home, okay?
Shut your mouth and go home.
- Two hours after that meeting
where Palmer's obviously
nervous as hell
that Webb might roll,
we found Webb dead.
♪ ♪
- Is this why you came by
last night?
- Yeah.
You're Palmer's alibi.
- For God's sakes, Tiff.
Why you just didn't tell me
what was going on?
I thought this was about him
trying to jam Palmer up
over that shooting
at the junkyard.
- We couldn't risk you
tipping off Palmer.
- Tip him off?
You mean cover for him
killing somebody?
Are you crazy?
- I don't know you, sir.
- Yeah, but she does!
Is that what you thought
was going on, Tiff?
- Of course not.
♪ ♪
- Palmer wasn't with me
at McCarren Park.
He said he was having
girlfriend problems,
asked me to cover for him
for a half an hour,
so I did.
I put his damn name
in that report.
- So you admit
you falsified that report?
- Yes.
- Okay.
That should be enough
for a warrant.
- You should've just told me
what was going on, Tiff.
- I'm sorry.
- You good?
- Yeah.
- Got a new owner,
spent a lot of money,
so don't be surprised
to see 'em
in the Series this year, Jimmy.
- Detective Palmer.
- What do you want?
- We're gonna need you
to come with us.
- Now is not a good time.
- We're not asking.
You need to put your hands
where I can see 'em.
♪ ♪
I said, hands, Palmer!
Put your hands
where I can see them!
Trust me,
you do not want to give me
a reason to shoot you.
♪ ♪
Roger Palmer,
you're under arrest
for the murders
of Howard Kirkland
and Detective Kyle Webb.
- I don't know
what you're talking about.
- We found the stolen money
from yesterday's robbery
in your attic,
traces of Webb's blood
on a shirt in your bathroom.
- There's been a mistake.
I was working
yesterday morning.
- Really?
'Cause your partner said
you came in late.
You had a personal thing
to take care of?
- Looks like your alibi
just went to hell too.
♪ ♪
You need any help with that?
- No, I'm almost done.
- Hey, uh, you decide what
you're gonna do about Dixon?
- What is there to do?
- Well, he perjured himself
in that report,
obstructed the investigation.
- Isobel already talked
to the AUSA,
and they're not interested
in pursuing federal charges.
- That doesn't mean
that we shouldn't
take it back
to his department, right?
You told me
that you left the NYPD
to get away from the blue wall.
- This is not about
the blue wall.
It's about Dixon...
A good man and a good cop
who was looking out
for his partner.
So I'm not taking it back
to the NYPD, but...
you know, if you want to,
if you feel like
it's necessary, then...
do what you gotta do.
- We got the guy
that murdered Howard.
That's enough for me.
♪ ♪
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN