The best IPTV in the UK
WWW.ALLIN1BOX.CO.UK
(dramatic music)
(wind howling)
(hooves clomping)
(horse neighing)
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
(hooves clomping)
(dramatic music continues)
(leaves rustling)
(tree squeaking)
Is the carriage coming?
(dramatic music continues)
(hooves clomping)
(gun firing)
(horse neighing)
(dramatic music continues)
You in the carriage,
your money or your life.
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
(door rattling)
(gun shooting)
It's a trap!
(dramatic music continues)
(fighters grunting)
(gun firing)
(dramatic music continues)
(fighters grunting)
(leaves rustling)
(dramatic music continues)
(cloth rustling)
- [Soldier] It's Turpin.
- (dramatic music continues)
(dramatic music)
(ominous music)
(fire crackling)
(lock thumping)
(footsteps thumping)
(ominous music continues)
(fire crackling)
You finally awake then, Turpin?
I wasn't asleep,
I was unconscious.
I vaguely remember you slamming
your fist into my face.
Must be your lucky day then
'cause here's another one.
(fist thumping)
(Dick grunting)
(fire crackling)
Now that's what
you get for trying
to rob the town magistrate.
I didn't know he
was a magistrate.
Well, here's the funny thing.
He's also the one that's gonna
be deciding your sentence.
He's already done your
accomplices, by the way.
What did they get?
Seven years transportation.
Do you know what that means?
They'll be separated out
up north to the islands
where they'll be doing a
little bit of hard labor.
You'll likely never
see 'em again, Turpin.
(ominous music continues)
(fire crackling)
- What happened to my horse?
- Your horse?
She is very valuable to me.
Yeah, well, not as valuable
as she was to her actual owner.
A man with the name
of Major came forward
and claimed her last night.
Major was too handy with a whip.
She preferred to
be ridden by me.
Ah, did she now?
Well, perhaps we can put her
on the stand at your hearing,
say a few good words
for you (laughs).
I'm only joking, there's
not gonna be any hearing.
No point in having
a trial, Turpin,
not with all this damning
evidence we've got here.
(ominous music continues)
(footsteps thumping)
One robber's hat,
one robber's mask,
one robber's pistol.
So I have seven years' hard
labor to look forward to?
You don't look like
you'd last seven days.
But with you being
the leader of the gang
and an notorious outlaw
in your own right,
there's only one sentence
he could pass down.
(ominous music continues)
(fire crackling)
(birds chirping)
(hooves clomping)
(dramatic music)
(The Earl sighing)
Not today, you
promised you wouldn't.
It's this infernal carriage.
Constant rocking
puts me on edge.
Then pay to have
the wheels repaired.
You know I would, only
there are other priorities.
You mean the kind of
priorities that come in a bottle?
That's not fair.
Well, where do you think
all these beautiful dresses
and jewelry come from?
Now, this jewelry
was my mother's
and this dress belonged
to cousin Charlotte.
She doesn't need it anymore,
not now she's married.
You know, it was your
mother's dearest wish
that you should marry well.
No, it wasn't, that's
your dearest wish.
Mother said that I
should marry for love.
We could afford to
be idealistic then.
Times have changed, Elizabeth.
The old estate is crumbling.
There's barely a skeleton staff.
If you could suitably
impress Mr. Winthroppe,
it might be our last chance
to hang onto Hargreave Hall.
Mister? How is it that my
father is the Earl of Pembroke,
yet my supposed husband
to be has no title at all?
He's what they call
new nouveau riche,
(laughs) a businessman.
I'm sure you'll find
him quite charming.
- (gentle music)
- We'll see.
(ominous music)
(fire crackling)
Beheading, they still
do that around here?
Not as a rule, no,
but there's a rather
influential local gentleman
who had a few words
with the magistrate,
persuaded him to bring the
old ax man out of retirement.
What local gentleman?
Somebody who wanted to make
quite sure you were dead.
Perhaps he's got a
grudge against ya.
(ominous music continues)
(fire crackling)
You know the sad thing
is, if I am to be executed,
no one will find
out where I hid it.
- Hid what?
- The loot, of course,
from all the robberies,
Such a shame all that
money going to waste.
- How much money?
- Don't know.
There was so much, I never
got around to counting it.
We just threw it
all in a wooden box
with the jewelry
and gold pieces.
Buried it in the woods
not far from here.
- Where?
- Why should I tell you?
If I dug it up, it
wouldn't go a waste.
And what do I care if
I'm going to be executed?
- I can help ya.
- How?
- Put it a good word.
- With who, the executioner?
Don't knock it, Turpin.
It can be the difference
between a single clean
slice through the neck
or a botched hacking
around the shoulders
that could go on for hours.
Now that old man, he's very old.
Could take him a good few
swings to get the job done
if I don't give
him a hand with it.
(ominous music continues)
(fire crackling)
(birds chirping)
(hooves clomping)
[The Earl] What's
that you're reading?
- (book thumping)
- Just some poetry.
So how did Mr. Winthroppe
come to acquire his wealth
if he wasn't born into it?
I'm a little hazy
about the details,
but I understand it's
about investing in land
and then digging up coal.
He's a manual laborer?
No, no, he doesn't
dig it up himself.
He owns a mine, Elizabeth.
He employs dozens of people.
We used to employ
dozens of people.
And we will again, as long
as you play your cards right.
- (fire crackling)
- Well?
- All right, I'll tell you.
- (ominous music)
Well, come closer.
You don't want anyone
outside these four walls
to hear, do you?
(ominous music continues)
(fire crackling)
(footsteps thumping)
Closer, I want to
whisper in your ear.
(ominous music continues)
Closer.
(keys rattling)
(ominous music continues)
(dramatic music)
(keys rattling)
(dramatic music continues)
(footsteps thumping)
(Turnip panting)
Oh, oh, damn, I need
to find a horse.
(ominous music)
(door rattling)
- Very nice.
- (dramatic music)
It's hardly Hargreave hall.
Of course it isn't.
They don't build houses
like that anymore.
This is brand new,
commissioned and built
to Winthroppe's own design.
And around the back,
there are great tracts of land
all the way down to the mine.
I tell you, Winthroppe
is a man of means.
Remember to flutter
your eyelashes.
(dramatic music continues)
(footsteps thumping)
Most of the coal extraction
going on in England today
is horribly primitive,
pits of only 50 feet deep
with no supporting
structure at all.
Very dangerous for the workers.
- I see.
- There was an incident
in Wales just over a year ago,
where there was
a huge explosion,
which took down an entire
shaft, trapping a dozen men.
And the worst of it was,
they were still alive.
They could be heard
tapping on their helmets,
trying to get a message
out from the rubble.
Nothing could be
done, of course.
Went on for days, apparently.
But that's why I insist in
the highest safety standards.
My shaft is the
longest in the country.
It goes deeper than anyone
else's, over 200 feet deep.
Hear that, Elizabeth, 200 feet?
And might a man breathe
the air that far down?
Well, with our patented
air pumping system, he can.
Fascinating, and
what do people do
with all this coal
you're digging up?
Why aren't you mining
for gold or silver?
- They burn it.
- [The Earl] Hmm?
Answer me this,
sir, if you will,
how much firewood does it
take to heat up Hargreave Hall
during the winter months?
(sighs) Half of
forest, it seems.
This house was built
with a coal cellar,
a room no bigger than
this, beneath our feet.
The coal in that cellar will
heat up this entire property
from October to March.
- Extraordinary.
- You must allow me
to give you a tour
of the mine someday.
That will be marvelous.
Tell me, this mine of
yours, what kind of income
might a set up like this
generate on an annual basis?
More than enough to keep
a young lady in a manner
to which she is accustomed,
I can assure you.
And what about an old man?
Well, my business
manager, Mr. Arkwright,
is as we speak
writing up a contract,
which I'm sure will
allay all your concerns.
Contract, what sort of contract?
A marriage contract.
(dramatic music continues)
(tree creaking)
(birds chirping)
(gravel crunching)
Did you hear that,
Elizabeth? A marriage contract!
- You did it.
- I don't know what I did.
He barely gave me
a passing glance.
Well, obviously, he's
too much of a gentleman
to talk to you directly
until after the marriage.
It's a sign of good breeding.
He seemed far more interested
in talking business with you.
That's another good sign.
I must have a good look
at this proposal of his.
I'm expecting a large
stake in that mine.
He's not getting his hands on
my only daughter for nothing.
Getting his hands on me?
Ugh, you make it
sound awfully tawdry.
And I haven't agreed
to anything yet.
(gentle music)
(tree squeaking)
An opportunity like this
will not come along again,
Elizabeth, not at your age.
Is Hargreave Hall
really at risk?
Well, I didn't
want to say anything,
but the East wing has
already been stripped.
Paintings, furniture,
anything of value, gone.
But that's where I grew up.
All my childhood memories
are of the East wing.
So now you can see how
important this marriage is.
(gentle music continues)
(birds chirping)
(hooves clomping)
Well, I will admit he's
not completely unattractive.
That's the spirit.
I tell you, he'd make
an excellent suitor.
He's tall, he's wealthy,
he's got huge tracts of land.
(ominous music)
(leaves crunching)
(hooves clomping)
(dramatic music)
It's all happening
terribly fast.
At this rate, you'll
have me married off
by the end of the week.
We can but hope (laughs).
(dramatic music continues)
(hooves clomping)
[Dick] Stand and deliver.
(horse neighing)
(dramatic music continues)
Your money or your life.
What the devil's
going on out there?
[Dick] You in the
carriage, show yourselves.
(door rattling)
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
(gravel crunching)
And who might you be, sir?
Who are you to ask who
I am, standing there,
blocking the road, making
demands with menaces?
Now the question is, sir,
who the devil are you?
[Dick] My name, sir, is Turpin.
Perhaps you've heard of
me and my notorious gang.
I heard you'd been arrested.
[Dick] No jail can hold me, sir,
or my gang, who
are at this moment
in the trees surrounding
your carriage.
And I must warn you, they are
all armed and prepared to die.
Well, I am the Earl of Pembroke.
And if you have any
sense of decency,
sir, you'll stand side.
[Dick] The Earl of Pembroke?
That sounds impressive,
you must be very wealthy.
My financial standing,
sir, is no business of yours.
[Dick] I'm making
it my business.
Now hand over whatever
items of value you have
in that carriage.
We are not carrying
any items of values, sir.
[Dick] Really? The Earl of
Pembroke travels the country
without a penny in his pocket?
Being an Earl isn't
what it was, sir.
[Dick] There must be
something worth having in there.
Daddy, who are you talking to?
Elizabeth, get back inside.
[Dick] Well, well, I
thought you said there
was nothing of value
in that carriage.
Sir, sir, she's
my only daughter.
[Dick] Relax, your earlship.
I was talking
about the necklace.
Elizabeth, is it?
- Come over here.
- Elizabeth, it's Turpin,
the famous outlaw (chuckles).
Don't let him lay
a finger on you.
You're betrothed, remember?
[Dick] That's it, come along.
My gang don't want
to be kept waiting.
(gentle music)
(footsteps thumping)
Are you sure you've got a gang?
[Dick] They're out
there in the trees.
Even now, they have
their pistols trained
on you and your father.
Now come along, hand
over the necklace.
I can't see anyone.
Just give me the necklace.
(book thumping)
(gentle music continues)
(birds chirping)
I do believe you're bluffing.
He's bluffing, Daddy,
he hasn't got a gang.
[Dick] Right, that's
it, nobody move.
You've really gone and
bloody done it now.
You're in big trouble.
Now, Turpin, don't be hasty.
[Dick] The young
lady is coming with me,
and if any of you move an
inch in the next 10 minutes,
my gang will let you have it.
(dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
How dare you lay a hand on me.
I am sorry, your ladyship,
I didn't plan it this way.
Where are you taking me?
I don't know, I'm
making this up as I go.
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
(dramatic music)
(door squeaking)
- (footsteps thumping)
- Ah, Mr. Arkwright,
just the man, is the marriage
contract drawn up yet?
Yes, sir, I have it here.
Complete with all the
special clauses I requested?
- Yes, of course, but I must...
- Excellent.
Leave it on the table
and I'll have a message
sent to the Earl,
inviting him back at
his soonest convenience.
Please, Mr. Winthroppe, sir,
I must talk to you about
this land survey report.
It's as I feared.
- [Henry] Let me see.
- (tree squeaking)
The men dug test
pits every 200 yards
in a circular formation.
- What did they find?
- Nothing.
(ominous music)
Nothing, they
found no coal at all?
Not a bit of it, I'm afraid.
It appears that the coal
seam that you found initially
was what they call an
outlier, a one-off.
There's nothing else like
it in a surrounding area.
This is quite unusual really.
I spent 100 pounds
on that survey.
And all the land I purchased?
Largely worthless, I'm afraid.
I suppose you could rear
cattle on it, except.
- Except what?
- The land's covered
in dangerous pits now.
You'd be forever dragging
the animals out of the holes.
You could spend
another 100 pounds
to have the holes
filled in, I suppose.
How could it cost the
same amount filling them in
as to dig them out?
Surely it's half the work.
Well, that's a question
for the surveyors.
But I'm afraid, what with this
and the situation with the
mine, well, that leaves you
in a bit of a precarious
situation, I think.
How about the other survey?
Ah, now, well, that
tip certainly paid off.
As good as we hoped?
Better, it's astonishing
what people have
in their possession and have
no idea that they've got it.
Then we're fine,
as long as this marriage
contract of yours stands up.
Well, it will, once
there's a signature on it.
Leave that with me.
But sir, what
about the situation
- with the mine?
- Yes?
Well, there's barely
any coal left to extract.
Tell them to dig
deeper, another 10 feet.
Well, the last 10 feet
didn't really reveal anything.
I don't care.
I just need to keep up the
appearance of business as usual.
I don't need to tell you
how many loans I took
out against that mine
for all that bloody
worthless land.
No, of course, sir, did you...?
Were you aware the
mine was in trouble
when you took those loans out?
And what if I was?
I would have recommended
strongly against it.
It could be seen as
deliberate fraud.
Mm, and whose signature
is at the bottom
of all those loan
agreements. Mr. Arkwright?
Well, it's mine.
- Thank you, Mr.
- Arkwright, good day.
I was signing on your behalf.
(laughs) I do it all the time.
- Good day.
- (gentle music)
(paper rustling)
(footsteps thumping)
(birds chirping)
(tree creaking)
Do either of you two have
some sort of time piece?
Just wondering if 10
minutes has passed yet.
(birds chirping)
- (footsteps thumping)
- Ow!
You don't exactly
blend in, do you?
What do you mean?
- [Dick] That dress.
- It was rather intended
to make me stand out.
I can see that.
I'm afraid it's the last
thing we need right now.
How long do you think
it'll be before your father
has people out combing
the woods for us?
Come on.
(tree squeaking)
(mischievous music)
(tree creaking)
That's it, turn us around,
straight back to Winthroppe's.
He'll know what to do.
(mischievous music continues)
(leaves rustling)
- Shh.
- What are you doing?
- Stealing this.
- Is that all you know
how to do, steal things?
All right, I'm borrowing it.
Haven't you ever borrowed
anything, your ladyship?
This dress is
borrowed from my cousin.
Well, there you are then.
I promise I'll give it back
when I'm out of trouble.
Are you ever out of trouble?
Occasionally, come on.
(mischievous music continues)
(birds chirping)
(dramatic music)
(hooves thumping)
- Winthroppe!
- (dramatic music continues)
- This is appalling.
- Turpin, did you say?
Yes, he's a well known outlaw.
Yes, I'm very well aware
of his nefarious activities.
In fact, I thought
he was in jail.
Well, apparently, he's free
and he's graduated from
burglary to kidnapping.
Don't worry, we'll get
Elizabeth back. O'Reilly.
(door rattling)
(door squeaking)
He works for me in
various capacities.
To take you back to where
the kidnapping took place.
You'll know what
to do from there.
- Yes, sir.
- (birds chirping)
(ominous music)
(footsteps thumping)
(leaves rustling)
(birds chirping)
Here, put this on.
That thing, ugh, it's probably
infested with something.
Come along, your ladyship,
we haven't got all day.
And in any case, you
should hardly expect me
to change my dress out here
in the middle of the forest.
Oh, for the love of, you know,
you're almost more
trouble than you're worth.
And what am I worth?
Well, I recently lost the
use of an excellent horse.
A horse. So what do you
propose to do, ride on me?
Let's not get
ahead of ourselves.
What I propose to do
is to request a ransom
from your father for
your safe return.
I'm sure the Earl of Pembroke
keeps an excellent stable.
He used to, not anymore.
(mischievous music)
(tree squeaking)
(ominous music)
(horse neighing)
He must have some money,
- at least.
- Not really.
Well, surely it takes a
considerable income just
to maintain such a large estate.
(ominous music continues)
(birds chirping)
He started selling
off family heirlooms.
I'd be absolutely distraught
if we lost Hargreave Hall.
Oh, bugger me, I know
how to pick 'em, don't I?
I must have the daughter
of the only earl
in England who's flat broke.
You'd have been
better off waiting
- until I was married.
- Yes?
(ominous music continues)
(birds chirping)
[O'Reilly] Turpin,
give me the girl.
- (dramatic music)
- Who's that,
someone who works
for your father?
I have no idea.
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
(leaves rustling)
Let's make a deal,
for her safe return,
I want a good horse
and 50 gold sovereigns.
(gun firing)
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
Okay, I'll take the horse
and 20 gold sovereigns.
(gun firing)
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
Okay, just the horse,
I'll just take the horse.
[O'Reilly] You'll get
nothing, give me the girl.
And then we'll say
no more about it?
[O'Reilly] No, then
I'll take your head.
That's what I thought.
(dramatic music continues)
(leaves rustling)
Come on, let's go.
Not right now, I afraid
he's got us outgunned.
We need to find somewhere
to hole up for the night.
It'll be dark soon, come on.
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
(fire crackling)
(liquid sloshing)
Here, this will
steady the nerves.
- Ah, perfect.
- Now, there's no need
to be too concerned.
My man O'Reilly never fails me.
What did you say
his line of work was?
A little bit of
everything, really.
Especially the things one
wishes to be done discreetly.
- I see.
- Now, if you'd like
to take a seat at the table,
as luck would have it,
the marriage contract is
ready for your perusal.
(gentle music)
(rain splattering)
(door creaking)
Well, this will
do for the night.
It most certainly will not.
Wait, what are you doing?
I'm sorry, your ladyship.
- Don't you dare.
- I have to protect my assets.
- [Elizabeth] Ow!
- Sorry, what's this book?
Can you even read?
Of course I can read.
Just don't have
the time right now.
Now where are you going?
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
To get some essentials.
But you can't just
leave me here like this.
Don't worry, I'll be back.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
(door rattling)
(thunder rumbling)
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
Does it say 50%?
Yes, that's right.
Once Elizabeth
and I are married,
50% of all profits from the
mine will be made over to you.
That's very generous.
Nothing's too good for
my future father-in-law.
And what's this
about Hargreave Hall?
Well, the hall and
the surrounding estate
will be made over
to my stewardship.
- Stewardship?
- Well, think on this,
in your later years, do
you really want be burdened
with maintaining
such a vast building?
Not to mention all the
land and the gardens.
You'd take care of all that?
Well, I could so
long as the estate
was under my stewardship.
Do you have an ink
pen to hand, sir?
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
(door rattling)
Good evening, your ladyship.
(goblet rattling)
- Where have you been?
- (match crackling)
I went back to that
little shack in the woods.
There was no one home, so I
borrowed a few essentials.
I thought you might be
hungry, so I brought dinner.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
I'm not hungry.
This isn't so you can
eat, it's so you can change.
I told you I'm not wearing that.
It's clean, I stole it off
a washing line, remember?
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
You stick out a
mile in that dress
and I'm afraid it's
not a risk I'm prepared
to take a moment longer.
I'm afraid I really must insist.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
If you were a gentleman,
you'd turn your back.
I'm an outlaw, not a
gentleman, but still.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
What kind of an
occupation is that anyway?
[Dick] Outlaw? I do all right.
Spending the night
in smelly barns,
is that what you
consider doing all right?
I'm sorry if the accommodation
isn't up to your usual
standards, your ladyship.
Will you stop calling me that?
[Dick] What, your ladyship?
I am not a lady.
(dramatic music)
(rain splattering)
You could have fooled me.
Stop gawking at me.
(dramatic music continues)
(rain splattering)
I meant I do not hold
the title of a lady.
How do you get that then?
You marry a lord.
Well, never mind,
I'm sure you will.
(dramatic music continues)
(rain splattering)
Didn't you say something
about getting married?
That is none of your business.
You don't sound
too happy about it.
Isn't he a lord, then?
I told you that is
none your business.
Wait a minute, you said
that I'd be better off
waiting 'til you got married.
- What did you mean by that?
- Nothing.
He's got money,
hasn't he, your fiance?
That's what you
meant, is it a lord?
- No.
- Or a duke?
- Not a prince.
No, he isn't anything,
just some nouveau riche upstart
named Winthroppe (sighs).
(dramatic music continues)
(rain splattering)
Winthroppe?
(gentle music)
(rain splattering)
Well, it all seems satisfactory.
(ominous music)
(rain splattering)
Mind you (chuckles),
I must warn you,
Elizabeth can be a
feisty young thing.
You're gonna have your work
cut out, that's for certain.
I've never been one to back
away from a challenge, sir.
(thunder droning)
(rain splattering)
How did you
acquire your fortune?
Must have taken quite a bit of
capital, purchasing the land,
setting up the mine
in the first place.
Well, I've always been involved
in one form of business or
another, ever since I was a boy.
I've always been just
a little bit better
at it than everyone else.
Hmm, you parents must
be very proud of you.
Will they be
attending the wedding?
No, I'm afraid not.
They both passed
away some time ago.
- Oh.
- (ominous music continues)
- Aunts, uncles, cousins?
- Nope.
- Shame.
- (ominous music continues)
You know, I adore
Elizabeth, but well,
sometimes I do wish he
had a younger brother,
a young man who might make
his own way in the world,
achieve something
to be proud of.
The trouble with daughters
is they just sit
there, looking pretty.
Well, you know what
they say about a marriage,
it's not so much losing a
daughter, but gaining a son.
Just your signature
at the bottom.
(rain splattering)
(ominous music continues)
- Shouldn't we have a witness?
- What?
- To the signature?
- Well.
(door squeaking)
(ominous music continues)
Ah, O'Reilly, perfect timing.
Would you please witness
the earl's signature?
Well, wait a minute,
what about Turpin?
Gave me the slip,
I have a fair idea
where they're headed, though.
You see, everything
is under control.
As I've always said,
O'Reilly never fails me.
Please, just your
signature, if you will.
- Mm, oh.
- (ominous music continues)
To tell you about Winthroppe.
What would a man
like you know of him?
More than you seem to.
He's 10 times the
thief I'll ever be.
Are you sure you're not jealous?
- Jealous?
- Yes, why not?
He's wealthy, successful,
not to mention handsome.
I found him quite impressive.
You don't know him
very well at all, do you?
For your information, I happen
to have spent several
hours in his company.
Several hours (laughs),
and that's enough to
decide to marry him?
You have no idea how society
marriages work, do you?
You're such a peasant, Turpin.
Call me Dick.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Listen, I'm trying to tell
you something important.
I wasn't always an
outlaw, you know?
What were you before?
A butcher's apprentice.
Oh, so you know how to
carve up a dead animal?
When I was a
butcher's apprentice,
this group of lads
started coming to the shop
with deer carcasses
they wanted to sell.
So I didn't think
anything of it.
(gentle music)
(straw rustling)
It was all fine, until
one night, these lads came
and said they were a man short
and they needed my
help hunting the deer.
Is it normal to
hunt deer at night?
No, but I didn't know that.
It turns out they
were poaching the deer
from the royal
forest at Waltham.
By the time we got
there that night,
it was too late to back out.
And by the end of that night,
I was as guilty as
the rest of them.
The trouble was it
wasn't just poaching
they were getting up to.
Soon enough, it was
horse theft and burglary.
I knew you were a scoundrel.
I was a boy, not even 20.
And there was another
young lad in the group,
even younger than I was.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
And believe it or not,
he was the ringleader,
probably because he
was the most ruthless.
Always carried a dagger
strapped to his back.
Anyway, it all fell
to pieces one night
when we were caught during
a burglary in Hampshire,
when an old man was killed.
Killed, who did it?
I don't know, I
was in another part
of the house at the time.
I have my suspicions.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
Anyway, once we
were all in jail,
this young lad pretended
that we'd forced him into it,
ratted us all out
and gave up a huge stash of
loot we had hidden in the woods.
Probably because he was
barely old enough to shave,
they believed him.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
We all got sentenced
to the noose
and he got a bloody reward.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
And do you know what
that rat's name was?
- Not Winthroppe.
- No.
People called Winthroppe
don't go around poaching deer.
This lad's name was Jack Jones.
Then why are you
telling me this?
Because after the trial,
this young lad took his
reward money and disappeared.
I heard a rumor that he'd moved
to this part of the country
and bought himself
a piece of land,
tried to reinvent himself
as a bit of a gentleman.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
I never had any proof,
but I thought seeing
as me and my gang
were in the area,
I'd have a little sniff around.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
And from what I've
seen and heard,
your Mr. Winthroppe is almost
certainly my Jack Jones.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
There, it's done.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
You may not understand this,
Winthroppe, as a father,
one takes one's responsibility
to one's family very seriously,
and to the family estate.
Knowing that Elizabeth
and Hargreave Hall
are in a safe pair of hands
gives one huge satisfaction.
It's liberating, it's almost
as if having signed this,
I'm no longer required at all.
(gentle music)
(rain splattering)
It's funny you should say that.
I feel the same way.
About you, I mean.
- [The Earl] Mm?
- (ominous music)
(dramatic music)
(The Earl grunting)
(dramatic music continues)
(The Earl thumping)
Careful, O'Reilly, he's
drooling all over it.
(ominous music)
(rain splattering)
Now you better make damn sure
you can get Elizabeth back.
- [O'Reilly] No problem.
- If I play this right,
Elizabeth will be begging
me to have Turpin dealt with
as harshly as possible.
(ominous music continues)
(rain splattering)
What an absolute
load of nonsense.
I knew you were jealous.
I am not jealous,
the man is a criminal.
That's rich coming from you.
I may be thief, but
I'm not a murderer.
The whole story makes no sense.
You said you were sentenced
to hang, yet here you are.
- I managed to escape.
- Oh, how convenient.
(rain splattering)
(mischievous music)
We'll spend one night here,
and then in the morning,
I'll take you to
your Mr. Winthroppe
for whatever ransom I can get.
(mischievous music continues)
(straw rustling)
Am I supposed to
sleep on the floor?
(mischievous music continues)
(rain splattering)
- You can have the blanket.
- (blanket rustling)
(mischievous music continues)
(rain splattering)
You better not come near me.
I can assure you, your ladyship,
you have nothing to worry about.
(mischievous music continues)
(rain splattering)
(birds chirping)
I'm sorry to bother you
so early, Mr. Winthroppe,
but you did say in the morning.
[Henry] Is that the report
I've been waiting for?
More bad news, I'm
afraid, news from the mine.
Oh, what is it this time?
Well, you know the men are
digging deeper and deeper,
what with the upper
levels drying up?
Well, apparently
the deeper you go,
the greater the risk of a
buildup of noxious gases.
Yes, I know that.
That's what the air
pump system is for.
Well, the foreman told me
that it hadn't been
working for weeks.
I do recall hearing
something about that.
17 men were overwhelmed,
one nearly died.
Well, we are running a mine,
not a workers'
welfare association.
There are bound to
be some casualties.
That's part of the job.
Besides, I'm not gonna
repair the air pumps.
Why is that?
Is to rid the shaft
of combustible gases.
- Yes.
- Well, it just occurred
to me that should there be
an explosion in the shaft,
it could render the
mine inoperable.
No, but that will be a disaster.
Only for my insurers.
People will be killed.
Again, not a problem
for me personally.
I most assuredly won't
be anywhere near the site
when it happens.
Do the insurers know the
current value of the mine,
given that there's no damned
coal to be found in it?
I'm getting a little bit tired
of your remonstrations,
Arkwright.
Now let me see report.
(gentle music)
(tree squeaking)
(paper rustling)
(birds chirping)
The men began by digging
outside the Eastern boundary
of the estate.
By digging in diagonally,
they were able
to see the start
of a new coal seam
just inside the boundary.
The surveyor thinks
that the best place
to sink the shaft would be here.
On top of the hall?
Well, underneath the
hall to be precise.
It would have to be demolished
of course to make way for it.
Excellent, looks like
we're back in business.
If this all goes to plan,
the old mine can go to
the crows, for all I care.
Assuming the earl signs
the contract, of course.
It's already done.
And the wedding
goes ahead as planned?
The law is very
precise about that.
You have to be
related to the earl,
by marriage or otherwise,
for you to take full
advantage of the estate.
It's all in hand.
(ominous music)
(birds chirping)
Where is the earl, by the way?
Well, his presence
was no longer required.
For his own daughter's wedding?
Is he not going to walk
her down the aisle?
I wasn't aware that
was a legal necessity.
Besides the earl sadly
passed away in the night.
- (ominous music continues)
- What,
after he'd signed the contract?
Fortunately for us, yes.
This is all very strange.
Even by your standards,
Mr. Winthroppe.
By my standards?
I've gone along with
a lot of your schemes,
but this just doesn't sit
right with me, this one.
Since the contract's signed
and the survey's completed,
I'd rather have no
further part in this.
Well, I'm sorry you
feel that way, Arkwright.
As it happens,
I do have no further
requirements you need fulfill.
Very good, I'll
be on my way then.
There is just one more thing
in regards to the late earl.
- Yes?
- Well, I have some good news.
You'll soon be joining him.
- (birds chirping)
- What?
(suspenseful music)
(Arkwright grunting)
(suspenseful music continues)
(knife whooshing)
- No!
- Nobody goes against me,
Arkwright, you should
know that by now.
(suspenseful music continues)
(Arkwright grunting)
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
(footsteps thumping)
(gentle music continues)
(birds chirping)
Now, fetch me a bride.
What about Turpin?
I think it's best to let the
authorities deal with Turpin.
I've already ensured he'll get
an immediate death sentence.
Oh, while you're out,
inquire where one might
purchase some explosives.
(dramatic music)
(wood creaking)
(birds chirping)
- (straw rustling)
- Elizabeth!
Wake up, your ladyship.
(birds chirping)
(pages rustling)
(tree squeaking)
Elizabeth!
Oh, what the hell, Elizabeth?
(dramatic music)
- [Elizabeth] Quiet.
- Ah.
I don't have to listen to
your nonsense anymore, Turpin.
- Untie me.
- And then what?
I'm going to
get Mr. Winthroppe
and he'll know exactly
what to do with you.
He'll kill me.
It's no more than you deserve.
But Mr. Winthroppe
is a gentleman.
I'm sure he will do
nothing of the sort.
In which case, he'll hand
me over to the authorities
and they'll kill me,
is that what you want?
It couldn't happen to
a more deserving fellow.
Well, now I know
that's how you feel.
Keep back, I'll
pull the trigger.
I'm sure you will.
I mean it.
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
I thought you were
gonna pull the trigger.
(gentle music)
(birds chirping)
Are you truly not afraid to die?
(gentle music continues)
Not really, a pistol
needs gun powder
and a lead ball to fire.
(gun clicking)
This is empty.
You mean all that time,
you've been waving
that thing around?
I was never gonna shoot anybody.
(gentle music continues)
(birds chirping)
Come on, let's go.
Don't you have a plan,
I mean, to get away?
I'll think of something.
I told you I'm making
this up as I go.
(gentle music continues)
(footsteps thumping)
(dramatic music)
(leaves crunching)
(birds chirping)
(door rattling)
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
(leaves crunching)
I could just walk
away, couldn't I?
(dramatic music)
(leaves crunching)
And you couldn't do anything.
Do you know your
way out this forest?
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
(leaves crunching)
(dramatic music continues)
[O'Reilly] Turpin, the
girl's coming with me now.
Is that thing even loaded?
My pistol's always
ready to fire.
Listen, if you work for
a man named Winthroppe,
(dramatic music)
(fighters grunting)
(Dick thumping)
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
(fire crackling)
(ominous music)
(lock rattling)
(footsteps thumping)
(ominous music continues)
(fire crackling)
Well, well, well, if it ain't
my old friend, Dick Turpin.
- Hello again.
- (Dick grunting)
(ominous music continues)
(fire crackling)
I ever tell you about the
stash of loot I have hidden?
(ominous music continues)
(fire crackling)
(fist thumping)
(birds chirping)
It's such a relief to
have you back, Elizabeth.
We were all getting
so terribly worried.
(birds chirping)
(tree squeaking)
Turpin is such a villain.
He could have done
anything to you.
(birds chirping)
(tree squeaking)
Did he do anything to you?
No, I'm fine, thank you.
(birds chirping)
(tree squeaking)
Well, the good news is we're
moving forward at a pace.
We've got an urgent appointment
with the Reverend
Peters this afternoon.
The Reverend Peters?
Well, we are due to be
married after all, Elizabeth.
Where is my father, is he here?
In the manner of speaking.
(somber music)
(birds chirping)
I'm sorry to say that your
father succumbed in the night
to the unbearable
stresses of the situation,
vis-a-vis your kidnapping by
the aforementioned Turpin.
He's currently laid
out downstairs,
awaiting transportation
to the church.
(somber music continues)
(birds chirping)
- What?
- There's no need to worry.
I've spoken with the Reverend
and he's agreed
to perform a sort
of combined wedding and funeral.
So as I say, there's
really no need to worry.
It's at three o'clock,
so you have plenty of
time to clean yourself up.
(somber music continues)
(birds chirping)
You actually want
to get married today?
There's no time like
the present, Elizabeth.
It's what your father
would've wanted.
(somber music continues)
(birds chirping)
It's all that Turpin's
fault, really.
The man's a veritable monster.
Thank goodness he's now
incarcerated in the local jail,
ready for the executioner's
ax this afternoon.
What, the executioner's ax?
Well, he has escaped the
noose before, Elizabeth.
This time we'll be
certain he's dead.
(somber music continues)
(birds chirping)
(papers rustling)
(somber music continues)
(birds chirping)
(papers rustling)
- What's this?
- (dramatic music)
It's just some business
papers, Elizabeth,
nothing you'd understand.
It's my father's
estate, that's our house.
It's just something
I was discussing
with your father before
his untimely passing.
(paper rustling)
(dramatic music continues)
It's a building plan.
- Elizabeth.
- It's a mine.
It just so happens
that Hargreave Hall
is sitting on top of a rich
vein of very accessible coal.
Accessible, how
can it be accessible
if it's underneath the house?
If the house was
no longer there.
You want to knock
down Hargreave Hall
and build a bloody
great mine in its place!
The return on the investment
will be phenomenal, Elizabeth.
That's my house!
The earl was in
complete agreement.
You're a liar, my father
would have never
have agreed to this.
- O'Reilly.
- (dramatic music continues)
Let's not make things
unpleasant, Elizabeth.
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
Your feelings not withstanding,
the earl was in
complete agreement
and signed all the
necessary paperwork.
All that is now required
for me to acquire full
control of Hargreave Hall
is for us to get married.
That is going to happen
today at three o'clock,
whether you like it or not.
(dramatic music continues)
(Dick grunting)
- (fire crackling)
- That's for the beating you
gave me yesterday.
- Oh, so we're even.
- Not even close.
We'll be even come three
o'clock this afternoon
when your head's on
the chopping block.
- Three o'clock?
- Yeah, that's right.
They're expecting quite a crowd,
you being a famous
highwayman and all that.
(fire crackling)
(bells ringing)
- What's that?
- (bells ringing)
It's the local
church across the road.
(bells ringing)
(fire crackling)
It's two o'clock.
(ominous music)
You got an hour to live.
You best make the most of it.
(ominous music continues)
(fire crackling)
This is all very irregular.
We normally ask that the
happy couple attend services
for three months
prior to the wedding.
Yes, I do appreciate that,
Reverent, but in this case,
time is very much
of the essence.
Ah, I see, well,
these things do happen.
And when is the young lady due?
- Half past two.
- I'm sorry.
For a three o'clock wedding.
She'll be arriving
at half past two.
Ah, yes, of course.
And I'm sure a suitably large
donation to the church funds
would help cover
any additional costs
due to these irregularities.
Well, of course there
are always costs associated
with a wedding, of course,
the church fee, my own fee,
the choir fee,
the organist's fee
and other
miscellaneous expenses.
Then we understand each other.
I believe we do.
(dramatic music)
(fire crackling)
(ominous music)
Listen, I need to
tell you something.
You think I'm gonna fall for
the same trick again, Turpin?
It's not that.
Listen, I have some
important information
about a local gentleman
called Winthroppe.
- Do you know of him?
- Of course I do.
Me brother-in-law
works down his mine.
Half the people in this
town owe their livelihood
to Mr. Winthroppe.
He's a great man,
one of the best.
- (ominous music continues)
- Oh.
So, what's this
valuable information?
- Never mind.
- (ominous music continues)
(bells ringing)
Relax, Turpin, it
ain't three O'clock yet.
What are the bells for?
- Must be a wedding.
- A wedding?
(ominous music continues)
(bells ringing)
(footsteps thumping)
(O'Reilly grunting)
(bells ringing)
Shall we get on with it?
- Don't touch me.
- Shut up!
But it isn't three o'clock
yet, the choir hasn't arrived.
Oh, we can do without
the hymns, Reverend.
I'd sooner get this over with.
Very well, music, please.
(dramatic organ music)
What's the matter?
Haven't you ever heard
of a shotgun wedding?
(dramatic music continues)
(fire crackling)
Are you sure those bells
are to signify a wedding?
Pretty sure, it's funny though,
they don't normally have
weddings on a Thursday.
Must be a rush job.
(fire crackling)
(ominous music)
Dearly beloved, we
are gathered here today
to join this man and this
woman in holy matrimony,
which is an honorable
estate instituted by God
in the time of man's innocence,
signifying the mystical union
between Christ and his church.
This union, which Christ
adorned and beautified
by His presence and was
commended by St. Paul
to be honorable amongst all men
and is therefore not
to be taken lightly.
Yes, can we skip
this bit, Reverend?
We haven't got all day.
(dramatic music)
Yes, very well.
(dramatic music continues)
(ominous music)
Do thou takest this woman
to be thy wedded wife,
to live together
after God's ordinance
in the holy estate of matrimony?
Will thou love her,
comfort, honor and keep her
in sickness and in health,
and forsaking all others,
keep thee only unto her
as long as you both shall live?
- I will.
- (ominous music continues)
Will thou takest this man
to be thy wedded husband,
to live together
after God's ordinance
in the holy estate of matrimony,
will thou love him, comfort him,
honor and keep him in
sickness and in health,
and forsaking all of others,
keep thee only unto him as
long as you both shall live?
(ominous music continues)
- She will.
- (ominous music continues)
Who givest this
woman to be married
- to this man?
- Oh, O'Reilly.
(ominous music continues)
(footsteps thumping)
(fire crackling)
(ominous music continues)
What's going to happen to me?
Well, just before three o'clock,
there'll be a knock at the door.
That'll be someone from the
magistrate's office come
to take you to the executioner.
(somber music)
(fire crackling)
What about my last words?
If you got anything
to say, say it now,
'cause any minute,
it's all gonna be over.
(somber music continues)
(fire crackling)
(birds chirping)
- And now we pray.
- (dramatic music)
Oh, eternal God and
creator of all mankind,
giver of all spiritual grace
and author of everlasting life,
send down Thy blessings
upon these, Thy servants,
this man and this woman,
who we bless in Thy name,
so they surely may keep
and perform the vows and
covenants betwixt them
and ever remain in
perfect peace and love,
according to Your laws through
Jesus Christ, our Lord, amen.
And now as much as this man.
What is it?
I don't know your Christian
name, Mr. Winthroppe.
- Henry.
- This man Henry
- and this wo...
- Elizabeth.
And this woman Elizabeth
have joined together
in holy wedlock and
witnessed as much before God,
I now pronounce them to be...
(dramatic music)
Jesus Christ.
Nobody move. You keep this
ready to fire at all times,
isn't that right, Mr. O'Reilly?
(dramatic music continues)
So all I have to do
is pull the trigger
and someone's losing their head.
Elizabeth, let's
not do anything...
- Shut up!
- (dramatic music continues)
- Which way to the jail?
- What?
The jail, which
way is it from here?
It's out through the
church gates, turn left,
and it's across the street.
(dramatic music continues)
(footsteps thumping)
She's going after Turpin.
(dramatic music continues)
(roses crunching)
It won't be long now, Turpin.
I'm looking forward to this.
I've not seen a beheading
since I was a little 'un.
We had a kick about in the
square afterwards with the head.
Jesus, what sort of revolting
backwater is this town?
This is Winthroppe's
town, bought and paid for.
(ominous music)
(fire crackling)
(door thumping)
(hands slapping)
Here we go.
(ominous music continues)
(fire crackling)
(wood scraping)
(dramatic music)
I'm looking for Dick.
I bet you are.
(pistol thumping)
(gaoler grunting)
- (keys rattling)
- Grab his keys.
- We haven't got much time.
- You're telling me.
(dramatic music continues)
(Dick chuckling)
(keys rattling)
(gate rattling)
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
- (footsteps thumping)
- Wait!
(gentle music)
Dick, I'm sorry.
You were right about Winthroppe.
You were right about everything.
Never mind mind about
that now, Elizabeth,
we've gotta get out of sight.
You certainly know how to
pick a dress, don't you?
- (gentle music continues)
- Sorry.
(birds chirping)
(tree squeaking)
You bloody idiot, O'Reilly.
How could you let
her take your pistol?
(ominous music)
How are we going to
get her back now?
Don't worry about it, sir.
I have a good idea where
they'll be sleeping tonight.
(ominous music continues)
(rain splattering)
(footsteps thumping)
(gentle music)
(rain splattering)
You know, you saved my
life today, Elizabeth.
You could have just
left me in that jail.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
It was something
Winthroppe said,
but I didn't realize it
until I was stood there
about to be married to him.
What was that?
He told me that you
escaped the noose before.
How could he have
known that unless...
- Unless?
- Everything you told me
was the truth.
(rain splattering)
(gentle music continues)
I'm so sorry I
didn't believe you.
(rain splattering)
(gentle music continues)
So what do you want to do?
I don't know, there
must be some way we
can stop Winthroppe.
For now, I just want to get
out of this blasted dress.
I can hardly breathe in it.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
I could help you with
that, if you'd like.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
- All right.
- (gentle music continues)
(footsteps thumping)
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
It's all tied up at the
back, like a corset.
Yes, I think I've got it.
Is that any better?
(gasps) It feels like it.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
- Almost there.
- Yes.
- [Dick] Closer?
- Very close.
- Almost there.
- (gasps) Yes.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
- Now what?
- (Elizabeth panting)
Now it just lifts over my head.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
Like this?
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
What now?
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
Why don't you decide?
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
Well, it is your
wedding night after all.
(gentle music continues)
(rain splattering)
(ominous music)
What about the explosives?
No, those are for the mine.
Paraffin then, the whole
place will go up like tinder.
(ominous music continues)
(rain splattering)
But we've got to get
the girl out first.
- (ominous music continues)
- That's your job.
I'll deal with Turpin.
(ominous music continues)
(rain splattering)
Make sure you do, I
want him dead, dead!
(ominous music continues)
(rain splattering)
Well, we finally found
something you're good at.
What do you mean?
Well, I was thinking,
you're not much of
an outlaw, are you?
The legendary Dick Turpin.
You get caught every
time you go out (laughs).
I don't write the legends.
They just get
exaggerated over time.
Everyone likes a good
story, don't they?
Even you.
(thunder droning)
I prefer the real thing.
(rain splattering)
(birds chirping)
Where did you
learn how to do it?
What, highway robbery?
No, stupid, how to treat a lady?
(rain splattering)
(thunder droning)
I was married once,
a long time ago.
(rain splattering)
I didn't know that.
Remember that story I told you
about how I fell in
with Jack Jones' gang?
Well, the girl I was married to,
she worked in the butcher's too.
Wasn't long before they had
her fencing stolen goods.
- What happened?
- (rain splattering)
Apart from Jones, we all
got sentenced to the noose.
I managed to escape.
She didn't.
(rain splattering)
(grass rustling)
(door squeaking)
(footsteps thumping)
(rain splattering)
(thunder droning)
(suspenseful music)
- Well.
- (Elizabeth gasping)
(suspenseful music continues)
I can't say I'm totally
shocked. Elizabeth,
not even married yet,
and you've already
been unfaithful to me.
(suspenseful music continues)
What are you doing?
I'm saving a life
of my fiance, Turpin,
from a notorious criminal
who's kidnapped her
and held her hostage in a
dangerously inflammable building.
- Inflammable?
- (suspenseful music continues)
Look at this, all
these candles everywhere.
Goodness knows
what might happen.
(suspenseful music continues)
(rain splattering)
O'Reilly, oil, please.
(suspenseful music continues)
(oil splashing)
Come along, Elizabeth.
For God's sake, put on some
clothes, you look like a whore.
I would sooner stay with Turpin
and burn to death than
go anywhere with you.
(suspenseful music continues)
She knows who you are, Jack.
- Oh, really?
- (suspenseful music continues)
Well, perhaps it will be
better if you did burn to death.
(suspenseful music continues)
(rain splattering)
O'Reilly, a little bit more
oil, please, on these two.
(suspenseful music continues)
Always ready to fire, O'Reilly.
(gun firing)
(O'Reilly grunting)
(suspenseful music continues)
(O'Reilly thumping)
(fire roaring)
(O'Reilly screaming)
Quick, Elizabeth, the door.
(suspenseful music continues)
(lock rattling)
(fire roaring)
(suspenseful music continues)
I meant go out through
it, not lock us in.
(suspenseful music continues)
(fire roaring)
So, this is it, Turpin.
(suspenseful music continues)
(fire roaring)
It's just you and me.
(suspenseful music continues)
(fire roaring)
I have waited a long
time for this, Jack.
You must have known
that sooner or later,
one of us would track you down.
I did, that's why I've
always been prepared.
(suspenseful music continues)
(fire roaring)
(knife whooshing)
(Elizabeth gasping)
(suspenseful music continues)
(fire roaring)
(fighters grunting)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Jack grunting)
(Jack thumping)
(fire roaring)
- (gentle music)
- Why don't you ever do
- what I tell you?
- I never do what men tell me.
But anyway, where would I go?
One thing at a time, Elizabeth.
Now let's get out of here
before the whole place goes up.
(gentle music continues)
(fire roaring)
(dramatic music)
(wind howling)
(hooves thumping)
(horse neighing)
(dramatic music continues)
(birds chirping)
(hooves clomping)
(dramatic music continues)
(grass rustling)
(horse snorting)
(dramatic music continues)
(hooves clomping)
Are you sure your
want to do this?
- (birds chirping)
- What else can I do?
I have no income,
nowhere to stay.
I can't possibly afford
to keep Hargreave Hall.
(birds chirping)
All right, then.
Now remember what I said,
when the carriage comes
around the corner.
I know what I'm doing,
I've read all the stories.
In those stories,
everything gets exaggerated.
Not everything does.
(dramatic music continues)
(leaves rustling)
(suspenseful music continues)
(hooves clomping)
[Dick] Stand and deliver.
[Elizabeth] Your
money or your life.
(dramatic music continues)
(upbeat rock music)
♪ These days, the
days are long ♪
(Mollie laughing)
That come in a (wags tongue).
♪ It's harder than I thought ♪
Sorry.
♪ It just shows ♪
♪ You can only go ♪
(Mollie laughing)
Sorry, I got stuck.
(Tom and Mollie laughing)
♪ I'm dying for more ♪
(Tom laughing)
Now it just lifts over my head.
♪ I'm dying for more ♪
That's not the line (beep).
♪ One down, and one to go ♪
♪ The devil sows the weeds ♪
♪ You pull them out and
then another grows ♪
♪ Downcast and made of glass ♪
♪ Looking for the softest
place to fall, ooh ♪
♪ I'm dying for more ♪
♪ For something that I never
felt that I never felt before ♪
♪ Stay low, the more you show ♪
♪ You make yourself a moving
target, uh-huh, uh-huh ♪
♪ One down, and one to go ♪
♪ Always back to where
I started, yeah ♪
♪ I'm dying for more ♪
♪ For something that I never
felt that I never felt before ♪
(upbeat rock music)
♪ I'm dying for more ♪
♪ For something that I never
felt that I never felt before ♪
(upbeat rock music continue)
♪ Dying for more ♪
♪ For something that I never
felt that I never felt before ♪
(upbeat rock music continue)
(gentle music)
(dramatic music)
(epic dramatic music)
The best IPTV in the UK
WWW.ALLIN1BOX.CO.UK