Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Morning, guys.
How's it going?
Bailey, what's up? What's up?
Hey, Chewie. Hey, Watson.
How's it going?
Looking good. Queenie. Rascal.
Yeah. OK.
Who wants some food?
Wolf it down. That's it.
That's all you get.
Water?
How are you?
There she is. There she is.
OK. Alright, Lexi. Alright. Hey.
Back it up. Back it up.
Hey, Lexi. Back it up.
Oh, hey! Hey! Hey. Big doggie.
Big doggie. Big doggie.
Holly, right?
Holly Garling.
Hi. How are you?
Hi. I'm sorry.
Do we know each other?
- Oh, Seth. Westbrook High.
- Oh. Were you in my class?
I was in the year above you.
We didn't hang out or anything.
But I knew who you were.
You did?
Sure. Everybody did.
I don't know about that.
So you're a writer now, huh?
- That's cool. It's great.
- Yeah.
This whole waitress uniform,
it's... it's just a disguise.
It's convincing.
I was gonna order
an ice-cream sundae.
- Extra sprinkles.
- You wouldn't be the first.
- This is my stop.
- Oh, this is you?
- It was nice to see you again.
- Nice to see you too.
Hey, if you're not
doing anything...
..get a coffee?
Hm.
We're looking at your numbers.
Hey.
There he is.
There's the man.
Nate. Let me ask you
a question.
Mmm?
If there was this girl
and you wanted her to notice you...
- Are you serious right now?
- Yeah.
Shit, man, I don't know you.
I don't know what kind of game you got.
Why are you asking me?
Sorry. I thought maybe...
Listen. Wait.
You like this girl?
We are talking about
a girl here, right?
Yes, a girl. I do like her.
So just be confident, you know?
Guy who's confident,
knows how to make 'em laugh.
Tell 'em about your day,
acting like you give a shit.
I mean, it ain't a mystery.
Confident, funny, make 'em laugh.
Got it. Good. Thanks.
Hey. And no more
bringing this shit to me, alright?
You and me, we ain't like that.
Cool.
Seth, Dr Jessup needs your help.
He's putting down
the German shepherd in 34.
- Lexi.
- Look, you're a sweet guy.
If you can't do your job,
I'll find someone who can.
Is that clear?
She's... really good dog.
Hey, Lexi. Hey.
Here's the thing. We just...
Hey, girl.
Hey, Lexi.
Hey.
How's it going?
Want to go for a walk?
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Good girl. Yeah, it's exciting, isn't it?
Alright, Lexi. Here we go.
Alright. That's a good dog.
Yeah. That's a good dog.
- You alright?
- Yeah. She's just a good dog.
Shh. It's OK, Lexi.
It's alright.
You want her,
you can always keep her.
My building doesn't allow pets.
Very strict.
Fucking find a new place.
$9 an hour?
I'm lucky I have running water.
That's your whole problem.
You got no initiative.
It's how come you're still working
in a shithole like this at your age.
You want something in this life,
you gotta take it.
So, what's it gonna be?
I mean, you want her, she's yours.
Do it. Do it already.
Alright, Lexi. Here we go.
You're a good dog.
Hold still. You're a good dog.
Hey, Holly, hey.
What time do you get lunch?
What... time do you get lunch?
I get lunch at 1:00.
1:00.
Hey. Hey. Hi.
Hey.
Hey. Remember me?
That's right. Uh...
Well, I guess table for one
while I'm here, but...
..really, I was just wondering
if you wanted to get, maybe...
dinner later.
I, uh... I don't know about you,
but I love seafood.
Oh, you do? Yeah. That's all I eat.
Seafood, seafood...
There's a, uh...
There's a place on...
There's a place on Wilshire
called The Crab Joint.
Oh, you know it?
Yeah, we could... Tonight?
It's, uh...
Hey, Holly. Hey.
Hey, Holly. How's it going?
Hey.
- Hi. Anywhere?
- Yeah. Anywhere is fine.
- Just...
- OK. Thanks.
Hey. How are you?
I'm Holly.
I'll be taking care
of you today.
You must be a writer.
- Sorry?
- A writer.
The, uh, disguise, from the bus.
We met a couple of days ago
on the bus.
- My name's Seth.
- I'm so sorry.
My memory, like,
totally sucks. I know.
Just what you want to hear
from your waiter, right?
No, that's fine.
Can I get you started with anything?
An appetiser? Or...?
Yeah. Um...
Let's, uh... Let's do water.
And then, by the time
you come back, I'll... I'll know.
- Water. Una agua. You got it.
- Hey, um...
I like your hair. It looks
different from... from the bus.
- It's nice. Yeah.
- Thank you.
You shouldn't feel insecure about it
or... self-conscious.
It's... It is a... a good haircut.
Why don't you take a look at the menu
and I will go grab your water.
Yeah. Pie.
Apple pie.
How's it going over here?
- Seth.
- What's that?
Seth. My name is Seth.
How's the food, Seth?
It's good. It's quality.
Actually, I had a question for you.
Do you like Ben Folds?
'Cause I have a couple of tickets
to his concert this week
and the girl I was gonna go with -
not a girlfriend or anything -
she can't make it,
she has a thing.
I was wondering
if maybe you'd want to...
..go?
I'm sorry, I can't.
I don't like going to shows
by myself.
It feels kind of strange, you know?
So maybe...
Not a big deal. No pressure.
We could just go.
Wouldn't have to be
a date or anything.
The thing is, I already
sort of have a boyfriend, so...
No, you don't.
Just gonna leave this here.
- Thanks for coming in.
- Hang on... a second.
But, like, when they
do speak, you know you're in trouble.
Hey.
- There's a guy out there.
- Ooh. Is he hot?
- I'm serious, Claire.
- Don't get paranoid on me, Hol.
You're no fun when you're paranoid.
Never mind.
10 bucks says it's him.
- Yes, Eric.
- Hey, babe.
What do you want?
Jesus! What's with the attitude?
I just wanted to talk.
- I've been thinking about you.
- Is he drunk and weepy again?
A little bit.
Who are you talking to?
You with someone?
Don't get paranoid on me, Eric.
You're no fun
when you're paranoid.
So, the other night with Eric?
Really? Are we gonna go there again?
He was two years. You can't
convince me he never mattered.
I'm serious, though, Hol.
Being alone is just... kinda shitty.
So, what, I'm just supposed
to forget everything he did?
Yes. Forget, forgive.
Move the fuck on already.
Just go back to the way things were.
You know I can't do that.
To us.
Hey, Sam.
- Someone's popular.
- What?
We put it
in the break room.
OK...
Lucky bitch.
Spill. Who's the guy?
- Hey.
Listen. I'm so sorry
for the drunk dial the other night.
- I mean, you know how it is.
- Yeah, I do.
Listen. Can I get you a beer
or something?
Eric. You have to stop
doing stuff like this.
Stuff like... What now?
Come on.
Roses? You know they're my favourite.
I didn't know that.
OK. Well, now I just feel stupid.
- I should go.
- Just one beer.
It wasn't all bad, right?
We had some good times.
Yep.
So, why don't we
give it another shot?
Are you really gonna make me
say her name?
..thousand times,
and you know if I could take it back,
I would, in a heartbeat.
This is so fucking stupid.
I mean, we had something.
Had.
Eric, past tense.
I'm gonna get some air.
Nice night.
- Yeah.
- Yep.
- Not a smoker?
- Me? No.
That's good. Don't ever start.
It's a terrible habit.
OK, I won't.
Thanks.
- Have a nice night.
- You like the flowers?
You seemed like a red-and-white
roses kind of girl.
- It was just a guess.
- Oh, my God.
You're that guy
from the restaurant.
Seth.
What, are you, like,
following me or something?
What? No. Just...
Look, I'm not some psycho, OK?
You know me.
- We went to school together.
- What do you want?
I don't want anything.
I just want to talk to you.
When I saw you on the bus
the other day,
after all these years,
I... I felt something.
I know you did.
I can't just walk away from that.
- I don't even know you.
- Yeah, but you will.
You can go. I just...
Can I just talk to you?
- Hey, come on.
- Don't! Don't touch me. Move!
You kidding me?
Just let me
talk to you?
- Fuck you. Fuck you!
- Holly?
- Just let me explain.
- He tried to grab me.
What? No. Hey.
That is not true at all, man.
Fuck off!
- Did he hurt you?
- I'm fine.
You think this is funny?
- Eric, stop. Stop it.
- Laugh it up, dickhead.
Let me handle this. Come on!
Get the fuck away from her!
Don't you ever
come back here!
Maybe if you retrace your steps.
No. It's gotta be here somewhere.
Well, was your name in it?
Or, like, any contact information?
What do you think?
Ah!
You fucking bitch!
Claire? You here?
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
What I just put in you
is called pancuronium bromide.
It's a paralysing agent. Stings a little.
Don't worry. It's safe.
I tested it on myself.
- What you doing here?
- Oh.
Boss lady calls
in the middle of the night.
- Gotta make a delivery.
- Not so fast, man.
Sign in.
Right.
- Excuse me.
- The hell's that?
I think it's, uh, delousing powder.
Alright. See you later.
- You hear that?
- What?
- Something wrong?
- Shh.
- You hear something?
- Quiet, man.
You heard that, right?
That "Uh!" sound.
I don't hear anything.
What is it?
Fucking AC, man.
Shit's always going out.
Got it. Got it.
- It's, uh, broken?
- It's always broken.
- This whole place sucks.
- Alright.
Ugh! Ah!
Shut up!
So...
I'm Seth, in case you forgot.
Fuck you.
- Your choice.
- Fuck you!
I'm doing this
for your own good.
We'll try this again tomorrow.
Fuck you!
Hi.
I brought you some water.
Here. Drink this.
It's alright.
Alright. Breathe.
Breathe. Breathe. Sit up.
Sorry.
Take it easy. It's OK.
I brought food as well,
in case you feel up for it.
Water.
Food.
Just take it easy, alright?
That's all you're getting today.
Wait!
Please don't leave me.
I know this is hard.
It's hard for me too.
But it's important
to define our relationship.
Establish some boundaries.
This. This doesn't work.
That's right.
I'll come back tomorrow
and we'll get started.
He's gonna kill you.
But you know that.
Maybe he'll lose his nerve, huh?
Chicken out.
- Or maybe he'll just get bored.
- You're not helping.
He won't even need a gun, Holly.
All he has to do is walk away.
Shut up.
Look at you.
You're letting him beat you?
That pathetic little shit?
If that's all it takes,
then maybe you deserve to be in there.
Shut up!
Are you gonna rape me?
No.
Kill me?
I hope not.
You HOPE not?
Might not have a choice.
And why's that?
I might not be able to save you.
What is this, some kind of
fucking religious thing?
Did God tell you to punish
all the whores, something like that?
It's a different kind of saving.
- And no.
- So, what?
You're just a sick fuck?
This is how you get your kicks?
I'm not doing this for me.
Doing this for you.
Because you're special.
Special?
It's true.
Before I met you, I was just...
..floating through life...
..like any minute,
I could just drift off.
No-one would even notice.
Then you came along.
And... the thing...
..the thing that made it so hard is...
..is I thought you were different.
You're smart. Funny.
When you talked to me, you saw me.
You really... saw me.
That's just what
you wanted me to see, huh?
The version of Holly you are
when everyone's watching.
We both know that's a lie, don't we?
Go to hell.
That's the question.
Which one's the real Holly?
The Holly on the outside or...
..the other Holly?
Because if there's even a chance
I can save you,
I have to take it.
But if that's it,
if there's nothing left to save,
then you're never
leaving this room.
What you doing here?
Man, if they catch you
fucking around in them tunnels...
They won't catch me.
I'm not going in there.
Just grab a mop.
We got that place
smelling like dog shit out there.
Shit.
This fuckin' dude is a joke.
So...
What are you gonna do now?
I'm gonna wait.
Good girl.
It's a real page-turner.
You're a hell of a writer.
You know that?
You're a thief.
And now what?
Suddenly, you've got me all figured out?
I wish. No.
Mostly, I just felt sorry for you.
You...
..felt sorry for me.
Yeah, just the part
where you talk about love.
"Love is just a label
for our biological imperatives."
I don't know. Felt ignorant to me.
Are you really gonna lecture me
on love, Seth?
You're keeping a girl in a cage.
I think I finally figured it out.
All these people
who talk about love
like it's this lightning bolt
from the sky,
this irresistible force.
So you think,
"Well, I've never felt that."
But those people are wrong.
Love's not a lightning bolt.
Love, real love,
takes work.
Sacrifice.
Real love is giving everything you have
to someone else.
- That's love.
- Fucking kidding me.
You don't think?
"Love is sacrifice."
You know who believes that?
People who hate themselves.
Who are alone, depressed.
Just like you.
- Think I hate myself?
- I know you do.
You hate yourself so much,
you can't even imagine
how fucked up someone would
have to be to love you back.
So you convince yourself
that love is this thing that you can buy!
That all you have to do is keep giving.
Well, like I said,
I just feel sorry for you.
Spare me the fucking pity.
I'm not the one who's alone here.
No, I guess not.
And how is Claire these days?
What are you talking about?
You know, sometimes
before I open that door...
..I can hear you talking in here.
To Claire.
The way you do two voices
scared the hell out of me at first.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
I know more than you think.
Is she here right now?
No.
She's not real.
You don't think I know that?
I think you're starting to forget.
Don't get paranoid on me, Eric.
You're no fun when you're paranoid.
You're sick, Holly.
Feeding that sickness
until all it does is eat.
You just have it all figured out,
don't you?
Almost.
One thing I still don't understand.
The journal.
First, I get it.
You and Eric are getting engaged.
Blah, blah, blah.
But here comes your best friend, Claire.
The real Claire.
Holly can't eat.
Holly can't sleep.
Holly wants to confront them,
but Holly's too scared.
Fuck you!
Then here.
Here's where it gets really interesting.
I get home and there's
20 messages from Dwayne, right?
He's like, "Where are you?
Why haven't you picked me up yet?"
Even though he's the one who said
he was coming to get me on Saturday.
You know, somehow, of course,
it's just magically my fault.
Were you gonna tell me?
Tell you what?
Come on, Claire.
- You know.
- Um, not really.
Eric.
How'd you find out?
His email. He doesn't know
I have the password.
- Shit.
- Yeah.
Holly. What do you want me to say?
You know, I'm sorry. We were so drunk.
It didn't mean anything.
Oh, well, as long as
it didn't mean anything.
OK. Holly,
please slow the car down.
You're unbelievable.
- Do you know that?
- I'm sorry.
You have no idea how shitty I feel
about this whole thing.
Holly, please
slow the car down. OK?
You're supposed to be
my best fucking friend.
Holly, come on. Jesus!
Holly! Goddamnit!
You're gonna kill us!
Boom.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my fucking God.
We're OK, alright?
We're gonna be OK, Holly.
We're... OK, Hol.
We're gonna be... be fine.
We're gonna be OK.
We're gonna be fine.
And you think that's what?
A confession?
I'm a writer, Seth.
Fiction's kind of what I do.
That's why I didn't go
straight to the police.
I had to be sure.
I thought I'd follow you around
for a few days,
but you didn't make me
wait long.
It was a risky move, even for you.
There were so many.
You want to know what I think?
I think you wanted to get caught.
That's why you kept the journal.
You wanted to get punished.
Lucky you came along.
You don't get it, do you?
This isn't punishment.
I'm trying to save you.
Then do it.
Save me.
I will.
I meant what I said.
I'm gonna stop you
hurting other people.
One way or the other.
And the Oscar goes to...
He wants to save me.
I have to let him think
there's a chance.
So that was all an act?
You were just humouring him?
Playing along?
If you've got
something to say...
I'm just making sure
your head's still in the game.
I don't need another
useless pep talk, Claire.
And I don't need you.
Yes?
What? No. Nothing.
Just... was curious.
Why you did it.
I guess when I saw Eric's email,
all those messages from Claire...
No, not Claire. I understand that.
It's a crime of passion or whatever.
I want to know why you didn't stop there.
Why you killed the others.
'Cause you felt guilty,
for what you did to Claire,
for getting away with it.
You wanted to get caught,
didn't you?
No.
Because I could.
Yeah. I don't believe that.
Well, I don't care what you believe.
'Cause, see,
here's the thing, Seth.
When someone dies in front of you
the way Claire died,
it's like your whole world
just snaps into focus.
- Cry for help?
- It was a way to pass the time.
Don't pretend
you know what I am.
You're wrong. I do know you.
I know you from this.
And the girl who wrote this,
you had dreams.
She cared about people.
Was scared to be alone.
This is the real you. Not...
Seth's got a little crush.
This isn't about us.
If you love something, set it free.
Isn't that how that goes?
You know I can't do that.
Do you know what happens
to a great white shark
when you put him
inside an aquarium?
It bashes its brains against the glass.
Every time.
Come on.
Stop! Holly! Stop!
Stop! Holly!
What are you gonna do
when you come down here tomorrow
and I'm belly-up in the tank, huh?
'Cause you can't just walk away.
Not with your fingerprints
all over the place.
I kill myself, your life ends too.
So how's that for the boundaries
of our fucking relationship?
- Seth?
- Hm?
Finish this up
and come see me in my office.
Something wrong?
"Is something wrong?"
That's the question, isn't it?
I'm not following you.
The kennels are filthy.
There's the stock room. Where's Seth?
He's not here, that's for sure.
Nate says you haven't been here
in two days.
Mrs Gundy, Nate is hardly...
Nate does his job.
You should have done yours.
You're firing me?
Disciplinary notice.
This goes in
your permanent record.
One more strike and you're gone.
Understand?
Understood. Thank you.
You don't know
how much this means to me.
This... this is
what's gonna happen to you
when you think
you're in control.
You think
you're in control, Holly.
Well, this is what'll happen
when you think you're in...
I control the situation.
There's the man.
Just doing some maintenance.
Didn't ask.
Hey, Seth,
I got your pay cheque.
Still here, huh?
Where's the rest?
There is no rest.
This is what happens when
you start acting like you're in control.
- That's not enough.
- You don't get to decide that.
Fuck you!
Fuck me? I go through hell for you
and you threaten me?
You ever pull that shit again,
I'll show you
what a real hunger strike feels like.
Fuck YOU.
I had a dream last night.
You were in it.
It was just the two of us,
and we were in this house
down by the water.
And I think we'd been
living there a long time,
'cause there were these
pictures on the walls, pictures of us.
It was weird looking at them, because...
..something about it felt right.
Like this, this whole world,
is the dream and...
..that house on the beach, that's reality.
That's how things are supposed to be.
Maybe get you some snacks
from the vending machine.
Thanks, Seth.
Holy shit!
There's a light on the wall.
Hey. What's your name?
Um... I'm Nate.
Listen to me, Nate.
You have to find something
to break open this lock.
Can you do that?
What kind of fucked-up...
Did Seth do this?!
Nate, there's no time
for that right now.
- OK, go at it hard, at an angle.
- We gotta call somebody.
- The cops or whatever.
- Get me out of here right now.
- Keep going.
- That's what I'm doing.
No, just... just...
- Harder!
- This is all fucked up.
- OK, that's great.
- OK, on three. Alright?
One, two, three!
Fuck.
Hold on.
Do you know
what real love is, Nate?
- What?
- You know, real love.
Say you loved somebody
but she got sick.
And then someone came along one day
to pull the plug on her,
to take her
away from you forever.
- What would you do?
- I don't know.
I just want to
get you outta here.
You would do anything
to stop that from happening.
Anything at all,
no matter what the cost,
because that's... what love is.
Love is sacrifice.
What the fuck?
You gonna die!
Oh!
Are you stabbing me?!
Arggh!
Motherfucker!
The block, Seth.
Use the cinder block.
- He's moving. Come on. Use it.
- I can't.
You have to. Seth, I can't lose you.
Oh, fuck! Fuck!
I can't feel my legs.
What the fuck?
Somebody help me!
Oh!
Oh, my...
Come on. Do it again.
One more time.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Seth. You have to listen to me. OK?
You have to do exactly what I say.
Are you listening? OK.
Step one is disposing of the body.
The sooner, the better.
OK, burn it, bury it, sink it, whatever.
Get it out of here.
But you can't do that
before you get rid of any identifiers.
Teeth, tattoos, fingerprints.
Fingerprints are easy.
You can use a carrot peeler for that.
The teeth,
you need to scatter them.
Dumpsters, in water, whatever.
Just not all in the same place.
And then there's just the body
to worry about.
It's not gonna fit
in the incinerator.
Well... not like that.
Here.
Do you want to practise
what you're gonna say?
Hey. Mrs Gundy, it's Seth.
Sorry to call you so late. Um...
Yeah. Nate asked me to watch the front
while he ran some errands.
And he's still not back yet.
I don't know where he went.
O...
OK. Goodnight.
Sorry.
- How do you feel?
- I don't know.
Disconnected. Like it happened
to someone else, you know?
The first time's always the worst.
There is no first time.
It was an accident. I told you.
You know what always got to me...
..was the questions.
I remember in the beginning,
all I could think about
was what if she had a pet?
This poor little doggie just...
sitting by the door
waiting for her to come home.
But all that goes away.
The more you think about it,
the more you remember
the parts that you liked.
How it made you feel.
Like you were in control of your life
for the first time,
like nothing could hurt you.
That's not how it was.
But the only problem is...
..that sooner or later,
it all goes back to normal.
All of a sudden, you're nothing special.
You're just you.
Stop, OK?
And that's when
you start to wonder
how far you'd have to go
to get that feeling back.
It's not the same.
There is no shame
in accepting what you are, Seth.
I did it to keep us safe.
I had no choice.
Didn't you ever wonder why...
..all the girls in the world,
but you get a hard-on for me?
And you think that's, what,
a coincidence?
You and me, we were born to do this.
Don't act like you know
a goddamn thing about me.
I know that a normal person
finds a murder confession
and goes to the police,
not to PetSmart.
Oh, yeah - "Excuse me, Officer.
See that girl over there, the waitress?
"She's Hannibal Lecter.
You know how I know?
"I broke into her apartment
and stole her shit."
Oh, and so plan B is kidnapping?
Because the fucking alternative
was sitting around
watching you hurt someone else.
Mmm.
Good thing no-one got hurt.
I told you.
I told you. It was an accident.
Face it, Seth.
This was never about saving lives.
You like this.
You like having that kind of power.
- Deciding who lives, who dies.
- Holly.
It's not too late.
I can save you.
Please.
Please. I can save you.
Maybe you're not supposed to save me.
Maybe I'm supposed to save you.
Don't. Don't.
Seth. Please help me. I'm so cold.
Please make me warm.
Can you help me?
Can you please make me warm?
I thought you loved me.
I do.
I do love you.
Holly.
Holly!
Come back as soon as I can.
- Oh.
- Seth.
This is Detective Meara.
Something wrong?
Is there
somewhere we can talk?
So you work with Nathan, yeah?
Yes.
When's the last time
you saw him?
Wednesday, I think.
Wednesday evening.
Yeah, he asked me to cover the front
while he ran some errands.
- What kind of errands?
- Um, he... he didn't say.
Uh-huh. And this would be
about... what time?
9:00, 10:00. Something like that.
- He leave out through the front?
- Yeah.
The front door? You sure?
Yeah. Why?
Well, here's the thing. Um...
The front door operates
on a keyless entry system.
As you know,
it records each instance in or out.
Now, you want to guess the last time
someone opened that door?
- Four. That's 4am.
- Oh.
And you said it was,
what, 9pm or 10pm?
That's kind of weird,
don't you think?
Maybe I'm
remembering it wrong.
He could have left out the side door,
loading docks.
Loading docks?
Oh, shit. Yeah. I should check that out.
You and Nathan friends?
Well, we worked together.
He was a nice guy and all.
- Till he tried to get you fired.
- What?
Oh. That is not what happened.
Nate and I were friends.
Oh, now you're friends again.
Or you were friends, past tense?
That's the second time
you said that.
Well, you know what they say.
First time's confusion,
the second time's a confession.
- What's this about?
- Standard procedure.
So, now, he asked you
to cover for him,
this is, what, Wednesday night,
9:00 or 10:00?
- Say where he was going?
- Think he had to meet someone.
He got a phone call, something.
It's funny, because
the first thing we did...
..was check the phone records.
And the last person he talked to
was his girlfriend.
5:32 that afternoon.
Hi.
Gotta eat something.
Holly. Come on.
Come on.
Come on. Don't do this.
Now, I know what you're doing.
It's not gonna work.
Just talk to me.
Please.
It's over, Seth.
I don't understand.
Because if you can't help me,
if you can't give me what I need,
then no-one can.
Tell me. Tell me what you need.
You know the answer.
You put me in a box.
That's not love. That's ownership.
You didn't give me anything.
All you did was take.
I can't let you out.
- You know that.
- Didn't ask you to.
Then what? What do you want?
Proof.
Proof?
A finger.
A what? A f...
A finger?
My finger?
No. No. No.
No. No.
This is fucked.
Can't you see that?
This is totally fucked.
No. I'm trying to save you here.
And I'm trying to let you.
Well, you can't
ask me for that, Holly.
And I'm not gonna do it.
I used to think
I was the only one.
Even when I was a kid,
I still knew...
..that if they ever found out,
my family, my friends...
..if they knew what I really was,
they'd run the other way.
And so you learn to...
..blend in, to fake it.
After a while, you...
..you don't even notice
how lonely you really are.
But then...
..someone comes along,
someone like you.
Even if he just doesn't know it yet.
And all of a sudden, you start thinking...
..maybe it doesn't have to be this way.
Maybe I don't have to be alone.
And so you let go of the rope.
Because this person,
he's not gonna let you fall.
He's gonna catch you. You know it.
At least, that's what
you keep telling yourself.
The whole way down.
Don't come back.
If that's all I am to you,
if I'm just a pet...
..then don't come back for me.
Don't come back for me.
If I do this for you,
then you'll believe?
Yes.
This is wrong.
Seth, you love me.
There's nothing more right than that.
Arggh!
You're almost there.
Open the door.
- What are you doing?
- Open the fucking door!
You're already
down a finger, Seth.
How much more
are you ready to lose?
Get back!
Holly.
Holly. Wait. What are you doing?
Shh.
I believe you.
You do?
Do you?
You saved me, Seth.
Of course I love you.
But you know what that means.
Holly.
Don't leave me.
Oh, God! Oh!
You've been
working on these pieces for years.
I know.
I'm not saying I'm not excited.
It's, like, great
to get that call. I just...
Figured you'd be
more psyched about this.
It's a big deal, getting published.
It's just a vanity press.
It's not exactly the 'New Yorker'.
Screw that. It's still awesome.
I'm proud of you.
I thought you didn't even
like my story.
I like you.
- Babe, can you grab my phone?
- Yeah.
..Panthers as they're
making their way across the field.
A good start
to their first possession tonight.
You ain't kidding.
Number 40...
Chavez takes the snap,
fakes the hands-off, right there in front
of him, one man to beat, can't beat him.
It's taken down at the 4-yard line.
But it looks like it's enough
for a first down.
And Chapman
keeps this possession going.
Really short drive after the fumble. And...
Just a great play.
Unable to get around that defender.
Colin Spencer, once again,
involved in that tackle.
- Here you go.
- Thank you, babe.
Hi.
I had another bad day
with Eric.
He's still fooling around with other girls.
This morning, I almost... hurt him.
But then I thought of you.
And how much you love me.
And what you're doing for me.
Then I felt better.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/s7c8
Help other users to choose the best subtitles