Shh, he's here.
You gentlemen look like
educated men
of good taste.
I have here some rare
old first editions.
He's not bothering us.
I'm interested
in his books.
Okay.
Now here are the
complete works
of William Shakespeare,
an old German writer.
I like that.
We move tonight.
Orders from Berlin.
Dr. Tobel is to be
across the border
before dawn.
But we'd had orders not
to break into his house
and he hides there.
Hasn't been
outside in weeks.
The Fuhrer wants no
trouble with Switzerland
at this moment.
We must be very careful.
If we can't break in,
he won't come out?
When the Fuhrer needs
something as badly
as he needs the
Tobel bomb sight
there is always a way.
Dr. Tobel is interested
in my scientific volumes.
He's see my forged papers
and he believes I
come from Yudthem.
No gentlemen.
The price is much too low.
I could not possibly
sell such a rare book
for such a price.
I will induced Dr. Tobel
to come and
visit to my shop.
It's the fastest way.
You're interested
in this book,
a rare old set of
Bismarck papers.
One last warning.
I've just had
word from Berlin.
The English spy hunter
will try to
take Dr. Tobel
from under our very eyes.
They are sending a
stupid bumbling
amateur detective.
His name is
Holmes, or Homes
or some such
foolishness.
He'll never escape
from Switzerland alive.
Now quick.
Get me thrown
out of here
and watch for my signal
from Dr. Tobel's window.
But gentlemen
you promised
to buy one of books.
I told you no.
Ah, stop bothering us.
They are not so
great prices.
[Arguing in French]
French, English, how
I hate those languages.
Calm yourself
my dear brother.
In a short time there
will be only one language.
Good evening, Dr. Tobel.
I have here some
very interesting
scientific books.
I thought you might
like to see them.
Please come in.
He's entering the house.
Quickly, get the car and
have the motor running.
I will follow.
We'll have the Tobel
bomb sight to the Fuhrer
while this Holmes is
still having his tea.
What are you doing?
I am sorry but for months
every move I have
made has been watched.
I am not a coward,
Mr. Holmes.
They won't watch
you anymore.
Tonight they
intend to take you
forcibly across
the German border.
Then why do we wait
here doing nothing
like rats in a trap.
Calm yourself my
dear Dr. Tobel.
We should not only
escape their trap
but we should also take
the cheese away with us.
But, but how?
The four sections
of your bomb sight
fit inside these
ponderous tombs,
although I must confess
that I shy
to the thought
of disembowelling
a complete set of
Charles Dickens.
Ah, but you cannot hide
me in a hollow book.
My dear fellow.
I'm sorry that
my good friend
Dr. Watson isn't here
to explain to you
that are my preparations
are never slipshot.
Stephan, Eric.
Why do you call
my servants?
Your servants, yes,
but tonight they
assume new roles.
Let me present Dr. Tobel
and our old friend,
the bookseller.
Holmes, it is so simple.
Yes, the obvious
always appears simple.
Quick now.
We must leave.
Stephan, the knapsack.
Stephan, and Eric are
proving excellent decoys.
And the Gestapo
has been fooled?
Completely.
The servants are leading
them into the next street.
But what will happen
to Stephan and Eric?
Nothing, don't worry.
I've taken care of that.
Away from here.
Come on quick.
Do you want to take
the Nazis own car?
One must adept oneself
to the tools at hand.
You think you've
made them believe
you're a harmless
old bookseller.
Yes, I've always felt
that a thorough
knowledge of the classics
might come in handy.
But how can we get
across the border
and through France?
There's no need
to get across.
This very moment a
Royal Air Force plane
is waiting for us at the
secret landing place.
How long before we
arrive in London?
In a very few minutes.
We're passing
over Dover now.
Thank you.
You'll have to get used
to our London
blackouts Dr. Tobel.
Ah.
Huh?
Dr. Watson is a
very untidy fellow.
And what, what are we
going to do
with, with these?
A problem of the most
elementary nature,
my dear Dr. Tobel.
You arent going
to keep them here.
And I have
always believed
in the theory
originally projected
by Edgar Allen Poe,
the American writer,
that the best place
to hide anything
is where everyone
can see it.
Yes, but...
You will remember
no doubt
in Poes story "The
Purloined Letter".
And the missing
in question
was always in plain view.
Hands up, gentlemen.
Scotland Yard, quick.
Oh, my goodness.
Good evening, Mrs. Hudson.
Oh, why it's Mr. Holmes.
Holmes!
Hello Watson old fellow,
it's good to
see you again.
Telephone.
Huh?
Who do you want?
Oh yes, you're
Scotland Yard.
I'm afraid there's
been a little mistake.
No need to get angry.
We all make
mistakes at times.
What?
Well if we didn't
you'd be out of a job.
Dr. Tobel, this is my
friend and associate
and as you may observed
my watchdog, Dr. Watson.
How do you do, sir?
How do you do?
Dr. Tobel and I flew in
from Zurich this evening.
You can put that thing
away now, Watson.
Dr. Tobel awarded
the maximum request
for physics in 1939.
My dear Watson,
there is only
one Dr. Tobel.
Without Mr. Holmes
there would have been no
Dr. Tobel I am afraid.
But I thought you were
living in America sir.
I have been working
in Switzerland
for the past two years.
And Holmes got you out?
In the nick of time.
There was not a
point he overlooked.
Every contingency was
foreseen and provided for.
It was magnificent.
Thank you, doctor.
The problem
was not without
its interesting points.
Is there anything you
would like, Mr. Holmes?
No thank you, Mrs. Hudson.
You can go to bed now.
He gave me an
awful fright
dressed up like that.
Well good night, sir.
She's quite right.
You can't blame me
for jumping to the
conclusions I did.
You looked like a
broken down musician.
Holmes, why didn't you
take your fiddle with you?
I never did think much of
this dressing up business.
It was necessary,
I assure you.
The Gestapo was
close on our heels.
Really?
This is Sherlock Holmes.
I want to speak to Sir
Reginald Bailey please.
Reginald Bailey?
Is that the fellow
who played rugby
for Black Heath?
Yes, Watson.
Oh.
Hello, Sir Reginald?
Holmes speaking.
Yes, from Bakers Street.
I have Dr. Tobel with me.
Well thank you.
Very well then, I'll
meet you in half an hour.
And there must
be no delay.
I'll arrange
with Sir Reginald
to have the test
tomorrow morning.
I suggest that only
cabinet ministers
and your best aviation
experts be present.
Naturally.
Watson, I leave
Dr. Tobel in your care.
Give him a sedative.
This has been
strenuous business
and he has a long
day ahead of him
again tomorrow.
Certainly Holmes,
of course.
He shall sleep
in my bedroom.
I'll keep watch
till you return.
Thank you.
It is not necessary
to guard me.
I am quite safe now.
Safe Dr. Tobel?
I shouldn't count
on it for a second.
But Mr. Holmes...
A great deal may
depend on your safety
and the enemy
understands that
just as well as we do.
Good night.
Keep alert, Watson.
Yes, sir, of course.
A couple of these
and you'll
sleep peacefully
through a blitz.
Thank you.
You better start
undressing at once
or you'll find
yourself fast asleep
in the middle of
taking off your trousers.
Well I'll sit over here
and keep an eye on things.
Oh by the way, if
you're nervous call out.
Good night, doctor.
Well funny I was
saying the same thing
at the same time.
Good night, doctor.
Untidy fellow, Holmes.
Hello?
Yes, I just arrived
about an hour ago.
It is most important
that I see you at once.
No, no.
I cannot explain.
It is now five
minutes past midnight.
I leave at once.
Goodbye.
Holmes, I don't
have to tell you
how much this
means to us.
We'll know a great deal
more about the bomb sight
after the demonstration,
Sir Reginald.
You always have a pretty
good idea of the value
of the Tobel bomb sight,
just as the Nazis have.
However.
Oh, if you care to place
Dr. Tobel under the
protection of Scotland
Yard until tomorrow.
No, no, no.
No, that won't
be necessary.
I shall personally
deliver Dr. Tobel
to your representatives
on Salisbury Plain
in plenty of time for
the demonstration.
Thank you.
Good night, Sir Reginald.
Good night, Mr. Holmes.
Charlotte Eberli, Flat B.
Right.
Get the car, ready.
I'll wait here
until he comes out.
Is that what the
Americans call doodling?
It is more serious
than you could possibly
realize, Charlotte.
Good.
More coffee?
No, thank you, darling.
I must get back
before they miss me.
We've been separated
for so long.
I couldn't bear
that anything should
part us again.
I want to work with you
and I want to know every
minute where you are.
Even for you
to know the details of
my mission in London
is to sign your
death warrant.
If you are in real danger
I want to share it.
There is one
thing you can do.
Guard this envelope.
If anything happens to me
see that it
reaches the hands
of Mr. Sherlock Holmes.
Mr. Sherlock Holmes.
Yes.
I pray I never
have to deliver it.
Help!
He got away.
Are you all right, sir?
I, I think so.
It must have
been a robber.
Yeah, since the blackouts
those have become
quite a nuisance, sir.
Uhhh.
I say you better
come with me
and have that fixed up.
Uhh, thank you.
Just lean on my arm.
Watson.
Watson, wake up.
Huh?
Where's Tobel.
He, he, he's there.
No he isn't.
He's gone.
That's impossible.
He's asleep in my bed.
I've been here
the whole time.
If anything's
happened to him.
Tobel, you all right?
Ahh, it is nothing.
Yes.
Sit down here.
Let's have a look.
Well it doesn't
look too bad.
Who patched you up,
the police doctor?
Yes.
It looks as if
you've been attacked.
Obviously, my dear Watson.
Dr. Tobel,
do you suspect
the woman
of arranging the trap?
Woman, What woman?
She's blonde.
Five foot six,
full lipped and
very affectionate.
Oh really?
You've known her
for a long time.
You were attacked after
leaving her apartment.
Holmes, how do
you know this?
The face powder
around your coat
tells me of her height
and her affection for you.
You held her close
before departing.
Huh.
It's all there
for the trained eye
to read, Watson?
But look here.
Why couldn't he
have been attacked
on his way to the
woman's apartment?
The mark of the blow has
erased some of the powder.
Obviously if the
attack came first
the powder would have
remained undisturbed.
And the full lips
that was a guess.
I never guess, Watson.
You have rubbed the
lipstick from your face
with a handkerchief you
now hold in your hand
and that amount
of lipstick
never came from a
pair of thin lips.
And the blonde hair?
Good gracious me.
Mr. Holmes, I am glad
you are on my side.
Well in that case
you will desist
from disobeying my
orders and slipping out
while your bodyguard
sleeps his watch away.
It won't happen
again, Holmes.
I was sitting in
front of the fire
and must have dozed.
All right, All right.
Oh, sorry.
Now, can you describe
your assailant?
I never saw him.
A great figure came
at me in the dark.
I felt a stunning
blow on my head and,
and instantly fingers
were at my throat.
But you must have noticed
something about him.
Think man.
A thing of little
consequence to you
may mean a great
deal to me.
Wait.
Wait a moment.
There was one thing.
Long fingers at my
throat like, like steel.
And then,
then a,
an odor,
a heavy drug-like odor.
A drug?
Opium?
That is it.
I am sure of it now.
Well, I suggest
we get the remains
of a good night sleep.
Remember, the test takes
place tomorrow morning
on Salisbury Plain.
The principal of
Dr. Tobel's device
involves the use of
three sonic beams.
Is that right, sir?
That appears to be it.
There he is.
We're on the
course now, sir.
Well gentlemen,
that load would sink
any ship in the world.
We must consider
the possibility
of good piloting
and a lucky hit.
I'd like to see
another try of it.
So would I.
They want you to
try again, sir.
He's coming into
position now, sir.
We're on the
course now, sir.
Well gentlemen, how do you
like the bomb sight now?
It's marvelous.
We'll revolutionize
the aerial bombardment.
Inspector Lestrade.
Yes, Sir Reginald?
I hope Scotland Yard is
taking every precaution
to guard Dr. Tobel
and his equipment.
Two plain-clothes men
ride with him
in his car sir,
and four others follow
in another one, sir.
Good.
He's coming to my
office in Whitehall
as soon as he lands.
Well shall we
start, gentlemen?
Well, here he
is gentlemen.
Congratulations sir.
It was excellent
amazing performance.
It was magnificent,
Dr. Tobel.
Magnificent.
I am glad we had such
ideal conditions
for the test.
I wouldn't have
believed it
if I hadn't
seen it myself.
We've been through
a lot, Holmes
but thank goodness
he's safe now.
You brought your
apparatus with you?
No, Sir Reginald.
I did not.
But why not?
It must be lodged
in the most impregnable
vault in this building
until we're ready to
start manufacture.
I have arranged for a
little office of my own.
I intend to supervise
the manufacture myself.
But you,
you offered it to our
government for our use.
Everything
Mr. Holmes has done
has been with that
ideal in view.
I still offer it
to your government
but no one else will know
the secrets involved.
I have devised the plan
to guard my invention,
a plan as intricate as
the bomb sight itself.
If you imagined
for one moment...
Please.
I will not change my
mind, Sir Reginald.
I am taking the matter
into my own hands.
Just what do you propose
to do, Dr. Tobel.
I am sorry.
I cannot reveal
the details
of my plan for
the present.
Do you think that's wise?
I regret gentlemen.
I cannot change
my decision.
I shall work
independently.
Can't you persuade
him, Holmes?
But supposing something
should happen to
you, Dr. Tobel.
You know, there's
already been
one attempt
on your life.
And if Holmes'
suspicions are right?
Quiet, Watson.
There is no use
discussing it, gentlemen.
My mind is made up.
Scotland Yard
will redouble
the guard about
you doctor.
In fact we'll
quadruple it.
That is just what I do
not wish done, inspector.
That would only
draw attention
to my activities.
Good day gentlemen.
Just the same I'll have
my men watching him
every moment from now on.
No, no, Wait Lestrade.
We must not
offend Dr. Tobel.
We must remember that he,
as a citizen
of Switzerland,
is under no obligation
to give us his invention.
We must do as he asks.
Now don't you
agree, Holmes?
But sure, Sir Reginald.
I'm not officially
connected with
the government
and I intend to
remain on the case.
Good, good.
That is if Inspector
Lestrade doesn't mind.
Not at all, Mr. Holmes.
We're always glad to
have you hanging around.
Thank you.
You can put those
away now, Lestrade.
Hoffner, I am
entrusting this to you
because first of all you
are a Swiss and second
there is no doubt in my
mind of your ability.
I am honored Dr. Tobel.
I have divided the
mechanism of my invention
into four units.
Each is meaningless
without the others.
You have delivered
the other three.
Yes.
No one but myself
knows the identity
of the four scientists
working on the four units.
Their names are not even
known to each other.
I think I understand.
From what you tell me
it will be easy to
reproduce the unit
assigned to me
at any quantity you wish.
I knew I could
rely on you.
I will get in
touch with you
as soon as I have made
the rest of my
arrangements.
No, no, no.
The back door if you
please, Professor Hoffner.
Au vaus.
Hello.
Yes, Lestrade.
Oh.
Very well.
What is it, Holmes?
Just as I feared.
Lestrade's men report
that Tobel is missing.
Missing?
Yes, I was afraid of this.
How long has he
been missing?
Practically since he
walked out of your
office yesterday.
If he'd only given the
address of this place
I shouldn't
have had to
waste so much
time finding it.
Empty.
The bomb sight's gone.
I didn't expect to find
here, Sir Reginald.
This is a pretty mess.
If you knew this
was going to happen
why the devil didn't you
do something about it?
You can rely on Holmes
implicitly, Sir Reginald.
Tobel is gone and heaven
alone knows where.
It serves me right
for listening to that
half-brained idea of his,
Dismissing Lestrade's
men and they went
leaving him here
alone and unguarded.
Holmes, if anything
has happened to Tobel,
if his invention
falls into the
hands of Germany,
it will be a major
disaster for England.
Christmas wrapping.
He did his
Christmas shopping
in plenty of time.
Yes, curious.
Do you, do you note
something, Holmes?
Scent.
Perfume.
Yes.
I noticed it the moment
we entered the room.
Claire de Luna.
One of the rarer essences
and very expensive.
That woman again.
Undoubtedly.
Get me Inspector Lestrade.
Sherlock Holmes calling.
So Holmes is
finally stumped.
First time I've heard
him call for help.
Call for help indeed.
He's only just beginning
his investigation.
Lestrade?
This is Holmes.
Check the records
and place a call
made on my
private telephone
of Bakers Street
approximately
twelve o'clock
on the night
of Dr. Tobel's
arrival in London.
Finally stumped,
hey Sir Reginald.
Yes, Lestrade?
Wait a minute.
Charlotte Eberli,
St. George's Street,
Flat B.
Excellent, Lestrade.
Thank you.
Where is Dr. Tobel?
I can't tell you.
You mean you
won't tell me?
I don't know.
How many
Christmas packages
did you take to
him, Ms. Eberli?
Five.
He dismantled
his bomb sight
and packed the units
in four of the boxes.
Is that correct?
Pardon me.
Hello.
Yes.
This is Miss Eberli.
Why, why someone
must have stolen it.
On Richmond Bypass?
Yes.
Yes, I'll arrange
to have it removed.
Yes.
At once.
Now I can be frank
with you, Mr. Holmes.
Dr. Tobel has
disappeared.
They found my car on
Richmond Bypass wrecked.
I loaned it to
him last night.
For what purpose,
Miss Eberli?
He wouldn't tell me,
but he said that
if anything should
happen to him
I was to give you this.
Holmes?
Then he must have
expected something.
Yes.
This envelope has been
opened and resealed.
But that is in impossible.
It hasn't been
out of my hands.
What?
Why that's not
the message.
It isn't even
the same paper.
I saw Dr. Tobel draw
little sets of figures.
What kind of figures?
Well they, they looked
like little dancing men.
Dancing men?
That's curious.
Who's been in this
apartment since Dr. Tobel
entrusted that
envelope to your care?
Why no one.
I've had no visitors.
Think.
Possibly a tradesman.
No.
Only the one for
a few minutes.
And that one?
A workman.
He came to fix
my light switch.
He couldn't
have possibly...
Did you send for him?
Why no.
My lights went out
and soon afterwards
he knocked at my
door and told me
the porter had
sent him up.
That's where he worked.
But he wasn't
alone in this room
more than five minutes
and he did fix
the lights.
They went on again.
The switch hasn't
been touched.
The paint still covers
the screw heads.
He simply threw the main
switch in the basement,
pretended to
work on this one
and after a few moments
an accomplice threw
the main switch back on.
But in those few minutes
- Did you get a
look at his face?
No, only a glance.
Now I realize he kept
his face averted.
But he was a large man?
Yes, he was large.
His eyes, heavy lidded,
a thin film
over the pupils.
And Holmes...
I remember now.
His eyes, they were
like a snake's.
Miss Eberli,
Dr. Tobel is being held
by one of the
most brilliant men
in the history of crime.
Come on, Watson.
There isn't a
moment to lose.
Goodbye Miss Eberli.
I don't see why I'm not
allowed to go with you.
You have your own
mission, Watson.
Yes, to take a sealed
note to Inspector Lestrade
while you search
through holes.
I shall not be
searching for him.
I shall permit him to
find me in the character
of a murderous lascar
once in his employ
and whom I may add
is still in jail.
Yes, but after
all these years.
Make no mistake, Watson.
This is not a
duel of intellects
or the cruel
but single-minded
Gestapo killer.
This is our
greatest problem
with England as the stake
and our antagonist,
Professor Moriarity.
You've got to beat him.
Once he's behind bars
I think I shall
entitle my memoirs
of these adventures
the end of Moriarity.
An excellent
title, Watson,
but we must arrange
that it isn't Moriarity
who's left to
write the memoirs.
Huh?
Ramsing.
Ramsing?
Who know Ramsing?
I do, you blooming
wharf rat.
You've been in
jail, ain't ya?
How you know?
I've heard from
the blighter
what left you to
swing instead of him.
You know who
I'm mean matey.
I know.
I'll have to kill him.
Would it be worth
ten pounds to you?
You know where he live?
For ten pound I know.
I only got two.
Goodbye matey
Five.
Ten pounds or nothing
you lying heathen.
You dirty...
Well it ain't
so much to ask,
for what you
want to know.
You make good bargain.
That does it.
Well?
You remember
Angel's Court.
Huh.
Then follow your nose
through the alley
till you come to Jed
Brady's Carpenter Shop.
He can tell you where
the blighter is
at this very moment.
You come too.
Me?
If you lie.
All right, mister.
I'll come along with you.
Easy matey, easy.
Follow me.
Please governor.
I hadn't had nothing
to eat for two days.
Ah, go away.
Who's there?
Peg leg.
Who's this bloke?
He's a bloodthirsty
heathen
but has good money to
spend for information.
What's he want to know?
He give me five pounds
to bring him to someone
what could tell him
the whereabouts
of you know who.
You no tell me
I cut two throat.
Cost you another fiver.
Five pound more, eh?
You pay him?
Me?
Come on you.
Come on pay him.
I'll tell you
all right I will,
the truth and
that's a fact.
The blight is in
Davey Jones' locker
and feeding the
fishes he is,
deader than a
blinking mackerel.
Now ain't that
worth a fiver?
I tell you he's alive.
And I say he's been
dead these many years.
You're lying.
Easy there Jack Brady.
I would say
you were wrong
and Mr. Sherlock
Holmes was correct.
Good evening
Professor Moriarity.
Welcome, Holmes.
My men have the
instructions
to bring anybody here
who inquires for me.
They haggled
while I watch,
an admirable
disguise by the way.
It fooled them completely.
Of course it
didn't fool me.
I never intended
that it should.
I meant only that
it should bring us
face to face.
Just like old times, eh?
The battle of wits of
superior intellects.
I may say I've
been expecting you
since I made off with
your precious Dr. Tobel.
And his code.
Ah yes.
But valuable
as your doctor
and his code are
to my business
I think my main
interest in this affair
is the chance it gives me
to battle with you again.
Moriarity,
this is no simple crime
that you contemplate.
It's a staggering blow
against your own country.
That doesn't
concern me overly.
I should make greater
profits from this affair
than all my other
adventures put together.
Then you refuse?
Oh, most assuredly.
In fact,
I intend to insure the
success of this venture
tonight by liquidating
you, Mr. Holmes.
I think that is the
American phrase.
Quite.
You are the one man
intelligent enough
to stand in my way.
Huh, a gun.
Oh, come now.
This is not the
Professor Moriarity,
the master criminal
I once knew.
A dock rat could
do as much.
Did you think I was going
to shoot you, Mr. Holmes?
Oh, oh.
Dear me no.
This is simply to prevent
a troublesome scene.
I expected you,
and made full
arrangements.
You see my good
Mr. Holmes,
these shelves lift out
and you will rest
somewhat uncomfortably
in the false bottom
of this sea chest.
My sailor friend,
Jack Brady,
goes to sea immediately.
Once out of
sight of land
he pushes the
chest overboard.
Tie him up.
Perhaps your good
friend, Dr. Watson,
can entitle
this adventure,
the end of
Sherlock Holmes.
He will be disappointed.
He intended to call it
the end of
Professor Moriarity.
Hurry.
Aye, sir.
Brilliant man
Sherlock Holmes.
Too bad he was honest.
That one-legged man,
he takes Mr. Holmes
right to that
carpenter shop.
He knocks on the door.
A man comes out
and in they go.
Thank you, George.
We'll take over the watch.
Good night, Dr. Watson.
Good night.
What does Mr. Holmes
hope to accomplish
by this masquerade?
He hopes to
frighten Moriarity
into rushing Tobel into
another hiding place.
Moriarity's dead,
I tell you.
Look out.
Over here, quick.
Hey, just a minute.
Who's there?
What have you got there?
Who's asking?
Scotland Yard.
Scot...
governor, I'll
show you me papers.
There you are, governor.
I'm Jack Brady,
ship's carpenter.
Shipping out tonight
in the convoy,
destination unknown.
Me pal here is helping
me get the chest aboard.
Make him open
it, Lestrade.
Yes, or course.
All right governor,
see for yourself.
There is nothing
here, doctor.
Just a couple of
simple seafaring men.
All right get on with it.
Thank you governor.
Come on, now.
Easy does it.
Right there.
Good night, my lordships.
Told you it was a
lot of nonsense.
I don't understand.
That thing must
weight a ton.
Look at that
man staggering.
Do you know
something, doctor.
A few tools wouldn't
take that much energy.
We've just looked inside.
On the top only.
There might be
a false bottom.
Hey you, you stop there.
Stop or I'll shoot.
Great Scott, Holmes.
Well I'll be blowed.
You're not hurt.
No,
but you needn't
have yelled at
them so abruptly.
Huh?
They dropped
me on my head.
Oh.
Moriarity would have
been delighted.
So Professor
Moriarity is alive.
Alive and in possession
of Dr. Tobel's code.
No point going back,
they've all gone.
Then what are
you going to do?
Well first I'm going to
wash this filthy
stuff off my face
and then I'm going to
see Miss Eberli again.
I've got to
find some clue
to the content of
Dr. Tobel's message.
Come on quick.
I only got one
glimpse of the note
while he was
preparing it.
He was seated
at this desk?
No, he was sitting
on the couch
when he wrote the message
but he sealed the
envelope here.
The message was written
in ink with this pen?
No he used a pencil.
This one.
Thank you.
He used this writing pad?
Yes.
Has it been used since?
No.
It should be here.
It must be here.
What, Mr. Holmes.
The lead in this
pencil is hard,
hard enough to
make an impression
on the course
fibers of which
this paper is made.
Impressions at the
moment are invisible.
If we immerse
this sheet
in the solution
of florescent salts,
dry it and then
photograph it
by ultraviolet light
the fibers broken
by the writing
will absorbed less
of the solution
than other parts
of the paper.
Switch off the
lights, Watson.
We place the slide
in the projector
and turn on the light.
The broken fibers
appear darken
than the rest
of the paper
and therefore visible.
Splendid, Holmes.
Now I recognize that code.
Do you remember a case
we had some years ago?
It's partly the same,
alphabet
substitution code.
Yes, Watson.
I believe Dr. Tobel
meant to communicate
with us by that means.
Substitution of
the alphabet.
I don't understand.
My dear, one of the
oldest codes in use
is based on the
repetition of figures.
E is a letter most used
in the British language
therefore the single
most used probably
in this message is e.
T-a-o-i-n.
Follow in that
order of frequency.
You mean you can
read these figures
as if they were letters
of the alphabet.
Elementary, my
dear Miss Eberli.
Give me one minute
and you shall
have the message.
And what is the
message, Watson?
This fellow Tobel
must have been
pulling our legs.
There's a lot
of gibberish.
L-y-z-l-m-t-h-k.
Reads like an eye
doctor's chart.
Dr. Tobel is a
brilliant scientist.
I saw immediately that
he wouldn't send us
a message so
simple to decipher.
Neither would he have
fixed these top figures
without a meaning.
Then it isn't the alphabet
substitution code.
Yes it is, Watson,
but with a very
clever variation.
You see the one,
two, three figures
means that we skip
letters in that order.
In other words,
observe Watson.
The first letter, which
is I skips one, becomes J.
The second letter, Y,
skips two and becomes A
and the third skips
three and becomes C.
J-a-c...
J-a-c-o-b, D-u-r-r-e-i.
Jacob Durrei, a
Swiss scientist
and friend of
Dr. Tobel's.
P-a-l-a-c-e, C-r-e-s...
Palace Crescent.
Right.
I say Holmes,
this man, Durrei,
must be important.
Obviously, Watson.
He must have some
connection with
the bomb sight
or Tobel wouldn't have
taken so much trouble
to see that
I got his name.
Take down the rest
of the message.
J-o-s-e-p-h, Joseph.
E-m-d-d-i-a-c,
number four doesn't
make any sense.
He must have used
some other variations.
Four names and addresses,
Jacob Durrei,
Professor Fallow,
Dr. Kern
and this forth
infernal cipher
which doesn't
get the code.
Christmas boxes.
Watson, I'm beginning
to see the plan.
Dr. Tobel divided his
bomb sight into four parts
just as we brought it
back from Switzerland.
He's given one section
of the mechanism
to each of these
famous scientists.
What a fascinating plan.
You see each
part is useless
without the other three
and undoubtedly none
of these scientists
is known to each other.
Professor Moriarity
also has the code
and we must allow for his
ability to decipher it.
We haven't time to break
the fourth code now.
We must get to the
first three men
before Moriarity does.
Palace Crescent first?
Right.
I'll go and get a taxi.
Miss Eberli,
will you please wait
here till we return?
Thank you.
Yeah, where are
you going, sir?
Jacob Durrei live here?
Yes, but there's
been a bit of trouble
so you can't go in.
Inspector
Lestrade's orders.
Oh, Hey, just
a minute, sir.
That's Mr.
Sherlock Holmes.
Oh, very sorry, sir.
Dead?
Dead as a door nail.
Mr. Holmes, how did
you know about this?
The Yard only got here
fifteen minutes ago.
We'd better hurry Holmes.
There's still time to
save Fallow and Kern.
Too late, Watson.
By this time Fallow
and Kern are dead too.
What?
Deductions again,
Mr. Holmes?
Facts Inspector.
Oh, facts.
But how did you
know about them?
Elementary, my
dear Watson.
This man has been dead
for at least two hours
and Moriarity isn't
wasting any time.
Hello?
This is Lestrade.
Put me on to Mackety.
Hello, Mackety, hello,
this is Lestrade.
Do you know anything
about two men named
Fallow and Kern?
Both of them?
Oh.
Thank you.
The report only came in
two seconds before
I telephoned.
What on earth are we
going to do, Holmes?
Moriarity's got
a big start and
he's got the code?
Note this Watson.
Scotland Yard reports
two murderers.
That makes three in all.
But there were four
boxes and four codes.
Obviously Moriarity
hasn't broken the
fourth code either.
What is the name
of the fourth man?
I can't remember.
What is the name
of the fourth man?
I have forgotten.
What is the name
of the fourth man?
I don't know.
What is the name
of the fourth man?
I can't remember.
What is the name
of the fourth man?
But Holmes,
don't you realize what
this means to England?
We not only lose the
Tobel bomb sight ourselves
but Germany gets it.
Coventry, Bath,
Plymouth, London.
And not to
mention Norigno.
All over again but with
ten times the effect.
Don't you suppose
I realize that,
Sir Reginald?
Don't you suppose
I give my life
to decode the last
name of that message?
Well there must
be some solution.
Naturally, Watson.
I don't mean to be
rude, I need a drink.
I'm all in.
I can't think anymore.
All these letters
and figures
running through my brain
all twisted around.
Twisted around.
What?
That's it.
That's what?
Twisted around you said.
It's so simple I
never thought of it.
Reverse the slide.
You see, gentlemen.
These figures
are now identical
with the first
three names.
In other words,
all the figures of
name number four
are written backwards
and read from
right to left
until we reverse
the slide
when they read correctly
from left to right.
Now let's work on it.
Pencil Watson.
But, um, why
would Dr. Tobel
want to reverse the
figures of number four.
An added
precaution, Lestrade
in case the cipher should
fall into the wrong hands.
Quite a compliment
to you, Mr. Holmes.
I mean, Tobel
taken for granted
that you would
recognize the difference.
Thank you.
Ohh.
F-r-e-d-e-r-i-c-k,
H-o-f-f-n-e-r,
Frederick Hoffner.
S-l-o-a-n-e S-q-u...
Sloane Square.
We must leave at once.
Wait a minute.
Information?
Will you please
give me the address
of a Frederick Hoffner
in Sloane Square.
I'll break this code.
I'll find the name
of that fourth man
before Holmes does.
There is not
much more time.
The submarine is to
pick us up off Shanese
in six hours.
I've beaten Holmes so far.
We don't need the
confounded submarine
with the bomber
sight in tact.
But Tobel is
unconscious again.
As last resort we
could abandon the code
and take Tobel
to Germany.
We'll try Tobel
again in here.
Wait.
Spilling that
glass of water
was a very
fortunate accident,
my dear street brawler.
Dr. Tobel's perversion
of the cipher
was so simple
that it fooled us.
I was looking for
something ingenious.
This is ingenious.
He simply
reversed the cipher.
F-r-e-d-e-r-i-c-k,
H-o-f-f-n-e-r,
S-l-o-a-n-e.
Frederick Hoffner,
Sloane Square.
Of course.
Hoffner would be the
perfect selection.
Then you want us
to tend to Hoffner?
No, we can use Hoffner.
He's a brilliant
scientist.
If Dr. Tobel
doesn't recover from
your persuasion,
Hoffner would be able
to put the four
parts together.
You and Godfrey
will call on Hoffner
and you will
bring him here
with the fourth section
of the bomb sight.
Hurry.
Put up your hands,
Professor Hoffner.
I'll take the box.
We Meet again, Professor.
Sherlock Holmes.
An improvement on
the other make-up.
Don't you think
so, Professor.
So you think you've
beaten me, Holmes?
I have.
The real Hoffner
is safely
in the hands of
Scotland Yard.
But I still have Tobel
and now I shall sell
Germany the inventor
instead of the invention.
You've learned
nothing from him
in spite of all
your torture
otherwise you wouldn't
be trying so desperately
to collect the
four sections of
the bomb sight.
A keen observation,
my dear Holmes,
but observe further that
you are now in my hands
and I have profited
by my last mistake
by allowing underlings
to attend to you.
Holmes took my place
and while the Nazis
were inside with him
he instructed me to
attach a small apparatus
underneath their car.
He's a brilliant
fellow, Holmes.
I helped him prepare
the apparatus.
Did you really, doctor?
That is I poured
the luminous paint
when he told me to.
Very clever, Dr. Watson.
The apparatus drips
at regular intervals
leaving a trail
of luminous paint.
I see.
Leading us to Moriarity
and Mr. Holmes.
Why are you so
confident, Professor?
Only a suggestion.
But how do you know
that Scotland Yard
isn't waiting to break in
at this very moment?
I selected this address
with special care.
No one can find it,
not even Scotland Yard.
Relax, Mr. Holmes.
There's no escape.
And I'd suddenly
dash to the window
and break it open and
shout to a passerby.
There are no passersby.
The glass in the
window is unbreakable
and the room
is soundproof.
This is my
stronghold, Holmes,
equipped with all the
modern conveniences
of a successful man
in my profession.
Sit down.
They cleared
up again, sir.
I don't understand,
Lestrade.
It stopped
and then it started
and now it stopped again.
Maybe the apparatus
broke down.
Oh, a suggestion,
gentlemen.
At a crossroad back there
a car might have gone
over the spots of paint,
picked some up
on the tires
and left this false trail.
Just what
I was about to...
Just what I was about
to suggest myself.
Very well.
We'll try it.
Now Holmes,
what will it be?
The gas chamber,
a cup of hemlock
or just a simple bullet
through your brain?
You disappoint
me, professor.
Indeed.
Yes.
Somehow I always
thought that in the end
you'd prove to be just
an ordinary cutthroat.
You know me
better, Holmes.
Gas, poison, bullets.
I assure you, professor,
were our
position's reversed
I should have something
more colorful,
more imaginative to offer.
I'm satisfied to
be the winner.
I shall be alive.
Alive, yes,
the winner, no,
for in the last analysis
I shall have proved the
more resourceful man.
You didn't trap me here.
I came here because
I wanted to,
to prevent your
getting Hoffner
and all you can
do in return
is to commit
ordinary murder
to relieve your sense
of frustration.
And what, my
good Mr. Holmes,
could you have conceived
that would have been
so much more colorful?
Well even offhand
I can improve upon your
suggestions considerably,
but that's only
natural of course.
And what is this
brilliant idea of yours?
You know that a man dies
if he loses five
pints of blood?
Yes, of course you do.
I should have you placed
on an operating table,
inject a needle
into your veins
and slowly draw off
your life's blood.
The needle to the
last, ay, Holmes?
Slowly, drop-by-drop
the blood would be
drawn from your body.
You would be aware of
every exquisite second
to the very end.
You would be
watching yourself die
scientifically noting
every reaction
and in full possession
of your faculties.
Interesting.
Yes, isn't it.
I humbly submit,
professor,
that to the very end
I've been more
resourceful than yourself.
You've played
into my hands,
Mr. Sherlock Holmes.
Time and again I've
used this place
as a haven for
friends of mine
injured in alterations
with Scotland Yard.
I have a fully
equipped hospital here.
The trail goes this
way, inspector.
Drop by drop, Holmes.
Drop by drop.
Ahh, in a way
I'm almost sorry.
You were a stimulating
influence to me
but it was obvious that
I should win in the end.
Only a matter
of moments now.
Take Tobel down
to the boat.
Start the engine.
Closer to the end Holmes,
closer and closer.
Each second a few
more drops leave your
desiccated body
ending,
you can feel
me touch you.
You're perfectly
conscious
aren't you, Holmes?
I shall be conscious
long after you're
dead, Moriarity.
Ahh.
Still the same old
swaggering conceded
Sherlock Holmes.
Wait.
If Moriarity hears a shot
he'll kill Holmes.
You keep an eye
on the boat.
Don't make a move
till Dr. Watson
and I get inside.
Understand?
You wait here,
Professor Hoffner.
Come on doctor.
The water's this way.
Moriarity's rooms
must be up here.
I can't wait any
longer, Holmes.
You'll have to forgive
the crudity my friend.
This is only the
coups de gras.
[Shot]
Stay still, Moriarity.
You're done for.
Holmes!
On the contrary,
inspector,
my men are outside.
It's you who are done for.
Really?
Just take a look
out the window
and see for yourself.
He's trying to get
to the speedboat.
Yes, he won't go
without Tobel.
Wait.
Here's Dr.
Tobel, inspector.
He ain't too badly hurt.
Thank heavens for that.
Look after him
will you Hoffner?
I'll take him to the car.
Well I expected you
but not with my revolver.
You realize, of course,
when I was brought into
the room blindfolded
I heard the mechanism
of this door.
Of course.
And yet knowing
that I'd heard it
you planned this
way of escape.
Not very flattering to me.
Suicide my dear professor.
Not at all, my
dear Holmes.
You see this is not an
ordinary passageway.
Oh, my mistake.
It has been equally
well prepared
as the rest of my
humble quarters.
I have a trap set,
electric eye principle.
My passing through
will break the beam
and automatically open
the highly deceptive
trap door behind
me, of course.
My pursuer, meaning
you my dear Holmes,
will then be plunged
sixty feet into
the sewers below.
Holmes.
Poor Moriarity.
I neglected to warn him.
It seems some
careless person
came across his trap door
and left it open.
Come along, Watson.
Germany wanted the
Tobel bomb sight,
but will send her
thousands of them
in our airplanes.
Yes, thanks to
Mr. Sherlock Holmes
and to Mrs. Tobel.
And, of course,
Inspector Lestrade.
Oh well, that's
all right, Miss.
Things are looking
up, Holmes.
This little islands
still on the map.
Yes.
This fortress built
by nature for herself,
this blessed plot,
this earth, this realm,
this England.