Anybody could have
sneaked up the stairs,
knocked on the door
When Jerome opened the door,
they shot him and went
right back downstairs again
At the time of the crime,
you said you were performing
the water tank trick
COLUMBO: You're not really
in that cube, right?
Where was I last night
when Jesse Jerome got it?
Was I here
or was I there?
You see, what we
have to remember
is that Mr Santini
is a master of illusion
You could create the illusion
of being somewhere
while you were not
If you know
what you're doing
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Good afternoon, sir
How are you, George?
Hey, that was quite a night
we had last night
Yeah, wasn't it?
It's good having you back
Oh, it's great to be back
Oh, Mr Jerome
was looking for you
a while back, sir
Huh?
Seemed important
Uhhuh Everything
is important to him
Could you do me
a favor, sir?
Sure, name it
Could you make him
disappear?
Don't tell him I said it
Oh, trust me, you're safe
I'll tell you what
One night, George,
just you and I together,
we'll go out
and have a couple of jars
You're on, sir
HARRY: Santini's
packing them in, Jesse,
but I need more help
JEROME: The kitchen is
your responsibility, Harry
Do as you wish
Of course
it's my responsibility, but
good help is hard to find
Harry, Harry
Don't bother me
with trivialities
Solve your problems
and leave me be
Santini
It's good to have you back
Harry Good to be back
Harry, be a good fellow,
shut the door
on your way out
George said
you wanted to see me
Have a shrimp Magnificent
From a special bed
off the Yucatבn coast
I have them flown in
Thank you, no
Tell me, Santini,
last month, before you
left for New York,
you didn't by chance
break into this office
and search
through my effects?
What a silly question
Of course I did
And I stole your Renי,
your Picasso, and got a lovely
price for your Rubens
You know I didn't
I thought not
It was dreadful of me
even to suggest it
Thank you
Speaking of New York,
I take it that this, too,
is some sort of joke
$5,000 is hardly a joke
Come, come, dear friend
I've assimilated
the rudiments of arithmetic
Your eastern tour
netted $100,000,
500% of which is
50% of which is $5,000
50%?
Mmmhmm
No, no, dear man
We've been over this before
Jerome,
I'm bored
with you bleeding me
I'm afraid we're going to
have to make a change
in our little arrangement
There are no changes
Sergeant Mueller
You see how the very mention
of that name renders you
completely helpless
You keep forgetting
that I know who you are
and where you came from
I was 21 I was merely a boy
No one in the SS
was merely a boy, Mueller
No one in the camps
was just a boy
Unless he was
being taken into the oven
Don't misunderstand me
If you push me,
I will tell the newspapers,
the lmmigration Service
the Israelis
Yes, the Israelis
Oh, how they'd love
to get their hands on you
I think not
I'm far too valuable to you
You call that value?
Mmmhmm
I'd do much better
turning you in right now
while I still have the chance,
before you break in
here again, trying to find
the old man's letter
And don't deny
that it was you
Jerome,
you really are an animal
You're lucky
I'm a businessman
When that old man
recognized you last year,
didn't I give you the money
to keep him quiet?
That was good business
And when he died
and I realized that
I was the only one who knew,
well, that was
very good business, too
That's why we're such
a good team, you and I
You know, you do rather well
considering the circumstances
Certainly better than spending
the rest of your life
in an Israeli prison
I urge you to
look at it realistically
Have the other
$45,000 for me tonight
before the performance
or, believe me,
it'll be your last
performance anywhere
Heil Hitler!
Have the money for me
before the show
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
DELLA: Danny, cut it out
(LAUGHING) Go rehearse
or something
DANNY: I've done
that already
Young man
Very good
But if you're going to
seduce my daughter,
at least have the decency
and the courtesy
to close the door
of my dressing room
Sir, I'm sorry
On second thought,
it's probably
to my advantage
to watch your
ritualistic mating
At least that way
I can see how far
you've gone in the open
Oh, Dad
See you later? Maybe grab
a late supper after the show?
DELLA: Where?
DANNY: Mama Lucia's
Sure Pick me up
around midnight
Right
Dad, I'm going to
continue seeing him
We'll discuss
your taste later
At the moment, I'd like to
check the props, daughter
Yes, Father
(MUSIC PLAYING)
DANNY: (SINGING)
When we played our charade
We were like children posing
Playing at games
Acting out names,
Guessing the parts we played
Oh, what a hit we made
We came on next to closing
Best on the bills
Lovers until
We took in a bundle tonight,
Mr Jerome
Did Santini ask for me?
No, sir
Fate seemed
to pull the strings
I turned and you were gone
While from the darkened wings
The music box played on
Sad little serenade
Song of my hearts composing
I hear it still
I always will
Best on the bills
I got to see my agent
about that job in Vegas
Hey, have a good show
See you at midnight
Okay
And now, ladies
and gentlemen, once again
to thrill and mystify you,
The Cabaret of Magic
is proud to present
the magnificent illusions
of The Great Santini!
(DRUMS ROLLING)
(CYMBALS CRASH)
(DRUMS PLAYING)
WOMAN: Oh! Thank you
Thank you
Ladies and gentlemen,
each evening here
at The Cabaret of Magic,
we like to
We like to have you
participate in our show
We ask for a volunteer
to help Santini
In the back, yes, of course
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(DRUMS ROLLING)
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
What about a nice hand
for Mr and Mrs Right?
Thank you
ANNOUNCER: And now,
ladies and gentlemen,
The Cabaret of Magic
is proud to present
The Great Santinis
world famous
water tank illusion
(TAPPING)
When this cube is shut,
bolted and chained,
it will be
hermetically sealed
with the Great Santini
inside of it
There will remain only
five cubic feet of oxygen,
adequate to keep him alive
for just nine minutes
and 12 seconds
(CHAINS RATTLING)
To guarantee that
the Great Santini
cannot get out of the cube,
it will be suspended
in the tank of water
while the time runs out
ASSISTANT: Hold it
(DRUMS PLAYING)
(DRUMS ROLLING)
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(DRUMS CONTINUE PLAYING)
(STAFF CHATTERING)
MAN: Okay, medium rare, mac
I've got one well done
and two medium rare
MAN: Two well done
My brandy, Mike
Here you go, sir
Thank you
CHEF: Medium rare coming up
MAN: Watch it,
coming through
(STAFF CHATTERING)
MAN 2: I got
a well done here
CHEF: How's your steak
coming along?
MAN 2: One done, one well
CHEF: Here Those steaks
Whose steak is this?
THACKERY: Your brandy, sir
Place it on the table
Right, sir
SANTINl: (THROUGH SPEAKER)
Want to play a new game
tonight, Thackery?
A new game?
Yes, sir
Haven't been doing too well
at the others lately
I'm going to think of
a number from one to four
and you will
tell me the number
If lm wrong,
you may come in
and collect $5
But if lm right,
no tip
Understood?
THACKERY:
Right, sir I understand
Only, tonight
I'm gonna get you
I'm thinking of a number
What is your number?
Four
Lift the skull from the table
and look under it
I don't know
how you do it, Mr Santini
That will be all, Thackery
Right
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
a nice hand for
the daughter of the Master
(TYPEWRITER CLACKING)
(LOCK RATTLING)
Who is it?
How did you
(THUDDING)
(DRUMS ROLLING)
Get him out of there
Take it up, bud, take it up
Send up some coffee, please
Coffee, right Right away
Thackery!
Yes, Harry?
Coffee for Mr Jerome
Right I'll take it
right up
Hold it
That's good, bud
Bring it down
(STAFF CHATTERING)
(DRUMS ROLLING)
(CYMBALS CRASH)
OFFICER: (ON POLICE RADIO)
A black 62 Buick convertible
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
OFFICER: I've been told to
stand out here and keep
people away from the door
OFFICER 2: Have you got
any witnesses at all?
OFFICER: I have no idea
MAN: We have an
11:00 deadline
JEFFERSON: When they
come out, you'll be able
to talk to him, fellas
That's all I can tell you
MAN: Can you help us
in any way?
I cannot
Excuse me, sir
Lieutenant Columbo
Oh, I'm sorry, Lieutenant
I didn't recognize you
You look different somehow
I've had a hair cut
Who's in charge?
Sergeant Wilson, sir
Wilson?
Detective Sergeant
John J Wilson?
That's him
You know him, Lieutenant?
Yes, I've worked
with him before
I want everyone assembled
in the main room
within 30 minutes
When Lieutenant Columbo
arrives, he's going to
want to talk to all of them
Sir, there's
156 customers down there
The Lieutenant
is a very thorough man
We won't leave here
until he finds
the person who did this
(SIGHING) Yes, sir
(COLUMBO HUMMING)
WILSON: Lieutenant?
Lieutenant
Good to see you
again, sir Wilson
Yes
John J
Detective Sergeant
How do you do?
Excuse me Watch my hand
It's full of grease
This is my dinner
Would you like
a piece of chicken?
No, no, thanks
Is the body in there?
Yes It's
That's a new raincoat,
isn't it, sir?
It's from my wife Yeah
Oh, a present
For my birthday
Fits beautifully
You think so?
Yes, I must say,
it's a fine looking raincoat
It seems a little
stiff to me
Well, it's new
You'll get used to it
Yeah
You break it in
So, what do you got?
Jesse T Jerome
Born August 3, 1923
Height, 5'8"
Weight, 174 pounds
What did you do,
weigh him?
No, took it off
his driver's license
What was he doing,
exercising?
Sir?
His back is damp
So are his pants
Oh I'll put that down
You know, sir,
it's a great honor
to be working with you again
I've gained
a lot of experience since
our last case, you know
Very good
Hello? Anybody down here?
(WATER RUSHING)
Santini?
Santini, you in there?
Yes, who is it?
I'm sorry
to bother you
The police want
everybody upstairs
Oh, yes, of course, Harry
I'll be right there
One shot
through the heart
The napkin was found
on top of his shoulder
The shot came from the front?
Yes, sir
The napkin was found
on top of his shoulders,
and this 38 caliber revolver
was found next to the body
I suspect
it's the murder weapon,
though I've learned
you can never
jump to conclusions
But you say the time of death
was between 9:56 and 10:06
How do you know that?
By Harry Blandford
Who is that?
Well, he's the maitre d'
Sort of a junior partner
You see, at 9:56,
Jerome called from his office
to order some coffee sent up
So he had to
have been alive
Ergo, Jerome died
within a 10 minute span
Yes, that makes sense
What about the money?
The money, sir?
There's a lot of money
in here
Is any of that missing?
No, no, none of it
According to the cashier,
it appears to all be there,
which rules out
robbery as a motive
So, robbery was
not a motive
No, sir
Let's assume he knew
the person that came in
I got to take off this coat
I can't think in this coat
Pardon me?
The coat,
I can't think in the coat
Sir
See, I think the problem is
it could have been anybody
I mean,
unless we trace the gun or
pick up some fingerprints
Lieutenant?
Yes
Anybody could have
sneaked up the stairs,
knocked on the door
When Jerome opened the door,
they shot him and went
right back downstairs again
That's what's
been bothering me
Did he open the door?
Well,
I don't follow you
Jerome was shot in the heart
from the front
But the body is not here
The body landed
8 or 10 feet back
I don't understand that
Suppose Jerome
comes from the office
and he opens the door,
somebody shoots him,
then the bullet
enters from the front,
but then the body
is here, not there
Suppose Jerome
opens the door
Somebody he knows
Opens the door,
"How do you do?
"Come on in"
He follows the person in
Now he gets shot
from the front,
but the body falls
this way, not that way
Now, suppose
he goes to the door,
opens the door,
whatever he sees is a threat,
he turns, now he runs,
now he gets shot
The body falls
just where we found it,
but he's shot from the back
See, I don't understand
how this happened
How does a man get shot
from the front
and have the body land here?
The door has to be open
The murderer opened the door
Jerome did not open the door
Jerome is in his office
He's anywhere
He hears the door open
Now he comes walking forward
to see what happened
The murderer sees him,
shoots him from the front,
and the body falls
just where we found it
That I can understand
Sergeant, excuse me,
but some of
those people downstairs
are getting a little restless
How much longer
do we hold them?
WILSON: Oh
Sir, I took the liberty
of holding some of
the patrons quarantine
The guests?
Yes
We don't need them
We
You get their names?
OFFICER: Yes, sir
Let them go If we
need them, we'll call them
Yes, sir
We don't
I'm sorry, sir
I thought it best
to hold them
I thought there might be
some questions that you
might have in mind
What I was
about to say, sir,
is I don't think
that the door was open
You see,
that's a new lock
I can see that
It was only installed
last week and
there's only one key,
and that was found
on Mr Jerome's person
Now,
according to his partner,
Jerome locked the door
every night
while counting the receipts
Have this lock
taken down to the lab
Have it checked
Yes, sir
I'm going downstairs
I'm gonna look around
Fine Lieutenant
COLUMBO: Yes?
Sir!
Yes?
Lieutenant?
Your Oh, sir?
Lieutenant!
What is it?
Your coat, sir
You forgot your coat
I should try
and call Danny
No, I'd prefer to
have you home tonight
Listen, dear heart
COLUMBO: Is that
the way backstage?
We've both been through
a great deal tonight
Excuse me
Excuse me, sir
Sir?
The gentleman smoking
on the stage
Forgive me,
but backstage is offlimits
No, I'm just gonna
look around for a moment
I can appreciate that,
but I don't care to have
my secrets
exposed to the world
Can you understand that?
Oh, you are the magician
How do you do, sir?
You look different
from your picture out front
Maybe it's the hat
Mmmhmm
May I know who you are?
Lieutenant Columbo
Los Angeles Police
Department Homicide
I'm terribly sorry,
Lieutenant
But you can understand
my cautiousness Forgive me,
I am at your service
Oh, that's quite
all right
It was a terrible thing
It was ghastly
I was informed of it
when I came off stage
Really?
Yes, I was performing
at the time
Apparently, it must have
happened during
the course of my trick
I was doing
my water tank illusion
You know, I saw you
do that on television
The wife and I,
when you were at
Madison Square Garden
I don't know
how you do that, sir
You're not supposed to
That's how I manage
to stay two steps
ahead of my creditors
I'm sure you do
a little better than that
Just a little bit
Lieutenant, if you'll
forgive me, my daughter
is waiting for me
If there's anything
I can do to help, please ask
Less baring the secrets
of my grand illusions
Thank you very much
It's my pleasure
I'm your obedient servant
Have a good night
The same to you, sir
Della? What's going on?
I'll tell you later
Come, let's go
Good night, boy
ROGERS: Handmade,
with two special baffles
I figured as much
when I saw the key
That's why
I can't figure out
how it happened
How what happened?
This lock was picked
Are you sure?
Take a look
Now, you see
those scratches?
Somebody picked it open
with a thin piece of steel
lmpossible,
but it happened
What else?
This is the napkin
the killer used to keep
the prints off the gun,
and also mask
any traces of nitrate
Hmm
As for the gun,
it's a standard
Smith & Wesson
38 caliber revolver
Now, we matched
the serial number
with a shipment that was
stolen from a wholesaler
in San Francisco
So, there's no record
of any ownership,
no prints,
no nothing
And there you are
There I am
May I borrow this
for a while?
Mmmhmm, go ahead
ROGERS: As long as
you sign for it
Bravo! That's fantastic
Who's that?
I've always wanted to know
how those things were done
Lieutenant Columbo
I guess you have to have
dexterous hands
How astute of you
You see, my hands,
they wouldn't
conceal anything
Too small
Mmmhmm Well,
you're absolutely right
Maximum facility
Large hands,
more facile
How goes your hunt?
Sir?
The murder of Jesse Jerome
Come up with any clues yet?
Not really, sir, no
We're stumped
I was hoping
you'd be able to throw
some light on it for me
Would you like
my opinion, Lieutenant?
Yes, sir
There was a gun left,
right?
That's a mark of a pro
Professional killing
It's common knowledge
that Jesse had
syndicated clients
That might be
very helpful
Thank you very much
My pleasure
I don't want you
to take this wrong, sir,
but I have to account for
everybody's whereabouts
At the time of the crime,
you said you were performing
the water tank trick
That's right
Now, when the cube
is in the water tank,
you're not really
in that cube, right?
Perhaps, perhaps not
No, it's not that
I want you to give away any
professional secrets, sir
My dear friend, I'd rather
confess to a murder
than to do that
I just don't know
what to write down
in the report
You don't know my boss
If I say you were
locked in this cube,
chained in without air
for 10 minutes
and suspended in water,
the man's gonna
look at me funny
So it really is a question
of an alibi, right?
Actually, sir, it's just
a question of the report
Let me tell you, Lieutenant,
I probably have
the best alibi
of anyone who works here
Anyone And the irony is,
the worst
Where was I last night
when Jesse Jerome got it?
Was I here
or was I there?
It's fascinating, isn't it?
Don't do that to me, sir
I admit it, you know
I don't know
where in the hell you were
All I want to do is just
please the superior here
with this thing
Let me clear
your head up for you
I had absolutely nothing
to do with the crime
I've spent half my life
working in that
grand illusion
It's been wonderful for me
and audiences love it
And I'm not about to
divulge the secret
But if
at some point in time
you and your superior,
and I know he's a tough man,
insist that I come up
with an alibi,
I promise you
I'll produce one
But until that time,
at least allow me
the privacy
of my professional secret
Is that fair?
Fair enough
Thank you
Have a good day
Thank you very much
My pleasure
Sir, would you mind
if I came to see
the show tonight?
I'd be honored
to have your presence
Thank you
COLUMBO: Could it be
done by 8:00 tonight?
LASSITER: (LAUGHING)
You young people
When I was a young man,
time was precious
You savored it
Today,
everything has to be
done yesterday
But, sir, this is very,
very important
and I would appreciate
I'll be a son of a gun
Where did you find that?
I've been looking
all over for it
In the lost and found
You left it in the cafeteria
I thought somebody stole it
At police headquarters?
All right, put it in my car
Anything you could do
to see to it
that I have that
by 8:00 tonight
Lieutenant
would certainly
be appreciated
Sir
Could I see you
for a moment, privately?
Mr Lassiter,
Sergeant Wilson
WILSON: How do you do, sir?
Yes, how do you do?
Well, I'll get started
on these cuffs
Danny Green, the singer,
he was having an argument
with Mr Jerome
about his contract
and he wanted out
And he has no alibi
He said he left the premises
to go see his agent,
but he didn't see his agent
until 11:00
That's very good
legwork, Sergeant,
but the singer
didn't do it
No?
No
Mr Jerome wanted a lock
that couldn't be picked
Mr Lassiter here made it
That rules out the singer
Unless, of course,
he turns out to be
an expert at picking locks
But you still think
it's an inside job?
Someone
Oh, it is Absolutely
All right
Well, I'll check
everyone else out
at the club, sir
Lieutenant, sir, your coat
Just leave it in the car
Best on the bill
Lovers until
Love left the masquerade
Yes,
of course, there'll be
a performance tonight,
even though Mr Jerome
is no longer with us
I have a very strong hunch
about you, my lady
Believe in
clairvoyancy?
WOMAN: Yes
Your pen
Tonight, for your benefit,
on that stage,
I will try
to reach Mr Jerome
With your head,
if your ESP is working,
when I'm up
I just wanted to say hello
Lieutenant Columbo,
delighted you're here
Wonderful crowd you have
Mr Santini
I was wondering, do you
JOHN: Mr Santini
Mr Santini
Yes, excuse me
Yes, John?
This gentleman is
from out of town
He says he knows you
How are you?
Glad to see you again
Michael Lally
The greatest wire act
He and his brother
You should have seen them
How is he?
Well, he's still working
I gave the act up I got
a little bit too old
JIMMY: Mr Santini?
Excuse me Yes?
Two minutes to show time
Thank you, Jimmy
Excuse me
Have a drink on me
Mr Santini,
I don't want to impose
Could you do something
about my table?
Of course Where are you
sitting, Lieutenant?
In the other room
In there?
Jimmy
JIMMY: Yes, sir?
May I have
the guest of honor table
for the Lieutenant, please?
Certainly
My apologies
Thank you very much
This might be
a bit embarrassing
I brought something with me
It's a little trick
I thought I'd
challenge you with it
I think you'll get
a kick out of it
I'd be
delighted to see it after
the performance, please
Thank you, again
Hope you enjoy it
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
Dom Perignon
This way, Lieutenant
Right down here
(DANNY SINGING)
Just a second
I always will
Best on the bill
Take good care
of the Lieutenant
Thank you very much
Enjoy yourself
Good evening
Can I have your order?
Yes, I'll just have
a soft drink, please
Ginger ale
ANNOUNCER: And now,
ladies and gentlemen,
The Cabaret of Magic
is proud to present
The Great Santini!
(DRUMS ROLLING)
(CYMBALS CRASH)
(DRUMS PLAYING)
(DRUMS ROLLING)
(CYMBALS CRASH)
The most beautiful woman
in the world, and why not,
my beautiful
daughter, Della
(DRUM PINGING)
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
(BAND PLAYING)
(DRUMS ROLLING)
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(CYMBALS CRASH)
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(DRUMS ROLLING)
Thank you
Ladies and gentlemen,
each evening here
at The Cabaret of Magic,
we like to ask a member
of our audience,
a volunteer,
to step forward on the stage
to be Santini's attendant
or assistant, if you would
Perhaps a beautiful
young woman
We have a beautiful
young man instead
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are honored
because this gentleman
who stands before you
is none other than
Lieutenant Columbo
of the Los Angeles
Police Department
Welcome, Lieutenant
Lieutenant, you look
like a man who enjoys
a game of chance
You play cards?
Yes, sir
Down at the station?
(CHUCKLING)
Does the Chief know
about that, Lieutenant?
No, sir
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
Lieutenant, do you possess
a deck of cards with you?
With me? No, sir
You're sure, not on
your person anywhere?
Me? No
Well, unfortunately,
I don't have any
either, but
(GASPS)
Well, maybe backstage
Lieutenant,
what do we have here?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
You're holding
out on us
Ace of spades,
Lieutenant
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
Lieutenant,
what do we have
King of hearts
Is that all you
Lieutenant!
Yeah?
What have we here?
Three bullets
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
That, Lieutenant,
is indeed a fine hand
in any man's book,
but I believe, sir,
that I could possibly
beat that hand
Are you holding
any more cards?
Lieutenant,
somewhere on your
(DRUMS ROLLING)
Do Oh, what have
we here, Lieutenant?
A full deck!
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
Quite a full deck
Lovely Della
Thank you, Della
Thank you, my lady
That Thank you,
Lieutenant, very much
No, no, no
Thank you
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
What about a nice hand
for Lieutenant Columbo?
Thank you very much
Thank you
Lights!
You know, I'd like to
challenge you to a trick
I brought something with me,
a trick I'd like to
challenge him with,
if I could
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
It's You know,
down at headquarters,
we've got
these special handcuffs
for dangerous criminals
They're absolutely foolproof,
you can't get out of them,
and the boys
down at the station,
they said nobody
could get out of them,
and I wagered that
you would I don't know
whether you can, sir,
but would you like
to try and see
whether you could do that?
Would you be good enough,
sir, though,
to explain to my audience
that I have never seen
these cuffs before,
and this is the first time
we've ever attempted this?
Oh, absolutely,
I can vouch for that
All right
Absolutely
(HANDCUFFS CLICKING)
I'll raise that up for you
Make it more convenient
And there we have them
Are they secured now, sir?
Yes, sir
To your satisfaction?
You can't get out of these
I know that for a fact
We shall try May I have
a drum roll, please?
Your handcuffs
I knew you could do it
A round of applause for
the Lieutenant who tried
to outwit the Master
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
Thank you
Thank you very much
Thank you Thank you
Oh, Lieutenant
You seem to have
forgotten your badge
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
ANNOUNCER: And now,
ladies and gentlemen,
The Cabaret of Magic
is proud to present
The Great Santinis
world famous
water tank illusion
DELLA: When this cube
is shut, bolted and chained,
it will be
hermetically sealed
with the Great Santini
inside of it
There will remain only
five cubic feet of oxygen,
adequate to keep him alive
for just nine minutes
and 12 seconds
BARTENDER: Lieutenant,
what can I do for you?
Does Mr Santini do
this trick at the same time
every night?
Like clockwork
(LOCKS RATTLING)
ASSISTANT:
Okay, take it away, bud
No one's allowed to
Oh, Lieutenant, okay
DELLA: To guarantee
that the Great Santini
cannot get out of the cube,
it will be suspended
in the tank of water
while the time runs out
(WHISPERING)
Lieutenant, I can't let you
go down there
Oh, I just wanted
Santini's orders
I'm only doing what I'm told
Has Santini
come backstage yet?
Of course not, sir
He's in that cube
Sir, about the other
possible suspects,
Harry Blandford
He owned 250% of the club
Now with Jerome dead,
he owns it all
(WHISPERING) Later, Wilson
WILSON: (WHISPERING) Yes, sir
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(STAFF CHATTERING)
Sliced carrots
Slice them up
HARRY: I tell you
every night, you slice it
thin and you keep it rare
And I need
about 100 servings
tonight at least
You keep it thin,
and you keep it rare
Right? Good
Luigi, remember,
lettuce doesn't swim
Not too much dressing
Hey, you're the guy
from the agency
Take that coat off,
put this one on,
you get yourself a tray,
you join World War III
Police
Police?
What's below the stage?
Where is Sergeant Wilson?
I'm Lieutenant Columbo
What's below the stage?
It's a basement
It's a storage room
How do I get there?
Go through that door
and down the stairs
to the left
Hey, Lieutenant Columbo
Yeah?
I am Harry Blandford
Harry Blandford
I was Mr Jerome's partner
Yeah, call me later
(STAFF CHATTERING)
Mr Santini?
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
SANTINl: Come in, Lieutenant
I've been expecting you
Good evening
Feel privileged, Lieutenant
I usually don't allow
anyone in here
I had a very
strong suspicion you'd be
looking for me tonight
Thank you, sir
Careful
That's how
you do it
Yes, that's how
it's done
I am not in the cube
I'm right here
And that should certainly
satisfy your report
Yes, sir, that's certainly
going to sound better
I mean,
I couldn't write that
That you were chained
in a cube and dumped
in a tank of water
without air
for 10 minutes
(CHUCKLING)
Well, let's see
Whereabouts during crime,
Mr Santini
in basement room
I couldn't very well
stop you from finding out
and now that you do know,
I would very much appreciate
your telling as few people
as possible
Well, certainly, sir
Can you verify that?
Can I verify what?
That you were
actually here?
You really are something
My good man,
where could I have gone?
If I had indeed exited
through these two doors here,
made a sharp left turn,
ran down the passageway,
gone up the stairwell,
the stage manager
would have seen me
Check with him
My alternative was
to go out these doors,
up that stairwell,
which would have led me
directly into the kitchen,
where at least
a dozen people would have
been aware of my presence
Well, that certainly
makes sense, sir
Thank you
Listen,
I gotta hand it to you
about those handcuffs
You sure got them off fast
Whew!
We all have our particular
talents, Lieutenant
Mine happens to be illusion
and yours, I suspect,
is reality,
and a rather grim one at that
Well, you cleared up
one thing
You know, that lock was
supposed to be pickproof?
You showed it wasn't
At least, not for a man
of your ability Whew!
Oh, any lock could
be picked, Lieutenant,
if you know how
I guess you have to
keep pretty good track
of the time
I mean,
you get up on the stage late,
you'll blow the whole trick
Absolutely
Have you had any luck
tracing the gun?
No, sir Could have
belonged to anybody
And what about
the napkin?
Oh, nothing special
Just a napkin
from the kitchen
Uhhuh
Wouldn't be
anything like this?
You son of a gun,
you devil, you
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
You did it again
You really must
excuse me now
Oh, incidentally,
Lieutenant,
I neglected to have
my usual brandy
this evening
It's right here on the table
if you care to imbibe
What did Brandy?
Oh, didn't I tell you?
I always have brandy
brought to me
exactly at the same time
each evening
It calms the nerves
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(STAFF CHATTERING)
Excuse me, could you tell me
who brought Mr Santini
his brandy last night?
Excuse me,
I hate to bother you, but
Can I have everybody's
attention, please?
This is police business!
Thank you very much
I just want to talk
to the individual
who brought Mr Santini
his brandy last night
I did
May I speak to you
over there, please?
(SIGHING) Right, sir
You can go back to work
Thank you very much
THACKERY: You'll have to
make it fast, sir
Got a boiled lobster
and a creamed crab
ready for table 18
About this brandy
What is that?
Is that a regular thing?
Oh, yes
During every performance
I think the old boy needs it
to calm his nerves
And you always
take it down to him
during that 10 minutes?
Yes, sir
You took him
the brandy last night
and he was there?
Yes, sir
My lobster
and my crab, sir?
Right
You're positive?
I know his voice,
Lieutenant It was him
What do you mean his voice?
You didn't see him?
Not actually But he was
moving around in there
That I saw
You're sure?
Yes Every night
he likes to play
a mind trick on me
Last night he asked me
to pick a number
from one to four
What do you mean?
A number from one to four
He didn't guess it right,
I'd go through the door
and he'd give me $5
So how could he have
not been there? If that's
what you're thinking
Thackery,
we've got hungry people
waiting out there
Right, Harry
Boiled lobster
and creamed crab
I'll hop right to it
Did he guess
the right number?
Yeah
Lieutenant Columbo!
I'd appreciate it
if you'd stayed out
of my kitchen during
dinner hours, right?
I'm sorry, I'm a pest,
but I'm very confused
Yeah, you look it
Simmons, get a wine list
over to table 31
right away Fast!
Mr Blandford,
one more thing and
I'll get out of your way
You were in and out
of the kitchen all night
during the evening
Would you know if there was
a new man on last night,
however briefly?
Look,
let me tell you something
about the kitchen, huh?
We run on a short staff,
so we run short
We call
the employment agency,
they send over a temporary
That's a temporary
The guy comes in here, I say,
"Get a red coat, grab a tray,
go on out there" That's it
So you wouldn't know
if a stranger
walked through here?
Are you kidding me?
I wouldn't notice
if my mother came in here
and she kissed me Why?
I'm trying
to explain something
that is not explainable
(LAUGHING)
It sounds like
you're talking to Santini
HARRY: Hey, Carlos,
get some flatware out here
We're running short
And hustle it up
CLERK: Good morning, sir
Good morning
What a nastylooking
thing
Nasty and lethal
Observe A simple carrot
A flick of the wrist,
a downward thrust and
A very handy kitchen device
On the other hand,
hardly mystifying
Now let me demonstrate
the magical aspect
of this device, sir
Will you assist me?
I'd like to demonstrate
this wonderful illusion
You do have faith,
don't you?
You don't mean my hand?
Please
In there?
Yes, please In there
And you want me
to put my hand in there?
Yes, right in there,
please, sir
What are you going to do?
Now just place your hand
a little further
in this, sir, if you will
What are you going to do?
Fully guaranteed for
two years against all defects
and it comes
with three extra blades
$8995
(CHUCKLING)
Oh!
I'll be a son of a gun
Don't ever do that again
Thank you very much
That's a hell of a trick
Yes Are you interested, Mr
Columbo is my name
No
Columbo
Excellent Very good
Is that the Great Columbo?
No, just Lieutenant
Police
Investigating a murder
The murder
of Jesse Jerome
Oh, dear Jesse
To know him
was to detest him
I was in San Marino
that night, Lieutenant,
at my inlaws'
Sir, you're not
under suspicion
No, I just want
a little information
Let's say that
a man is in one room,
but he wants
someone to think
he's in another room
To make his voice come
from another room Do you
have a trick like that?
No, not really
I assume you're talking about
some kind of radio device
I'm talking about
making your voice
come from another room
Well, someone could speak
into a small concealed mike
and have his voice
come from somewhere else
Right
Well, that's not
really magic, Lieutenant
More like the gaff
in a head act
The gaff in a head act?
A head act
Mind reading
You know,
a guy up on the stage
and an assistant
in the audience,
usually a broad,
and she asks some guy
in the 20th row
if he has something
he wants to ask the swami,
so he whispers it to her
But what the mark
don't know is the broad
is rigged with a mike
and the guy on the stage
has a little receiver
behind his ear
So, if you had
a couple of those things
and an amplifier,
you could create the illusion
of being somewhere
while you were not
If you know
what you're doing
Do you have something
I could look at?
Sure
Mr Lally?
Yeah,
what can I do for you?
Do you remember me?
Yeah, you were
at the Cabaret club
the other night
Yeah, I sure was
Come on in
Thanks
Help yourself to a beer
in the fridge
What do you pay here?
$40 a month
Maid service?
Are you kidding?
And where is the bathroom?
In the hallway
Hotplate yours?
That's my hotplate
Still not bad
What did you think
of that magician?
Oh, he's always
been great
You know, I would've
bet money that he couldn't
get out of those cuffs
Don't ever bet
against Santini
He's the cream of cream
They tell me
you go way back with him
Oh, yeah, way back,
when me and my brothers
were the top wire act
in Europe
He was the gaff
in the head act,
and he always brought it off
very smooth, very smart
That's where
he got his start
Was his name Santini then?
No, no, not then
It was Arlington
or Kensington,
something English,
but he had an accent
you could chop off
with an axe
Oh, what kind of an accent?
I think it was German
Where'd you first meet him?
In Budapest
Maybe the accent
was Hungarian
But it didn't go along
with this English name
Then zippo
Five years later,
we run into him in Oslo
The accent's gone,
he's very British,
and now he's carrying
an Italian name
Santini?
The Great Santini
So the name stuck,
and now the accent
is American?
Yeah, but he grew
into a master of accents
I think he can
even imitate you
I figure
he's the kind of man
that he could do
almost anything
if he put his mind to it
You mean his hand to it
Right
What's his real name?
I don't know,
I never did know
The television yours?
Yeah,
that's mine
and the hotplate
is mine
The rest belongs
to the joint
What time do you have?
1:00
The tub Is there
a tub in the john?
No, no, no
There's one shower
on the third floor
for everybody
Listen, thanks
Don't mention it
My agents are
putting together
a completely new tour
and I'm going to
require a new assistant
Whatever happened
to your daughter?
Well, unfortunately,
the poor child has gone soft
on a rather mediocre singer
She lacks taste
Genetically, I don't
quite understand it
Well, maybe it comes
from her mother's side
of the family
Not likely, since she was
the lady who taught me
everything I know
Seriously, though, I
I wish you would
consider it
I have a feeling
you'd make a marvelous
traveling companion
I'll think about it
Please do
I shouldn't be long
You stay put now
or I'll revoke
your driving privileges
I'm gonna leave
this coat in the car
If somebody tries to lift it,
you look the other way
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Yes, may I
help you, sir?
Oh, no
What's the matter?
Someone I thought
I'd seen the last of
Do you have
a match, sir?
Yes, sir
Well, do you think
you could make him
disappear, too?
It's a splendid suggestion,
but in his case,
I think, rather doubtful
I'm just gonna join
that gentleman at that table
for a moment,
if you don't mind
Thank you very much
Mr Santini, I'm sorry
I didn't mean to intrude
I'm sure you didn't
This will
only take a moment,
unless you prefer my waiting
until you're finished
Lieutenant, what is it
about me that you find
so irresistible?
Well, you know
how it is, sir,
I gotta check out
all the leads
until I get my man
Could have been
a woman, you know
Of course
There was
a homicide at the club
The owner was murdered
Please sit
Ironically,
it happened during
the course of my act
Oh, forgive me,
Lieutenant Columbo,
this is Miss McCarthy
How do you do, ma'am?
WAITER: Would you like
to order cocktail?
No, nothing for me
Do you know
a Michael Lally, sir?
Yes, of course
I know Michael Lally
And you know
very well I know him
because you saw me
talking to him
last night in the club
Well, according to
Mr Lally, when he first
knew you in Europe,
you were going
under another name
Kensington or Arlington
What of it?
You didn't think
Santini was really
my name, did you?
"Does not look Italian"
That's the very first
note I made, sir
How astute
But you do use
the name of Santini
on your passport
Why, Lieutenant, you've been
checking up on me
Well, I really don't
have any choice, sir
Why are you so preoccupied
to find out my real identity?
Your origin
may be more humble
than you make it appear
And what about you,
Lieutenant?
Beneath
that ruffled exterior,
there ticks away the heart
of an empiricist
philosopher,
probing for the truth
at all costs
I'm just
doing my job
But you make it
sound so proletarian
And my job, if you will,
has to do with appearances
I'm not what I appear to be
and then again,
neither are you
Mr Lally remembers that
in the old days you spoke
with a different accent
(IMITATING GERMAN ACCENT)
Was it this one, mein Herr?
(IMITATING BRITISH ACCENT)
Or perhaps this one, guvnor
Is it better? All right
(IMITATING FOREIGN ACCENT)
Or maybe
it sounded like this
Ooh, you're
a remarkable man,
Mr Santini
How keen of you
to notice it
I could do
my East Ukrainian
but unfortunately,
Miss McCarthy and I
have an appointment
If you'll excuse us,
Lieutenant
Could you at least tell me
which name it was?
Was it Arlington
or was it Kensington?
Well, neither, actually
It was Washington
Do you have
a first name on that, sir?
Martha
Sir, you sent for me?
Yes, Wilson, I
Lieutenant,
I've got an idea
The waiter, Thackery
He was the one
who brought the coffee
up to Jerome, remember?
All right, Jerome left
the door open for him
Thackery goes upstairs,
goes inside, shoots Jerome,
then he fools around with
the lock to make it look
like somebody picked it
That's very good
The magician did it
What?
Mr Santini
killed Mr Jerome
Santini? Santini was
in the basement
You yourself said
he was down there playing
the trick with Thackery
He was going to personally
hand Thackery $5
if Santini couldn't
guess the number
Well, his voice
was in the basement
He wasn't there
Only his voice
You see, what we
have to remember
is that Mr Santini
is a master of illusion
He makes you believe
what he wants you to believe
Pick a number
from one to four
Pick a number?
Pick any number
from one to four
I got it
What is it?
Two
Lift up
the telephone receiver
Turn it over
"I knew you were
thinking of number two"
How did you do that?
If you had picked
number four,
I would tell you
to look under the ashtray
"I knew you were thinking
of number four"
If you had said number one,
I'd tell you to pick up
the hole punch
"I knew you were thinking
of number one"
If you had picked
number three
"I knew you were thinking
of number three"
That's
Where did you learn this?
That trick cost me
$1735 in a magic shop
Oh, that's expensive
All right, let's say Santini
wasn't in the basement
I mean, let's say
Santini did it
But what's the motive? I mean,
there has to be a motive
Yes, there is
always a motive
We just
have to find it
Come on
Where are we going?
We can't find
a motive here
Yeah, where are we
going to find it?
I don't know
So where are we going?
Wilson, will you
I forgot my coat
Coat?
We'll get some air
Right
Think
(TYPEWRITER CLACKING)
Lieutenant, what happened
to your new coat?
Oh, that? It didn't fit
The wife,
she's gonna change it
for something new
Oh
Excuse me, mac,
you were just sitting down?
I beg your pardon
Wilson, this man
was just sitting down
Forgive me
Would you turn around?
I just want to see
the back of your shirt
Perspiration
You were sitting?
Yes, I was sitting
Where were you sitting?
That corner chair
right over there
Leather Wilson,
take this down
Just before
Mr Jerome was killed,
we know he was sitting
The next question is
where was he sitting?
There are seven chairs
and a couch
Where was he sitting?
Well, his jacket was on
this chair So he could have
been sitting in this chair
There was
a glass of wine on the desk
and the reading glasses
He could have been
He was sweating
Yes
His shirt was damp
You can see
the discoloration
It starts at the belt
and works halfway
up the back
So we rule out
all the chairs with cloth
He was sitting
on leather
Sit in that chair
That's a highback
leather chair
We rule that out
The sweat line
would come to the shoulders
Highback leather chair
We rule that out
He was sitting in this chair
Sweat line hits
in the right place
So, we know where
he was sitting
What was he doing?
Well, we know he came up
to check the cash receipts
But the cash box
was never opened
The reading glasses
There were reading glasses
on the desk
He might have been
reading
Was there
reading material around?
Books, papers or letters?
No
He wasn't reading
No, nothing, sir
The telephone! He might have
been on the telephone,
talking on the telephone
Here for 40 minutes?
Maybe part of the time
I don't see
any connection between
taking out reading glasses
and making a call
He could have been writing
The pad is bare
He never did
what he came up here to do
He came up here
to count his money,
doublelocked the door,
put the money on his desk
but he never
opened the box Why?
Was it because he got absorbed
in listening to music?
Or did he have something
more important to do?
I would assume it was
because he had something
more important to do
I think he had something
What was it?
Lieutenant Columbo
Good afternoon
You know Sergeant Wilson?
How do you do?
Do you know
how unnerving it is
for everyone who works with me
and works in this building
because you and your men
are snooping around?
Now, is there any chance
that you could be
a little less conspicuous?
It is unnerving
My apologies, sir
Thank you
Now, may I know how long
you and Dr Watson here
are going to be poking around?
Well, we are
making progress, sir
Oh Anything significant?
Tell Mr Santini
about the trick that I played
on you today
The Lieutenant's
become a magician
Go on, tell him about it
He'll get a kick out of it
The Lieutenant asked me
to think of a number
between one and four,
and then he would guess
the number that I was thinking
and prove it
And there was
no doubt about it
The number was two
I was thinking
of the number two
He asked me
the number I was thinking
and I told him two
And then he asked me
to look under the telephone
I looked under the telephone
and there was a little slip
of paper and on it said,
"I knew you were
thinking of number two"
Bravo
SANTINl: That's magic,
wizardry
Actually, Dunninger
used it in his act
It's an old standby
Now, you said you were
making some progress
Yes, sir, we've determined
where Mr Jerome was
just before the murder
Of course, he was right here
in the office
Where in the office?
Now, how would I know that?
He was sitting in this chair
Do you know that for a fact?
Yes
What were we talking about
before Mr Santini came in?
Well, we were concerned with
what Mr Jerome was doing
while he was sitting
in the chair
Right
We were concentrating
on the reading glasses
Right
Actually, sir,
we were concerned
with the motive
Right
You see, sir,
we're stumped with the motive
Do you have a suspect?
Yes
You do?
We do,
but we don't have
a motive for you
Oh
I am the suspect
How interesting
Well, finding a motive
should be a piece of cake
for a couple
of clever men like you
And I promise you
I will not disappear
before your very eyes
when you come to arrest me
The reading glasses
You know, Lieutenant,
you would wear reading glasses
if you were typing
Yes,
you would wear reading glasses
if you were typing,
but there was no paper
in the typewriter
And there was
no typewritten documents
in either the desk,
in the drawers or on top
There is nothing
in this room to indicate
that that man was typing
What's this?
What's what, sir?
This
Looks like a golf ball
That's how it types, sir
The ball types the letters
But it's not moving
The typewriter
This thing is not moving
Carriage
This is the carriage,
but there is no carriage
on this typewriter
You see, the ball
moves from left to right
Allow me to demonstrate,
sir, please
You see, I used one of these
at the Academy Typing School
Oh, I didn't know
they had one
Oh, yes
I'll be a son of a gun
Oh, it's a remarkable
machine, Lieutenant
Very modern
See this?
This is a disposable
carbon ribbon
for a very crisp image
Top speed of this machine
I'd say is about
220 words a minute
Beautiful Beautiful machine
Well, sir,
shall we get cracking?
"Now is the time
for all good men to come
to the aid of their party"
Lieutenant, shall we
continue the search?
Very good, Wilson
Very good
Thank you, sir
Thank you
Harry, what's going on?
That Lieutenant's
got Danny Green
up in Jesse's office
Something's about to
break on the murder
Why do you suppose
he wants to see me?
He didn't say
I've got work to do
DANNY: You're crazy
Santini couldn't have done it
COLUMBO: He killed him,
Mr Green, and I can prove it
I can prove how
and I can prove why
Blackmail
Blackmail? Come on
Jesse Jerome knew
that Santini was really
Stefan Mueller,
a former SS guard
at the end of World War II
And when Jesse Jerome
threatened to expose him,
Mueller killed him
But how?
He was in the basement
I can prove it
When he gets here
I'm gonna show you
how he did it
COLUMBO:
There's no sense running, sir
There's no place to run to
I just heard you
talking upstairs in the room
with Green
No, sir,
we were never up there
It's an easy illusion
to create
All you need is some miniature
radio equipment
The receiver,
a wireless mike
and a transmitter
You used something like this
the other night
You used it when you fooled
the waiter into thinking
you were still in the basement
when you were performing
that "pick a number from
one to four" trick,
when in reality
you were upstairs,
killing Jesse Jerome
Bravo
Wrong,
but an interesting theory
More than that
It shows opportunity
And the letter shows motive
A letter?
A letter addressed to
the Department of lmmigration
and Naturalization
It identifies you
as a war criminal Means,
opportunity, and motive
It's enough to convict
for first degree murder
It's impossible It's a trick
and not a very good one
A trick? No
That's the letter
Oh, no, Lieutenant
No, you see,
this letter was burned
So much for your letter
There's the letter
I hope
you were watching carefully
That's my best trick
Of course,
I don't have your style,
but I get pretty good results
You can burn that one, too,
if you like
There's plenty more
where that came from
Wilson
You made one mistake
You did not look
closely enough
at that typewriter
If you had, you would have
seen that it used
a plastic carbon ribbon
Disposable carbon ribbon, sir
The kind you don't reuse
And when the key
strikes the ribbon,
it punches out a letter
that is clearly visible
on the used ribbon
You can see it
I want you
to see for yourself
If you look carefully
at this section of the ribbon,
you'll see that it says,
"Now is the time
for all good men to come
to the aid of their party"
I typed that
Sergeant Wilson typed that
But Jesse Jerome
typed something else
And if we unwind
the entire used section
of the ribbon,
we see what Mr Jerome typed
"Department of lmmigration
and Naturalization,
Washington DC
"Enclosed find a letter
which proves
"that Santini is
in reality an exNazi
"named Stefan Mueller"
I don't think there's any need
for me to go any further,
is there, sir?
No
Means, opportunity,
motive
And I thought I'd performed
the perfect murder
Perfect murder, sir
Oh, I'm sorry,
there is no such thing
as a perfect murder
That's just an illusion
Officer
(CHARADE PLAYING)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org