PAUL ON TV Good afternoon,
this is Paul Gerard,
and once again,
the world is my kitchen,
a world of fine dining
in the restaurant
and in your home
In Japan, it is said,
meals are prepared
for the eye,
as well as the palate
This is not true, however,
of an eating ritual
known as Odori,
the dance of the flesh
In a country
where most people like
their seafood fresh and raw,
there are those
who prefer it lively
The shrimp is still wriggling
as it is quickly dipped
into the sauce
and eaten with gusto
You can never say
he allows himself
to be blinded by good taste
Only by money
Still, he's done
all right for us
Not me, not anymore
PAUL In the case of fugu,
the Japanese blowfish,
this is quite literally true
The tiger fugu,
considered to be
the most delicious variety,
is also the most deadly,
a remarkably potent poison
unless the highly toxic liver
and other organs
are removed with great skill
I'm getting out
Ah, when?
Tonight
Tonight?
He's finished
or a tiny residue
of the poison
A taste of eternity
Adorable
(ALL LAUGHING)
Paul, we need a couple
with just the package, now
Life would be unbearable
without my daily portion
of Bon Snax
Good
Yes, yes,
my anchovies would weep
and my patי would be desolate
and my Camembert inconsolable
Am I breaking
your heart, Charlie?
CHARLIE: Keep it up,
you're doing great
How many more, fellas?
Oh, just one more, please
Always just one more
If you gave a photographer
20 lashes,
he'd still ask
for just one more
Terrific Enough
Bonjour, and Bon Snax
Thanks, Paul
EVE: This way, gentlemen
Eve, we'll have the proofs
and we'll get them back to you
in a couple a days
The check would be
even nicer
(DOOR OPENING)
My notes for the
Restaurant Writers' dinner?
Notes
Did you call
the airport?
Mr Ozu's flight
will be on time
You are flawless A gem
What kind of gem?
A sapphire
Too cool
I'd rather be an emerald
Consider it done
Paul, can I ask you
a question?
Certainly
Are we having an affair?
I would say
a prelude to an affair
That's terrific, Paul
Why do I have to do
that stuff at the bank?
Because you must
I hate it
Banking is part
of your job
It's underhanded
Are you
an accountant, Eve?
No, I'm not
And I'm not
Irene DeMilo, either
Why do I have to pretend
to be Irene DeMilo?
Because we're having
an affair
I thought
it was just a prelude
The prelude is
almost concluded
The affair
is about to begin
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Vittorio
You flatter
my poor restaurant,
Mr Gerard
Come on We both know
your restaurant is superb
Let's dine together
and we'll be friends again
We'll dine
You invited yourself
and so we will dine
Albert,
my favorite chef Italiano
Mr Gerard
What have you been
concocting for us here, hmm?
My antipasto
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Rosemary, shallot,
a touch of juniper
Very good, very good
Anything else, Vittorio?
No, that's it, Alberto
You've done very well
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
So
It seems
you do not take seriously
what I told you on the phone
I do not require
your praise anymore
Not your radio,
your television,
no more newspapers,
no magazines
As you please
It's your restaurant
I'm finished
with our little arrangement
Not one penny more Capisce?
This is very good
So it's no more
250% for you,
Mr Paul Gerard
Mr Famous Paul Gerard
I'll tell the world
what you are
Haven't you
forgotten something?
Proof? I have proof
No, you forgot the wine
May I suggest a cabernet?
May I suggest a Margaux,
maestro?
Fine, fine
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
When I'm finished
with you,
you'll starve like
a beggar in the streets
Margaux
(VITTORIO CHATTERING)
What a pity
it has to end like this
VITTORIO: What'll you write?
Vittorio's is
a rotten restaurant?
What a pity Well,
ciao,
old friend
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Now, wait, wait
Tonight I gave you a lesson
(BOTH SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(VITTORIO GROANING)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(GROANING)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
Paul Gerard?
Yes
I was called
I'm Sergeant Burke
You wanna wait here
a minute, please?
The police asked me to get
in touch with Paul Gerard
He's here now
(INAUDIBLE)
Mr Gerard?
Mr Paul Gerard?
Yes
Ah, forgive me, sir,
for eating this way,
but I didn't have
a chance to go home
and Chef Albert,
he was good enough to prepare
me a bowl of his cioppino
It's terrific
He uses a freshly grated
lemon peel to give it
that extra zing
Well, I don't have to
tell you that, sir
Mr Gerard,
this is a real pleasure
I never miss
one of your columns
My name is
Lieutenant Columbo, Homicide
Lieutenant,
I came immediately
as soon as
the police called
I can't believe,
Vittorio dead
Poison?
Well, that's the medical
examiner's opinion
Please, sit down, sir
Thank you
My God, poison
I ate the same meal
Albert prepared it
Ah, yes, sir,
that's what he told me
May I ask, sir,
how you feel?
I don't know I'm not sure
I was at the airport,
then home
No ill effects
And then you came
directly here, sir?
Yes, I
You said
Albert cooked that?
Delicious and it's all
in the basil and the garlic
Oh, I see
what you mean, sir
Albert, the poison
Oh, I doubt that
very much, sir
When we brought him
in to question him,
he became very indignant
He grabbed a knife and fork,
he started to eat
everything in sight
He's in perfect health, sir
And the boy? Mario?
As I understand it,
he didn't eat
I wonder why the mussels
that you buy in the store
never turn out this way
Oh, I do a little cooking,
sir, nothing fancy
Mrs Columbo,
she's a remarkable woman
She has lots of interests
But cooking
isn't one of them
She gives me plenty
of encouragement
Feeling better, sir?
Yes, yes, thank you
Well, what I was
going to ask you, sir,
didn't the
Did you say you went
to the airport tonight?
Yes, to meet a friend
And then you came right here?
No, Lieutenant,
the call from the police
didn't reach me
until I returned home
And how long
would you say it took you
to get from your home
to here?
I came immediately
From the phone call
to my arrival,
about eight minutes
Is this important, Lieutenant?
Not at all, sir
Just for my report
What I wanted to ask you,
did the victim show any signs
of being in trouble?
No Certainly nothing
like that
Are you sure, sir?
Nothing you
might have forgotten?
Lord knows you'd be entitled
if something slipped
your mind
All this stress,
all this poison flying around
What makes you think Vittorio
was in some sort of trouble?
Mainly because
he was murdered, sir
The two, trouble and murder,
they seem to go together
At least that's been
my experience, sir
Lieutenant
Albert,
can all this be true?
Mr Gerard,
Vittorio was a fine man
You're a food critic,
a great critic
I'm a simple chef,
but I'm sure I speak
for chefs everywhere
when I say
I wish it was you
dead in there
Oh, Albert
Lieutenant, the boy, Mario,
you can speak to him now
I'm going home
to finish getting drunk
Thank you, Albert
We'll be in touch, Albert
Poor man He's overwrought
Well, I guess
we're all overwrought
May I help with Mario?
Certainly
You want to hear
a coincidence, Mr Gerard?
I was listening
to your program
on my car radio
one day last week,
and I go through
this tunnel
and I missed the end
of a terrific recipe
on some kind of sauce
Do you remember
the name of that?
Could it be bיchamel?
No This is something
I'm gonna spring
on Mrs Columbo
Rיmoulade? Hollandaise?
I'm gonna think of it
in a minute
It's some kind of
a French name
May I ask
who called the police?
He did, sir Mario
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
But he doesn't speak
a word of English
Well, he's a very
bright boy, sir
As Sergeant Burke
understands it, he called
his mother in Genoa
and she called the police
here long distance
Genoa
He's remarkable
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
As I understand it, sir,
you left without
finishing your dinner
Yes, fortunately
And before the victim
showed any effects
from the poison
Well, yes
I'll just question
the witness
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Calm Calm
(COLUMBO SPEAKING ITALIAN)
He says
he loved his uncle
I believe him
Why would he
kill his uncle?
What else did he say?
He said his uncle
was very angry
Slamming drawers
Why would he be
slamming drawers?
I mean, why would
he even open drawers?
He put the tray there
Nothing has been put away
Why would he open drawers?
Have to think about that
Look at those beautiful pots
The boy said something
about an argument
and a lot of shouting
What was that about, sir?
It was a trivial matter
Yes, sir
Most arguments seem
to start that way
Every year
the restaurant writers
have an awards dinner
For the past three years
we've held it here,
at Vittorio's
This year the committee
decided to have the dinner
at Chez Duvall
Vittorio saw it as a slight,
an insult
I'm on the committee
and he accused me
of suggesting the change,
of influencing their choice
Did you do that, sir?
Yes, sir
In all honesty,
I must confess that I did
Mr Gerard,
I want to thank you
for your help
Oh, I'm pleased
to do what I can
Oh, there's just
one other thing
The victim's
appointment book
He had you down
for dinner at 8:00
Yes
And the entry before that
at 4:00
was for a meeting
with an M Choy
and an M Duvall
Do those names
mean anything to you, sir?
M Choy would be Mary Choy,
She owns the House of Choy
And M Duvall?
Who would that be?
Max Duvall,
the owner of Chez Duvall
Vittorio knew them both
But I don't see
how this meeting could be
of any importance
Well, it probably isn't, sir,
but Vittorio thought it was
He has the entry
heavily outlined
with four exclamation points
after it
That's odd
Well, what's even odder
is he did the same thing
with your name
And he drew a circle
and an arrow
PAUL: That's bizarre
Linking your name
to theirs
That's pretty bizarre
Do you know, sir,
any reason
that he might have
marked his book that way?
No None
I must say
it's very strange
Lieutenant, it's very late
It's been a harrowing day
Good night
Sorry, Mr Gerard,
but I can't let you
get away with it
What?
Your recipe
You didn't think
I'd remember, did you?
It's onion sauce
Then it was Soubise
Sauce Soubise
It's a simple recipe
I'll get it for you
I'd certainly
appreciate that, sir
Good night, sir
Good night
MAX: Nobody lives forever,
but poison?
Who can figure poison?
Who could imagine
a thing like that?
Vittorio Rossi
We were apprentices together
Hotel school, Switzerland,
just boys
As I understand it, sir,
you had a meeting
with him yesterday,
and I was wondering
Is that what I think it is?
Is that galantine of duck?
Yeah, this is my galantine
You know,
I've read about these
in a cookbook,
but I have never
actually seen one
And those black buttons,
are they real truffles?
Why, of course
And the green mosaics here,
pistachios
And there's another
kind of meat there, inside
Mmmhmm Ham
It's a real
work of art, sir
What I wanted to ask you,
you had a meeting
with Mr Rossi
at 4:00 yesterday
Can you tell me
what that was about?
Well, it was social
Cocktails, shop talk,
gossip among old friends
Since you were
one of the last few people
to see him alive,
can you
Do you suppose
Could I try to do that?
This? Oeufs en Gelיe?
Eggs in aspic
I'd really like
to try to get the feel
The way you garnish
a dish like this
Yes, go right ahead
Thank you very much
What I wanted
to ask you, sir,
it has to do with
the victim's frame of mind
Lieutenant Columbo,
I am Louis, the chef
Well, it's a very
great pleasure, sir
Vittorio was my friend
I wish you luck
And I've prepared
a little something for you
Stuffed mushrooms
Champignons farcis au crabe
Are those made
with a bיchamel sauce?
Exactly
Well, I'm going to
enjoy this very much
Merci, monsieur
Thank you, sir
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
We all loved Vittorio
We'll miss him, Lieutenant
Tell me something
In your last meeting
with Vittorio,
did he express any fears?
Did he mention anything
about a death threat?
No, not a thing In fact,
I found him preoccupied,
withdrawn
He was strangely silent
A lot on his mind?
It was all
bottled up inside,
ready to explode
No, there was nothing
to suggest that he was
a potential victim
On the contrary,
he seemed like a man
about ready to commit
murder himself
And you got all that
through his silence?
You're a very
perceptive man, Mr Duvall
WAITER: Would you care for
some chartreuse, Mr Gerard?
Thank you Light lunch today
Well, this is
quite a coincidence
I had no idea
you were here
Would you care to join me?
Well,
I'm really not hungry, sir
I just polished off
three mushrooms
stuffed with crabmeat
But I'll join you anyway
If you're anything like me,
you're not too crazy
about eating alone
I'm beginning to regard you
as an old acquaintance,
Lieutenant
Well, thank you
very much, sir
I'm beginning to know you
pretty well, too
Would you care
for some champagne?
No, thank you
I know you're going to be
very glad to hear this, sir
I got the poison report
back from the lab
They still don't know
what kind of poison it was
that killed
your friend Vittorio,
but they found out
it wasn't in the food
It was in the wine
The wine?
That's extraordinary
Why should I be glad
to hear that the poison
was in the wine?
Well, don't you see, sir?
That immediately strikes you
right off my list of suspects
According to the boy,
Vittorio didn't even open
the bottle
until after you left
I wasn't aware that I was
on your list of suspects,
Lieutenant
I must say
I find all this very puzzling
It is puzzling, isn't it, sir?
I mean,
here's this boy, Mario,
sent to the wine cellar
for a bottle of Margaux
and he picks it at random
and it's laced with poison
How do you explain
a thing like that?
Lieutenant Columbo,
I was a friend of Vittorio's
With my compliments
Caviar? Smoked Salmon?
And fois gras
Well, thank you very much
This is a sensational layout
Good luck, sir
Gee, this reminds me
Mrs Columbo said
to pick up something
for dinner
PAUL: Now, I know this isn't
my area of expertise,
but I have a theory
Now, please, don't laugh
I wouldn't consider it, sir
It's just that
it could have been
an accident
An accident?
The poison got into
the bottle by accident?
It could have happened
at the chateau,
where the wine was bottled
Some insecticide, perhaps,
it spilled, wasn't noticed
The wine was corked
and shipped
Well, that's a very
interesting notion, sir
But the World
Health Organization
has no record
of any outbreak of poisoning
in the French vineyards
I see
Does this feel ripe, sir?
I don't think
it's squishy enough
It's ripe
Sorry about your theory, sir
But there is
another possibility
That Vittorio might have
been planning to murder
somebody himself
And he did have that
dinner date with you, sir
You mean
he planned to murder me?
Well, let's examine it
Suppose it was Vittorio
who put the poison
in the wine bottle
thinking that
you would drink it
And when you walked away,
he made the fatal mistake
of drinking it himself
Yes
I can see how that
could be possible
You can, sir?
Well, maybe you can
explain it to me
I mean, how could a man
make a mistake like that?
I don't even understand
why Vittorio
would want to kill you
Can you think of a reason?
Of course not
You're perfectly right
The whole idea
is ridiculous
Well, it was my idea,
but I'll think
of better ones
How did the poison
get into the wine?
That's the question
But don't worry
about it, sir
I'm gonna write
that out on a card
and I'm gonna paste it up
on my shaving mirror
and that's all
I'm gonna think about
PAUL: Eve
I've been a fool
Interesting
How long have you
been a fool?
Since I forced you
into that damn business
with the Irene DeMilo account
It wasn't fair
Did you say affair?
Eve, go to the bank
one last time
Oh, no
Close out the account
and go home
and pack your things
I'm moving in?
You will need a passport
A passport?
Your next assignment
Go to Paris
Why?
A new book
It's time to revisit
the great restaurants
of Europe
I'm tied up, so you eat
the food of the gods
I'll meet you in one month
And then we'll travel
the Mediterranean, Spain
Oh, and the Greek islands?
Yes
How selfish I am
You have so much to do
and I keep you in my arms
It's all right
To sum up,
first the bank,
an end to the DeMilo account,
then France,
Italy, Spain
And Monte Carlo
You will never forget
Monte Carlo
You have the bank book?
Yes, it's in my bag
Good Hurry back
I'll have your itinerary
You leave tomorrow
Oh, Paul, I need
at least three days
Three days
Wait, what about the dinner?
Europe is calling
Go, go, go
Mario, come ahead
Gerard is still
sitting here
Vittorio, he's over here,
he's putting his plate
on the sink
Yelling, carrying on
Gerard gets up
and leaves
The bottle is still corked
Mario goes after him
Mario
Here's where Vittorio
had to open the bottle
Drinks
Mario comes back Mario!
This is depressing
This is very depressing
Vittorio picks up the tray,
takes it to the sink
Slams a couple of drawers
He turns around
"What's this? " he says
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(GROANING)
All right,
enough of that
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
What was he doing
slamming drawers?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Like he broke the drawer?
Cancelled checks
drawn from
Vittorio's bank
$5000, $8000,
$4000, $6000
Holy Toledo Must be
$100,000 worth
Restaurant
Developers Association
They're all made out
to the Restaurant
Developers Association
Here's their stamp
on the back
What's the Restaurant
Developers Association?
Never heard of it
Nevertheless,
you'll observe
I'm taking these
into police possession
They gonna tell you
how the poison
got into the wine?
All right, now,
we do it all over again
Not with me
This is too depressing
Wait a minute, Albert
How does this thing work?
I know there's
some kind of cartridge
This
Another clue?
COLUMBO: If there's poison
in that cartridge,
then that's a clue
COLUMBO: I want to take this
down to the police lab
We'll see if the boys there
find any poison
Good
You're a good detective
Leave no stone unturned
You want me
to fix you anything else
to eat before I go?
No, thank you very much,
Albert
The poached scallops
will hold me just fine
See you later, kid
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
That's the kind of man
Vittorio was,
tough when it was good
to be tough,
generous when it was right
to be generous
Now let me tell you something
I don't think you know yet,
how generous he was to me
and to his nephew, Mario
In his will, Vittorio left us
his restaurant
To both of us
With one condition,
that I train Mario
the way Vittorio
would have trained him
To me that means
just one thing
That I train Mario
to be a great man
like his uncle
ALBERT: A great chef
and a great manager
Tough and generous
Okay, Vittorio,
I make you this promise
(INAUDIBLE)
(ALBERT CONTINUES SPEAKING)
ALBERT: Now, friends,
before you go
I know you all want to
get back
You're all busy people
But I want you to know
that the man in charge
of investigating
Vittorio's murder
is here today
The man who is
going to catch that murderer,
Detective Lieutenant Columbo
Lieutenant,
we're behind you,
all of us
And I want you
to know this
As long
as you're on this case,
you'll never go hungry
Arrivederci, Vittorio
Arrivederci
Lieutenant, the opener,
the cartridge,
what did the lab say?
Well, it was
just a cartridge
We still haven't
figured out the poison
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Sir, if it'll make you
rest any easier,
I think those checks
are gonna be
a very big help
That dim sum reminds me
of the kind I used to have
at home
At home, Lieutenant?
Right around the corner
from Chinatown
was an Italian neighborhood
When I was a kid
I bet I had more egg rolls
than I had cannelloni
Do you recognize this, ma'am?
It's a cancelled check
I noticed
that you tore it up
at Mr Rossi's grave
But that's all right, ma'am
I've got a lot more
$100,000 worth
I only passed that around
to see who would react to it
Only two people did
You and Mr Duvall
How very clever of you,
Lieutenant
I've been in touch with the
Department of Corporations,
ma'am
I know that Mr Rossi
was the treasurer
of the Restaurant
Developers Association
I know that Mr Duvall
was the vicepresident
And I am the president
Exactly, ma'am
Why was
the Association formed?
To help develop
certain promising restaurants
into commercial successes
And it's been
a smashing failure
Do you know why
Mr Rossi made out
all those checks?
I haven't got
the vaguest idea
We never received the funds
and our commercial account
consists of $175
Well, that's quite
a spread, ma'am
between $175 and $100,000
What happened
to the rest of the money?
You don't think
poor old Vittorio
was up to something nasty?
Ma'am?
I'd hate to believe
he committed suicide
Oh, no, ma'am,
that's the furthest thing
from my mind
Never even thought of that
I want to thank you very much
for this tea lunch, ma'am
I enjoyed it immensely
I'll have somebody
come by and pick up
the Association's books
Yes, of course
Lieutenant, you forgot
your fortune cookie
To tell you the truth, ma'am,
I could use some good news
"Cheer up
"There is more
than one fish in the sea"
That's the kind I always get
Once I would like it to say
I'm gonna be rich
and go away on a long trip
Just once
Goodbye, Lieutenant
(GEISHA STRUMMING SHAMISEN)
Charming
Join us, please
You're a most welcome
part of this
surprising evening
I wanted you to have
one last taste of Tokyo
before you begin your tour
of American restaurants
They won't believe this
when I send back the story
They think I'm eating
hot dogs and grits
Have you ever eaten grits?
OZU: No, not yet
Don't bother
PAUL: And now,
the piיce de rיsistance
Fugu sashimi? Incredible
This cannot really be fugu?
I did it myself,
exactly the way
you taught me
Is it authentic?
I can't believe it
Fugu sashimi in Los Angeles
(DOORBELL RINGING)
I'll get it
I'm definitely not home
To anyone
Good evening, ma'am
My name is
Lieutenant Columbo,
Homicide
I'd like to speak
to Mr Gerard
Is he home?
I'm not sure
Is it a big place?
Or is he just out
to the police?
Paul, Lieutenant Columbo
is here
Good evening, Lieutenant
Oh, I beg your pardon, sir
The young lady
didn't tell me
you were eating
It's quite all right
How may I help you?
Well, I expected to
Sorry
I expected to see you
at Mr Rossi's funeral
I guess
you couldn't make it
I never go to funerals
I prefer
to remember my friends
as I saw them last
I believe Mr Rossi
was yelling at you
when you saw him last,
isn't that right, sir?
You mustn't
take me literally, Lieutenant
Have you eaten?
Yes, sir
It seems I've been eating
quite a bit lately
It's terrific
A pity
You could have joined us
Well,
that's very good of you, sir
Maybe a small bite
I'm delighted
A new setting, please,
for our latest arrival
Sit down, Lieutenant
I'm Eve Plummer,
Mr Gerard's assistant
Pleased to meet you, ma'am
My distinguished colleague
from Japan, Kanzy Ozu
How do you do, sir?
The two modest maidens
are professional entertainers
Geishas
Are you a lieutenant
with the American Army?
No, sir
Los Angeles Police
Homicide
Right, Lieutenant?
That's right, ma'am
There was a murder movie
on the plane Brilliant
I'm afraid I bore Paul
with the detail
all the way
from the airport
That must have been
the night that Vittorio
was murdered
The very same night
Do you have a hot suspect?
Well, I've got my eyes
on one
COLUMBO: Mr Gerard,
this is a lovely place
you have here
Thank you
Oh, that's quite a dish
I've never seen a dish
like this before
What is that called?
Raw fish
In Japanese,
it is fugu sashimi
A delicacy
Why don't you try it?
It's a developed taste
I think the Lieutenant
would prefer
one of the cooked dishes
Oh, I am sure
there is nothing wrong
with his taste
Allow me
Fugu for the Lieutenant
Gee, that's funny
I thought that the fugu
was gonna taste
like tuna fish
Did I say something wrong?
Not exactly
Shall we tell him?
I don't think
our guest is interested
in fish stories
Eve's off tomorrow night
on a trip to Europe,
to visit
every major restaurant
on the continent
Lieutenant,
they're having a little joke
at your expense
The fish
you have just eaten,
what you call a blowfish
or puffer fish,
is deadly poison
Is it?
Except when it's prepared
by a master chef
Then it's heavenly
In Japan,
the chef must be licensed
by the Department of Health
Every year
hundreds of people die
trying to prepare
fugu themselves
Holy mackerel
Excuse me?
I was just thinking
about a fortune cookie
that I read today
Mr Gerard,
this has been educational,
but I really have to be
running along
Ma'am, enjoy your trip
Mr Ozu
Sayonara, sayonara
Oh, one more thing
Gee, I almost forgot
what I came here to ask you
Fortunately you remembered
As you're an expert
on restaurants, sir,
I wanted to ask you,
do you know anything
about the Restaurant
Developers Association?
I don't know
anything about it,
Lieutenant
I've never heard of it
Have you?
No
No, Lieutenant, I'm sorry
Well,
that's all right, ma'am
As the Chinese say,
there's more
than one fish in the sea
CRAWFORD: Vittorio and I
had a binding agreement
He didn't lend money
and we didn't make lasagna
This was his favorite
coffee cake
I used to serve it
every time he came by to talk
Oh, my, oh
Oh, this is sensational
We always used to think so
Restaurant Developers'
commercial account
Oh, thank you
Scrumptious
Let me help you, ma'am
This is the best cake
I have ever eaten
As you can see,
Mr Crawford,
a balance of $17512
As I told you, Lieutenant
Then we have
the savings account
Say what? Account, what?
The Restaurant Developers
also has a savings account
at the bank
You know that's what
Mrs Columbo said?
She said there's probably
two accounts
and somehow
they got mixed up
I beg your pardon,
Lieutenant,
these accounts
are not mixed up,
but a corporate savings
account is a little unusual
This savings account,
excuse me,
is where Mr Vittorio's
checks were deposited
Also the checks
from Chez Duvall
and the House of Shanghai
(WHISTLES)
Who has access
to this account?
Just one person
A Mrs Irene DeMilo
I would like to speak
to Mrs DeMilo
Claire
Her only address
seems to be
a post office box
She came in two days ago
and closed out the account
She asked me to draw up
a cashier's check
for everything in the account
Except $3000
She took out $3000 in cash
In travelers' checks
This is the best cake
I've ever eaten
Would you say
this looks like me,
Lieutenant?
I'd say it doesn't
do you justice, Miss Plummer
You're an angel
I'm sorry about Mr Gerard
I know, ma'am He's busy
at the Chez Duvall
He's getting ready
for tonight's
Restaurant Writers' dinner
I'll be thinking
about you on the plane
You are going to the dinner,
aren't you?
Oh, certainly, ma'am
Mrs Columbo and I,
we appreciate the invitation
Wouldn't miss it
for the world
You should've
been there last year
It was terrific
Oh, Mrs DeMilo
Yes, Lieuten
The bank
The bank, Miss Plummer
Only in this case,
it's more like a laundry
I have a feeling
I just blew a trip
to Europe
I suppose
there'll be questions
Let's begin
with where Mr Gerard
buys his fish
His fish?
His fish, ma'am
How did the poison
get into the bottle?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
The banquet, I know
How did the poison
get into the
Who's been here?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Nobody's been here
Now we're going
to the banquet
Now we're gonna get
something terrific to eat
(WHISTLING)
No Mrs Columbo this evening?
Oh, well, sir
It's her night school
Final exam in accounting
She was dying to come here
but at the last minute
she decided she'd better
take the exam
Oh
Once again, dear friends,
we are dining together
on the finest cuisine,
drinking the best of wines
And once again we,
the restaurant writers,
are about to bestow
our coveted Award of Merit
But this is not
the happy occasion
we had so eagerly
anticipated
One who was very special
to us all is no longer here
For three years
in succession,
we have held
our annual dinner
at Vittorios
This year
the awards committee
decided that it would be
more appropriate to meet
somewhere else
Lieutenant Columbo,
perhaps I should have
told you the reason before,
but it was a closely
guarded secret
I couldnt even
tell Vittorio
Ladies and gentlemen,
I now present
our coveted award
posthumously
to the great Vittorio Rossi
And I call on his nephew,
Mario DeLucca,
to accept Mario?
(ALL CHEERING)
MAN: Bravo, Mario!
Bravo, Mario! Bravo!
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Thank you very much
(ALL LAUGHING)
Tenente Columbo
Hi, lover Hi
What are you doing here?
You're supposed to be
on a plane to Paris
That was Irene DeMilo
Eve Plummer's been grounded
lm Tenente Columbo
and this is my friend Mario
He doesnt speak
much English yet
So I want to say this
I know the two things
that he wants
more than anything
in the whole world
One is to be a success
here in America
Youve given him
a start with that
The other is that
the murderer of his uncle
be punished
I think
I can help with that
By this same time
tomorrow,
the person who murdered
Vittorio Rossi
will be under arrest
and thats a promise
Oh, that was
a lovely speech
Would you like
to hear mine? I quit
Ciao
Mr Gerard, sir
Yes, Lieutenant
Now that this case
is almost over,
this might be
our last opportunity
to cook
something up together
Yes
Who knows when our paths
will cross again?
Vittorio's will still
be closed tomorrow
Maybe we could
get to use all those
terrific tools
and that beautiful stove
What do you say, sir?
Would you join me
around noon?
Lieutenant,
if you hadn't brought it up,
I was about to
suggest it myself
Lieutenant, I'm late
I'm sorry
I'm just chopping up
some shallots
Two should be enough
For what?
A recipe from my pop
He used to cook for us kids
when my mother
was in the hospital
having a baby
That was about
once a year
for a while there
Veal scallops
Slightly seasoned
with salt and white pepper
Somehow it looks
better on veal
than black pepper
The dried fresh
mushrooms, sir,
they're diced
and they're soaking in a dish
on the counter
Now could this dish of yours
possibly be
escalopes de veau
aux cיpes?
Well, pop just called
it scaloppini
Let's see if we can find
a goodsized pan
This is fine
I'm just gonna heat up
some sweet butter
About a tablespoon or so
And a dash of olive oil
Olive oil first keeps
the butter from burning,
Well, this is the way
they did it
where pop came from
He was from the
old country, like Vittorio
Oh, I'll prepare the dressing
for the salad
You know, I've been thinking
about the murder, sir
We were all wrong
about the poison
It wasn't in any
of the bottles down
in the wine cellar
So the only other possibility
is that the killer
brought it with him
But why?
I'm gonna start
browning up the veal, sir
Just a few at a time
Yes, I think you're gonna
be interested in
the killer's motive
Undoubtedly
He was a silent partner
in the Restaurant
Developers Association
You remember
I mentioned that to you
Yes, you did
Vittorio and the others were
paying the killer a lot
of money for many years
You see, he was someone
in a position to
publicize their restaurants
and make them successful
Or else he could
print a few bad items
and demolish them
What it was,
it was a form of extortion
Would you like
some wine, sir?
There's an open bottle
on the table, help yourself
Thank you
Would you care for a glass,
Lieutenant?
Yes, sir
Coming up
I could also use
about a half a cup
for my scaloppine
Please, please,
go on with your explanation
I'm fascinated
It went on that way
for some time, sir,
with Vittorio paying off
along with the other people
But after a while,
he didn't want to pay anymore
He might even have
made threats on his own
And that was the motive
for the murder, sir
You're right
That's very interesting
But
But it's only conjecture,
of course
Oh, yes
We have no way of knowing
for certain
No, unless we got
a lot of cooperation
from the other people
in the Association
Correct
Oh I forgot your wine
I'll open another bottle
I'm taking out the veal, sir
Then I'm gonna add my shallots
and my mushrooms
and let 'em bubble
around in the pan
for a minute or so
You look perfectly at home
in a kitchen
It's amazing
When I was growing up, sir,
that's where we spent
most of our time
We had a living room
that was mostly for visits
from the teacher
and funerals
I'm adding the wine, sir
Your wine
Oh, just set it down
for a moment, sir
I want to stir this around
for a minute or two
By the way,
the night Vittorio died,
you never did intend
to eat his whole meal,
did you, sir?
What makes you say that?
Well,
the appointment book, sir
Mr Rossi had you down
for 8:00
I arrived at 8:00
Well, then you went to the
airport later on
To pick up Mr Ozu
Mr Ozu says
that he came in
on the movie flight
and according to
the airline schedule, sir,
the only movie flight
arrived at 8:55
And since you
planned to meet that plane,
Mr Gerard,
there is no way that
you could have enjoyed
an entire meal
and still got to the airport
in 55 minutes
So, you knew that
you were going to
leave early, sir
You never intended
to eat Vittorio's dinner
Bravo
Lieutenant,
guilty
I was going to make
some excuse to Vittorio
As it turned out,
I didn't have to
You're doing very well
Very well
What else have you learned?
I'm adding the veal
to the pan, sir
Oh!
The boys at the lab
finally got a fix on
that poison the killer used
It was Japanese
blowfish poison
Fugu?
You can't be serious Fugu?
It's a terrific poison
The killer knew
we couldn't trace it
And between you and me,
he had access
to that kind of fish
There's a fish store
in Little Tokyo
that buys them off
a couple of fishermen
But how did
the murderer get the fugu
poison into the bottle?
Excuse the outburst,
Lieutenant
Lieutenant,
Vittorio was alone
when he opened the bottle
Right, sir
Right
Vittorio was indeed alone
Ah, that's the point, sir
Now, a very odd thing
happened here the other day,
when I was recreating
the crime as they say
Just before you arrived here
at Vittorio's kitchen,
Albert took this apart for me
because I wanted to
take the cartridge
down to the lab to have
the boys check it out
And what did they find?
Not a thing, sir
But, and here's what's odd,
Albert put a nice,
fresh, new, full cartridge
into the opener for me
And nobody used
that opener until last night
when just
before the banquet,
I myself, sitting right here,
tried to open
a bottle of wine
and the opener was empty, sir,
flat out
From which you concluded?
I asked myself,
how does a full cartridge
become an empty cartridge
without opening any bottles?
And the answer was,
somebody's been switching
bottle openers around here
Switching?
Switching more
than once, sir
That's my opinion
And then there's this
You see this, sir?
Yes
Well, this hollow needle
could also hold a tiny bit
of poison,
probably injected with
a hypodermic syringe
And that's what
the killer prepared, sir
He took an opener
identical to the one
that Vittorio used
and he put poison
in the needle
And he took that opener
with him to the dinner
and at an opportune time,
he switched the openers
So when Vittorio
was by himself in the kitchen,
and the boy was showing you
to the door,
Vittorio used
the switched opener
to poison his own wine
You understand, sir?
Lieutenant,
I regret to tell you
that I understand
all too well
It was
a terrific scheme, sir
Your only mistake
was coming back
the next night so that you
could switch back the openers
so we couldn't find
any trace of poison
and that was right
after Albert put in
the fresh cartridge
Brilliantly deduced
Shall we drink
to your successful
solution of the case?
I couldn't have done it, sir,
without your help
On the other hand,
there remains
a matter of proof
Oh, I can't prove
any of this, sir
But it did bother me
that there was a poisoned
opener around
the exact twin of this one
So when I came in
here today,
I took the trouble
of putting a little nick
in the top
Right there, sir
But you'll notice
there is no nick
See?
Yes
It must be
a different opener
No question about it
Ah! I wouldn't, sir
Don't drink
You switched
the openers again
but I switched the glasses
That's the poisoned
glass, sir
The glass I was
supposed to drink
I'll just keep this for
the boys down in the lab
That's what they call proof
You must try this, sir
I'm really interested
in your opinion
You're a very
able man, Lieutenant
I respect that
But I really don't
care for you very much
You know, sir,
I was thinking
the same thing about you
I respect your talent
But I don't like anything else
about you
The dressing is perfect
Thank you
When did you
first suspect me?
Well, as it happens, sir,
about two minutes
after I met you
That can't be possible
Oh, you made it
perfectly clear, sir,
the very first night,
when you decided to
come to the restaurant
directly after
you were informed
that Vittorio was poisoned
I was instructed to
come here by the police
And you came, sir
Yes
After eating
dinner with a man
that had been poisoned
You didn't go to a doctor
You came because
the police instructed you
You didn't go to a hospital,
you didn't even ask to
have your stomach pumped
Mr Gerard,
that's the damnedest example
of good citizenship
I've ever seen
I see
What do you think?
Lieutenant,
I wish you had been a chef
I understand, sir
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org