Remember, my friends,
the task at hand is not
an impossible one.
The Defiance is not rigged.
Mr. Paer has before him
every tool, schematic,
and safety precaution necessary
for him to save his own life.
Ladies and gentleman,
drink in the moment.
I want you to let the numbness
of life wash away...
even if only for tonight,
for this moment.
The love. The fear.
This is what it is to be alive.
This... is The Defiance.
This is Les Fleurs du Mal.
I can't.
Please, you have to let me out of here.
I can't do this.
Are you listening to me?! Make it stop!
I can't!
Aah! I did it!
I did it! I beat the game!
I beat the game!
I did...
No. Wait, no!
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Shoot.
Let me help with that.
Oh, no, that's okay. I got it.
Nonsense. I insist.
No thanks. I got it.
Oh, do you want some coffee?
I was just going out for some.
Come on. I insist.
So happy we finally get a chance to chat.
Is Agnes at school?
Yeah, I just dropped her off,
and, uh, I was
on my way home and realized I didn't have
anything for dinner,
so I picked up a few things.
What do you do for work?
I'm a government employee.
What about you?
Me? Ha, I'm retired.
I moved here to be closer to my daughter.
We're estranged, but...
I'm hoping to get closer to her.
Agnes is in full-on princess mode.
What?
Oh! Right.
I know it's not very woke,
but she's irresistible.
No, fairy tales are very important.
They help children cope
with separation anxiety and loss.
Oh, and I love a fairytale.
Just not the part
where you got to get saved
by Prince Charming.
Um... that's work.
I'm so sorry. I got to go.
Have you seen my keys?
I could've sworn
I just put them right here.
Oh! Here.
I must have knocked them off the table.
Uh, keep the mug. Bring it back later.
I'm really sorry about this.
Don't be. I got what I came for.
"To creep softly like a coward
toward the treasures of your body,
to whip your joyous flesh
and bruise your pardoned breast,
to make in your astonished flank
a wide and gaping wound."
As a general rule,
I believe the sword is mightier
than the pen.
But in the hands of a free-spirited,
syphilis-ridden French dandy,
I'd say the odds shift considerably.
How's my grandfather?
We saw him this morning.
He's still... critical.
And the woman who tried to kill him?
You know Baudelaire was prosecuted
for offenses against public morality?
The woman.
His words were so provocative
that six of his poems were
banned for nearly a century.
You said you had a lead.
I do. A secret society
named after Baudelaire's
"Les Fleurs du Mal."
Poetry lovers?
Thrill seekers.
People who go to extreme lengths
to offend public morality.
A society of decadent misanthropes.
People who have everything,
so nothing is special.
And this connects to the woman
who abducted you in Paris?
It does.
According to Reddington,
Les Fleurs du Mal is
our best chance of finding Steinhil.
Because whoever runs it contracted
him to create an illusion.
Well, whatever he did for them
can't top the illusion
he created for himself...
rising from the dead.
If we can get to him,
he can get us to the woman
who put Elizabeth's grandfather
on life support.
All right, I combed
through every database,
and there's nothing concrete
on Fleurs du Mal,
only rumors about a man given a knife
and locked in a room with a tiger,
a woman who fell off the Eiffel Tower,
and something about... piranhas.
You said Reddington had a lead.
A name. Charles Radcliffe.
According to Reddington,
he attended one of the society's events.
Ressler, Aram, go see Mr. Radcliffe.
See if he can I.D. these people
before they hurt someone else.
How's Agnes?
Uh... amazing.
She's sweetly oblivious
to the guards you have
sitting outside our apartment
to protect her.
If you need anything...
including time off...
Is that why you sent Aram instead of me?
I sent Aram because he needs
more experience in the field.
You are a single mom with a hard job.
I just want you to know
if you need to come in late
or leave early...
I don't. But it's good to know I can.
Thank you...
for everything.
Elodie Radcliffe?
Agents Ressler and Mojtabai, FBI.
I knew you'd come sooner or later.
You did?
Les Fleurs du Mal. That's why
you're here, isn't it?
Uh... how could you know that?
I thought you'd given up.
On what?
On my husband, Charles.
Well, if he's here, we'd like to
have a word with him, as well.
We have a lot of questions
for the both of you.
Charles can't help you.
Because those people in Les Fleurs du Mal
all but killed him.
So, The Defiance... It's done?
You said this one was important.
And the Player
will be provided with tools?
Yes... as discussed.
Mm. All useless.
For the Player to survive,
he needs to be willing to, uh...
break his index finger
and dislocate his thumb,
work his hand into the cam slot,
and disengage the lock.
It's the only way.
So, one could survive.
Could? Yes.
Would? Incredibly unlikely.
But the narrow chance of survival
is the whole point, right?
Is this a diving accident?
An arterial gas embolism.
That's the lie they told me
to hide whatever they really did to him.
Did you go to the police?
And say what? I don't know what happened.
And even if I did,
these are powerful people
with the resources to protect themselves.
So, how did you find these people?
Charles found them.
It was a gift... for our anniversary.
Our marriage wasn't perfect.
We were bored, drifting apart.
Charles thought this might be exciting.
To... To watch people die.
Sharing an experience,
something so rare and raw
and extraordinary
that it can't be forgotten...
that it can only bring you closer.
They called it "The Defiance."
Sounds terrifying.
Which is why I didn't go.
Do you know how to make contact?
Y-You want me to talk to them?
Yes. Help us expose them.
And find out what happened
to your husband.
Mm, Charles had an e-mail address
for the man in charge,
Thelonious Prackett.
That's all I know.
_
Motya?! I'm sorry
to barge in unexpectedly,
but I've called repeatedly,
and there hasn't been
hide nor hair of you,
so I thought I'd come and check
to see if you're okay.
- Please go.
- And you're okay! Thank God!
I thought maybe Ed Broadfoot and his sons
had finally tracked you down
and dragged you off
to one of those gravel pits.
What do you want?
It's about the Townsend Directive.
I understand it's been reactivated...
that you and everyone else who bought in
are actively hunting for her.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Motya, I need to take care
of this myself. It's personal.
Ah.
Do you know your conversations
with the Minister of Finance
single-handedly responsible
for getting my operations
pushed out of Kiev?
I lost millions in rail lines alone.
I lost my relationship
with contractors, politicians.
My own wife left me for the competitor.
To be fair, she'd been
screwing him for months.
Forget about The Directive.
Forget about Katarina Rostova.
I'm not gonna help you find her.
I'm gonna hunt her down,
and I'm gonna kill her myself.
And the next time I see your face,
I'm gonna shoot
before you can start talking.
Too soon, the comment about the wife?
Good talk.
I told you.
Yeah, you were right.
But we had to try.
And now he's forced our hand.
Sir. Sir, there is nothing
on Thelonious Prackett.
It's... It's got to be an alias.
But whoever he is,
he agreed to let Mrs. Radcliffe
- recommend a new member.
- Did you tell Ressler?
Prackett agreed on one condition...
that if the new member gets
invited to an event,
Radcliffe has to go with.
That'll be all right as long as
Ressler is with her the whole time.
Yeah, um, about that.
If, um...
If we're doing this,
I'd like to go with her.
Instead of Ressler.
We need to be a convincing
couple to have a connection,
and we have one...
I can relate to her loss.
Samar.
Not that what I went through
even compares.
You went through plenty.
I'm sorry I haven't asked you
about it more.
I'm fine.
Um, still a bit, uh, numb, I guess.
But, um, when the last real
feeling you had was devastation,
you're not super psyched
to get out there and feel again.
But... I'm good. I'm good.
I agree.
That I'm good, or... or devastated?
That you should go with her.
Work on your cover... you're going in.
Greetings!
Where are we going?
And why do I have to go with you?
Because you remain in my debt.
I saved your life.
Yes, after putting it at risk.
And I told you about Steinhil's contract
with Les Fleurs du Mal.
Why aren't you looking at them?
I've got people working on that.
I'm supposed to be at dinner
tonight at The Peppermill.
It's my wedding anniversary.
Congratulations!
That shouldn't be a problem.
You're holding me hostage.
I prefer to think of it
as looking out for my best interests.
Please, find yourself another seat.
Relax. Read a book. Watch a movie.
Do you like Truffaut?
We have the complete collection.
What did Stevenson say?
The room is being swept.
He can't get a camera in.
Someone from the hotel staff, then.
Surely we can incentivize a maid
or someone from room service
to take a photo.
They're only allowing
authorized personnel.
We're too late to get anyone
on the inside.
Can I ask you something?
- "Day for Night." Definitely.
- The photograph.
Oh, that's none of your concern.
If I got it for you,
would my debt be paid?
Conceivably.
We met at Ascot.
I had a horse racing
in the Dubai Shergar Cup.
And how did he do?
Fractured his left-front
pastern. Had to be put down.
Cost me $300,000 in stud fees.
Per stud?
40 studs a year,
that's $12 million... per year.
That must have been a dark day.
Until I saw Elodie.
Things brightened considerably
after that.
How is Charles?
The man I married is alive,
but my husband is gone.
And our role in that tragedy?
I don't hold you responsible,
if that's what you're asking.
He wanted the risk.
We both did.
Well, I know you did.
I'm surprised you still do.
I didn't.
For a long time,
I thought I never would again.
Then I met Shameel.
I was a guest in one of the royal boxes,
and she was three rows below,
and still the peacock feathers
in her hat blocked my view.
Ah.
Your interest is... unusual.
I don't see why.
I can buy anything I want.
So, naturally what I want is
something I cannot buy.
It's unusual because it coincides
with an upcoming event.
Why is that unusual?
Because we haven't issued
invitations yet.
Which makes your interest
an usual coincidence or worse...
not a coincidence at all.
I understand your caution
and why you need
to vet your guests as closely as you do.
I would expect nothing less.
But we've told you our story,
we've exchanged wiring instructions,
and I'm one text away from depositing
$1 million into your account.
The Defiance is an experience
money can't buy.
Of course not, which is why
I'm all the more happy
to pay for it. So, I need to know...
Are we in, or are we out?
Welcome to Les Fleurs du Mal.
I'm confused.
We have no idea where we're going,
who will be there, or how to get out.
I mean, we don't even know
how to get to this event.
Prackett said he'd send instructions.
- Which he hasn't.
- He will.
We sold our story well,
but if you're uncomfortable...
I am. Because I...
Look, I don't quite understand the plan.
Can we go over it again?
The location of the event is
a closely guarded secret.
Which means
you and Aram will be on your own.
When Prackett makes contact,
you'll follow his instructions.
Well, if you don't know
where we're going,
and you can't follow us,
how do you plan to find our location?
With an ELT beacon.
We'll smuggle the device in disassembled
so we can get it past security.
Disassembled.
You're going to wear the device
into the building in pieces.
Once inside,
Aram will assemble the device,
activate the signal, and it'll
give our team your location.
And once you get the signal...?
We'll come and get you.
Okay. I get it.
We literally have no idea
where we're going.
No. We don't.
It'll be okay.
I promise.
Miss Radcliffe, Mr. Aubeelauck, welcome.
If you would.
For The Defiance. Enjoy your stay.
- Thank you.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Hmm.
Why do we need these again?
I have no idea.
Signal's clear. We're good.
I miss having children.
- I need to tie my shoe.
- Mm.
Hand me the antenna.
And what are you two up to?
What? Oh.
Uh... We, uh... Hmm.
We were, uh...
We were just, uh, talking about
how delicious those
little shrimp tartlets are.
Uh, he's quite a foodie.
- I am a foodie.
- Mm-hmm.
I am... I'm such a foodie.
I'm... I'm a foodie.
Well, eat all you like.
Drink all you like.
Tonight is an event that
none of us will soon forget.
Have fun, my friends.
And... good luck.
"Good luck"?
Why would he say, "Good luck"?
I have no idea...
and I don't want to find out.
Let's keep moving, shall we? Okay.
That's Motya Morozov.
He's one of the two men
I need you to photograph.
But you already have his photograph.
I have photographs of both of them.
What I need is a photograph
of them together.
- Why?
- The other man's name is Fields.
Despite staying at the same hotel,
being seen together would be...
...quite damaging.
They'll take every precaution
to prevent that from happening.
How can I help you?
You see that tall drink of water
behind me?
I'm gonna ask him to marry me.
Good for you!
We stayed here once and had
the most incredible time.
In room 267.
Any chance it's still available?
I'll see what I can do.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
The lobby is crawling with security.
I'm not surprised.
The FBI are not known
for their discretion.
That's who's scanning the room?
The feds?!
That's who doesn't want
a photo to be taken.
As I said, neither party...
You didn't tell me that one of
the parties was the FBI.
An oversight, admittedly.
I thought you were working with the FBI.
A small, select group of agents
are in my employ.
- Any of these guys?
- Unfortunately not.
I can see this was a mistake.
10 minutes. The valet line.
Be there with the engine running.
How are you gonna do it?
Ding-dong ditch.
I loved playing that as a child!
May I have your attention, please?
The Defiance is here.
The spectacle we are about to witness
only has meaning
because each of us is invested.
The pledge we made is what binds us.
It's what lets us feel like we're alive,
even if only for one night.
Each of us has agreed
to embrace this challenge,
and yet only one of us will face it.
For that unlucky member,
may it be some small consolation
to remember... we ask no risk of you
that we have not taken ourselves.
With that, The Defiance
begins in one hour.
Good luck to us all.
Oh, my God. The Player.
They choose one from the guests.
I don't know what's taking so long.
It's online and transmitting.
So, why aren't they here?
Are we maybe out of range?
No, it doesn't matter where we are.
It's GPS activated.
Okay, so, where are they, then?
I don't know.
But the only thing
that could possibly interfere
would be... a sun-flare...
...a jammer.
So, the FBI has no idea we're here.
- I don't think so.
- So, now what?
Ladies and gentlemen, it's time.
Are you ready to meet the Player?
- Oh, my God.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
Oh, my God!
Okay, Elodie,
we're gonna figure this out.
We're gonna figure this out.
It's gonna be fine.
- It's gonna be fine. Just...
- No. No. Wait.
No, wait! Wait! Wait!
Hold on! Hold on, stop! Please don't! No!
I'm gonna come for you, okay?
Stop it! Please! Stop! Don't do this!
Him. That's Kirilenko.
Head of Russian Vor in America.
Get away from me!
Stop, you're hurting me!
FBI!
Stop her!
Oh!
- Oh, my...
- Wow.
Hi.
Nice noodle.
She's good... She is very good.
I believe this makes us even.
Dembe, we can tell Edward we'll
be ready for takeoff in 20.
Francesca.
Your husband, what's his name?
Paul... Paul Farwell.
Absent head winds,
in two hours, you and Paul
will be celebrating your anniversary
at The Peppermill as planned.
I recommend the corn chowder.
Oh, my! Ding-dong ditch.
Hey. Hey! We finally got something.
Bring up the map overlay.
End of the hall to the left.
Oh.
Connections are all solid. Oh.
What happened?
I don't know. We lost the signal.
But we got a location.
Scramble the HRT choppers.
You and Keen need to get there now.
Ladies and gentlemen,
after our brief interruption...
it's now time.
Welcome... to The Defiance.
Tonight, our Player faces
a most desperate challenge.
Using only the tools
left inside the chamber,
our Player must find a way
to save her life
by unlocking the device
and climbing free from her tomb.
But this device, this Defiance offers
an additional challenge, one involving
time.
Our Player not only has to get out,
she has to do so before she suffocates.
Player...
...give us a show we won't forget!
Stop it! I mean, stop it!
And good luck.
Please, don't do this!
I can't get this open!
I... I... I can't!
I don't know how to do this!
Come on, guys.
Is that stroganoff?
Yes!
Mmm!
I'm always hunting for a new recipe.
The woman. You sent her?
I did. After our last conversation,
I felt you needed
a soupçon of motivation.
I told you that
if you come back, I'm gonna...
Yes, I know, you'd shoot first
and not bother with the questions later.
But... But, quite a bit has
changed since then.
This photo prove nothing.
They prove you went to Miami
to meet in secret with the FBI.
I was told you were a snitch.
And unless you do as I instruct,
everyone else will know
the truth, as well.
Rostova.
When you get a lead, I get a lead.
When you get a location,
I get to go there first.
Mmm.
The nutmeg is nice.
Needs salt.
Please stop this!
The police! The FBI... they know.
They know all about you.
They're gonna arrest all of you.
Aram!
Aram, please, make it stop!
Please tell them!
Please! Please tell them.
Mr. Aubeelauck. I need you
to come with me, please.
- Make it stop!
- What? No.
Sir, I'm not asking.
Aram!
...could you, uh... could you just, uh,
- uh, give me a minute?
- Sir, we're leaving now.
Mr. Prackett's gonna be
very upset with you.
Upset with me for what?
FBI! Everybody on the ground.
Nobody move.
- Where are we going?
- I don't know.
The jammer's back up.
They're not going anywhere.
Secure the east exit.
- Shh, shh.
- Check that door!
Where are your friends?
I don't know.
What was that for?
Thank you.
We have to keep moving.
Okay.
- We're almost there.
- Okay.
Aah!
- Welcome back.
- Let her go.
This really is a first.
I'm an FBI agent,
and you're gonna let her go.
You must know, if you're an FBI agent,
that we can't let you go
and expose our guests.
So, you're going to come with me,
you're going to tell my men
exactly what the FBI know,
and then we're gonna
take you to the water's edge
and drown you.
- No, wait.
- She had nothing to do with this.
- I'm the one you want.
- What's done is done.
- Kill them slowly!
- Drown them!
FBI!
- Go, go, go!
- FBI! Hands!
- Hands up!
- Let's see 'em!
Hands! Hands in the air.
Some Defiance.
You find this funny?
I think it's thrilling.
The other society members
don't share your enthusiasm.
They're too busy turning on you.
So far, they've detailed six murders.
People want risk.
I give it to them.
The chance to feel... alive.
Is that what you gave Vance Palmer
when you locked him in a box
with a bomb he couldn't defuse?
If everyone's talked, why talk to me?
Snitches roll uphill. I'm on top.
Not quite.
Louis Steinhil.
I'm told you hired him once.
Never heard of him.
Well, that's too bad.
'Cause if you had, we could have
recommended to the D.A.
that he take the death penalty
off the table.
Then again, lethal injection
sure would give you a chance
to feel alive...
you know, before it kills you.
What... What's his name again?
Steinhil. Louis T.
It's an anagram for The Illusionist.
You said The Peppermill
didn't deliver the champagne?
They said there were no reservations
under Farwell or Campbell.
Francesca said she was married.
But according to Glen,
the DMV database lists her as single.
Hello?
When it's appropriate, I'd like
to engage your services.
I thought we were even.
We are. You're under no obligation,
but I could use a capable operative.
Do you need an answer right now?
Oh, my goodness. Oh, how rude of me.
It's your anniversary.
Did you make it to The Peppermill?
I did. We're here now.
And here I am talking shop. Go, have fun.
I hope Paul knows how lucky he is.
How could he forget?
I remind him every day.
Hello? Elizabeth?
Elizabeth.
Oh, hey, sorry about that. Um...
Give me one second.
Okay.
So, I was just calling to tell
you I got what you wanted.
- An address on Steinhil.
- Tell me.
Hmm.
_
Some people are so thoughtful.
Steinhil. Where is he?
They found Steinhil.
That's too bad.
I'd grown quite fond of him.
_
Well, hello, young lady.
Thank you for the books.
You're very welcome.
Would you like to read one to me?
Oh, well, I'd love that.
Would you like me to?
You did well out there today.
Uh... eventually.
You did well.
I'm proud of you.
"Once upon a time,
there lived a little country girl,
the prettiest creature who was ever seen.
Her mother was extremely fond of her;
and her grandmother
doted on her still more."
How's Mrs. Radcliffe?
She's, uh... She's okay.
You know, I think part of her
found all the danger... exhilarating.
It's crazy, right?
I've long since given up
trying to figure out
what excites people or why.
Yeah, and getting your kicks
from Les Fleurs du Mal is crazy.
But, uh, as a general rule,
I admire people
who insist on finding ways
to be exhilarated.
As opposed to being okay
with feeling numb.
You're not okay with it.
You're scared to feel again,
which is understandable.
But I want to encourage you to try.
Because as... hard as it is
to feel pain...
it's much harder to feel nothing.
"The poor child did not know
of the danger she was in."
Hey.
Hi.
Come in.
"'Grandmother, what big ears you have.'
'All the better
to hear you with, my child, '
replied the wolf."
I wanted to come by
to make sure you were okay.
I am... thanks to you.
I also, uh, stopped by, uh,
to say that...
that you shouldn't, um...
you know, feel badly about...
About what?
Kissing me.
You shouldn't feel badly
about that at all.
I shouldn't?
Absolutely not.
"'Grandmother, what big teeth you have.'
'All the better to eat you
with, ' replied the wolf.
And, saying these words, the Wicked Wolf
fell upon Little Red Riding Hood
and ate her all up."
She's an angel.
How did it happen?
You becoming estranged
from your daughter.
All that matters now
is that I want to make amends.
I was estranged from my mother.
I would hope that she would want
to make amends with me, too.
I'm sure she does.
Well...
I hope it happens.
Ohh.
For a long time,
I didn't think that would ever happen.
Now I'm beginning to think it will.