Previously on
Star Trek: Picard...
BENAYOUN: For a relic,
you're in excellent shape.
Just that little abnormality
in the parietal lobe.
Index. Identify
this painting.
This painting
is called Daughter.
JURATI:
Maddox's theory
was Data's entire code,
even his memories,
could be reconstituted
from a single positronic neuron.
You are something lovingly
and deliberately created.
You're telling me
that I'm not real.
RAMDHA:
Which sister
are you?
LARIS: The heart of
the Zhat Vash mission
was hate and fear
and pure loathing
for any form
of synthetic life.
I know who you are!
You are the Destroyer!
PICARD:
Thank you, Will,
for not trying
to talk me out of all this.
Believe me, I know better.
RAFFI:
The Romulans send in a mole,
a half-Romulan Vulcan
named Oh.
I will take care of Picard.
Nine years ago,
a Starfleet vessel
had first contact
with a pair of emissaries
from a strange
new world.
The Zhat Vash
have been searching
for this world ever since.
Which they have now found
because of me.
RIOS:
Ghulion system. Fourth planet.
I'm home.
Welcome, all of you.
Dr. Altan Inigo Soong.
I take it my face
looks familiar.
I'm just trying to understand
the logic of sacrifice.
I don't like the sound of that.
(Saga screams)
PICARD:
Starfleet Command,
I have a first contact
situation.
The Federation
will listen to me.
They didn't listen to him
after the attack on Mars.
And they're not
going to believe him now.
SUTRA:
My mind to your mind.
My thoughts to your thoughts.
Fascinating.
ALTAN:
There is some sort of higher
synthetic beings out there.
ALTAN:
There is some sort of higher
synthetic beings out there.
Dr. Soong and I have designed a
suitable beacon to summon them.
To them, we're monsters.
A mother would die
for her children.
Would you?
Yes.
SUTRA:
Their purpose
is to seek out
SUTRA:
Their purpose
is to seek out
advanced synthetic life
and excise it from
the oppression by organics.
You will become the Destroyer
after all.
Take him away.
(electronic warbling)
Would the xBs be
better off dead?
Everyone hates them.
They have no home.
They don't belong anywhere.
SEVEN OF NINE:
Am I better off dead?
I'm an xB. I have no home.
I don't belong anywhere.
Why don't I just put a phaser to
my head and get it over with?
Because... I'd miss you.
(grunts softly)
(panting)
Well.
Have you found them?
Yes. They're all here.
Have you fucked any of them?
Mm, not yet.
Killed any?
One.
Well, I call that progress.
Come see my hiding place.
Oceanfront. Crashing waves.
You'll love it.
♪ ♪
Lucky you.
(beeping)
SOJI:
I just wanted to see
if you were okay.
I will be when I'm set free.
Picard, try to see this
from our point of view.
You choose if we live.
You choose if we die.
You choose.
We have no choice.
You organics have
never given us one.
To say you have no choice
is a failure of imagination.
Please,
don't let the Romulans turn you
into the monsters they fear.
Stop them, Soji.
Stop building that beacon.
Shut it down now.
The beings you are attempting
to summon may well be
your salvation, but they
will be our annihilation.
♪ ♪
NARISSA:
You're telling me you want
to use those grenades
to destroy flowers?
Ship-killing flowers that fly.
No, not this time.
I made my way out of the nest,
I can make my way back in.
You have to stay here and bring
the weapons systems on line.
Our parents died for this,
Narek.
Many more gave their lives.
I found her, Narissa.
Me. The family disgrace.
The Zhat Vash washout.
I found Seb Cheneb.
Well, go on, then.
I have my work to do.
(device trilling)
RIOS: Honestly,
I'm a little afraid of it.
Like, if I use it too much,
it's gonna...
eat my soul.
RAFFI:
Well, luckily,
you don't have a soul, so...
(chuckles)
But what does it do?
Like, how do I even...
Well, when Saga gave it to me,
she said,
"You have to use
your imagination."
Oh, she said that, did she?
Mm-hmm.
Well, I don't have
one of those, either.
Okay, well, Chris,
this is your ship.
You know what's wrong with it.
It's not too complicated.
Now, the intermix reactor
is fused.
I need to unfuse it,
which is impossible.
I need to replace it,
but the maintenance replicator
is off-line because...
the intermix reactor
is fused.
Mm.
Well, just, you know,
give it a try.
Okay. Fine, I'll do it.
I got a lot of imagination.
To you, everything's a hammer.
No. I'll do it.
T-There's no kind
of trigger or-or switch.
Hmm. Well, maybe what-what
she meant was
you have to imagine the fix.
Have you been, um,
hitting the horgl again?
(chuckles)
Visualize that it's
no longer fused.
You know, see the hole
patching itself.
(exhales)
(chiming)
Whoa.
Ay, caramba.
Uh, what's happening?
Nothing that makes any sense.
(chuckles)
(sighs)
Say it.
Say what?
Mm, those three beautiful words.
You were right.
Mm, just one more time.
Piss off.
(clattering)
I know that sound.
ALTAN:
All of Bruce's work
on the downloading
of consciousness
into a synthetic body
should be on that machine.
Let's hope so.
We don't have much time.
Mm-hmm.
You know...
(exhales)
This really is a remarkable act
of self-sacrifice on your part.
But I suppose
that's what mothers do,
isn't it?
(door whooshes shut)
(quietly):
It's okay. It'll be okay.
You can do this.
You have to do this.
I'm not their mother, asshole.
RIOS:
Someone's throwing rocks
at my ship.
The abusive Romulan boyfriend.
Comms.
RIOS:
Go ahead, throw it.
I want to see what a photon
torpedo can do at this range.
I have 12 wide-dispersion
molecular solvent
grenade canisters.
I'm throwing rocks.
What do you want?
And don't think we won't
kick your ass, dirtbag,
because we will.
Raff.
What are you doing here,
snakehead?
Trying to save the universe.
We can keep fighting,
or we can work together.
Stop what's coming for us.
It's your call.
JL. JL, come in.
Damn it.
NAREK:
They are building
some kind of transmitter.
They are signaling something
to come here.
To do what?
We believe
synthetics are fated to destroy
all organic life.
We call it Ganmadan.
The place is on lockdown.
Whatever that
transmitter is,
they don't want anyone
interfering with it.
(laughs softly)
The thing about Picard is...
Yeah. Interfering
is definitely his thing.
Try him again.
JL, come in.
Admiral Jean-Luc Picard,
retired.
Damn it.
I told you.
They won't respond.
The synthetics have
jammed all comms.
Feldor stam torret.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I do. I very much
choose to live.
Hold up, kid.
We disarmed him, searched him.
We may very well
have a common enemy
coming for us. You're
gonna want to hear
what he came here
to say.
Altan, I...
What are you doing?
I'm transferring Saga's memories
into a V-module.
As a memento for Arcana.
But the damage
to her optical processors
corrupted
the data stream and...
Do you need something?
Yes, I've been, um,
I've been working on the
neural lace for your golem,
but some of the files
are encrypted.
And Bruce always said that your
crypto kung fu was the best.
Well... (chuckles)
Uh, okay, I'll, uh, see if
I can get into those files.
Keep an eye
on the transcoding rate.
Got it.
♪ ♪
(squelching)
(whispers): Sorry.
ELNOR:
I still don't understand
why we're trusting him.
His sister murdered Hugh.
Good thing she didn't
come along, then.
I don't like you.
No?
How do you feel about Ganmadan?
Because if we waste
any more time
fighting each other,
we will all die,
and then whether or not you
like me will matter even less.
Whoa, hold on.
(chuckles)
What is Ganmadan?
What is the story?
It's just that.
A story.
A story of the end.
Of...?
Everything.
Like Ragnarok or Judgment Day.
An ancient myth.
Some say it dates back
from long before our ancestors
first arrived on Vulcan.
The story of Ganmadan begins
with two sisters.
Twin khalagu.
Demons.
Twin demons who come
at the end of time
to open the way
and unleash the ch'khalagu.
Very bad demons.
One sister
is called Seb Natan,
the Foreteller.
She plays a drum made
from the skin of children.
She strikes it
with a chain of skulls,
so hard and so long
that her heart bursts
from the effort.
Mm.
The other sister
is called Seb Cheneb.
Seb Cheneb?
Yeah, see,
w-we know about her.
So you know that
she carries a horn
from a great pale hellbeast
called Ganmadan.
You know when she
blows a blast on the horn,
it will unleash
all the ch'khalagu
who have been waiting since
the beginning of time.
You know the sky will crack,
and through the
crack in the sky
the ch'khalagu
will come ravening.
You know about the
Thousand Days of Pain.
You know the streets
will be slick
with entrails
of half-devoured corpses.
You know
the worlds will burn,
and the ch'khalagu will feast,
and nurse their brats
on blood,
and pick their teeth with bones.
No, we did not know any of that.
But, I mean, do you really...
you really believe
this is a-a prophecy?
No.
I believe it's history.
And the fascinating thing
about history is...
it always repeats itself.
(thunder rumbling)
NEDAR:
At last,
our great work
is nearly at an end.
NAREK:
Molecular solvent grenades.
Short fuse.
Push button, throw.
Intended for those orchids.
Now the transmitter
is our target of opportunity.
Okay, h-hold on, hold on.
(chuckles)
How exactly are we planning
on getting ourselves
back into Synthville?
We walk in the front door.
(grunting)
Oh! Hey. Hi.
(chuckles)
RIOS:
And how are we gonna do that?
By bringing them
the Romulan secret agent
that killed their beloved Saga.
I still don't like you.
Check it out, you guys.
Look who we found
sneaking around last night.
Thought you might want him back.
RAFFI:
So, how are we gonna
blow the transmitter?
RAFFI:
So, how are we gonna
blow the transmitter?
A single, concentrated blast.
Remote detonation.
Sounds like we need
a delivery system.
A drone.
Your weapons?
Oh, of course.
The molecular solvent.
It's stable?
Until it's detonated.
Except in metal, so the
container needs to be, uh,
carbon fiber, ceramic.
CODEX:
Bags.
Oh. Certainly.
You bet.
And with the transporter block
the synths have in place,
we can't beam anything
in or out.
So, we'll need
a way to conceal it.
Do you play?
Oh, I love the game.
RAFFI: Ha.
All right, let's go.
Thanks.
(beeping)
(whispers):
Picard?
Admiral Picard. Hello?
Are you...
Still here.
Okay.
They're about
to power up the beacon.
We have to hurry.
What is this?
I'm busting you out.
I honestly thought I was
the worst secret agent ever,
but I'm starting to believe
I may have a gift.
No-- Where are we going?
Back to La Sirena.
Come on, we've got to move
while they're still distracted.
COMPUTER VOICE:
Synthetic matrix complete.
Ready to receive neural engrams.
(electronic chirping)
NAREK:
The tower's almost active.
We need to get
a clear line of sight
on the superluminal tuner
at the base.
RAFFI:
How are we gonna get up there
without being seen?
RAFFI:
How are we gonna get up there
without being seen?
An excellent question.
JURATI: I guess they
went looking for us?
We'll worry about that later.
Status report on the Romulans.
Uh...
Come on, Doctor.
Uh, the attack wing is
seven minutes from planetfall.
Any sign of Starfleet?
No, but even if your
message got through,
they'd still be
behind the Romulans.
We've got to find a way
to stall them somehow.
And, of course, hope that
the Federation arrives.
Yeah? And then?
I mean, say we do find a way
to hold off the Romulans.
We save Soji.
Now she and the golden children
are free to call up
the uber-synths,
and then vapor and ash.
A galactic-level biocidal event.
Well, clearly,
we've got to stop them, too!
They've left us behind, Picard.
They're generations beyond us.
In one sense, yes.
But in another, as you said,
they are children.
And until now,
the only teachers
that they've had
are a couple of hermits.
And the fear of extermination.
But fear is
an incompetent teacher.
Yes. They have life.
But no one is teaching them
what it's for.
To be alive is a responsibility.
As well as a right.
How are they
supposed to learn
that lesson in...
six minutes and 11 seconds?
The way that children
learn most things.
By example.
Now...
let's see how closely
I was watching Rios.
(whirring)
All right.
Make it so.
SUTRA:
Brothers and sisters,
as soon as the beacon is
at full capacity,
we will begin transmitting.
And once the signal is received,
a portal will open
and our liberators will be here
nearly instantaneously.
(exhales)
And then we'll be free.
Watch them.
I wanted to return this to you.
You reasoned correctly
that your fellow synthetics
needed persuading.
An emotional jolt to drive them
to the decision
you wanted them to make.
To build the beacon.
I'm glad you see the
reason behind my actions.
I do.
But reason isn't everything.
How could you help that Romulan
kill your sister?
I thought I taught you
better than this.
Turns out...
you're no better than we are.
(whistles)
Ah, come on.
Move, mija, move.
JURATI:
So, how do we hold off
218 Warbirds till Starfleet
gets here?
If they get here.
Are you not answering
to build suspense, or...?
At the present moment,
Dr. Jurati,
I am trying to pilot a starship
for the first time
in a very long time,
without exploding or crashing!
If that is all right with you.
No, totally, good call.
One impossible thing at a time.
(grunting) Soji!
Please!
You don't have to do this!
Soji! Please!
You're making a mistake!
(beeping rapidly)
(beeping accelerating)
Soji!
(grunting)
COMPUTER VOICE:
Launch detected.
Attempting to acquire
weapons lock.
Drop your weapon.
Over the edge.
Step away from the console.
I'm unarmed.
Oh.
I seriously doubt that.
You know, you're rather pretty.
Or would be.
If you weren't
a disgusting half-meat.
(grunting)
Incoming warp signatures.
Wouldn't happen
to be Starfleet, would it?
ROMULAN OFFICER:
General, they appear to be
concentrated in one settlement.
Sterilize the entire planet.
(alarm blaring)
Here come the orchids.
Let's see how much time
they can buy us.
(grunting)
Sad Queen Annika.
Six years old,
and all she got for her birthday
was assimilated.
(grunts)
(beeping)
(beeping continues)
Why didn't you just
put a phaser to your head
and get it over with?
Because I still had this
to live for.
This...
is for Hugh.
(screaming)
Now might be a good time
to reveal the secret plan.
Once these orchids have had it,
there will still be
200 Romulan warships
and only one of us.
If you figure out a way
to get us out of this one,
they'll name it after you.
Picard Maneuver.
Wait, no, t-- No, that's
actually a thing, isn't it?
You made it look
like the Enterprise was
in two places at once.
It was the Stargazer,
and it was a long time ago.
It would be useless
against so many enemy vessels.
We'd have to multiply
the sensor images
and then find some way
to disperse them.
Like an ancient warplane
scattering bits of mirror
to overwhelm
a radar system.
Yeah, how the hell
will we do that?
If only we had some kind
of wacky fundamental
field replicator
with a neurocotamic interface.
(echoing):
Look at my face.
Picard, what are you doing?
Soji, I want you to reconsider
your present course of action
and power down the beacon.
You know that's not
going to happen.
I... have something
I want to give you
and your people.
And... I hope it will
change your mind.
And what's that?
My life.
Picard out.
(alert whooping)
OFFICER:
Orbital defenses
neutralized, General.
OFFICER:
Orbital defenses
neutralized, General.
All ships, target
the abomination's nest.
Ready? And they'll all have
warp signatures?
On my mark.
What is that?
OFFICER:
Unknown vessel.
Scanning now.
Ignore it.
Ready planetary sterilization
pattern number five.
Agnes, now.
Now, now!
General, there are
hundreds of them.
Reposition disruptors.
Engage them.
(metal creaking)
No!
(high-pitched ringing)
(heart beating)
(panting)
(echoing):
Picard, are you
all right?
(beeping)
Oh, no.
They have activated the beacon.
Resume sterilization
targeting pattern.
On my command.
They're here.
Admiral, you did it.
OFFICER:
General,
their flagship
is hailing us.
Acting Captain Will Riker
in command of the USS Zheng He.
And?
And it is my duty to inform you
that the United Federation
of Planets has designated
Planet Ghulion IV
in the Vayt Sector
as under the protection
of Starfleet.
According to the terms
of the Treaty of Algeron.
Too late. Our claim to this
world takes precedence.
Move aside.
Afraid not.
I have a priority request
to open diplomatic negotiations
and protection for
the inhabitants of Ghulion IV.
RIKER:
General or Commodore
or whatever
you're calling yourself,
right now I'm on the bridge
of the toughest, fastest,
most powerful ship Starfleet
has ever put into service.
And I've got a fleet
of them at my back.
We've got our phasers locked
on your warp course.
And nothing would make me
happier than you giving me
an excuse to kick
your treacherous Tal Shiar ass.
But instead,
I'm going to ask you one time
to stand down.
OFFICER:
General. Your orders?
Retarget weapons systems.
Prepare to fight.
Weapons hot, deflectors to full.
(faint trilling)
Picard?
(grunting)
(trilling stops)
I know.
(panting)
(mutters)
I have to speak
with Soji
on an open channel.
You're in no shape.
Get me some polisinephrine.
20cc.
No.
I-I...
It will only
hasten the inevitable.
Do it.
(sighs)
(exhales)
(pants softly)
Open the channel.
Now.
Picard...
Soji. Please,
power down the beacon.
Show them how profoundly wrong
they are about you.
You're not the enemy.
You're not the Destroyer.
If that doesn't convince them,
then they will have to answer
to the Federation.
The same Federation
that banned us
and threw us on the scrap heap?
If we wanted
to destroy you, Soji,
we would've joined forces
with the Romulans.
We would be training our phasers
on you right now.
We aren't. We won't.
You know why?
Because we trust you
to make the right choice.
I trust you, Soji. I know you.
I believe in you.
That's why I saved your lives,
so that you could save ours
in return.
That's the whole point.
That's why we're here.
To save each other.
♪ ♪
OFFICER: They
destroyed the beacon.
What are your orders?
Captain, it looks like the
Romulans are standing down.
Excellent decision.
Stand down from red alert.
Now prepare to be escorted
out of Federation space.
That won't be necessary.
Really, it's no trouble at all.
Will.
How the...
When I heard
you sent an SOS,
I asked for temporary
reassignment.
Just because I didn't try
to talk you out of it
didn't mean I was gonna
let you go it alone.
I'm supposed to sit around
in the woods making pizza
while you have all the fun?
Admiral Picard...
(chuckles)
...I leave this situation
in your capable hands.
Thank you, Will,
for always having my back.
I learned from the best.
I've got it from here.
I'll see you around, my friend.
Riker out.
Adieu.
(grunts softly)
JURATI (echoes):
Picard.
(exhales)
(grunting, groaning)
Doctor...
Picard!
Picard.
DATA:
Would you like
to finish it, Captain?
DATA:
Would you like
to finish it, Captain?
No.
PICARD:
I don't want the game to end.
Picard!
Goddamn it!
It's all right.
Wait, what-what's happening?
W-What's wrong with him?
His brain abnormality.
He's failing.
Uh, can't you get him
to the med lab
or a sick bay
on one of your ships?
There's no point,
is there, Doctor?
No.
I'm dropping
the transporter block.
I'll beam you guys right here.
No.
PICARD:
Ah, it's all right.
No.
PICARD:
Ah, it's all right.
It's all right.
No.
What did you just do?
I gave you a choice.
Not being the Destroyer
was up to you.
It always was.
Elnor.
Raffi.
Yes, JL? I'm right here.
You were quite right.
A-About what, JL?
JL...
(Raffi sobs)
♪ ♪
(sniffles)
You heard?
Just now.
Yeah. That's what passes
for alcohol here.
I really don't recommend it.
(grunts)
I said I would never
do it again
and then I fucking did it again.
Same.
Never again do what?
(laughs):
Oh...
Mm.
So many things.
But in this instance,
never again kill somebody just
because it's what they deserve.
Just because it feels wrong
for them to still be alive.
You?
(sniffles)
Never again let another
self-righteous,
hard-assed old starship
captain into my heart.
(chuckles)
Never again have to stand
there and watch him die.
Is there anything you could have
done to prevent it?
No. I guess there wasn't.
Hmm. Then I win.
♪ ♪
(sobbing)
It's okay.
Let it all out.
You cry.
I got you.
(both crying)
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Another damn dream.
DATA:
No, Captain.
It is a massively complex
quantum simulation.
I would imagine, however,
from your point of view,
hearing me say so
would not be out of place
in a dream you might have
about me.
If you ever have
dreams about me.
I dream about you
all the time.
Interesting.
Are you wearing the clothes
you had on when you died?
Data...
am I dead?
Yes, Captain.
Do you remember dying?
I think I do.
Something in my head
seemed to just go away.
Like a child's
sand castle collapsing.
Hmm.
I'm aware that I
was killed in 2379,
but I have no memory
of my death.
My consciousness exists
in a massively complex
quantum reconstruction,
made from a copy
of the memories I downloaded
into B4, just before I died.
You don't remember your death?
I can't forget it.
Apparently, I ended
my existence
in the hope of
prolonging yours.
That's right.
Before I had even grasped
the nature of our predicament,
you had conceived
and executed it.
I was furious.
My apologies, Captain.
But I am not certain
I could have done otherwise.
True. That might have been
the most Data thing
you ever did.
I always wished
that I could have said
I was sorry that
it was you and not me.
Captain, do you
regret sacrificing
your life for Soji
and her people?
Not for an instant.
Then why would you
imagine I regret
sacrificing mine for yours?
Ah.
PICARD:
Did you say all this
was a simulation?
PICARD:
Did you say all this
was a simulation?
DATA:
Yes, sir.
An extremely sophisticated one.
DATA:
Yes, sir.
An extremely sophisticated one.
My memory
engrams were extracted
from a single neuron
salvaged by Bruce Maddox,
and then my consciousness was
reconstructed by my brother,
Dr. Altan Soong.
I don't much care for him.
Mm. The Soongs can be...
I believe the phrase is
"an acquired taste."
Mm-hmm. Well, whatever this is,
it's wonderful to see you, Data.
To see your strange,
beautiful face.
Among the many, many things
that I regretted
after your death
was that I never told you...
That you loved me.
Knowing that you loved me
forms a small but
statistically significant
part of my memories.
I hope that brings you
some comfort, sir.
It does.
Thank you, Data.
Which is why I would like to
ask you to do me a favor.
Of course. Anything.
When you leave...
Leave?
(stammers)
I'm sorry,
I-I don't understand.
I thought this was
a simulation.
Yes, sir.
But you are not.
Before your brain
functions ceased,
Doctors Soong and Jurati,
with help from Soji,
were able to scan,
map and transfer
a complete neural image
of your brain substrates.
Do I have to go?
Yes, Captain.
Uh, you wanted me
to do you a favor.
Yes, sir.
When you leave, I would be
profoundly grateful
if you terminated
my consciousness.
You want to die?
Not exactly, sir.
I want to live, however briefly,
knowing that my life is finite.
Mortality gives meaning
to human life, Captain.
Peace, love,
friendship.
These are precious.
Because we know
they cannot endure.
A butterfly
that lives forever...
...is really not
a butterfly at all.
Very well.
I will do what you ask.
Thank you, sir.
Goodbye, Commander.
(echoing):
Goodbye, Captain.
(breathing deeply)
JURATI:
Hi, mister.
Am I real?
Of course you are.
Ah.
Tell me about this body.
This, uh... golem.
Well, it has no augmentations,
no, you know, superpowers.
I knew you wouldn't want
to have to adjust
to something new,
not after 94 years
in the same body
with the same face.
Ah.
I see.
Everything is new, though.
Everything works.
And the brain abnormality
is gone for good.
Extraordinary.
Y-You... you haven't
made me immortal?
Oh, relax, man.
Everyone was paying attention.
We took care of you.
(quietly):
Ah.
We designed
a cellular homeostasis
algorithm that should
give you more or less
the same number of years
you would have expected
without the brain condition.
Ah.
I wouldn't have
minded another ten.
Twenty?
(sighs)
Well, Dr. Soong,
I must thank you.
My gain is your loss.
But now we both
have something to lose.
I have a promise to keep.
("Blue Skies" playing)
♪ Blue skies ♪
♪ Smiling at me... ♪
It says a great deal
about the mind of Commander Data
that...
looking at the human race,
with all its violence
and corruption
and willful ignorance,
he could still see kindness,
immense curiosity,
and greatness of spirit.
And he wanted
more than anything else
to be part of that.
To be a part of...
...the human family.
♪ Nothing but bluebirds ♪
♪ All day long ♪
We are such stuff
as dreams are made on.
♪ Shining so bright ♪
♪ Never saw things... ♪
And our little life...
is rounded...
with a sleep.
♪ Hurrying by ♪
♪ When you're in love ♪
♪ My, how they fly ♪
♪ Blue days ♪
♪ All of them ♪
♪ Gone ♪
♪ Nothing but blue skies ♪
♪ From now on ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Blue skies ♪
♪ Smiling at me ♪
♪ Nothing ♪
♪ But blue skies ♪
♪ Do I ♪
It's time.
♪ See. ♪
Soji, you have
endured so much
and traveled so far
to find your way home.
Now you leave it
all behind.
I think I'm just more
cut out for wandering.
And now that they've lifted
the ban on synthetics,
I'm free to travel.
Hmm.
Me, too.
(console powering up)
Ready, Admiral?
Engage.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org