Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
BETTER THINGS
- I'm getting the worst hands.
- Me, too.
Don't say those words.
The P.C. police might show up
and arrest me for playing cards alone
with you three gorgeous women.
I think all this Me Too stuff is good.
Seeing all those horrible men
being taken down.
Lord knows I wish my daddy would be
around to get his reckoning.
Oh, things used to be so different.
I'd probably be in prison
for ten life sentences.
Kidding ! Just kidding !
I can't even joke anymore ?
Whenever a man would pinch my behind,
I took it as a compliment.
And I would pinch him right back.
My sexuality was my greatest asset.
I didn't have higher education.
I couldn't type.
And yet I got hired for every job
I ever applied to,
and I knew it was because of the way
I looked.
- Hi !
- Phil ?
- What ?
It's today.
We're not putting it off anymore.
Give me your spit.
- What is it ?
- I think it's a DNA test.
No, I don't want to. And the advances
of my co-workers were just part of it.
- Part of what ?
- Not your business.
Okay. That's fine.
Let's go. Come on.
Let's just do it today.
You guys don't mind for one sec ?
She promised me she would do this.
Spit in here.
- Stop it !
- Spit in here, it'll be fun.
No !
It does not sound fun to me.
I have no interest in some Irish
third cousin I've never heard of
tracking me down,
trying to get money out of me.
This is so annoying,
you said you would do this.
- I'm not going to do it.
- You're gonna do it.
- I'm gonna get you.
- You're not.
- Goddamn it, Phil.
- Phil. Stay.
- No !
- Phil... Stop it !
- I'm not going to do it.
Phil, you want me to chase you ?
I will chase you.
- You'll never catch me.
- You're not... Phyllis ! Phil, you...
- Mom !
- No !
- Phyllis !
- I won't.
This is silly. You are such a child.
- Phil ! Goddamn it.
- I'm not going.
Fine. I'm not letting you through. No.
Mom.
I'm taking you down.
Mom, give me your spit.
- Stop.
- What ?
Spit.
Not just one spit,
you got to fill the phone vial.
- Jesus, I may puke.
- I may puke.
Just do it.
There, go away, for God's sake.
Jesus. I better be Samoan or something
cool worth doing this for.
- Bye.
Hey, Sam. What do you call Jewish girls
that won't give blow jobs ?
Married. Ha ! Good one, Hal.
- See ? She doesn't mind.
- Oh, my God.
You're a dirty old man.
I like it.
After seeing three other doctors,
only Dr. Ballinger was able to make me
pain-free again.
Dr. Ballinger is a miracle worker.
Thank you.
What are you in for ?
Eh, wear and tear.
- I don't got a good story.
- Same.
When did your hands start to go bad ?
When I was about 78 to 79,
not too long ago.
So, what should we do ?
Oh, man.
I think I'm a little emotional.
It took me six months
to get this appointment.
- Why'd you wait so long ?
- Because you...
Anyway, I'm here now,
so I will do whatever it takes.
I know you're the miracle worker.
Whatever you want to do P.T., O.T,
supplements, steroids.
Well, this side is mild to moderate.
And this is moderate to severe.
Your hands are much older than you are.
- May I touch you ?
- Yeah.
- This hurt ?
- How about this ?
- Yeah.
Yep. Your muscles have atrophied.
Jesus !
Well, what about physical therapy ?
Won't help. Listen, I'm a surgeon,
I would love to go in there and cut,
but your hand could wind up like this.
Well, what about all the patient
testimonials in the waiting room ?
How am I supposed to function without
opposable thumbs ?
I'm sorry, Sam. The technology just
isn't here for what you've got, yet.
You are a lot younger than your hands.
Jesus. That's the first time in forever
anyone ever said I was young.
This blows dead donkey dicks.
Well, you don't need hands for that.
It's true.
Yello ?
Sam, quick thought. I spoke with my
producers, and we want to move you up.
Oh, wow. Really ?
Yeah, I can't stop thinking about you.
And then I started thinking about me.
I just got tired of being
some gun for hire, you know ?
Fuck, I'm gonna be 30 in five minutes.
- Yeah.
- You need to prepare yourself, Sam.
You're gonna wake up and be 50,
and then what are you gonna do ?
Well,
I hadn't actually thought about that.
You need to have something of your own,
right ?
Because if we don't come up with it,
then nobody else is gonna do it.
Yeah. Fuck yeah.
And I'm aware of the irony here,
that technically you're my hired gun.
That's okay. I'm okay with the irony.
But I really want you to make this your
own thing. I think you are brilliant,
and I want that Sam Fox brilliant brain
splattered all over my show.
That is cool.
Can you say how brilliant you think
I am to my daughters ?
See ? Fucking hilarious !
I am so excited. I discovered you.
I want everybody to know that you never
existed before this moment.
It's gonna be amazing. Think of some
ideas, and then we'll chat.
I cannot even begin to tell you
how excited I am about this.
Okay.
Okay, boy. Okay, boy.
Okay, boy.
Gonna get somebody to...
- Is it gone ?
- Nope.
- Why isn't it leaving ?
- It's probably just scared.
Maybe it got a letter from Hogwarts.
Mom, this is serious.
An owl in the house is bad luck.
Don't say that !
So, owls have traditionally seen
as a harbinger of death,
but they can also be a sign of change
and fertility.
So which is it ?
We should take the snake out.
- Owls eat snakes, shit licker.
- Not baby ones.
- So you want to murder a baby owl ?
- No. That ain't no baby owl.
- No, I just want to scare it off.
- You want me to go get my dad ?
I'm gonna go get my dad.
Did she just go in there ?
Why do you have a penis on the wall ?
- We have a lot of penises on the wall.
- We've lots of penises on the wall.
We should really take the penises off
the wall. It's not good with company.
Hi, I'm Duke.
I promise I'll be careful,
if you promise not to peck my eyes out.
Take the penises off the wall.
- Cool.
- Oh, my gosh. Look at its little beak.
- What ?
- You don't touch it.
With the finger oil, his mother may
kill him or not come back or something.
Mom, that's a myth. You just want to be
careful, you don't want to hurt it.
Oh, my God. Be careful.
So soft.
Little guy, we got to get you back
where you belong.
I got to, like,
call animal control or something.
- We should name it first.
- What's his name ?
- Edwin.
- Oh, my God. It's perfect.
Edwin, oh, my God.
- The softest thing in the world.
- Okay, let's get him to... because...
- Be careful, be careful, be careful.
- I got it.
- Oh, my God.
- You're, like, his mommy.
- Hi, José.
- Hey. Hi, Sam.
Hi.
Everything okay ?
Yeah. The pets are fine, it's just that
I had them take away the girls.
- Couldn't housebreak them.
- Reinita's behaving herself ?
Oh, yeah. She's the best.
I'm keeping her.
She made a list for me the other day.
All the colleges she wants to go to,
all out of state.
And she said,
"papi, if I get into these schools,
can you help pay for them ?"
What can I say to that ? I want to give
her everything, you know ?
Yeah, she's a really great kid.
Between that and her quinceañera
next month,
my wife thinks we should move
to Phoenix to save money.
Really ?
What am I supposed to do for work ?
Nothing grows there.
- You know, maybe we should team up ?
- What do you mean ?
Frankie was talking about doing
one of those...
- A quinceañera ?
- Yeah.
But aren't you guys Jewish ?
Even though I do bring you
a Christmas tree every Hanukkah.
Yeah.
No, is that weird ? Is that bad ?
They're a lot of fun. She should.
Hey, have you seen your new trees ?
Grapefruit, Meyer lemon and kumquat.
You like the pots ?
- They're so gorgeous !
- Yeah ?
Thank you, José. I love it.
- José, I'm so glad you haven't left.
- Oh, hi.
It seems you've pruned the wrong
branches on my plum tree.
- ¿Qué ? I'm pretty sure I didn't.
- Afraid you did.
- Okay, I'll go check it out, then.
- No, no, no, no.
What are you doing ?
It's not your day.
I know that, but he likes my latkes.
Come along, José.
- No.
- She made it a little weird.
Oh, my God ! That's so rude.
- Sam, I got it.
- He won't be long.
- I'm coming, Phil.
- Phil !
- Be nice !
- I will.
Is this the Meyer lemon ?
I love it.
Mom ! Mom !
Mom, can Pepper start the El Camino ?
Just, just start it.
Oh ! God, geez !
Say yes, Sam !
- Oh, God. Just don't tell your mom !
- Oh, my God !
- Your chariot, miss.
- Oh, thank you, kindly.
What happened ? What happened ?
What happened ?
Oh, okay, let me see.
Raise your hand in the air. I got you.
I got you. It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, sweetie. It's okay.
Let me just wrap it up.
- What is wrong with you ?
- I'm sorry, I can't help it.
Get a towel !
- Is it bad ?
- It's okay, baby.
No, honey, honey, just calm down.
Lay your head back.
Yeah, you just cut it a little bit,
sweetie. Yes, it's okay. It's okay.
Hey, Mom,
is it qualm with or qualm about ?
- Mom !
- Frankie, call Pepper's mom.
It's okay, honey.
Mom, Chewy's got something.
- Chewy, release !
- What is that ? Come here, come here.
Duke, Duke, where are the keys ?
Duke, where are the keys ?!
- I don't know.
- Looks like a worm or something.
- Duke !
- Pepper has them.
- Okay. Okay.
- He swallowed it.
Oh, God. Oh, shit.
Oh, Jesus.
It's okay. That's fine.
That's fine. No, no, no, no, no.
Don't look at that.
Pepper ? Pepper ! Okay. Frankie !
Good boy. What a good poop. Yes, a good
poop. Good boy. Who made a good poop ?
- Mom, where's my black dress ?
- What ?
- Like, with the neck.
- Check your closet.
No, it's not there,
and I have to go to work.
Well, I'm sorry.
I'm kind of busy 'cause I have to sift
through Chewy's shit right now,
so maybe you can just look yourself ?
Mom. That's disgusting.
Yeah, and she's probably gonna have to
put him down, too.
- What ?
- Frankie !
- He tasted human flesh.
- Mom, you can't kill Chewy !
- Nobody's killing Chewy.
- Mom, I'm gonna be late.
So wear something else.
I can't wear something else
'cause I have my period.
Max, can you just check
the laundry room,
because I'm sorry, full disclosure,
I forgot to put the load in last night.
- Sorry.
- Mom, the laundry ?
- And, Duke, no one's killing anyone.
- Promise ?
Yes, I promise. Chewy's gonna be
around for a long time,
unless that coyote comes back.
Mom, if you don't do the laundry
and we think you are, it's messed up.
I was counting on that to be clean.
So sorry.
Oh, my God.
I didn't check the laundry.
Mom, get out. Oh, my God. Nothing fits.
I'm so bloated.
I'm sorry that you feel bad, but you
have to learn to rein this shit in.
I never took my period out on anybody
the way that you do.
Sorry, Mom. Maybe I should just go,
like, lie down in my trailer, right ?
- What ?
- This is actual work, Mom.
I have to be on my feet all night.
It's not like some movie set.
Max. I know you're a little stressed
out, and this is your first job,
but that doesn't mean you get to be
super shitty to me whenever you want.
Mom, I'm not being super shitty.
You're so dramatic.
I can't believe I still have to put up
with this bullshit.
You realize you live here rent-free,
right ? You do realize that ?
Oh, you want me to go ? I'll go.
I am fucking gone.
- Good.
- The second I save up some money.
You have a paycheck.
What's stopping you ?
- You think I won't ?
- Goodbye.
Good. Your dirty dress
is in the laundry room.
My dad said I can live with him
whenever I want.
Oh, that old chestnut. Perfect.
That's great. Go, go. Great.
- Great.
You know what would be great, Max ?
If you helped me.
It would be great if you helped me.
If you cleaned up after yourself,
that would be great.
If you helped me with your sisters,
Kids aren't supposed to help their mom.
Their mom is supposed to help them.
Oh, is that the law ?
I didn't realize that I was breaking,
like, the Mommy Law.
Yeah. And great job you're doing,
by the way, Mom.
Frankie basically does
whatever the fuck she wants,
and I'm probably gonna be fired now.
Oh, yeah. I'm bad. That's bad.
I'm a bad mommy.
No, you're a disaster, Mom. And you
don't always have to be so hard,
just 'cause you don't know
what it's like to be a woman anymore.
You cunt.
What ?
You're a cunt, Max.
- I'm a cunt ?
- Yep. You're a cunt.
You're a cunt.
No, Max. You're a cunt.
- No, you're a cunt, Mom.
- No, you're a cunt, Max.
- No, you're a fucking cunt, Mom.
- You're a fucking cunt, Max.
You're a big fucking cunt, Mom.
You're a bit fucking cunt,
your sister's an asshole,
and your other sister's great.
Thanks, Mom ! Love you, Mom !
Oh, my God.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
- I am a cunt.
- No, I'm a cunt.
No. You're not. You're the best.
And I am such a cunt.
Well...
My Uncle Sid called me a cunt.
I was nine.
- Uncle Sid ?
- He's dead now.
Fuck you, Uncle Sid.
- I love you.
- And I love you.
I don't want you to move out.
But I do.
So you shouldn't.
But please move out soon.
But don't.
- Oh, wow.
- What ?
Just realized you're gonna have to go
through this three times.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org