(panting)
God damn it!
♪ Mother, you had me ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
♪ I, I wanted you ♪
♪ You didn't want me ♪
So do me a favor and wake him up a bit.
Huh?
Just, it's on him now,
so I need you to surprise him
because he's, he's too controlled now.
- Okay.
- Do you mind?
No. Totally, I, I think I got it.
- All right, good.
- Okay.
WOMAN: Okay, last looks, please.
So... it's the big turning
point now, right?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Right?
This is on you, this is real close.
We want to see this
thing hit you, right?
Yeah, I got it.
And, and... the feeling.
- Right.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, uh...
- Thanks, Kunta.
Are you, uh, above
this? Because I want to...
You're tight. You're tight.
All right, all right.
- WOMAN: All right, finishing up.
- Here we go.
WOMAN 2: All right, and
let's roll sound, please.
WOMAN 3: Rolling, rolling.
MAN: Quiet, please.
WOMAN 2: Sound speed. Marker.
Uh... Cameras are set.
Action.
So I'm really sorry.
There's nothing I can do.
You lost custody of Maggie.
Oh, my God, Maggie.
Yeah.
You're never gonna see her again,
and it's all your fault.
What?
Cut!
Why did you say that? That's...
- Sorry.
- That's, that's not in the script.
- That's not in the script.
That felt... That felt weird.
Big man, that was... That was amazing.
- Yeah?
- It's a great, great day.
(chuckles)
It's a great, great day.
You're doing... Yeah. Oh, yeah.
- Oh, okay.
- Right.
Thank you.
Hey.
How are you holding up?
I'm all right. You know, it's, uh,
- this is work, but, uh,
- Yeah.
I'm blessed to be working.
That is right.
I just want to say
I'm a fan from way back.
- I mean, you are great.
- Oh, no, no.
You are so...
You don't have to say
that, Mel, but I do.
I love your movies.
Well, I used to, too, when
they were my movies.
I know, but you're great,
and it's an honor to be
working with you, really.
Oh, thanks, Sammy.
Well, then it's only fair to tell you
that my brother and I used to say
"Oh, stop it" all the time.
Oh, my God, that's a nightmare.
No, no. Seriously,
that show killed us.
And when you did the sad episodes,
we'd both pretend not to be crying.
Aw.
Yeah, the sad shows were the best.
I don't need you. I don't need anybody.
(chuckles)
Well,
not to jerk each other off too much,
but Move Down is my Bible.
And it formed me.
- Really?
- Yeah. It did.
A little bit. It did a little bit.
Well, that's... That's all right.
DAVID: Melly Mel!
Mel, I found these,
uh, Tibetan prayer beads
over at, uh, props, and
I-I want to wear them.
Teak's, uh, Teak's going to wear these.
I know it doesn't match,
- but continuity's for pussies, right?
- Uh...
So Teak's a Buddhist
now. Right? It's cool.
- Or Hindu.
- Prayer-prayer beads?
Yeah.
He's...
(laughing)
Well... we used to
both do our own thing,
and, uh, now we're doing his thing.
Yeah, but it's good to
work with good people, though,
along the way.
Well, that's what keeps me going.
You doing okay?
Yeah. I mean,
it's hard for me being out here.
I mean, I-I need my-my
home comforts
and, uh...
living in a hotel for a month,
you know, gets old, but, uh,
Yeah, of course it does.
I'm whining.
No, no. Everybody needs to be home.
You should come to my house for dinner.
Come have dinner with me and my girls.
And my mom. Just be
with a family for a
night. You could have
some home-cooked food or
some home-ordered takeout.
Come on, Mel, we're bros.
Seriously?
Because, I mean, I
mean, I'm-I'm tempted.
Yeah, you want to come tomorrow?
Um, I could swing tomorrow.
Good. You're coming.
Tomorrow.
You bet.
Wait. I'm sorry. Was that Mel Trueblood?
Yeah.
Are you having dirty with Mel Trueblood?
Oh, my God, I love your life.
You love what you pretend my life is.
And no, we're not
doing any dirty things.
You are. You totally are.
How would I not tell you?
On what planet am I not telling you?
Okay, so you're hoping.
No.
No, he's a nice guy.
And, uh, he's also a genius.
(deep gasping)
Sunny, stop. That's gross.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry
for being gross.
Yeah. I mean,
he's cute, he's sexy.
And I'm pretty sure he's married.
Let's find out.
What are you doing? Don't.
I'm googling your genius new boyfriend.
No, no. Not while you're driving.
We're gonna get into an accident.
- I hate this!
- Dummy...
- This is nervous...
- A Tesla.
It drives itself.
Can you please put your
hands on the wheel?
This gives me a
terrible feeling in my stomach.
I hate it.
Aw, man, he's wicked married.
Okay, good.
Now you driving and
not the robot doing it.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Do you have to go right home?
Yeah, honey. I don't want to go out.
No, just come over for a little bit.
Fine.
You know, you still
could sleep with him.
Who?
Mr. Mo' Money Farouk back there.
(groans)
(quietly): No.
You just have to
promise to tell me if you do.
You promise to tell me if you do.
Pinky swear right now before
we go into the house.
I'm not gonna do it. He's married.
- Uh-huh.
- Will you make me a lemon drop?
Totally.
MAN: Hey, Sammy.
Hi, Jeff.
SUNNY: Hey, hon.
Hey, baby. Your I, uh,
deal keeps making noise.
Yeah, I know.
Can you look at it like I asked you?
All my stuff is broken.
Oh, Jesus, I'm so tired.
You know what, though? Later, maybe.
So are you wasted right now?
JEFF: Okay, eat shit.
Kidding.
You know, but eat you some shit, though.
Right? (laughing)
(laughing): What?
Baby!
(sighs)
Eh, women, huh?
SAM: Yeah.
- Right?
- Mm-hmm.
Seriously, though,
she's often a psycho.
Right, Sam?
Yeah.
I mean... (chuckles)
I don't want to preach to the choir.
No, totally. I get it.
You're awesome, Sammy.
Yeah.
Hey, seriously, for a second, though,
like, what would she do without me?
You know?
Or you, for that matter.
I mean, I know I don't have to tell you.
It's like you know...
You know her forever.
You guys go, like, way back.
Yeah. We go way, way back.
You know this.
My dad and I got in a fight, and, uh,
he kicked me out of the house,
and I was so scared,
and she took me in,
and she got me a job.
Whoa.
Yeah, she was
19, she was already taking
care of people.
She was amazing.
She was full of confidence.
She was so beautiful.
I mean, I never knew
anybody who had so much potential.
And then she met you, Jeff.
Jesus, did she love you.
Yeah.
And here's Sunny...
All right, this woman who
loves so hard and she tries so hard,
and she just ends up
pouring all of that
love into you for years.
Jeff, do you know what that's like
to watch your friend, someone you love,
someone who is like a goddess
with the power to fly to the moon
and shine a light on the world,
and she ends up using all of that power
just to keep her fat, shit,
useless, boring
stoner husband barely afloat?
It's just a shame, Jeff.
(scoffs)
Well, here's the thing.
I know that you have...
sucked your share of dicks, huh?
I've heard about you.
That's okay, buddy. Don't bother.
I don't care what you know.
Okay, well, here's the thing.
I'm gonna have to
say that I cannot believe
that you just said all of that to me.
Jesus, I'm offended.
Serious.
Don't worry about it.
You won't remember.
You know why I know that?
Because I said all of this to you
five years ago, and you don't remember
because you've smoked 10,000
joints since then,
so... good night, Jeff.
See you at the next thing.
All right, good night, Sammy.
Hello. I'm home.
Mama, you're home. I missed you.
Hi.
- Oh!
- Where were you?
Mommy had to work today, remember?
- FRANKIE: Hi, Mom.
- I told you.
Hey, come meet our guest!
Mel, this is Max,
and this little one I'm holding is Duke.
She's very small.
- Hiya, Duke.
- Hi.
Sam?
Oh, this is my sitter Lauren.
It's Mel.
Can I talk to you?
Yeah. What's up?
It's just getting really
difficult the way
your girls talk to
me when you're not here,
- and I just think that they should
learn some respect, - Oh, okay.
- And I don't know anything about...
- Okay, I have
to cook good dinner, and
so thanks for coming.
I love you. Bye.
Frankie, come here.
Mel, this is Frankie.
Hi.
Oh.
- Hi.
Hi.
Wait, one more hi.
Oh, then I got to do this again
to make it even. Hi.
Put on pants.
What?
Are you gonna marry him?
Hey, Duke?
(whispers): You need
to learn how to whisper.
Wait, so you're, like, an actor
in the movie Mom's in?
No, I'm the director.
- PHYLLIS: Hello!
- Oh.
There's my mom.
You're about to meet my mother.
Hi, Mom.
Hello, sweetheart.
Mom, this is Mel.
Mel, this is my mother Phyllis.
- Oh. Hello.
- Oh, hello, Mrs. Fox.
It's very nice to meet you.
Yes, well.
Mom, did you take our phone book?
Because I noticed all the neighbors
- have their phone books.
- No, no.
Why would I take your phone book?
I took my phone book,
which was left at your step.
No, that's mine.
I always ask for two phone books,
and they only brought one,
so the one at your step must be mine.
Mom!
I learned a piano song, come listen.
Come with me to the kitchen.
Okay, off you go.
♪ ♪
(humming "Sleeping Beauty Waltz")
I know this one.
Um, did you not tell your mother
that you were bringing home a black man?
What? Oh, no. Of course not.
That's not... No.
- I mean...
- What? No!
You should've told her.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm telling you, that's not a thing.
My mother is just insane. She
makes people feel weird.
It's like her hobby.
No, Sam.
She's over 70, okay?
You warn her that a
black man's coming over,
even if it's to fix the cable box.
Oh, my God. I'm telling you,
My mother is not like that.
She marched for integration.
It doesn't matter, okay?
I'm not calling your mother racist.
I'm calling her over 70.
You tell an old white
lady ahead of time, okay?
You warn her. It's the right thing to do
for the old lady and the
black guy coming over.
Okay. No. I think you're wrong.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm hearing you,
and I know you feel certain of this,
but I think that this is your thing.
That's not real. It's not.
Oh, yeah, we don't have a mezuzah.
- What's up with that?
- We're not that.
- Yeah.
- FRANKIE: Mm-mm! One time,
Max was going to dance class,
and she had this awful stomach virus.
- Frankie, don't tell that story.
- It was like a dress rehearsal
- for a dance concert.
- MEL: Right.
And she was wearing this white leotard.
- Okay, stop it.
- SAM: Frankie?
- MAX: Stop.
- DUKE: No, let her tell it.
- Come on. What?!
- Mm-mm.
So she misses the, the dress rehearsal.
She's gonna be
dropped out of the concert.
- MEL: Mm-hmm.
- MAX: Mom!
But she has this stomach virus...
Frankie, you can't tell this story
- 'cause we're eating.
- Oh, come on. Mom...
MAX: No! Shut up!
Frankie, you're stopping.
Fine. Fine. Fine.
- Thank you.
- Okay, I'm done.
- You're welcome.
- I'm done.
And then, right in the
middle of doing a big split,
brown poop squirted out of her butt
all over the perfect white leotard!
(laughter)
Mom!
(laughter continues)
SAM: Sorry, Mel.
We like that kind of humor at dinner.
Oh, no, no, no. It's-it's fine.
(quietly) What are you doing?
MEL: Are you, uh, still studying dance?
MAX: I do this thing.
It's-it's a modern class.
It's based on this
thing called Alvin Ailey.
I don't know if...
Sure, I-I-I studied there, actually.
You did?
Yeah, in New York when
I was in high school.
That's great that you're doing that.
Even if you don't dance, which,
you know, I gave it up when I was 19,
but you'll never regret it.
I mean, it's still a part of me.
Yeah?
Thanks.
No, you're lucky,
because when I was your age
and I was aching to be an artist,
I had to explain that to my parents.
My father was a janitor.
My mom's still a nurse.
But they didn't know from art.
You're lucky because your
mother is an artist.
Well, she's not, like, an artist.
Yes, she is. She's, like, an artist.
Well, thank you, Mel.
That's very nice of you, Mel.
The last time I was in London,
I went to Harrods to
buy pantyhose, and so,
I go to the lingerie department,
and Harrods had their
own brand of pantyhose,
and they're the only ones I wear,
and you can only buy
them at that counter.
And their hose has three colors,
Nude, White, and Nigger Brown.
That was the name of the color.
And that's the color I always buy.
So I go to the counter,
and the young woman
who was working there
happened to be black.
And I said to her, "I
would like medium-size hose."
And she says, "What color, please?"
and so I said, "Nigger Brown."
And she was shocked.
I said it just like that.
I could see she was upset.
I said to her, "I did you the honor
"of not noticing your color.
Would you do me the honor
of getting my item for me?"
So she went and got them,
and after that, I paid for the hose.
Just so you know.
Oh, I need to use the loo.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
You know, you're are really nice fimily.
Thank you. They love you,
and I am sorry about my mom.
No, no, no. Don't be
sorry about your mom.
Never be sorry about your mom.
No, Mel. I'm very
sorry about my shitty mother.
Okay, well, I don't know her.
No, you don't.
Um...
Yeah.
I...
You know, I have a friend
who is very invested in
wanting us to have sex.
Really?
She needs us to do it. It's pretty bad.
Well...
But I'm not about to get
into a thing with a married guy.
That's just not, that's not me.
Well, I mean, I'm going through
a divorce right now,
and I've been going through a divorce,
and we've been separated for months.
But I, uh, you know,
am going back to New York tomorrow.
Yeah.
And as much as my brother
would want me to throw
down with Sammy Fox, I mean...
- Hey.
- Hey. You know.
I don't know. I mean...
I mean, I like you.
But I don't want to hook up with you.
I mean, actually, I really like you.
Yeah, me, too.
I mean, there's...
No. Yeah.
...a feeling there. Uh, it's...
it's a nice feeling.
Yeah.
But me, too.
I-I'm... I don't want to...
I mean...
- No, I...
- Just like...
That's... There's your ride.
- That's my ride.
- Yeah.
Come here.
Mm.
♪ Oh, baby, in this world ♪
♪ You can't count on nothing ♪
♪ One moment it's clear... ♪
Can I just tell you this
was the first peace I've felt
in a very long time?
Same.
♪ Maybe the next one ♪
Bye, Sam.
♪ See things always changing ♪
See you, Mel.
♪ Each day some new song ♪
♪ On the radio station ♪
♪ But baby, I always ♪
♪ Will be standing by your side ♪
♪ Sure as the ocean ♪
♪ And a shoreline entwine ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org