Willard, bring in
the videocassette recorder.
Aah!
Suddenly, I realized that,
uh, I don't have a pension plan.
I don't have a health plan.
I don't have a dental plan.
I don't have--
Willard.
Willard!
Where the hell
is my blue hat?
I, uh, I don't know,
Miss Crock.
Do you expect me
to go to my 10:00 meeting
like this?
Oh, no, no.
Absolutely not, Miss Crock.
I'll-- I'll help you
find it.
I'm cold!
Taking a coffee break,
lazy bones?
All right,
this is a good job.
This is a good job.
Aha!
I should have known
it was you.
Uh, you know, Miss Crock,
you have such an appreciation
of fine clothing,
I was thinking
maybe it was time
you buy me a new uniform.
You look just fine
to me, Willard.
And you're dismissed.
But it's disintegrating.
The buttons are barely
hanging on.
Oh, Willard,
that is a terrific suit.
Your father worked
for me for 30 years.
Wore that suit every day.
Never complained.
Yeah, and then he died,
and then at the funeral,
you made the undertaker
give it back to you...
so you could stick me in it
for another 15 years.
Just what
are you implying?
Miss Crock,
it's Christmastime.
I'm only asking
for a new uniform.
Only a new uniform?
And pretty soon it'll be
only a new broom, maybe.
And before you know it,
I will be only bankrupt.
Now, would you please
get out of my sight...
before I kick you
in the ass?
It's not my fault you have
frost on your strawberries.
We have a contract.
Oh, well, then,
I'll see you in court.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I've got the Danish.
Okay, bring them in.
Miss crock,
I'd like you to meet...
Gunn Froling,
Erland Vetterlund,
Per Malmsjo
and Bertil Guve.
The executive team
from Copenhagen Snak Food.
I'm just flattered
that you're even considering
my little factory.
Ja.
Lovely output.
Oh, that's terrific, Gunn.
You are truly a great Dane.
Come, gentlemen.
I'd like to show you
the bun room.
I'm sure
you're gonna love it.
It's just past
jellies and creams.
What a bunch of bores.
I never know what the hell
those guys are saying.
Never mind about that.
Do you think
we've got a deal?
Does Big Boy
have a weight problem?
Mm-hmm.
Soon you're going to be
the richest,
prettiest, sexiest lady
in the entire pastry industry.
I've told you, Chip,
not in the office.
Hey, nothing says
Christmas eve like some
hot spicy chicken wings.
All right!
If they're so goddamn yummy,
how come you only show up
when it's free?
- Hey, there he is.
- About time.
Can you believe it?
The old prune had me
cleaning her chimney.
Oh, she thinks
Santa's coming
to pay her a visit.
Now, look here.
Be careful with this
'cause it's kind of strong.
Willard, you need to make
a new year's resolution--
quit working
for the ball buster.
Show her who's boss, man.
Take a shit in her soup.
Thanks. That's
real constructive.
You know the way things are:
a man has a job,
he holds onto it.
In your case,
till he dies of old age.
Yeah, like my old man.
You know what he said
to me on his deathbed?
He said,
"Stick with Miss Crock.
You'll get ahead."
I don't know what
he was talking about.
Merry Christmas, Willard.
Merry Christmas, Rusty.
# Good King Wenceslas
looked out #
# On the feast
of Stephen #
Oh, chip,
it's beautiful.
Now open yours.
Oh, I'm so excited.
Oh, Virginia,
what a sweet gift!
Well, I know how much
you like money.
It's $50,000.
You can buy anything
you want with it.
What are you standing
around for, Willard?
We don't want a mess now,
do we, on Christmas?
Will that be all?
That will not be all.
Merry Christmas.
Miss Crock,
I wasn't expecting this.
I thought of something,
and I knew you'd be thrilled
to death with it.
Oh, Miss Crock,
God bless you.
Open it! Open it!
You are
a good woman.
- Hey, what's this?
- Your favorite.
Mincemeat pie.
Where the hell
is my suit?
Oh, goodness gracious.
Sakes alive.
I thought you'd like it.
Like it?
Yes.
I-I put
a pair of cuff links
in there as well.
Oh, you went all out,
didn't you?
A pair of
crackerjack cuff links
and one shitty pie!
Hey. Hey, man.
What are you doing?
I thought we were going to
Leroy's Christmas kegger?
Yeah, well, Miss Crock
said I gotta spend a night
in the box.
Damn, it's like
a Filipino prison.
Get in that sweatbox!
Leave me alone!
Fine.
Uh, feliz navidad.
Oh, just in case
you get hungry.
- Beat it.
- This is my dinner.
Oh, you rat,
I'll squash you.
Come here.
Whoa.
I can't believe
I've tolerated him
for as long as I have.
He's just a user.
Willard's exploited
your generosity.
That's exactly right.
I mean, his father,
Teddy, was a nice man.
- But enough is enough.
- Really.
Well, tomorrow, we'll--
we'll fire him.
Throw his stuff
in the furnace.
Santa Claus must be stopped.
- There will be no Christmas
this year.
- You got that right.
You're not gonna
believe this.
The old grinch
is gonna fire me.
That's ridiculous, man.
Why would somebody fire
their slave?
Because she's mean.
She picked Christmas day
to do it.
Damn!
You need revenge.
Revenge!
We need revenge!
Let's kidnap Santa Claus.
We'll break into his North Pole
toy shop and seize him.
Maybe those moon men
are, uh, are onto something.
You mean we should
kidnap Santa?
Wait a minute.
Why don't we just kidnap
Miss Crock?
That's crazy.
No, that's brilliant.
We'll grab granny,
we'll hold her ass
for ransom.
And if they don't pay,
we start hacking off
her fingers.
First her thumb,
then her pointer,
then her little
nasty finger.
Hey, man, what are you
talking about?
We're not criminals.
You fry chicken,
I drive a car.
When that money
comes rolling in,
I'll go crazy, man.
I'll-- I'll laminate
my menus.
Hey, shut up, okay?
We know nothing about
kidnapping an old lady.
Hey, but
what about her dog?
You mean Biscuit?
No, Muffin.
Yeah, she loves him
more than anything
in the world.
I bet she'd pay plenty
for that old bag of fleas.
Yeah, I bet she'd pay
a million bucks.
# A million bucks
a million bucks #
Remember,
we have to be quiet
inside the house.
Miss Crock
is a light sleeper.
You ain't gotta worry
about me.
This place is nice.
What the hell
are you doing?
I'm checking for
electric eyes.
There's no electric eyes.
How do you know that?
They're invisible.
Trust me.
I've lived here
my entire life.
So, this is where
the old bitch sleeps, huh?
Shh.
Okay, give me the weenie.
Okay, Muffin.
I have a special treat
for you.
Oh, cripes.
What kind of aim
was that?
Muffin, Muffin,
bite my weenie.
Oh, the hell with this.
Plan B.
Will you shut
that dog up?
Aah!
- Shh.
- You bastard!
Oh. Mm. Shh.
Aah!
Hey, would you
keep it down?
Ow! Keep it down?
This thing is eating
my hand!
Aah!
Oh, Jesus,
this is a nightmare!
Put him in the box!
Who's smarter, huh?
Now who's smarter?
What should it say?
Um, um, we've got him.
Pay us $1 million,
or he's a dead dog!
How does that sound?
Fine.
Let's get
the hell out of here.
One million dollars!
This is the happiest day
of my life.
- Yeah, with that money,
we can do anything.
- I know what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna buy me
a four-star chicken hole.
I'll get a better
neighborhood and a listing
in the Zagat guide.
I'm gonna go someplace warm
where you don't need
layered clothing.
Start over. I got
some good years left in me.
I can better myself.
I'm gonna register
at one of them
four-year universities.
My friend, here's
to second chances.
Did you have
a lovely sleep, Muffin?
Oh, yes.
Now we'll have
a lovely breakfast,
you and--
oh, my... God!
Oh, my God.
Look at me.
Muffin, look
what they've done
to your mother.
I don't know--
"We've got him.
Pay us $1 million,
or he's a dead dog."
Who's a dead dog?
Willard? Willard!
Man, we've got
so many choices.
I'm just trying
to get out
of Pittsburgh.
You said it.
Hey, check out this, huh?
Bora Bora.
I was thinking more
like the Caribbean
myself.
Yeah, well, whichever one
has a school with a strong
liberal arts program.
Oh, my lord!
I'm dead!
We're going to jail.
What do you mean "we"?
That's my picture
on the front page.
Who would have thought
kidnapping a dog would make
the front page?
Wait a minute.
They think it was me.
They think I was kidnapped.
They-- they don't even
mention Muffin.
Ridiculous.
Why would somebody
kidnap you?
I don't know,
but they think someone did.
"There were signs
of a scuffle,
"the chauffeur's blood
was found on the wall...
and a note demanded
one million dollars,
or he's a dead dog."
Sweet Jesus!
We kidnapped a turd.
According to sources,
the missing chauffeur...
had been a loyal employee
for over 15 years.
Virginia Crock,
known for her
mouthwatering treats,
awoke this morning to news
that was not so sweet.
Do you have
any enemies?
Not that I know of.
I'm just an elderly lady
who makes pies.
Well, uh,
does Mr. Fillmore
have any enemies?
Who?
That's Willard's
last name.
Oh.
Not that I know of.
Did he have anybody
that he used to, uh,
bring around the house?
Not that I know of.
Does he have
any living relatives?
Not that I know of.
Ma'am, excuse me,
but, uh,
this man worked for you
for over a decade,
and you don't know
if he has any friends
or any relatives?
Detective, Miss Crock
has told you
everything she knows.
What are you talking about?
She hasn't told me anything.
Sir, if it
makes you happy,
you go right ahead
and find Willard Fillmore.
As for me,
it's time for my nap.
According to sources,
Fillmore moved to Pittsburgh
at the age of six.
Here's the thing.
I hardly knew Willard.
Police say if you have
any information,
call the Pie Hunt hotline
at 1-800--
How did this get so big?
Rusty, we gotta
turn ourselves in.
How? They think
you're the victim.
Shit. You have to be
really dumb to accidentally
kidnap yourself.
Wait a minute.
This is all gonna
get pinned on me!
You gotta get un-kidnapped!
You gotta escape!
The kidnappers,
they go out to dinner,
you chew through the ropes,
you get away.
Yeah, that's good.
That's good, but--
but it should be real.
Uh, there was a struggle,
and I got all bruised
and beat up.
This is an airtight alibi.
Here.
Let me help you.
Good. Good.
You like that, right?
Yeah, wait a minute.
Oh!
What?
Oh, I got an idea.
What are we worried about?
Why don't I just
stay kidnapped?
Why?
It makes perfect sense.
Instead of them paying
a million dollars
for Muffin,
they pay it for me.
Why would somebody pay
a million dollars for you?
'Cause I'm a man.
Muffin's a dog.
But he got a pedigree.
Gimme a break.
I'm better than he is.
Come on!
I'm better than a dog!
I'm five times better.
"Five million dollars."
It's repugnant.
It's like
a rising stock.
Why did he jump
from one to five?
All right now, let's see
some real emotion here.
You're kidnapped.
Let's see some tears.
I want to feel
something real.
- And action.
- Help! Save me!
Miss Crock,
I'm begging you,
please, oh!
Hey, whoa.
I got into MSNBC.
How do you plug that camera in?
I think like this.
And in a startling development
in the Pittsburgh kidnapping,
this shocking videotape
was e-mailed to MSNBC.
Help, Miss Crock, save me.
I'm begging you.
They got me
wearing chains!
I'm living in a-a cage.
Oh, they're gonna kill me.
They're gonna kill me
if you don't pay.
Oh, open your wallet,
you tight ass!
Jesus, somebody
has to do something.
Oh!
Dinnertime, dog.
They got me
eating kibble. Aah!
I don't know
how much longer
I can last.
Oh, God, Chip.
He's wearing a collar.
Oh, collars don't hurt.
He's trying to intimidate us.
Ow! What is that?
Oh, is that urine?
Oh, it is!
- It is!
- It's human urine!
Chip, we're late.
Miss Crock! Miss Crock!
Do you have a reaction
to the kibble video?
I don't--
Have you changed your mind
about paying the ransom?
Miss Crock will not deal
with criminals.
This is a police matter.
Your chauffeur was
chained up like a dog.
Don't you have any compassion?
I'll show you compassion.
Get your asses
off my property!
I'm afraid
you didn't hear me.
you didn't hear me!
Today, dessert baron
Virginia Crock reiterated...
she will not
pay the ransom.
We went to
the man in the street
to find out what he thinks.
She-- she's rich.
She can afford it.
If I worked for that
slut,
I'd tell her to
get down, get busy
on my , man.
More concerned citizens
have started a formal protest.
No more pies
if Willard dies!
Hey, is that Hillary?
Oh, she's looking good.
- Whoo!
- Rich people are no good.
I never gonna eat
her pie again.
This media blitz
is killing us.
Our sales
have dropped 50%.
Miss Crock, go to hell.
Miss Crock--
Miss Crock,
many bad things
are happened.
We thought we were buying
your wholesome
American image.
But it's terrible shock
that you don't rescue
your loyal houseman.
Sweet old lady on pie box
is now super-villain.
I'm sorry, honey.
They're playing hardball.
If you don't pay up,
they're gonna walk.
Fuck!
Of course
I'm gonna pay the ransom.
I just didn't want
to encourage those
underworld criminals.
But now I want Willard
home again with me.
The old hag
is coughing up!
Thank you, Miss Crook.
And thank you Hillary
for kicking her ass.
I'm free!
We are millionaires!
Millionaires!
Anybody here?
Hello?
Hey, what can I do
for you?
Are you Rusty P. Hayes?
Yes, I am.
Can I interest you
in my shrimp boat special?
No, I'm here investigating
the kidnapping
of Willard Fillmore.
- Who?
- You must have read
about him.
I don't read newspapers.
We thought
you might know him.
We were going through
Mr. Fillmore's belongings,
and we found this, uh,
chicken dinner special
punch card.
Oh, really.
Oh, yeah, this guy.
I was wondering
what happened to him.
He was kidnapped.
Look. When he came
in here, did he, uh,
ever do anything unusual
that would draw attention
to him?
Well, one time I seen him
eat 50 chicken gizzards
all by himself.
- Oh.
- Look, if you come across
anything that might help us,
give me a call.
Sure.
I hate loose ends,
and I want this case to end.
I was so scared, I thought
I was gonna pee in my pants.
He knows something.
He had a funny look
on his face.
Why'd you have to
tell him so much?
I didn't tell him nothing.
All I told him
was about the time you
ate 50 chicken gizzards.
That wasn't me.
That was some Chinese guy.
Oh, Fong did do that,
didn't he?
I'm telling you
we got problems.
That evil Kojak
hates loose ends.
And when they pay
and I don't show up,
that's a loose end.
He'll go nuts.
But you'll be someplace
nice, like Jamaica.
Yeah, well,
he'll track me there.
Hey, hey, wait a minute.
What if we fooled them
and made them think
I was dead?
Like, uh, like maybe
if we borrowed a corpse.
Hey, don't we know somebody
who knows somebody
who works at the morgue?
Hillary.
Yeah, Hillary used to live
across the street...
from a fat dude who was
in the army with this guy
who worked at the morgue.
Oh, I forgot
it was Hillary.
Oh, yeah, you can't
hit her up, man.
She just walked
a picket line for you.
Oh, my God!
I never thought
I'd see you again,
and here you are.
I brought you flowers.
Oh, my God.
Wow. You're such
a class act.
You get ransomed,
then you buy me flowers.
Well, I didn't
get ransomed, per se.
Did you escape?
No, I didn't escape
literally.
- Aah!
- Shit.
Where'd they go?
All right,
how did you do it?
It was really no problem.
I told her the truth,
we had a little sex,
she told me
the guy's name, Grover.
Damn. Did all that
in ten minutes.
Ooh, spooky.
Grover?
Grover.
Hmm?
Hey, what are you doing?
Get away from that.
I'm-- I'm sorry.
Oh, it's just a rock.
Oh, it's not
just a rock.
It's a pet rock.
Oh, jeez, a pet rock.
Man, I haven't seen
one of these in years.
Yeah. I just dug it out
of his colon.
- Aah!
- Oh.
Yeah, yeah,
it's still warm.
I got a whole collection.
Yeah, it's--
it's really amazing...
what you dig out of
the inside of dead people
when you cut them open.
People swallow everything.
Here's some dice.
The guy must have been
to Vegas.
Yeah, got all kinds
of stuff here.
This beautiful harmonica.
Oh, oh, don't put that
in your mouth.
This is interesting here.
Ah, yes.
You gotta go in that way.
It couldn't have gone it
this way.
He would have noticed.
A broom.
Oh.
Oop! Where'd it go?
Ooh, forget about it.
Oh, he's dead,
and then you find it.
You know, it's all kinds
of stuff like that.
Oh, this is good.
Yeah. This is a clicker.
Hey, honey,
where's the clicker?
I don't know.
Inside me.
Here. Look at this.
A perfectly good comb.
Grover, how would you
like to make $100,000?
That's a lot of cheese.
What do I got to do?
Well, I want... people
to think that I'm dead.
Dead?
Yeah, you just take
one of those dead bodies...
and dress it up
like my man Willard here,
and when they find it,
they think it's him.
Oh, oh, you think
it's that easy?
I can just take up
any old body
and give it to you?
I-I got filing slips.
My bodies are catalogued.
This is a tight ship.
Uh, why don't you
just take some old bum
that nobody would notice?
A bum? Hmm.
Come on, man. If you do it,
there's a hundred grand
in it for you.
- Will it show up on my W-2?
- No. No, tax-free.
Okay, good.
Because why should my money...
go to pave roads
and build schools?
Yeah, good point.
Listen. This is the plan.
Dump the body tomorrow night
and make sure you get somebody
that looks like me, okay?
No problem.
Piece of cake.
Now, here's
some clothes of mine
that you can put on him.
And, uh, I got
my driver's license.
You put that
in his pocket.
Yes.
And, uh,
here's some jewelry.
Jewelry.
Oh, those are nice.
Oh, whoa, whoa,
wait a minute.
Isn't this suit
kind of ratty?
Ain't it gonna be
degrading for a dead man
to have to wear this trash?
Just do it.
All right.
I'll do it.
Miss Crock,
I just want to thank you...
for agreeing
to pay the ransom.
'Cause most folks--
most folks
just don't appreciate
the work we cops do.
- Virginia.
- Hmm? What?
Willard, bring in
our guests some coffee.
Willard!
- Willard?
- What's that?
I don't know.
The cover page
is from Pick 'N Shop.
It's from the kidnappers.
"Miss Crock, bring the cash
to Three Rivers Stadium
at 10 p.m.
No cops
or the chauffeur dies."
No cops?
What if those bums
run off with my money?
Don't worry, ma'am.
That ballpark is so gigantic,
we're gonna be able to hide
a million cops in there.
I thought these guys
were smart,
but they're in
way  over their heads.
You think those cops
are gonna show up
at the stadium?
You kiddin' me, man?
It's gonna be like rush hour
at Dunkin' Donuts.
Yeah.
I'll be waiting for you
in the runway lounge.
- Don't forget.
The flight's at midnight.
- then, tomorrow,
we'll be lying
on the beach.
- Sipping margaritas.
- Smoking a fatty.
This is the most
distressful day
of my life.
Do we have to pay them
all the money?
I mean, couldn't we,
I don't know, sort of
shortchange them a little?
Virginia,
bite the bullet.
I'm sure your tax men
will figure a way
to write it off.
Hmm.
That's a lot of green.
Jesus Christ,
what the hell is the wheel
doing on this side of the car?
God almighty.
I don't know how poor Willard
ever put up with this shit.
- Hello?
- This is the kidnapper.
- How did you get my number?
- Shut up. There's been
a change in plan.
Don't go to no stadium.
I gotta go to the stadium.
You're not gonna do nothing
until I tell you to,
you smelly old bitch.
Now listen.
You meet me
at midtown park.
That place isn't safe
after dark.
Oh, cork it.
I'll see you there
in ten minutes.
Quick, get me the police!
I'm still here!
Try any more games like that,
and I'll put a bullet
right through Willard's head.
Give me the money!
Oh, you're the kidnapper.
You no-good hooligan!
You decimate my house.
You violate
my public goodwill.
And why? Why me?
What did I ever do
to you?
- Gimme the money!
- You oughta be ashamed
of yourself.
Does your mother know
the kind of work that you do?
Don't you ever
stop talking?
Gimme the money!
Gimme the money.
Now I expect you
to return Willard...
in exactly
the same condition he was in.
He was a strong worker,
and he had good teeth.
I got the money!
Ha ha!
I gotta buy Hillary
a nice dinner.
Yeah, and I'm gonna buy
my mom a new headstone.
Yeah, one with her name
on it and everything!
I got the money!
Mister.
Hey, mister.
What's in the suitcase?
- Get away from me.
- Hey, mister.
What's in the suitcase?
- Hand it over.
- Get away from me,
you little shit.
- Mister,
what's in the suitcase?
- Show us some respect.
- What's in the suitcase?
- Hand it over.
I don't like your attitude.
Ah, take a hike.
Hey!
Ow, Jesus Christ!
Harder!
- Oh!
- Zap him!
Aah!
Oh.
You can't let 'em down now.
You can't let 'em down.
Yeah, let's see.
No.
Nah. That's no good.
Hmm. Oh.
Not bad.
Uh--
Don't pay any attention
to me.
I'm just gonna take
some work home.
I'm very conscientious.
I'll-- oh, boy.
I'll go get it.
Wake up.
Where am I?
What is this?
What's going on here?
The police found you
beat up in the park.
But, of course,
those incompetents...
let the kidnappers
get away with my money.
So, I was in the park,
and-- and they got away
with the five million--
You owe me,
and you're going
to work off that ransom...
until the day
Jesus calls you home.
Just the chunk light
in spring water,
not in olive oil,
and a Diet Coke.
Got it.
Oh, there you are,
as I live and breathe.
Pittsburgh's finest.
I'm truly sorry, ma'am.
But if it's any consolation,
we had every inch
of that stadium covered.
We had snipers.
Who-o-o cares?
Would you do me a favor?
Find... my... cash.
I gotta get outta here.
Aah!
Mr. Fillmore, I, uh,
I was wondering
if I could have
a few words with you.
Sure, of course.
How can I--
how can I help you?
I wonder, Mr. Fillmore--
Mr. Fillmore--
Mr. Fillmore,
I wonder if you would, uh,
give me a description
of the kidnappers?
The kidnappers.
Well, I-I never actually
saw the kidnappers that well...
because I was, uh,
I was kept blindfolded.
- Blindfolded.
- Uh-huh.
But you were not blindfolded
on the video.
No. No, I wasn't.
Uh, no, I wasn't blindfolded
on the video, you see,
but I didn't see
the kidnappers then either
because, uh, uh, uh,
they hired a TV crew
to shoot the video.
Yeah, yeah,
we did it in a vid--
in a studio with a crew.
You got any Nuprin?
No. Why?
What happened in there?
The bozo's covering
for the kidnappers.
I really gotta
get out of here.
Where do you think
you're going?
Rusty!
Yeah, Rusty.
Where you been?
Rusty, the drop-off
did not go as planned.
Yeah, I concur,
because the plan
never mentioned...
my best friend
two-timing me.
I didn't two-time you.
Come on, man.
"I'll do the drop
all by myself,
that way Rusty
won't get in trouble."
Where's the bag of money?
Why ain't you
at the airport?
- What are you doing
in a hospital, hmm?
- A street gang took the money.
Bullshit.
You're ripping me off.
I swear to God.
It was these big muscle men
in the park.
They-- they beat me up,
and they took
the five million bucks.
They had guns and tattoos
and-- and they had those
two sticks on a chain...
that you swing
and you hurt people with.
You expect me to believe
that you were mugged?
Mugged?
It was more like a rape.
Well, not a real rape.
Look, grand inquisitor,
if you had ripped me off,
would you barricade yourself
in a hospital room
with 20 cops outside?
You make
an interesting point.
It's not imaginable
that things could be
more botched.
Oh, yeah?
What about Grover?
Oh, no.
That fruitcake's gonna be
dumping my fake body.
Hello. County morgue.
Rita speaking.
Can I help you?
I'd like to speak
to a Grover Cleaver.
I'm sorry. Mr. Cleaver
no longer works here.
Bitch, what are you
talking about?
Mr. Cleaver
quit yesterday.
He said he was joining
the super rich.
Aah!
Grover retired
from the morgue.
Too wealthy
to hold a job.
Man, we are no good at this.
We gotta stop this guy.
How? We don't know
where to find him.
Call Hillary.
Hillary doesn't know him.
She knew his name
because he was in the army
with that fat dude...
who used to live
across the street
from her.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
You're so defeatist.
Fine. I'll track him
down myself.
If you did it,
you'd probably
muck it up anyway.
The guy can't do
anything right. Oh!
Oh, d-detective.
Mr. Hayes,
what are you doing here?
Huh?
Well, I was, um,
I'm visiting--
I'm visiting my Aunt Mabel.
She's real--
she's real sick.
She got polio and emphysema.
All that shit together.
It's-- it's gonna kill her.
I swear.
She, uh, she's staying
in this room right here.
I'm gonna go say hi.
Aunt Mabel,
come give me
some sugar, girl.
I told you don't listen
to them doctors.
No!
Hey, Aunt Mabel!
Okay, you're convulsing.
You gotta relax.
All right, Aunt Mabel!
I'm gonna let you
get some rest!
Get some rest, Aunt Mabel!
All right,
give Uncle Gordon my love.
Oh.
That medicine got Aunt Mabel
real irritable, man.
She's crazy.
She's normally
a real sweetheart.
Detective!
Detective,
you're not gonna believe
what's happened.
We've just discovered
a dead body.
Oh, shit.
They found the body!
Oh, my Lord.
That dumb-ass Grover.
He's the only one of us
who follows directions.
We're going to jail.
We're gonna be somebody's bitch.
Maybe if we confess--
maybe if we confess,
they'll go easy on us.
Yeah. Yeah, maybe
we'll just get
community service.
Or maybe they'll take us
to one of those
country club prisons.
We'll talk stocks
with bankers.
- We could really make
some connections.
- You're insane.
We're gonna be
somebody's bitch.
Willard.
I have some shocking news.
They found
your kidnapper.
Oh!
You sure it was
the kidnapper?
Of course I'm sure.
They found his dead body
on the front steps
of the Quaker Wax Museum.
He was wearing
all your clothes...
and those divine
cuff links I gave you.
Any idea why the kidnapper
would be wearing your clothes?
Huh?
Um, no.
Any idea why the kidnapper
would be dead?
W-well, that kidnapping den
was a real hothouse of emotion
you know.
Anything
could have happened.
Well, let's just hope
that body isn't so ripped up
that you can't identify it.
Yep, that's the guy.
No question.
That's the kidnapper.
- That's the guy?
- Uh-huh.
That's the guy
who beat you up
and held you prisoner?
Uh, yeah, well, he was
a lot more ferocious...
back when he was,
uh, alive.
Ferocious?
He's an old midget.
Yeah, but he had
a real low voice.
You know, very intimidating.
Uh, uh,
"Put your hands
behind your head.
Get in the corner."
That's him.
I'd recognize
that voice anywhere.
Okay. Okay.
Well, in some weird, screwy way
that I will never understand,
that is the kidnapper.
I'm telling you,
this whole thing stinks.
That Fillmore
and that Hayes,
they're connected.
Yeah, well, that midget
was no tough guy.
No shit, Sherlock.
They are definitely hiding
something or someone.
Detective?
Our 1-800 line
produced an eyewitness.
Meet Edgar Kettle.
He saw the drop.
Yeah, I saw
the whole thing.
The whole  thing.
Last night, I was in
my check-cashing store.
I look out, and I see a man
toss a body onto the steps.
- What kind of man?
- Oh, he was ugly.
Real ugly.
Get me the sketch artist
in here right now.
This case
is about to break.
#
That looks just like me.
"Wanted. Crock kidnapping."
Make this go away.
Make this go away!
Oh!
I'm screwed!
Willard,
take away my salad plate.
I'm ready for
the second course!
Yeah.
"Stick with Miss Crock.
You'll get ahead."
Apologize to the man!
Apologize for what you did!
I'm sorry for misbehaving
in the park.
You better be!
This is the man
you wronged, Tito?
Now, give him back
what you took from him.
Here it is, mister.
- I didn't even open it.
- That's 'cause you couldn't,
liar!  It was locked!
Soon as I noticed the address
on the luggage tag,
we drove it straight over her.
Oh.
Uh, thanks.
Come on!
Your hide has an appointment
with my hand!
Whoo! Yeah!
Let's party!
"Willard,
clear my salad plate!"
Yeah, well, lick me,
you old bag!
Your busboy's gone to Bermuda!
We're going to Bali,
so I can date her.
- Yeah!
- Get some Bali booty.
# I'm gonna get
some Bali booty #
Hurry up!
Come on!
Hey! You can't park there!
That's a tow-away zone!
We ain't never comin' back.
Go park it up your ass.
Whoo-hoo!
Excuse me.
We'd like two tickets to Bali.
First class.
- And how will you be
paying for that?
- Oh, that's a good question.
That hadn't really
occurred to us, really.
Well, I don't know.
How about this?
Cash!
Uh-oh.
Oh.
- Don't worry, we got money.
- Back off there, lady.
There's no money!
Oh!
There's no money.
Miss Crock double-crossed us!
The old crow never paid!
She didn't care
if I lived or died!
She just ransomed me
with cabbage!
The white zone is for...
the immediate loading
and unloading of passengers.
I told you
not to park there.
She double-crossed us.
We'll triple-cross her.
But this time,
we'll kidnap Miss Crock...
like I said we do
in the first place.
Nah, man, it's over.
Hey, listen, sorry
I had to leave so, you know,
quickly the other day.
That's all right, speedy.
I know you had a crime wave
to get to.
So what do you need tonight,
dynamite? Nitro?
A getaway driver, maybe?
No, no, no.
None of that.
Our gang's gone straight.
All I need now is a--
a new life.
Willard, answer the door.
Willard!
Oh, God.
Honest to God, he kills me.
His father never would have
goofed off like this.
He's never around when--
I'm coming!
- Who the hell are you?
This is who the hell I am!
Huh?
I'm wanted by every cop
in Pittsburgh!
I don't even know
what I did wrong!
Oh, my God.
You're the son of a bitch
who's got my money!
What money?
I never got no hundred grand.
A hundred grand, my ass!
- It was five million big ones!
- What are you, batty?
The deal was for
a hundred thou.
What deal?
You ripped me off!
Oh, yeah?
Good shot, huh?
Would you get the hell
out of my house?
No!
Where's Willard?
No, no, no.
Wh-where's Willard?
Where is he?
You want Willard?
I'll get him. Please--
Don't-don't do that to me!
You think I'm stupid?
I'll get him! I'll get him!
You sons of bitches
ain't ripping me off no more!
Holy shit!
- Go on!
- Oh, my God!
Help me!
- Oh, Jesus, Mary and Joseph!
- Come here, sweetie pie!
- Oh, God!
- I got ya!
I got ya.
Watch your head.
Come on!
Muffin!
Muffin, attack!
Nice doggie.
Please, attack!
Come on, lady!
Miss Crock,
I got news for you!
I'm quitting!
Miss Crock,
where are you?
Hey, Miss Crock!
I got some news
for you, whore!
I'm packing up and
moving out of this dump!
That's right, you heard me!
Good-bye, pie hag!
Where's she at?
Oh, my God.
Grover stole my idea.
Virginia! Where are you?
We're late.
Virginia,
the party starts at 9:00.
Are you ready?
Hey.
- What's going on here?
- W-w-w-we were just
turning down the sheets.
- Where's Miss Crock?
- Huh?
Who are you?
What's that note in your hand?
What'd you do that for?
I was scared.
- What do we do now?
- Run!
This is so bad!
Oh! Jesus forgive me!
Help. Police.
That stupid Grover!
What kind of kidnapper
uses his own stationery?
You know they're gonna
catch him.
And when they do,
he's gonna blab all about us!
Oh, my God!
They're hunting us down!
Stop! This is the police!
- No shit!
- Let's jump that fence!
I'm gettin' a charley horse!
I gotta start workin' out!
Freeze!
You're under arrest!
Details are sketchy,
but in a twist
stranger than bizarre,
Miss Virginia Crock herself
has been kidnapped.
Oh, my God.
Snowball, baby, let me in!
Open up!
Have you heard the news?
Yes, I know.
It's terrible.
Roger,
what are we gonna do?
I don't know.
But this is not our fault.
You said it wouldn't
hurt anyone!
You said if we switched
the ransom money with cabbage,
nothing would happen.
The kidnappers would be stuck!
All I meant was they couldn't
complain to the police.
Yeah!
Now we've pissed them off!
You deserve that money.
She's been a figurehead
for years.
Oh, stop it!
You're the only one that's been
holding that bakery together.
I had to.
She's out of her mind.
Exactly.
So, why don't we just
let the kidnappers keep her?
Get me out of here!
I was framed!
I got a medical condition!
All right, Fillmore.
Time to talk.
My dick hurts!
I want the truth.
Now, what's your connection
to Rusty P. Hayes?
I've known Rusty my whole life.
Our mothers were in
church choir together.
I don't even know this
chauffeur guy, all right?
The first time I seen him
was in my restaurant
two weeks ago.
Last night, like every week,
I called up Rusty...
and I told him to come over and
watch Monday Night Football.
Last night was Thursday.
Oh.  Yeah.  I'm sorry.
It wasn't Monday Night Football.
It was Oprah.
Last night, I get this call
to make a delivery...
to this Wilbur guy.
- So--
- You mean Willard.
Yeah, right, right.
Willard.
So anyway,
I drive up to this mansion
in my chicken delivery truck.
You know your truck
was impounded at the airport
earlier that day?
It was?
Oh, yeah, right, right.
No, I was on foot.
Anyways, the doorbell rings,
and it's the kidnappers!
So, so, uh,
they started chasing us.
And then Miss Crock,
I remember she showed up.
She ran in, and she'd
just been-- just been taking
a bath, so she was nude.
Of course, naturally,
this upset everybody.
Gunshots started goin' off, man.
The windows was explodin'.
I heard screamin'.
So I run to my truck
as fast as I can.
I mean, I run away...
because I was scared.
Chip Oswald says you hit him
over the head with a desk lamp.
Huh?
No, no, he's mistaken.
He's mistaken.
That-that was not me.
So Rusty's got this desk lamp,
and he's beating the hell
out of Chip.
And, uh, he's pounding him
and pounding him.
So I say, I say,
"Rusty, that's not
the kidnappers.
That's Chip!"
That's when the cops showed up
and they distracted everybody,
and, uh,
the kidnappers got away.
One final question.
Let's forget
all this other crap.
Where is Miss Crock?
- I don't know.
- Who is Miss Crock?
Come on. Open your mouth.
Come on.
You want some food, Blackie?
Come on. Eat some dinner.
Yum, yum, yum.
Come on. Eat it, Blackie.
It's good. Look.
Come on, Blackie.
His name is Muffin.
It is not Blackie.
Hey, shut up!
The dog's name
is whatever I say it is...
until somebody takes you
off my hands.
The sooner the better, poopy.
The sooner the better!
Yeah, go on.
Help!
#
That's my favorite TV program.
We're gonna watch it, Blackie.
This is it.
Ooh, look at that.
Look at that.
See that?  Hmm?
Hawaii Five-0.
What do we got, Danno?
Klaus Marburg.
West German passport.
How bad?
Pretty bad.
Went right through him.
Any witnesses?
Yeah, lots of them.
- Only one shot?
- Just one.
He was hit just after
he stepped off the ramp.
Steve, take a look.
Finished.
What is your obsession
with that guy?
Hey!
It's Jack Lord!
I'm the vice president
of his national fan club.
Clam up, will ya?
Hey, what are you, crazy?
The show's not over yet.
Give me that.
- Excuse me. May I have
your attention, please?
- Oh, my God.
I am pleased to announce that
Miss Crock's bakery...
is now merging with
Copenhagen Snak Food.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Additionally,
in accordance with Miss Crock's
established policy
regarding kidnapping,
we will not pay the ransom.
I know Miss Crock
will be proud of us
standing behind her like this.
Hey, wait a minute.
I'm gonna get screwed
on this deal.
That's two dozen anthuriums.
What?
What did I do?
Oh, Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
I swear I'm innocent!
No! No, please! Don't!
Who's the crybaby?
We just busted the guy.
He was trying
to pass the marked bills
from the Fillmore kidnapping.
Well, what do you know?
The brains
behind the operation.
Hey, get me
Fillmore and Hayes!
Whatever you do, don't
tell them about Grover.
Why not?
Because things are bad enough
without us getting blamed
for killing that old midget...
at the wax museum.
Maybe we should just
tell them the truth.
Yeah, right.
Like they're gonna believe
this all started 'cause
we kidnapped Muffin's turd.
There you are.
Get in here!
Sit down!
All right, the days
of dicking Dewey are over.
We found the kidnapper.
Your partner extraordinaire
is in our custody.
So tell me all about Roger.
Who?
Oh, no.
You can't play
those games anymore.
We nailed him with
marked bills.
All that
five million
was traceable.
What five million?
Miss Crock never paid.
What do you mean,
she never paid?
Uh-- uh--
I-I-I don't know.
You just said
Miss Crock never paid.
What do you mean,
she never paid?
What do you mean?
- I didn't say that.
- You did say that.
I just heard you say that.
You said that.
You said
Miss Crock never paid.
I didn't!
- I wanna know
what you meant by that.
- I don't know.
What did you mean by that?
What did you mean,
Miss Crock never paid?
What did you mean by that?
What did he mean by that?
What the hell are you doing?
That man's a cop!
I was scared.
Every time you're scared,
you hit a guy
with a desk lamp!
I'm gettin' out of here.
Who gave you
the marked money?
I don't know!
It was change
in a restaurant.
If you don't tell us,
you're spending three years
in hard labor.
It was Chip Oswald.
Hey!
Come on!
Willard, this is a cop car.
Should we really be taking
a cop car?
I'm gonna kill you!
Put your ass to the gas!
Go! Go, go, go, go, go!
Where are we goin'?
I don't know!
Oh, shit. We're not
making things any better.
We gotta find
Miss Crock and Grover
and clear this whole thing up.
How are we gonna do that, man?
We don't know nothin'
about the guy.
We don't know where he lives,
how to reach him.
He's a complete mystery.
Hold on.
I got an idea.
Directory assistance.
What city, please?
Pittsburgh.
Grover Cleaver.
Is that a business
or residence?
Uh, residence.
Is that Kleaver with a "K"?
No, with a "C,"
like cupcake.
Thank you.
Press 1 to be connected.
Got it.
#
Aloha. You've reached
the Jack Lord fan club.
- I got the Jack Lord fan club.
- The who?
- For membership, send $25...
to the Jack Lord fan club.
Attention: Grover Cleaver.
Wait!
It's Grover!
He lives at
910 Mabley Terrace.
Mabley Terrace?
That's a shitty neighborhood.
Damn it!
Turn around!
Hey, we got away!
As you can see
from our skycam,
they are traveling in
a stolen police car.
Again, to recap for
those viewers just tuning in,
less than 15 minutes ago
the two key suspects
in the Crock kidnapping...
escaped from
a downtown police station.
We'll stay with this story
until its conclusion.
#
Hi!
Here we go.
I got it all.
Here it is.
One box of Fixodent.
One bag of prunes
for the old chute.
And four pounds
of lamb and rice...
dog chow!
- That's for you.
- Where's my Bengay?
You forgot my Bengay,
didn't you? You know
my muscles get sore!
"You know how sore
my muscles get."
Zip it, you nag!
I wish I never met
that dang chauffeur.
Come on.
The first rule of life,
Blackie:
never do no favors.
You call kidnapping a man
doing him a favor?
I didn't kidnap that guy.
He kidnapped himself.
What did you say?
Hmm?
Uh-oh.
You ain't gonna
take me alive!
Grover!
Jesus Christ!
Why is he shootin' at us?
He thinks we're the police!
Grover, we are not the police!
We are not the police!
Oh, yeah! Tryin'
to fool stupid Grover, huh?
I'll show ya!
Grover!
Grover, it's us!
Don't shoot!
Oh, it's you guys.
Come on up!
Hurry up!
Any word yet on that car?
Yeah, it's been spotted
on Mabley Terrace.
Mabley Terrace?
Ah, Jesus.
I'm gonna need some backup.
Let's go!
Grover, you have to let
Miss Crock go, man!
Grover!
Too much shit's goin' on.
No way!
I'm out 18 bucks
for groceries.
What?
All right. Look,
here's a twenty, all right?
Yeah!
I can't break no twenty.
Keep the change!
All right.
- Miss Crock,
we're here to rescue you.
- How dare you kidnap yourself!
Oh!
You tried to swindle me?
I am going
to have your ass!
- Miss Crock, I'm sorry.
- What nerve!
After all I've done
for you.
I was under a lot of pressure,
and-and I--
After all you've done for me?
Oh! Oh!
Willard Fillmore,
the building is surrounded!
What exactly, Miss Crock,
did you ever do for me?
I've been your slave
for 15 years!
I worked my butt off!
And then when I got kidnapped,
you wouldn't even pay
the ransom money!
Well, after all, you--
you were just
a hired servant.
Hired--
Well, does a hired servant
watch TV with you
when you're lonely?
Does a hired servant
read to you that time
you broke your glasses?
Does a hired servant
visit you in the hospital
when nobody else does?
I did everything
my father would've.
Mmm--
not everything.
Hmm?
Your father was, uh,
a very special man.
He provided...
extra services.
Oh, my God.
Your dad didn't say,
"Stick with Miss Crock.
You'll get ahead."
He said,
"stick with Miss Crock
and you'll get head."
Would you butt out?
We're talking here!
Yuck! Oh!
Let's move!
Move, move, move, move, move!
Can you see them?
I think they're on
the third floor.
Oh, man!
That's why I couldn't
compare to my dad?
Oh, now, now, now.
Don't be silly.
It's just that your father
was... very gifted.
Oh!
- That's some big shoes
to fill.
- I don't wanna hear this!
Man, you must've been
a total letdown.
No wonder she ransomed you
with an empty suitcase.
That suitcase wasn't empty.
I paid every cent.
Oh, yeah?
Then why do Roger and Chip
have the money?
Roger and Chip?
Wait!
Stop! Don't shoot!
They're stupid and confused!
Position! Move out!
- I'm goin' in.
- Come on!  Come on!
I can't believe it.
I can't believe
Chip shafted me.
you came through.
Beaver team, move in!
Go, go, go, go!
Ooh! It's like
an army out there.
I'm on parole for mail fraud.
I gotta hide.
Grover!
How'd you get in there, man?
I mean,
Come on, Grover!
I-I-I took care of
all of Chip's gambling debts.
Grover!
I-I-I paid for all
his methadone treatments.
I guess we both
got the big screw.
Come on, Grover!
Don't move!
Hayes and Fillmore,
you're under arrest again
for the abduction
of Virginia Crock!
And this time,
it's gonna stick!
You clod.
They didn't kidnap me.
They rescued me.
If Willard hadn't shown up,
I'd be dead and buried
in this hellhole!
I don't understand.
Then who's the kidnapper?
#
First, I wanna upgrade
the assembly line.
Toss out mincemeat.
Ooh.
Bring in vanilla custard.
Ahh!
Then I'm gonna mix strawberry
into the rhubarb.
Muffin?
Freeze!
You're under arrest.
Chip Oswald,
you are hereby apprehended
for the kidnappings of Willard
Fillmore and Virginia Crock.
That is ridiculous!
How dare you!
I demand you leave my house!
Put on your pants.
You're goin' to jail.
All right, let's keep
them hands behind your back.
Oh, my God!
It's the new Village People.
You're all crazy!
- Put down that gun!
- I'm not goin' back to prison!
What do you mean "back"?
Up yours!
I've got nothing from all
of those years of suffering,
working for you!
- Chip, nobody  does.
- Stay out of this!
I'll see you all in hell!
I'll slice you
and I'll dice you...
and I'll bake you all
into meat pies!
Well, it's an ugly ending,
but the case is solved.
I knew he was the kidnapper
the whole time.
Never trust a black man
named Chip.
This is so beautiful.
I can spend
the rest of my life here.
Yeah.
And we found a place where
almost everyone speaks English.
Oh, there's my juicy,
succulent chicken.
Come here.
- How's business, baby?
- Great, Rusty.
You guys got a package.
Huh? Oh.
Oh! Hey.
Look.
It's from Miss Crock.
What did she send?
Wow! Check it out.
It's an Armani suit.
And there's a letter.
Dear Willard,
I hope you're enjoying
your retirement money.
Here's a suit you can wear
when you graduate from USC.
Back in Pittsburgh, I decided
not to sell the company.
And I have a new man
in my life.
Grover's quite special.
He's a little slow,
but he does what he's told.
So, thanks again
for introducing us.
Your everlasting friend,
Virginia.