Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Come on, break it up! Break it up!
- Break it up!
- That band geek's a psycho.
He just hit me with his tuba.
Take him to the nurse.
What's gotten into you?
He called me Tuba Turd.
So you bashed him in the head
like that? Look at him!
What's your mom going to say?
She told me to.
Sure, she did.
Come on. Let's go find her.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Mr. Levine?
Mr. Levine!
What's wrong?
Why aren't you moving?
What's happening?
Dad, wake up.
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy?
Hello.
What's happening?
Don't worry, child.
He'll be all right.
What's wrong with my dad?
Well, what's happening right now,
to your father, and to all of them...
They're going to think
differently when they wake up.
They're going to believe
in all the right things.
All the things they should.
They're going to become
better people.
Good people.
My dad's already a good person.
You'll see.
Pat?
Pat! Pat, wake up!
Court?
Courtney? Your mom's not moving.
Oh, don't you worry about
Ms. Barbara.
In less than 30 minutes,
Brainwave's reprogramming
will be complete...
and permanent.
Courtney's mother will become
a part of our new society.
Our New America.
Like everyone under
Brainwave's little spell.
Unless of course, Ms. Barbara is
one of those unlucky "one-in-fours" that
pushes back too hard,
or for too long.
While they do that,
their entire nervous system
will shut down.
- Mr. Levine?
- Oh, my God!
- They'll expire.
- Mr. Levine!
Poor things.
Dad?
Here, Pat, it's me!
It's Courtney!
Your daughter.
Ever since we came to Blue Valley,
you've been there for me...
every time I needed you.
I need you now, Pat.
I really, really need you.
- What's wrong with him?
- Brainwave's got him.
Remember, Justin,
you are the Silent Knight!
The Shining Knight.
Well, I don't know.
Chuck. If Brainwave's broadcast
is affecting every adult,
why not the bad guys?
I'd theorize they're wearing
a signal-blocking earpiece
of some kind,
protecting them
from the broadcast.
Okay. Can we mimic
the blocking signal somehow?
I'm afraid I'd need to examine
one of the earpieces to do that.
Beth, Pat's fighting
Brainwave's control!
What? No,
that could kill him, Court!
We need help, Beth.
I know! I know!
I hear you, guys!
Wait.
I hear them.
Chuck! That's it, I hear them.
When I was under Cindy's house,
I couldn't hear anyone.
Can we see if there's
some kind of signal blockers,
like those earpieces,
down in the tunnels?
Great thinking, Beth.
I've located several frequency blocking
systems within the tunnels below.
They're currently off.
Because they know
we're down there.
But, if we can turn
the blockers back on,
we could free Pat and Justin!
You think you can break into
my security system that easily?
He's correct,
Beth. It's proving difficult.
Every time I break through one of
his firewalls, he puts another one up.
It's a stalemate.
If the Gambler's so focused
on keeping us out,
maybe we can divert
his attention elsewhere.
What else can we
hack into, Chuck?
Hmm. How about we target what the Gambler
cares about more than anything else?
What's that?
His money.
What?
I've accessed his various
bank accounts, both onshore and off.
Hey.
- Get out of there!
- I volunteer every Christmas
for the American Red Cross,
but there are so many
worthy charities.
Why pick one?
Stop it!
No!
Stop!
Get out of there!
With the Gambler
occupied, I've accessed
the frequency blockers
in the tunnels.
I can't keep them on very long,
but even a momentary
interruption in the signal
should disconnect
Pat and Justin from Brainwave.
Something's wrong.
Courtney?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
- Let's get to the machine.
- Court...
I heard you.
Every word.
I meant every word.
Let's go.
Is he back to normal?
I'm free to slay the dragon.
His normal.
Great job, Beth. Let's go.
It wasn't me, Rick.
It was my best pal, Chuck!
It was a team effort, best pal.
But we aren't
out of the woods...
Courtney, your mom's still
under Brainwave's control.
And if we don't
destroy that machine,
your mom could still die.
Millions could.
Jordan? The Justice Society,
those kids!
I know, Steven. They're here.
But, perhaps it's for the best.
Alert the others.
We'll take care of them,
once and for all.
After we take out this machine,
I'm going after Grundy.
I'm going to rip that vault door open,
and I'm going to kill him.
You really think
that's gonna help you?
Yeah. I sure as hell do.
Why?
Because I'll know that that
thing won't hurt anyone else.
It won't make another orphan.
- But killing is wrong.
- Says who?
God?
Yes.
Then God shouldn't let
bad things happen.
Like my parents
being thrown into a tree.
So don't try and stop me,
Yolanda.
It's empty.
Where has the dragon gone?
Court, no one's here.
Yeah. Everyone okay?
- All good.
- Aye.
So, where's this machine?
Uh...
According to the map,
it's through there.
Look what we got here.
That's as far as you go.
No more ice mask, Jordan?
I've got nothing
to hide anymore, Courtney.
Anyone else have deja vu?
I do. Wasn't that a fun night?
Time to kill the JSA again.
How 'bout some reinforcements?
You only came back
to die, knight.
One of us will today,
there is no doubt!
You shouldn't have
locked me up...
Daddy.
Don't.
Rick!
Get to the machine, Courtney!
- But, Pat...
- I've got Grundy! I'll protect Rick!
Go do what we came here to do!
I got it.
Court!
Go!
Gambler, loop my signal
for the next five minutes.
It will continue the
reprogramming until I return.
Where are you going?
To help kill these children.
Jordan,
Brainwave's left the machine.
You need to find that
horrible little girl
and stop her
from using those goggles
before she takes control
of our whole damn system!
Jordan! It won't matter what
happens down there if she gets in!
I'm on my way.
Wait, wait! Yolanda!
Henry?
Henry!
We need to get out of here.
My dad...
- He's coming.
- What?
What, I don't understand.
The cave-in didn't kill me,
my dad didn't either.
I've been hiding,
wearing these clothes for days.
Pretending to be one of them.
I know where my dad is,
and how we can stop him.
You...
You remember what I said?
How I was sorry for everything?
- Yeah.
- You're all I've been
thinking about
this whole time.
Okay. What's...
What's the plan?
Where are your friends?
They were Henry's friends, too.
I watched Henry die.
And now,
I'm going to watch you die.
My turn.
I don't have time for this.
Yolanda!
Oh, my God.
- Yolanda...
- I killed him.
What?
I know it's wrong,
but I did it.
I think the machine's over here.
Come on.
- Oh, my God!
- Whoa!
Staff, this is where
you come in.
What are you gonna do?
What do you think? Blow it off!
- Run!
- Go, go, go!
It's okay,
I'm right here. It's okay.
Love you so much.
Are you okay?
Mrs. Whitmore? Mrs. Whitmore?
Mmm-hmm?
Beth?
You! You have no idea
what you've done.
Courtney?
- Jordan's here.
- Mom!
No more Dr. Mid-Nite.
Beth?
Beth, please help me.
Chuck?
Beth?
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Barbara...
- She's in trouble.
- I heard.
Go save your wife.
Pat, you don't need
the damn robot! Go!
I've got five minutes left...
and it's all for you!
Beth.
He killed Chuck.
Where is my mom?
I want to show you
something so you'll understand.
Look! Look at what I made.
Do you remember what this town was
like before I came here? It was dying.
We brought it back,
better than it ever was.
That's what all of this is,
to help people. I just...
I wanna help people.
Tell that to Joey Zarick
and his parents.
And to Henry King.
Over half a million Americans die
from cancer every year, Barbara.
Every year.
What if I told you it would take
a half a million lives right now,
but I could cure cancer?
Forever.
What would you do?
No one was going to die
because of the way people think.
Yeah, but they do. My wife died
Because of greed and politics,
but I can change that.
And it's not too late. It's not.
I can still save America,
Barbara.
It doesn't have to be today,
but I can do it.
And you could help.
And Courtney could.
I can protect her
from the others. I can.
I can keep her safe,
and we could go somewhere.
We could go somewhere else,
and we can start again. We can start anew.
You're out of your damn mind.
Your wife would be horrified
to see the person you've become.
You didn't know my wife!
I will succeed, Barbara.
Look at me!
I will succeed
and I will kill your daughter,
and your husband for what
you've all done.
I want you to think about that
on the way down.
- No! No!
- Hey, Jordan!
You wanna kill me?
Well, here I am.
What are you doing up here, Pat?
You got no powers. No STRIPE.
I'm here to protect my wife.
With what exactly?
Our daughter.
Damn you! Fight back!
Fight me!
You stupid animal.
You stupid animal!
Go on! Get outta here!
And never come back!
You spared the beast.
Whatever. My hour was up.
Let's go!
Court!
I won't let you stop me.
Beth?
- Rick, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Where is Yolanda?
Oh, no.
Courtney?
You can never save America.
You're filled
with too much hate.
Barb!
Gotcha.
You saved my life.
Just returning the favor.
Does this mean I get to be
in the JSA?
Oh, I like it.
Huh. Huh.
Look at that.
It's like it never
even happened.
Not really.
You okay?
Yeah.
Hey.
We'll fix the goggles, Beth.
Somehow we'll fix them.
It's not them, Courtney.
It's him.
It's Chuck.
Well, then, we'll get him
up and running, Beth.
Okay?
Right, Yolanda?
Yeah, sure.
Why you taking all this junk?
This is all I have for now.
I came to Blue Valley
to slay that dragon.
But I didn't do it.
I did nothing.
Hey.
You helped us figure out
what was going on here.
And you helped us stop
the Injustice Society.
You know that?
Besides...
there'll be other dragons
to slay, Justin.
- Other dragons?
- Oh, yeah.
There will be, won't there?
Starman, he'd be
so proud of you.
Of all of you, he would.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go
and find my horse, dear lady.
Any other soldiers, I think.
Hey, let me know
if you find 'em.
I'd like to see 'em again.
Aye.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
Until the next battle, Stargirl.
Until the next battle.
- Everything okay?
- Seems to be.
At least as far
as anyone can see.
I wonder what the rest of the
world's going to think happened here?
They always come up
with a story.
Who does?
The National Weather Service
confirmed
that it was an earthquake
that struck Nebraska yesterday.
This tremor ultimately caused a
malfunction in a weather satellite.
Government officials say that
the satellite has been fixed,
and an event like that
recurring again is impossible.
Oh, Jordan,
I told you it was folly.
I see you in there.
Eclipso.
Peanut butter cookies.
Wow! Those look so great.
- Make yourself at home.
- Thank you.
And, uh,
I'll be checking in on you.
Not too many sprinkles.
Barb will freak out.
Thanks, honey.
- That's a great sweater.
- Thank you.
Oh.
Mike, how you doin'?
You getting enough vegetables?
- Oh, yeah.
- This looks so good.
No! This is the last straw,
damn it!
Mike!
Golly, gee,
Buddy! Stop!
♪ Rock the night away ♪
♪ Jingle bell time
Is a swell time ♪
♪ To go gliding in
A one-horse sleigh ♪
♪ Giddy-up, jingle horse
Pick up your feet ♪
♪ Jingle around the clock ♪
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
Everything's great.
I just...
What is it?
Something I've been waiting
to give to you for a long time.
Now?
World's greatest Dad.
I love it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas, Pat.
Merry Christmas, Court.
Yeah!
All right, Whitmore-Dugans,
let's do this.
♪ Where's the silver lining? ♪
♪ I wake up to the sound To the
sound Of the whole world crying ♪
♪ You hear it long enough
Long enough ♪
♪ And your hope starts dying ♪
♪ Got a million things to do
What's the point In trying, trying? ♪
♪ I'm trying anyway ♪
♪ I'm gonna be
Grateful every day ♪
♪ Make a little way
Then we'll ride it ♪
♪ I'm gonna keep
Shaking off the shame ♪
♪ Make a little way Yeah,
we'll shine it Shine it ♪
♪ Shine it on ♪
♪ You'll never get a halo ♪
♪ Don't look like heaven But
you're always Gonna be my angel ♪
♪ 'Cause there may be
Nobody gold ♪
♪ But that's okay, though
Okay, though ♪
♪ That's okay, though ♪
♪ We'll keep on rising ♪
♪ Never gonna stop ♪
♪ Yeah, we'll keep on shining
Shining, shining, shining on ♪
♪ I'm gonna keep
Shaking off the shame ♪
♪ Make a little way
And we'll shine it, shine it ♪
♪ Shine it on ♪
♪ Shine, shine it on ♪
- Can I help you?
- I'm looking for Pat Dugan.
He doesn't live here. Moved.
Months ago now.
Any idea where I can find him?
Who are you?
I'm an old friend.
Name's Sylvester Pemberton.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org