- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Previously on
The L Word: Generation Q...
- Yay!
- I told you!
I love seeing you like this.
- I'm in.
- You know who's mean?
- Who?
- Dani.
She processes everything alone.
I mean, how do I get
her to open up to me?
Milner's team bought
up a ton of airtime.
I'm hearing that it's going to
be a negative attack campaign.
Your job is to help me shape my message
and get it out into the world.
There are a lot of voices in the room.
So, I would like to make some changes.
Quite frankly,
we don't know if there
will be a next season.
We need a viral video.
Are you ready to hear
your baby's heartbeat?
Oh, my God.
Today was really hard.
I didn't feel anything.
Aren't you scared just a little bit?
No.
You were wondering if I could
get over the whole priest thing.
Well, I can, because
you're not a real priest.
You have deep wounds.
And I don't know who hurt you,
but somebody did.
I can't really talk right now.
I'm at your sister's engagement party.
Faith's getting married?
Have you told that sweet boy
that you love him yet?
'Cause he loves you, too.
They were fucking, Shane!
Throuples are complicated, Al.
I don't want to lose her.
You know, we've spent
the last few days, Gigi and I,
really getting into our issues.
I'm so glad I could be
there to help push you guys
towards hashing out your divorce.
- So, I'm gonna go.
- What happened?
- Oh, my grandma fell.
- Come here. Come here.
I think you should have
been there for her today.
She really needed you.
She knows I'm fucking
tapped out right now.
I-I'm giving her all I've got.
You're, like, the best part of my day.
I love the shit out of you.
What are you doing, buddy?
What are you doing?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Tonight's the night,
and you can certainly feel
the excitement out here.
Bette Porter's campaign has had
quite a few bumps in the road,
but people have really
responded to her commitment
to address the opioid crisis head-on.
Now, if Porter wins tonight,
she not only would be the first
woman elected to this office,
but also the first openly
gay mayor of the city.
It would truly be an
historic day for Los Angeles.
The polls are about to close,
and members of our team will be here...
Okay, everyone. Here we go.
Polls are closed.
Make sure you're all on
the registrar's website.
We hit the doors in CD 11.
I know that we phoned our
voters this past weekend,
but how many did we pull to vote?
I don't have any hard numbers,
- but we're doing all we can.
- Well, I need numbers.
Go get me the numbers.
- You all good?
- Yeah.
All we can do is wait.
Good luck, Ms. Porter.
Thank you, everybody. Thank you.
- You got this.
- Good luck.
All right, ladies, gentlemen,
all you gender nonconforming
folks out there.
Are you ready to welcome
the guest of honor this evening?
Your next mayor
of Los Angeles, Bette Porter!
♪ Baby ♪
♪ You won't be messing a good thing... ♪
Good luck, Bette!
Hi, everyone.
♪ With the break of day ♪
Oh, my goodness.
♪ You're not like them other men... ♪
Aw, this is so sweet. Hey.
Ah, Ms. Porter.
Recent polls are
increasingly in your favor.
Would you say that you're taking this
last-minute ascent as a good sign?
Well, you and I both know
never to trust the polls.
Right, Maya?
But I have to say we are
cautiously optimistic.
But, come on. I mean, off the record,
you have to admit this
is really exciting.
Well, I-I have to admit, um...
absolutely nothing.
- No.
- Ugh, we're looking for me.
What about her?
No.
I can't believe
I went from the greatest girlfriend
to two girlfriends to no girlfriends.
- What about her?
- No.
- No?
- Give her a chance!
- No. Please, trust me.
- Okay.
- No. Ah, what about her? What about her?
- Oh, she's cute. Okay, okay.
- No, I like her, I like her.
♪ If we'd kept our wildest dreams... ♪
What?
Every picture's with a parakeet.
So what's wrong with a bird?
I don't know if I'm ready for birds.
They're so chatty.
All right, all right,
all right, all right.
What?
Check out the woman
at your twelve o'clock.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Okay. All right, I'll be sly.
- That is your six.
- Oh.
I don't know clocks, okay?
- Everything's digital now.
- Hey, you guys.
- Hi.
- Angie's on her way.
I told her to find you two
when, when she gets here.
- Yeah, of course, of course.
- We got her.
- Okay.
- Hi.
Who is it?
Wait, what?
Are you okay?
- Um...
- Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Um,
I-I-I'll be back soon.
- I-I-I'll call you.
- Okay.
Are you already home?
Hey, Bette. What do you think of her?
Is that a parakeet?
- Yeah.
- Is that a thing?
Uh, they called the
11th District for you.
Wait, what?
Are you... a-are you
sure? I mean, we weren't
polling very well on the Westside.
- And Milner was supposed to have a...
- I'm sure. I'm sure of it.
The county registrar just reported it.
Bette.
Oh, my God.
- We can actually win this thing.
- Yeah, well,
that was the goal, right?
- Right.
- Yeah.
Hey.
- Hi.
- It's good to see you.
You, too. Congratulations
on the whole campaign.
Oh, thank you so much.
I mean, it's all her.
Hey, you're young, let
me ask you a question.
What do you think of her?
I dated her. The birds
were her whole thing.
Oh.
We are outside the Porter campaign's
official watch party,
where we are able to
confirm now that Bette Porter
has won the 11th District.
Once again, the 11th
District has been confirmed
of going to Bette Porter,
while Milner takes the 2nd,
and this race is still
too close to call.
Stay tuned for further results.
♪ Feeling like a stranger ♪
♪ I am afraid of it ♪
♪ When it's too hard ♪
♪ When I am in danger ♪
♪ The feelings get much stranger... ♪
Soph.
Hey.
- Hi. Oh...
- Hello, gorgeous.
Mwah.
Oh, I like this.
- Thank you.
- Look at you together.
Guys, hi.
Hi, baby.
Oh, I'm so glad you're here.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
You look beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Well, this looks amazing.
- Wow. Yeah.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Except that I have literally never been
this nervous before in my life.
Like, I could puke any second.
Hey, hey, look at me.
- Hmm?
- I am so proud of you.
No matter what happens, all right?
Thank you.
Yeah.
This is cute.
Oh, fuck.
How did we lose the 13th?
♪ Feeling like a stranger... ♪
Mm, that was nice while it lasted.
You'll get her back
in, like, three hours.
Ooh, yeah, I'm not gonna hold my breath.
Okay, please, can we see a preview
before your opening tomorrow night?
No, you're gonna have to wait
like everyone else.
It's a painting of me.
All right, doesn't
that entitle me to some
- advanced viewing? Right?
- No.
Hey. I didn't know
if you guys wanted limes,
but, uh, I thought they looked fancy.
- Thank you.
Also, no straws because the planet.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Y... sure.
Everything okay?
- Never better.
- Oh, yeah.
♪ Men run round like
a bad thing comin' ♪
♪ Bad thing comin'... ♪
Excuse us.
- Hey, boss.
- Hey-hey.
- Oh. Hey!
Hi.
♪ Take my pills but I still get sicker ♪
♪ Still get sicker... ♪
So... what do you think?
You think she'll win?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
Yeah, me, too.
You know, I don't think I've
ever seen her lose anything.
Like, not even her keys.
Uh-huh.
Can I ask you something?
Oh.
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
What's up?
When did you lose your virginity?
Mm. Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Um...
I haven't yet.
I know you're lying.
Okay, yeah.
I was, um...
I was, like, 37.
You know what?
- I'll just ask Shane. I think that's perfect.
- No.
- No?
- No. No, I'll talk, I'll talk, I'll talk.
Okay, uh, whew.
Well...
I was 17, and...
it was with this guy
who played my mom's son
in a movie of the week.
So that was a little... weird.
What's a "movie of the week"?
That was your takeaway?
From what I just said?
I guess I just figured
that you'd, um...
yeah, that you'd never
want to talk about it.
Yeah. No, that's, like,
definitely my move for sure.
But...
I don't know, I can be kind
of a shit storm for people.
No. You're not a shit storm.
No, I can be, and...
I just, like, don't...
really, really don't
want to do that to you.
And I know you love Dani,
and...
I just, I promise that
none of whatever happened
is gonna mess any of that up, okay?
Let's just, like, undo it.
Okay.
Just, like, a "select all",
"delete" sort of situation.
I don't even know if
that's right. It's just...
- No, I...
- I'm not a big typer.
- Okay.
- I'm just talking words at you.
- Totally get it.
- Okay.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
So we're good.
Yeah, we're so good.
- Awesome.
- Yeah.
All right, I'm gonna go, I don't know...
make drinks with limes.
- All right.
- I'll see you in there.
Oh, fuck.
- Hey. Hi. Are you okay?
- Hey.
- Did the bleeding stop?
- Not completely, but, um...
Okay, okay, okay. How
long have you been waiting?
Not that long. They said it shouldn't be
any more than ten minutes.
Okay, hold on. Hi. Hi. Excuse me.
Hi. Is there a reason you're
making my pregnant wife wait
- to see a doctor?
- Ma'am, there's a process that we have.
- We have to go in the order that...
- Look, no, I-I underst...
I understand your process,
but she's bleeding, so she
doesn't have time for that.
- Babe, no, seriously, it's not...
- Hold on, honey. I got this.
Did you hear what I said?
Yes. We will call you
up in just a moment,
but if you'll just please...
Lady, she's not gonna
fucking wait for a doctor,
so please go get one.
Hey. Okay.
- All right...
- I'm fine.
- It's okay.
- You sure?
All right, the doctor's, I think...
- I think she's getting him.
- Okay.
I mean, it's just... it's normal.
Is it?
Yeah. I-I hear women, you know,
they bleed early, and...
it's-it's just spotting.
- Okay.
- Okay? It's fine.
So, we've done well in the 5th.
If we get that, we just
need one more. The 3rd...
or the 14th.
Our numbers in the 5th are slipping.
Those negative ads really hurt her.
- I know.
- Polls as recent
as yesterday have Jeff
Milner leading Porter
in all three of the remaining districts.
Porter's only path to
victory is to win the 5th,
where she has struggled
since Milner's onslaught of
negative ads were released.
Okay, I know.
And Garcetti won the 14th with
68% of the vote last time...
which leaves us with the 3rd.
- Maybe if we get the 3rd, we...
- Dani. Dani.
We won the 5th.
We won the 5th? We won...
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my... oh, my God, we won the 5th.
We won... we won the 5th!
We won the... we won... we won the 5th!
We won the 5th.
Bette, we've won the 5th.
The 5th? You're kidding.
Just one more.
One more.
The celebration for the Porter campaign
has proven to be short-lived.
Can you just give us
a few minutes, please?
The registrar is now ready
to call the 3rd District
for Jeff Milner.
That means, with only
one district remaining,
this race has proven closer
than anyone expected.
For both sides it all comes down
- to the 14th District.
- Sorry, do,
do you, do you want a
glass of water or something?
- Oh, no, no, God, no.
- Okay.
Yeah.
The energy, I think,
on both sides is shifting a bit.
It feels like both of the camps
- are kind of holding their breath
- _
as the results continue
to roll very slowly in.
Come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on.
Come on.
- May I?
- Yeah. Go ahead.
- Let me just...
- Yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Shit.
- Jeff Milner will be
- _
the next mayor of Los Angeles.
Fuck.
I'm sorry, okay?
I-I, I did...
everything that I could.
I...
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
All right?
You did a great job.
Hmm.
I need to go talk to everybody.
Okay, I got to go find Angie.
Okay.
It's okay.
Come on. It's okay.
Thank you. Thank you, everyone.
I know you're disappointed.
I'm disappointed, too.
How you feeling?
Want some tea?
All right, well, I'll
make some, just in case.
Holy shit, you're still here.
Yeah.
- Can you believe it?
- Not really.
What are you gonna do today?
Nothing.
Oh, bullshit. You don't
know how to do nothing.
Let's get married.
That's the plan.
No, I mean, let's do it now.
Oh, what, 'cause you suddenly
- have time for me?
- No.
Because...
why not?
Well, you know...
I could think of a few reasons.
I'm serious.
You've always wanted to go to Hawaii.
We should just do it there.
- Really?
- Yes.
We-we can go tomorrow.
We can get on a plane
tomorrow, after your show.
I'll book the tickets right now.
Well, wh... well, what
about our families?
We'll have a big party
with them when we get back.
Um...
Come on.
This is just for you and me.
So we can start our
family on our own terms.
I love you and-and...
I really think we should do this.
I just want to be your wife.
Hmm?
Come on, come on.
My mom is gonna kill me.
Mmm.
She'll be fine.
I'm gonna book the tickets right now.
I'm so excited.
I remember when Tina miscarried.
Yeah.
I was thinking about that.
God, it was so painful.
- Hey.
- Is she okay?
- Yeah.
She'll be okay. She has to, uh...
... go back and get the D&C.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, God.
- Yeah.
- I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
How are you doing?
I'm fine.
No, I mean really.
How are you doing?
I don't know.
Listen.
Quiara is okay,
and that's the most important thing.
- Yeah.
- Right?
Yep.
And... we're here for you now.
Yeah, and if my show gets canceled,
I'll be here a lot more.
And since I'm homeless,
then I'll actually be here more than...
- I realized a second ago.
- Wow.
We're doing great.
How you doing?
I'm... I'm good, actually.
Milner called this morning.
- Really?
- Yep.
He wants me to spearhead a task force
addressing the opioid
crisis in the city.
So, that feels good.
You're handling this all really well.
Well, we went out swinging.
I gave everything I had to the campaign
and I found a way to be myself.
What more could anyone ask for?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
That's true.
Hey, Finley. Come here.
Um, can we get everyone in here?
Just for a minute. Just kind of...
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Hi. Hi.
Hey, guys, uh, Alice
has something to say.
It feels kind of important, so...
- All right, guys, come on.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- I, uh, I couldn't sleep
last night, and I probably should have,
because I've had a fuck sandwich
of a week and I'm exhausted.
Um... two of my best friends
suffered horrible losses last night,
and i-it got me thinking.
Um...
You know, none of us know
how things are gonna turn out.
Maybe the best thing to do is just...
stay true to who we are.
I have worked too hard, and...
I know it sounds ridiculous,
but I set out to change...
well, I don't know,
not change the world, 'cause that's...
but change a few people's minds
about a couple of things.
And if we can't
use this platform to do that,
then I don't think I want to be here.
Sometimes we have to
take a risk, and-and I say
let's make the show we want to make.
Well, make the show I want to make.
We have to make the show I want to make.
So fuck the viral videos.
Fuck the network mandate.
Sophie.
I want Roxane Gay.
You got it, boss.
Great.
The downside
is, uh...
... we might not make it, you know.
This might be our last show.
And if-if that's the case, I am...
so sorry I failed you.
I'm so sorry.
I-I'm not gonna cry because
my eyelashes will come off.
But thank you for everything.
I would not have any of
this if it weren't for you.
You've all worked so hard.
Let's go down swinging.
Yeah.
I love the enthusiasm.
Uh, if I could pipe in
for just one second,
uh, may-maybe we can find
- a-a compromise.
- Drew.
No more.
If you can't get on board,
then get the fuck out of here.
So, so you're gonna,
uh, get Roxane, um...
- Roxane...
- Roxane Gay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, can I call her that?
- Oh, my God.
- Or... ?
- I didn't know if that was a joke.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
So, I bought tickets to Hawaii today.
Sophie's never been.
We head out tomorrow.
Which island?
- Oahu.
- Oh.
Well, you should go to Maui.
No, we're going to Oahu.
And we're getting married.
Dad,
she's going to be my wife.
I need you to be okay with that.
Well, uh...
I don't understand why you think
she isn't good enough.
Our family had to work very hard
to get what we have now.
She doesn't want your money.
It's not about that. It's never been
- about that.
- Then what?
I taught you
- to have ambition and pride.
- Mm-hmm.
- Her family is...
- Is loving
and kind and supportive.
I don't want you to
take a step backward.
- I'm not.
- Listen.
When you are...
When you come from a
broken family like Sophie,
that's the only way
you know how to live.
She's not from a broken family.
She doesn't know stability,
and I'm afraid that
when things get hard,
she's gonna leave you,
because that-that's what she knows.
Dad, she's so much better than that.
She's not gonna leave me.
We love each other,
and we're good together.
I need you to be okay with that.
Okay.
Tough loss last night.
Yeah. It was.
What are you going to do next?
You know, I'm not sure.
Do you want your old job back?
No, I don't need a job.
You sure?
We're moving ahead
with our corporate expansion
at Lincoln Heights Jail,
and there's plenty of room for you.
And how is that possible?
I negotiated the terms
with Milner months ago.
So, so you bet against me?
No. I don't see it that way.
Well, it is pretty fucked up.
Don't talk like that.
You know I don't like it.
Yes, I do, and that
is partly why I do it.
- Daniela...
- And as I adjust
to the idea that I can't change you,
I invite you to do the same for me.
It's gonna be a whole
new world for us, Pa.
Hey.
How you feeling? You
want something to eat?
What's all this?
Oh, that's just some stuff
our friends sent over, um...
I thought you wouldn't want to see it.
Why would you think that?
I don't know. Um...
I'm still gonna have a baby, Shane.
I'm gonna try again
as soon as I'm ready.
Yeah... um... yeah.
I fucking knew it.
You knew what?
You were relieved.
- I lost a baby, and you were relieved.
- No, no, no, no, no.
I was relieved that you were okay.
That's bullshit.
What?
You win. You get whatever you want.
Hold on a second. That's not fair.
- None of this is fucking fair, Shane.
- Hey, listen.
You knew I didn't want this, but
you showed up pregnant anyway.
So what was I supposed to do?
You could have been
honest from the beginning.
I was honest with you.
Well, then why did you agree to this?
Because I love you.
And I agreed to do this
so I could be with you.
Do you want to be with me now?
Yeah.
So you're saying you would
like to try again, too?
I'm-I'm saying...
... that, uh...
I want to be realistic
and to... and to plan.
- That's-that's what I thought.
- What?
You're never gonna change, Shane.
Wait, w-w-w-wait.
Hold on. I'm sorry. What is... ?
No one is ever going to love you
because you're incapable
of loving anyone
but your fucking self.
Remember this?
I never got rid of it.
- Yeah.
- I got the door.
You know, all of this is just gonna sit
in my garage until...
Yeah, I don't even know
what the end of that
sentence could possibly be.
Well, you never know.
Angie might think it's cool one day.
Doubtful.
So, what's next for you?
Uh, Sophie and I are
actually going to Hawaii.
Yeah, we're gonna go get
married out there, just-just us.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Well, when you come back,
I hope you'll consider
joining me in the Milner administration.
He's asked me to spearhead a task force
addressing the opioid crisis.
Bette.
It's a setup.
What do you mean?
I had lunch with my dad.
And, um...
he's been supporting
Milner this whole time.
His connection to Big Pharma runs deep.
Milner's using you.
He just wants it to look
like he gives a shit.
I'm sorry.
Was it worth it?
Was any of it fucking worth it?
Yes.
Yes, I think it was.
I don't know anymore.
Good night, Sophie.
Hey. Good night.
Uh, I'll see you tomorrow, yeah?
- Have a good night.
- Bye.
- Hey.
- Hey. Um...
I'm-I'm on my way home.
- Do you want a ride?
- Yeah.
That'd be awesome. Um, do
you mind if I just drop this
in the greenroom really
quick? I'll be a second.
Oh, yeah, go ahead.
Okay. Sweet.
Hey, can we stop by Jeni's Ice Cream?
I want one of their salted cones.
We're getting married.
Me and Dani, uh, in Hawaii.
We leave tomorrow.
Oh.
Dude, that's-that's so cool.
You, uh... you've always
wanted to go to Hawaii.
Yeah.
Yeah, and now I get to
go there and get married.
To Dani tomorrow.
Yeah, I hear you.
That's... that's awesome.
You can have one of your
little coconut drinkie-drinks.
All right, how do you really feel?
I don't...
I don't... know how I feel.
Okay, well, does it feel
calm inside of your body right now?
Like... like everything's
exactly how it's supposed to be?
You are, like, the
world's worst Catholic.
What? How?
Don't you know how to,
like, shove it down?
Just, like, way down
- and never talk about it?
- Oh, my God. Is that what you're doing?
Of course that's what I'm doing.
That's what everybody does.
That's how you survive in the world.
- Really?
- Yes.
You know what?
I cannot fucking stand you.
I know. I know.
'Cause I'm ridiculous.
No, no, no, you're...
You're not.
Don't look at me like that.
You're getting married
in Hawaii, and you leave tomorrow.
Yeah.
Shove it down.
Shove it way down.
Yeah, but I don't want to.
What do you want?
I can feel your heart.
Your heart is racing.
I know.
It's a good race.
Oh, you smell so good.
It's just me.
Oh, okay.
You're laughing at me.
- I'm not.
- Pulled my pants off, and
- you're laughing at me.
- I'm just having a great time.
I swear.
Then why are you laughing?
Look at these ashy-ass legs.
- Fuck off.
- Oh.
Help me here.
It's a lot, this.
Okay.
It's okay.
This feels too good.
This, this is amazing.
Are you ready to see yours?
Yeah.
I feel like the eroticism in my
work has never been this overt.
It's always been a thread in the
conversation I wanted to create,
or something.
Sorry. I'm talking a lot
because I'm very nervous.
Don't be.
I don't know anything about art,
and I am so proud of you.
There you are.
♪ Some days I wake up and I realize... ♪
Wow.
It's beautiful.
It's you.
♪ All my life been running ♪
♪ Running away from something... ♪
Is it?
Yeah.
It's how I see you.
♪ I just wanna get back to shore ♪
♪ Just want to get my life on track ♪
♪ Give up myself a little ♪
♪ Some days I wake up
and I feel light... ♪
I love you.
I love you, too.
♪ Some days I wake up and I realize ♪
♪ Some days I wake up and
I know I'll be all right ♪
♪ Some days I wake up
and I know I'll be... ♪
Hey, baby.
Hey.
You scared about tomorrow?
- Mm.
- It's gonna be incredible.
I'm gonna treat you so good.
You deserve all of it.
I'm still learning.
But I'll always be here for you.
No matter what.
Always.
Nope.
- Hi.
- Oh, my God.
Um, hey, hi. What are you...
- doing here?
- I'm... I'm sorry. I...
I, like, really messed up.
I-I slept with Sophie,
and I just...
Finley, you can't show up
at my house like this.
I can't be this...
person for you.
I know. I know that.
I... I just, I'm sorry.
You said I was a good person,
and I'm so clearly not that.
I, like, I think I
really hurt her, and...
it made me sort of, like, realize
that I really hurt you,
too, and I'm just...
I am so, so sorry.
Um... yeah, that's it.
I'm gonna fuck off and
get the fuck out of L.A.
Wait. Um...
Hey. Thank you.
That really meant a lot to me.
And you are a good person.
Good people make mistakes.
Was it...
was it a mistake?
It doesn't matter.
She's getting married,
and I might have, like,
really fucked it up for her,
- and she does not deserve that.
- What about you?
What do you deserve?
Uh...
not you.
Not her. You guys are both,
like, way better than me.
See, that? That's shame.
You have to a-address that.
- How the fuck do you do that?
- I don't know.
It's not a cut-and-dry thing.
It is a lifelong journey...
of cultivating...
self-worth, self-love.
Love? I don't even
like myself right now,
like, at all.
And I just need... I need
something, like, concrete.
I need... I need some help here.
Okay.
Anything.
It feels really good sometimes
to take responsibility
for the mistakes that you've made.
And... you're actually already doing it.
- Okay.
- Just little things.
Just start small.
Little baby steps.
I got it.
Thank you.
Um, and I'm sorry for
showing up like this.
And...
you are a real priest.
Thank you.
You know I'm a minister, though, right?
Mm. Mm-hmm.
Ha! And I totally know the difference
between those two things.
Um...
I'm gonna go, because...
I have a person inside.
Yeah, course. Um, I'm-I'm-I'm...
sorry.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hey, do you have, like,
a-a piece of paper?
And maybe, like, a pen?
I know.
God. Yeah, wait here.
His work has...
has changed significantly,
don't you think?
- Um, yeah. I've heard.
- Mm-hmm.
- You must be a new fan.
- Yes.
I-I... Yeah.
Have we met?
Maybe.
You a friend of José's?
Yeah. Yeah.
Um... I'm Micah.
Scott.
I'm José's husband.
- Hey, Scott.
- Hey.
Hi.
_
Fuck.
Hey.
Mom?
Okay.
Mom.
Hey.
- Mom?
- Hmm?
What's wrong?
Mom, what's wrong?
I'm just tired.
Okay.
Do you want coffee?
Something to eat?
No, I just need to rest.
We could watch TV.
Not now, sweetheart.
I knew that it would hit you eventually.
It's okay.
You know?
To be sad.
But maybe you should come with me.
Can you get dressed?
I'll, I'll get your shoes and
I'll meet you at the front door.
Okay?
Do you recognize this place?
Of course.
Yeah, we spread some of
Auntie Kit's ashes here.
I haven't been up here since then.
I come up here with Jordi a lot.
You do?
Well, yeah, sometimes. Just
whenever I'm sad about...
Aunt Kit or...
Mama T or...
Are you sad about her getting married?
Yeah.
I guess a tiny part of me always hoped
that... you two would get back together.
- I know it sounds stupid, but I did...
- No, no, no, no, it's not...
it's not stupid.
I'm really sorry that...
that you saw me like that.
It's okay.
You never let yourself be sad.
- What do you mean?
- Well, Mom left
and then Aunt Kit died, and...
like, I see you. You just...
What?
You just kept going.
I think...
I think that I felt that if I...
... if I truly let myself grieve,
then that would mean...
saying a final goodbye,
and I wasn't ready to do that.
I guess I just try
to outrun my feelings.
Did I ever tell you that I...
one time I went on a silent retreat?
No. How did that go?
How do you think it went?
- Not good.
- No.
- No?
- No, not well.
Not well at all.
But, but I did learn,
um, one thing that helped.
What was that?
- Uh...
- What?
Do you want to scream with me?
Yeah, scream. I said scream.
- Yeah.
- Yeah? Okay, but you really have to do it.
Like, you have to fully
do it for it to work.
You-you have to commit to it.
- Can you do that?
- Yep.
Okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
One...
- Two... three.
- two... three.
Do you want to do it again?
- Oh, God, yeah.
- Okay. One,
two, three.
Oh, my...
How you guys feeling?
Yes! That is what
I like to hear. We're feeling good.
We're ready for the show.
I'm feeling good.
- I got a new car...
- Hey.
- Do you need anything else?
Thanks, Tammy. Um, no.
- Thank you for everything.
- Oh, of course.
- Thank you.
- You're gonna kill it.
- Okay. Big show.
- They love you.
- Okay.
- Eye of the tiger. You got it.
- Hey.
Um, look, I'm-I'm sorry,
- but I...
- I-I'm going home.
Oh, um, okay.
Uh, no, like, home home.
To Missouri.
Reliable car...
Oh.
Okay.
- Um...
- Yeah, I'm gonna duck out now
'cause my flight's tonight.
Wow. Um...
Okay, well, are you...
leaving because of me?
Because of...
us, what happened?
Uh, no.
No, uh, it's my sister's wedding, so...
- Oh.
- I'm gonna go be there for her.
Okay.
The doors don't function.
You're coming back, right?
Yeah.
I mean...
Um...
I'll catch you on the flip side, bud.
You ready?
Rule number one: put yourself out there.
- Yeah, I'm ready.
- Are you ready for the show?
We got Alice and Roxane Gay
coming right at you.
Are you and Jordi having sex?
- Mom.
- I...
We literally just started dating.
Okay, I know that you
don't want to talk to me
- about this, but...
- No, I really don't.
I just asked Alice one question.
It does not mean that
I'm doing anything.
Oh, well, look, I'm not gonna tell you
that you're too young or you're...
or you're not ready or...
- anything like that.
- That's good. That's great.
Yeah, 'cause that would be pointless.
- Mm-hmm.
- Right, but I-I will say
that sex is supposed to feel good.
- Oh, my God, Mom. Mom.
- Yeah, for both of you.
- Okay, okay.
- Yeah, so...
- Got it.
- And if you're scared
or you're feeling
pressured, it's just...
- it's not gonna feel good.
- Okay. Okay.
Can this be over now? I really don't...
Uh, sure. I mean, it's the preamble,
- but, yeah, sure.
- Okay, cool. Oh, my God!
Look at that dog. Hi!
- Is this your dog?
- Yeah.
- Hi. Hi, sweetie.
- Her name's Lynn. Oh!
- My God, Bette. Hey.
- Oh!
Hey, Maya. Nice to see
you out in the real world.
You, too.
I... Look, I know I'm
supposed to be impartial,
but I was really pulling for you.
Oh, well, thank you.
Means a lot.
Well, have a great hike.
Thanks. Um,
do you want to grab dinner sometime?
Uh, I'm not really doing
any press right now,
- but thanks.
- Oh. No, no, no.
I-I meant off the... off the clock.
Oh, uh...
- Uh...
- You know what?
Just think about it.
- You've got my number.
- All right.
- Nice to meet you.
- You, too.
All right.
Well, she's pretty.
- Stop it. Don't.
- Just saying, that's...
- Stop it.
- This is exciting!
Why is it exciting?
- Nothing happened.
- You just found
- the love of your life.
- No, that's not true.
I see sparks in the air.
And we're back with Roxane Gay.
I've always been obsessed
with your idea of bad feminism.
You know, like, I really
identify with that.
You know, I hear that from women a lot,
and I think it's
because, for a lot of us,
we have this idea of what a feminist is
as angry and man-hating
and hairy, which...
There's nothing wrong with any of that,
but, you know, there has
to be space in feminism
for us to be human and flawed
but also to really care about
the state of women in the world.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Can you be a bad queer?
Oh, absolutely.
Historically, in the queer community,
we've tried to resist
heteronormative ideas.
- Mm-hmm.
- And, so, these days,
to be a bad queer
is probably to want a wife and two kids
and a picket fence.
I think I might be a bad queer.
- Oh, really? How so?
- Well,
I've been in a relationship
with a really wonderful woman
- for about two years.
- Mm-hmm.
And we were really happy,
and not too long ago, we
introduced a third person
into our couple.
Like, a poly situation?
With her ex-wife.
Wow.
That's certainly
an original way of
getting into polyamory.
I wouldn't recommend it.
You think?
But that is the queerest
thing I could ever do,
- right?
- Oh, absolutely.
On a scale of one to "what the fuck",
- that's way out there.
- Right? Right.
'Cause I thought I was this cool,
open, you know, understanding queer lady
who wanted to live outside
of every box, and...
I'm not.
I-I'm just, uh...
I'm heartbroken.
Yeah, that's understandable.
Because I just want Nat.
- You know, just Nat.
- I'm here.
- What?
- Hi.
What's happening?
Sorry. Um, I'm here.
It's... Excuse me.
It's me. Uh...
Um...
- Can we cut?
- Yeah, of course.
- This, this isn't the show, so...
- No. Keep rolling.
We need this.
I was gonna wait for you in your office,
but then I heard what you
were saying, and I just...
I-I'm in the middle of a show.
Sorry. Um, can I...
- Can I go up there?
- No.
- Yeah? Okay.
- All right.
- Oh, okay?
- Absolutely. Yes.
I don't know. I just...
Hi. Hi.
- Hi. I'm a huge fan.
- Hi.
- Sorry. Just...
- Thank you.
- No, go ahead.
- I didn't...
Okay.
- Um...
- What's happening?
Oh.
No. No, I'm not proposing.
I'm just trying to get closer to her.
Yeah, I don't do marriage.
Okay.
I want you, too.
I lost a marriage
because I was afraid to
fight for what I wanted,
and I'm not gonna make
the same mistake twice.
I love you.
I am in love with you.
And I feel like my
complete and total self
when I'm with you.
And you make me laugh.
Even when I'm mad,
which is so fucking annoying.
But it makes me love you even more.
And your maternal instincts
are a little off, but...
- Well, I'm-I'm...
- Well, I know.
And you wake up every morning
and you burn the shit out of their eggs,
and I love that.
They're deceivingly hard to make.
Not really. They're very easy.
Love, you tried to make
it work with my ex-wife
because you thought
it would make me happy.
- I did.
- Yeah.
- I really did that.
- I know.
I mean, she's the fucking best.
- I'm pretty great.
- Yeah, you are.
I love you.
I'm gonna fight for you.
Okay?
Just me?
Yes. Just you.
Micah, please open the door.
Micah, I'm sorry.
It's not what you think.
I just want to talk to you.
Please open the door.
Stevenson. Party of two.
- Maya?
- Yes.
Your party's at the bar.
Boarding pass.
Thank you.
Hi.
How you doing?
We will now begin boarding
Flight 1256 to Honolulu,
starting with boarding group one.
Group A, we welcome you to board
our nonstop flight to Kansas City.
This is the final boarding call
for Flight 1256 to Honolulu.
Final boarding call for
Flight 1256 to Honolulu.
Boarding all passengers.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN