Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Do you want your man or not? ♪
♪ Do you know your plans or not? ♪
♪ You gonna go back home or not? ♪
♪ You gonna claim your throne or not? ♪
♪ Is you Khaleesi or
that other bitch... ♪
- [snapping fingers]
- ♪ Whose name I don't remember? ♪
- Molly: Issa!
- Huh?
- I'm hungry. Let's go!
- Okay!
♪ Why you gettin' loud? ♪
♪ Yo, you need to tone it down ♪
- ♪ Why you come around? ♪
- Wait a minute,
so you're trying to tell me you
went all the way to Daniel's house
and nothing happened?
Like, at all?
- I didn't even go inside.
- Hold the fuck up!
You got on stage and went all Dej
Nope about my broken pussy for nothing?
Like, all that drama for zero dick?
- Tsk, bitch, you buggin'.
- It wasn't for nothing, though.
Like, it wasn't even about Daniel.
It was about me.
Like, I became someone else up there.
- Mm.
- You know, it was like brave me.
It was "no fucks" me.
And I wanna be that person.
You used to be that person,
all freestyle and drunk
in my backseat and shit.
So, what, you trying to be a rapper now?
No! I just wanna not be
scared to do shit anymore.
Well, you know what?
That sound real cool, real noble,
but can you just leave
my shit out of it?
- You right.
- Okay, thank you!
And I'm really sorry for
saying your pussy's broken.
- You know, I was just talking.
- No, no, no, shut up.
You was right, my pussy is broken
and I need to take better care of her.
So, I'm gonna get her a tune-up.
A tune-up?
Like, she needs her oil changed?
Like, your pussy gonna
pass a smog check or...?
- Shut the fuck up.
- [laughs]
- I'ma get her fixed.
- How, Sway?
I'm making today Molly Maintenance Day.
I'ma get my hair done, nails done,
everything did.
Ooh, like a fancy day!
- Basically, yeah.
- [phone buzzing]
If I'm feeling fancy and well
taken care of, so will she.
- That makes sense.
- Right?
Yo, Issa, you got
Lawrence calling me now.
What? Just... just ignore it.
[line ringing]
Woman's voice: Hello, you've
reached the voicemail box for...
Molly's voice: Molly Carter.
Woman's voice: Please leave
a message. [beeps]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Man: Watch him, watch
him, now, watch him.
- That's what's happening.
- Watch him, watch him.
- Loving 80 right now, man.
- [phone buzzing]
- Yo, it's Wrence.
- Wrence!
- About time.
- Yo!
Hey, who all is there?
Oh, Fast Mike and Brandon. Where you at?
Man, Pasadena is far as fuck.
Nigga, it's only, like, four freeways.
- Grab me a Guinness, B.
- I got you.
Yo, bro,
Fast Mike got fat as fuck.
I wanna call him Slow Mike, but you
know how sensitive that nigga get.
- Ah.
- [chuckles]
What's good with you, man?
Aw, shit is up right now, money.
I sold a house to Tiger earlier, man.
I was starstruck, tap
dancing for his ass and shit.
That nigga swole as fuck.
Commission was crazy.
- Oh, that's cool.
- What's up with you, man?
How's that new project
going, the Whoopty-Whoop?
- It's Whoop-Whoop.
- What'd I say?
Still working on my business plan, man.
Plus, you know, there's so
many apps out there now,
it's hard to break into the market.
Am I going too broad, do
I need to be more specific?
- It's just a lot, you know?
- Cool, cool.
That's what's up, man. Hey, I'ma
be selling you a house soon, fam.
- How are you and the old girl?
- Issa's cool.
She, um...
I kind of fucked up her birthday, man.
Aw, damn, man, you gotta fix that.
But other than that, you good, right?
Uh, actually, man,
I was calling 'cause I just wanted to...
Oh, shit, this motherfucker
hit a three, bro.
Hey, man, let me finish the rest of
this game. I'ma shout at you, all right?
Yeah, all right. All right, cool.
I can't hear you. I
was on the phone, girl.
- [phone clangs]
- [music playing]
You getting a pedicure?
Mm, I probably should.
Ooh, girl.
Lawrence ever suck your toes?
Once, but it made us both uncomfortable.
Ugh, he was sucking on
your big old man feet?
Girl, I tell ya, that nigga is the one.
Or someone else might be.
What are you talking about?
I like Lawrence.
Bitch, I love him, but...
I mean, maybe I'm not satisfied.
You know? Maybe I wanna
be dicked down properly.
You know? Maybe I wanna be face down,
ass up, surrounded by
foreign freaks, you know?
Maybe I wanna ask a nigga
what he wants for breakfast
and he replies, "That pussy,"
and he's talking about me, girl.
- You know?
- I can't with you. Mm-mm.
You don't know.
I'm just saying
Lawrence hasn't put it down
in a very long time, okay?
And maybe I need to get on one
of those apps like you, girl.
Girl, calm your deprived ass down.
You are not about this app life.
Try me.
Bitch, I'm not gonna sign up. I
just wanna see what's out there.
All right. You asked for it.
Check it, that's OkCupid.
It's free, so it's like
"bottom of the barrel" dudes.
Bought a bunch of new
movies at the barbershop.
Bootleg and chill?
Tinder used to be cool,
but now it's basically a fuck app.
So, what are you in the mood for?
We could ditch the menus
and have our own dinner for two.
Heh, I'll be six, you'll be nine.
[chuckles]
Hinge at least pulls from
your network of friends,
but apparently all my friends
only know Hotep niggas.
Uh-uh, no.
I just want a queen that respects
herself, who lays off the swine,
who stands beside her king like
a strong black woman should.
- Yeah.
But my queen gotta be a freak, too.
I fucked that nigga 'cause he was fine.
But then he had the nerve to dump me
'cause I told him I never
went to the beach till college.
Nigga, you sell Obama puzzles
at the African marketplace
and you gonna judge me?
You grew up in LA and you
never went to the beach?
Okay, Windsor Hills, I was a hood rat.
All I knew was Florence and
Crenshaw. Whatever, I am still fly.
Basically, most of these dudes
are not looking for a relationship.
- They're just trying to fuck.
- Really?
Yep.
I mean, I just wanna up the
quality of dudes that I meet.
There's this one app called The League.
It's for elite dating.
Like, girl, you gotta be a
professional just to get in.
I mean, I've been on, like,
a three-month waiting list.
Three months?
To meet one nigga?
Yeah, this is a lot.
You gotta fuck a lot of
frogs to get a good frog.
That's not the saying. Or any saying.
The point is it's a numbers game.
Check it, I'm going on a
date with this frog tomorrow.
- Mm.
- He could be different.
- You never know.
- Mm.
So, what we doing next?
I gotta get my hair done
and then something else.
What?
It's a "vagacial" appointment.
It's like a facial for your vagina.
- I said everything did.
- Mm.
I saw it on Draya's Instagram.
I mean, you could roll if you want to.
Fuck! I guess I'll go home and deal
with this motherfucking relationship.
You should write Hallmark cards.
- Bitch, shut up.
- [chuckles]
I'll see you later.
Go handle your man, girl.
Do you know who you are?
You the bossiest bitch.
You a grown-ass woman
like Solange's sis.
You gonna take control like
Janet, or lose control like Missy.
The decision is yours...
boss up or be a pussy.
Mm-mm, no.
[music playing]
[indistinct chatter over P.A.]
_
♪ If you're reading this,
it's your birthday ♪
♪ We're gonna sip champagne like we... ♪
Thanks, man.
Issa.
- Lawrence?
- Where have you been, huh?
- I've been calling you.
- Oh, I... I...
you know, I had my
phone on airplane mode.
- What the fuck?
- I'm just buying...
- You're buying panties?
- Why you being all loud?!
Why are you buying a six pack?
It's cheaper and it's not
like it's the cute kind.
Wait, are you not coming home?
Lawrence, I'm not ready to
talk about this right now.
No, no, no, no, no. You can't keep
ignoring me, Issa. I wanna talk!
Lawrence, we are not about to be
the black couple fighting in Rite Aid.
Okay, listen, I know that this
is about your birthday, okay?
It's not even about my birthday.
- See? You don't even...
- I don't even what?
I... I can't do this right now.
- I'm sorry, I gotta go.
- Wait, Is-Issa!
[sighs]
Lawrence, wait.
Can I get your Rite Aid
card for the discount?
Come on, man.
Woman on TV: I [bleep] men and women.
I got two bitches
waiting on me outside...
and two counts of murder on my head
that they know about. [chuckles]
And I ain't sorry.
Girl, hey! Look at you.
Uh, how was your "vagacial"?
This bitch blew bubbles
at me. My pussy is still broken.
At least I have an icebreaker
for my date tomorrow night.
But what are you still doing here?
I thought Miss No Fucks was going home.
Um, can I stay one more night?
Flavor Flav said yes already.
Issa, what's going on? Why
are you avoiding Lawrence?
I kissed Daniel.
But it was like... it
was like... [kisses]
And then it was... and
then it was finished.
Bitch, I knew it with
your old lying ass.
Okay, I did not lie,
because, technically, I did
not go inside or fuck him.
That's a sound defense.
[sighs]
And I saw Lawrence
and, girl, he just doesn't get it.
And I don't know what to do
and I'm just... I'm tired.
Stay as long as you need.
Thank you.
[sighs]
And just so we're clear,
I'm still Miss No Fucks.
It's a... it's a whole
process. It's a thing, so...
Yeah.
How's your presentation going?
Girl, I got too much on my mind, okay?
I am about to just wing
this shit "no fucks" style.
And these white people, they're
not even gonna know the difference.
They're not gonna know!
You're so stupid.
Oh, can I borrow some
clothes for work tomorrow?
♪ Told y'all, I told
y'all she a pimp, too ♪
♪ Told y'all she a pimp, too ♪
♪ I told y'all she a pimp, too ♪
♪ Growing up, I was a dorky dame ♪
♪ Got money, then the story change ♪
- ♪ Glory came, now all I crave... ♪
- _
Boy, bye. Nope!
♪ I told y'all she a pimp, too ♪
♪ Told y'all she a pimp, too... ♪
Um, blazer twins.
Look at that.
Hey, I'm so glad you came in early.
So, about our youth... your
youth outreach initiative,
um, did you get my email?
Oh, no, I had a lot to do this weekend.
Well, I don't wanna step on your toes,
but I spoke to some of the
teachers at Thomas Jefferson
and it turns out the students
have a high interest in sports.
Sports? That's not exactly
outside of what they know,
and don't you think
that's extremely limiting?
No, I hear you.
That is sadly stereotypical.
But to your general point about exposing
them to new and untraditional things,
what about partnering with
USC for sports like lacrosse,
water polo, or even real polo?
I don't... Culturally
speaking, I just...
It's crippling for inner city kids
to rely solely on sports
to achieve success...
- you know?
- That's true.
Well, my other idea was to take
them to different neighborhoods
and to do a community cleanup.
You mean take a bunch of black kids
and have them clean up the
streets like a chain gang?
That's the whitest
shit you've ever said!
You know, community service is cool,
but I think I found my stride.
- I've got this.
- Okay.
- Thank you, though.
- Thank you.
Guys, I've been doing this a long time,
but I still get excited when
my staff takes initiative
to maximize their
impact in the classroom.
Issa, Frieda, the floor is yours.
Thank you, Joanne.
Ahem, so the kids of Thomas
Jefferson Middle School
are stagnant because they don't
know what else is out there.
So, my idea is to expose them
to the arts around Los Angeles.
Which arts?
Uh, all of them.
Are you referring to, like, visual arts,
theatrical arts, or did you
really just mean the arts?
Um, what I'm asking is, is that it?
[chuckles] No, that's...
uh-uh, that's not it.
Um, if they're interested
in painting and sculpture,
we can take them to The Broad.
If they like music,
we can take them to the Hollywood Bowl.
There's the Watts Towers...
Have you put together a budget on this?
- That sounds expensive.
- It does, right?
No, I was gonna get people
excited about it first
and then I was gonna
take a stab at the budget.
A stab?
So, you have really no idea how
much this is gonna cost at all?
This sounds like a whole lot
of work for very little benefit.
Joanne: I see where
you're going with this,
but have you thought
about the risk factors,
the executions, how
is it mission-driven?
Uh, the... the mission would be... help.
We were also considering a
community service component
- which I...
- Not yet, Frieda.
- This is Issa's idea. Let her finish.
- Okay.
Yeah, no, uh, a community
service component
could also be included, um...
Culturally, I'm just like...
Wouldn't they rather go to
an African American museum
or, like, a Latino museum
and just see how much more
grateful other generations were?
Oh, my God, what about
hip-hop Shakespeare?
The kids would love "Othello."
An interracial romance.
Ooh, what about a drum circle?
That really helps with aggression.
I took an African dance
class in high school,
so I could do mask work with the kids.
- [voices overlapping]
- We watch "Lemonade"
and then we go to Lemonade and we eat.
We eat good food that's good for you
and we see art.
[voices overlapping]
Can I have a few minutes, please?
[chatter stops]
Everyone,
let's reconvene at the end of the day.
[phone rings]
Yes, but when the plaintiff
took this job, he signed a waiver
that completely indemnifies our client
of any and all risks associated
with operating heavy machinery.
You are so fucking smart.
[chuckles] I'll keep reviewing
the employment contract.
- [knocking]
- Sorry to interrupt.
- Hey.
- Molly, good points today.
Oh, thank you, 'cause, you
know, actually, I was...
Diane, I never got a chance
to formally congratulate
you on your engagement.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Wedding planning is the most stressful.
My wife and I went crazy.
- Are you going crazy yet?
- You know, I am going crazy
with all this work we have to do.
[chuckles] Oh, my God,
I haven't even thought about
the wedding yet, you guys.
It's, like, only been a few days.
- Did you see the ring?
- Man: Oh!
- Woman: Well, there it is. Wow.
- Diane: It's a princess cut.
- Woman: That is a diamond.
- Man: Look at mine.
- Look at that.
- Woman: Mm-hmm.
- Come in.
- Hey.
Um, so, I'm sorry about
the presentation today.
- I know you were expecting more.
- I was.
Um, and I just wanna let you know
that I am fully committed to
and invested in We Got Y'all.
- I've just had a lot...
- Let me stop you right there.
- You're not.
- Um, sorry?
I hired you because I saw someone
who wanted to make a difference.
You seemed passionate at first,
but I've noticed you've been
on autopilot for a while now.
If you don't wanna do the work,
if you're no longer invested
in what we're trying to do here,
maybe this isn't the
right place for you.
No, it... no, it is!
And you're right.
I... I wanna be here.
And I will do better.
The leader who does not take advice
is not a leader.
That's a proverb from
Kenya, date unknown.
Okay.
[music playing]
♪ Every day a new escape ♪
♪ I awake, looking for the sun ♪
♪ Hoping that I never break ♪
♪ I'm on the edge, wanting
me to trip and fall ♪
♪ Feeling every eye on me to ignore ♪
♪ Got the feeling that
they wanted more ♪
- [vocalizing]
- _
♪ Wanted more ♪
♪ Bound to you. ♪
♪ If you're reading this,
it's your birthday ♪
♪ We're gonna sip champagne
like we're thirsty... ♪
- What up, yo?
- Nothing, bro. I'm good.
♪ So let's have a toast,
it's your birthday ♪
♪ Birthday, birthday, birthday... ♪
Hey, something up?
I ain't seen your girl
in a minute. Y'all good?
- She leave you for another bitch?
- What? No.
- No.
- Talk to me, blood.
Me and Nala was just about
to go watch the "Bare Bears."
- "Care Bears," Daddy.
- Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
We don't use no C-word, sweetheart.
This is a blood house.
Are you sure you're "bool," man?
[exhales]
I've just been messing up.
I started this business
that didn't pan out.
Now I'm watching all my
friends just pass me by.
It's just been
frustrating on all levels.
Yeah, a nigga's stuck.
Yeah.
You ain't working, you ain't providing.
Shit, you probably ain't
even putting it down.
- Man, hey.
- Nah, nah, no disrespect.
- You love your girl and shit, right?
- Yeah, I do.
I just... I just don't know
how to change things, man.
Well, hear me out.
I used to be out there fucking bitches,
being inconsiderate and shit.
But then when I had Nala, I was like,
"What if she meet a nigga like me?"
I even tried to make it work with
her moms, but her moms is a H-O-E.
- So F-U-C-K her B-I-T-C-H-A-S-S.
- Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
Gotta spell fast. She getting so smart.
She know her ABBs and shit.
That's little Einstein, huh?
Daddy's little Einstein.
Anyway, bling your shit up, blood.
Hey, and if it don't
work out, I got bitches.
Cool.
"Bool."
I completely forgot about
the surveys these kids did.
Yeah, well, they were
still in sealed envelopes.
The voice of the children.
You believe this? It's so telling.
And you were right, they did mostly list
basketball and football
in their interests.
Mostly spelled wrong, but still.
They wanna be part of a team.
Or they wanna take it out the
hood. Look at this question...
"What is something you'd like
We Got Y'all to do next year?"
- This is sad.
- "Take us to the Crenshaw mall."
"Go to Benihana's."
"Dave & Buster's."
"Stand in line for Jordans."
These kids can't even
imagine past the 10 freeway.
No, I'm not... I'm not laughing at...
- That's... that's sad.
- It's sad.
No, my friend grew up around here
and she was talking about how
she never went to the beach
- until college.
- No way.
- Is she okay?
- Yeah, she's fine.
- She's a lawyer, but...
- Okay.
I don't know,
what if we just took these
kids to the beach to start?
You know, we could even do your
service idea and make it a...
Both: Beach cleanup.
Word twins.
Hello.
- It's becoming our thing.
- Mm-mm.
[music playing]
[chatter, laughter]
No, no, no, look,
hands down, the worst
dating experience I've had...
- Coffee Meets Bagel.
- Wait, worse than OkCupid?
Listen, I've never had so
many women eyeing my shoe size
and asking me, "So,
are the rumors true?"
- Wait, about your...?
- Uh-huh.
Yep, white girls have no shame.
Oh, so you mostly date white girls?
Not at all. I just
went through this period
- where black women weren't feeling me.
- Now I know you lying.
No, no, no, listen, you're
the first black woman
who's responded to me in a minute.
- I don't know what it is.
- Really?
Really.
Wow.
You two, okay?
You want some more wine
or are you in a rush?
Sure, no rush here.
Can we have your Argentinian Malbec?
- Okay.
- Thanks, man. You're gonna like this.
- Oh, am I?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Am I gonna like it like
I like your chicken?
Uh, I mean, you know...
- I mean, just a taste!
- You got pasta.
- This was fun.
- Yeah!
You wanna grab some coffee?
Uh, definitely.
You trying to fuck, though?
- You motherfucker.
- All right.
You think that just 'cause
you know some fancy wine-speak,
I'm just supposed to
let you take me home?
What, three glasses of
Spanish wine means we fuck?
- Malbec's Argentinian, but...
- [sighs]
I spent all this time trying to
make sure that my pussy is fixed,
but it turns out you are just like
every other single asshole out here.
I didn't break my pussy,
niggas like you broke my pussy.
[phone buzzes]
_
So, I'm home.
You still the same nigga?
"Yep, but who else you gonna be with?"
Oh, I got options, nigga. I got options.
"So, you ready to talk now?"
You ready to man-up now? Ha!
You wasn't expecting
that, huh? That was good.
That's, like, pow. "What's my mama
gonna say about us breaking up?"
I don't give a shit
about your mama, nigga!
She's really nice.
"Where'd you put all my
shit?" In a box to the left.
[chuckles] It's like a
jungle sometimes, nigga.
"So, you know I'm
gonna take all my DVDs."
Don't nobody want your
Steve Harvey box set.
"You know I'm still working
on my business plan."
I got a plan... start the business.
Nigga, how 'bout that?
"Bitch you know I love
you." I love you, too.
[sighs]
Hey, broken pussy!
Jared.
- Right, right.
- What's up?
You got... you got a little...
something all over your face.
Okay, so you got jokes.
Somebody runs out of a
club and don't say good-bye.
[chuckles] Yeah.
- Uh, who is this?
- That's Flavor Flav.
Oh, you should get a
Doberman and name him Chuck D.
- Thank you.
- Real clever.
I tried. Did a little something.
Got an interview with
a headhunter tomorrow.
That's great.
I shouldn't have ignored you today.
Thug Yoda spelled an
entire sentence today.
For real?
- That's "brazy."
- [both chuckling]
♪ Heartbreaks, setbacks ♪
♪ Breakups, makeups ♪
♪ Love, love ♪
♪ Love, love, love ♪
♪ Breakdowns, build-ups ♪
♪ Knockdowns, broke down ♪
♪ But still try, try, try, try ♪
♪ Baby, this could be a
chance for us to see ♪
♪ Maybe we'll figure out
where we're supposed to be ♪
♪ Until we find the truth ♪
♪ There's something we should do ♪
♪ Can't let the love stop
flowing from me to you ♪
♪ You know we tried
way too hard to find ♪
♪ A love that's really blind ♪
♪ So why even try? ♪
♪ Baby, this could be a
chance for us to see ♪
♪ Maybe we'll figure out
where we're supposed to be ♪
♪ Until we find the truth ♪
♪ There's something we should do ♪
♪ Can't let the love stop
flowing from me to you. ♪
[vocalizing]
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org