Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
No!
I can't run! My legs hurt!
I can't wait till we're older.
We can leave this place.
Where do you want to go?
Just somewhere different.
Somewhere where
the sun's always shining.
Like today.
California.
Let's go.
Really?
Promise you won't
go without me?
Of course.
It's friends
till the end, right?
Friends to the end.
- Bam.
- Oh!
Kevin, hurry up!
We have to go to the game!
Come on!
Kevin?
Kevin!
Okay, Kevin, this...
this, uh... this isn't funny.
Kevin?
Augh!
No! No!
[Door slams
Gah!
Help!
Somebody, please! Help!
Help... Help!
Help, please!
Somebody, help! Please!
Guh! Help!
Help me...
Guh!
Help!
Help me!
Help! Help!
Please, stop!
Somebody get me out of here!
Please!
Help!
Help! Please!
Stop! Help, please!
Help!
But we have to try with all
the help we can get.
Now, I'm going to point out
the windows and doors.
Do you understand?
We'll be all right here.
We'll be all right here
if someone comes to rest,
but we'll have to
work together.
You'll have to help.
Now, I want you to go in
and get some wood
so I can board the place up.
Do you understand? Okay?
Okay?
Shhhhh.
Don't cry.
There's nothing to cry about.
It's okay.
Shh, you're safe here.
You are.
Hey.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Come on,
don't do that.
Do not cry.
Stop now.
What was that?
It's okay.
You don't have to hide from me.
I just want to talk.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Don't be shy, now.
You can come out.
It's okay.
- Rrgh!
- Ough!
Ugh!
Guh...
Come on, come on, come on!
Ugh!
There you are.
He... Help me!
Help me, please!
Shh, shh!
Stop that.
There's nothing to be scared of.
I just want to talk.
That's all I want to do.
Calm down.
It's okay.
That wasn't very nice, was that?
What are you gonna
do with that?
Hmm?
I need you to listen to me.
Be a good boy
and put the knife down.
Mnngh.
I'm sorry.
I said... Rgh!
Ugh!
Ugh...
I'm sorry.
Kevin.
Kevin, can you hear me?
It's me, Bobby.
Kevin, please answer me!
Can you hear me?
Kevin.
Bobby.
Kevin?
Kevin, are you okay?
Did he hurt you?
No, I'm fine.
Where is he?
H-He's gone.
What about the other one?
I-I don't know.
Can you come to the door?
No, he put something around
my ankle, and I can't move.
I'm scared, Bobby.
Me, too, okay?
But I'm not gonna leave you.
It's it's friends
till the end, remember?
Friends to the end.
Don't worry,
I'm gonna find keys.
Aw, come on.
Bobby?
Bobby.
Hey, I'm gonna drive
and get help.
- What do you mean?
- I can't find the keys.
Yeah, but you can't drive.
I-I'll be right back.
- Bobby!
- Just trust me!
A-And that's the thing...
these aren't law-abiding
Americans.
These aren't good people.
These are rapists.
These are criminals.
Now, I'll tell you something...
they're coming for you.
They're coming for your jobs.
They're coming for your women.
Whoa. Whoa!
They take and take
till they...
No-no-no-no-no.
- Come on!
- They want to take your guns.
No, no, no.
No! Come on!
Augh!
Kevin, I need you.
Bobby, do you find help?
I found a phone.
It's like the ones
you see in movies.
It's big, heavy.
It has a curly cord thing.
Oh, my grandma
has one of those.
I-I don't know how it works.
You need to plug it
into a wall.
It doesn't have a plug.
Well, t-t-there should be
some cord around,
and it ...it looks like
an Internet cable.
Dang it.
Come on, come on, come on.
Agh!
Ugh!
Yes!
Kevin, it's working!
911, what's your emergency?
Yeah, w... M-Me and my friend
have been kidnapped.
What's your name, sir?
- Bobby. Bobby Green.
- Okay, Bobby.
Is the person that took you
still there?
- Can they hear you?
- N-No, they're gone.
but my friend's still stuck.
You have to hurry, please.
We're tracking your location.
Can you tell me anything
about where you are?
- It's a house.
- Okay, a house.
Do you know where it is?
There's a lot
of grass and trees
and a big oil rig out front.
Oh!
Ooh!
Oh...
Bobby, hide!
...see anything else...
No.
He... He's back.
He just came back.
You have to hurry, please.
We'll... We'll be there soon.
Just stay on the line.
We almost have your location.
Just stay with me
a little longer.
No, I have to go.
Is there a place you can hide?
N-No! No, he'll find me!
He'll see me!
He'll see the body, okay?
- Bobby, talk to me.
- I have to go.
Do you really think...
I don't think anything.
I just know that
I'm going to my room.
And if anybody comes in,
I'll shoot him.
Or her.
O-Ow!
Okay.
Augh...
Oh, I wish
this night were over.
Those are guns.
I tell you, it doesn't make
any difference.
They're not through
with us yet.
Mnngh...
Rrghh!
Rgh.
Certainly not.
And right as somebody else
in this house
who once has left his room.
Did you hear anything?
Organ music.
That and someone walking.
You look downstairs,
and I'll look out here.
Why not together?
There may be only minutes,
seconds left of someone's life!
Why waste time?
It's almost over, Nelly.
You really keep
the hours passing.
What's happening?
We've done it.
A perfect crime.
Beautiful.
Ahh...
What are you doing?
What is that?
Please!
I just want to go home!
Please.
I won't cry, I swear.
I swear.
Ple... Please don't!
Please! Please!
Gah!
Get away!
Please, go away!
Just go away!
Why?!
Please, stop!
Augh!
Help! Help! I'm up here!
Please! Hello?! Please!
Up here at the window!
Please! Hello?!
It's me! It's me up here!
Up here at the window! Please!
Hello?! Please!
Please, I'm up here!
Help me, please!
Help, please!
I'm up here! Help!
There is a pattern
to all that lives!
An order, an arrangement!
She had a heart, and a brain,
and her spirit was in both!
Not in one or the other!
No.
I'll give her a brain
and a heart.
Yes, and what of her soul?
You say you love her and...
You can remember
her love for you.
Then how can you make of her
an experiment of horror?
All the skill and
science I possess was meant for this.
Life has a pattern.
The whole pattern of my life
is shaping itself
to save her now.
Then, you intend to
go through with it?
Yes.
Good evening.
Are you the owner
of this residence?
Yes, I am.
Can you cut that down?
I'm sorry.
Are you the owner
of this residence?
Yes. Yes, I am.
Um...
m-may I ask what this is about?
We received a distress call
about a suspected kidnapping.
Dispatch traced it
to this general area.
Oh, my God. You're kidding.
In this area?
Have you seen anything
unusual tonight?
No, no.
It's just another
quiet night around here.
W... Except for the TV,
of course.
It's just nice to hear
something in the background.
Mm. Do you have
any kids, Miss...?
Burton. Uh, no.
No kids.
What about a Mr. Burton?
Are you making a pass
at me, Officer?
No, ma'am, I'm not.
It's just me.
Can I see some I.D.,
Miss Burton?
Of course.
It's, uh, just right inside.
I'll be back in a minute.
Ms. Burton!
Miss Burton, can you
hurry this up, please?
Ms. Burton, I'm comin' in!
People fear what
they don't understand.
And what they can't see.
- Ms. Burton!
- No, what are you talking about?
You're nothing a freak of life.
And a freak of death!
Why should I be afraid of a few locks on the door?
But last night, you ran.
Hello?
Ms. Burton?
Help us!
Oh, my God.
Gah!
No!
Ah...
Ungh.
Open the door, kid.
Open... the goddamn... door.
Okay, listen to me.
I know you're scared,
but I'm coming in there
one way or another.
So, if you open the door,
I promise you,
I will not hurt you.
Do it!
Let me in.
Come on!
Open the door!
Open the goddamn door!
Open the door, bitch!
Fuck it!
You know, I never really planned
on taking you out of that trunk.
I figured you'd
suck all the air out
and that'd be the end of it.
But, here we are.
My friends like
tough boys, though.
Not like your crybaby
buddy upstairs.
They actually pay good money
for the ones who put up a fight.
They don't normally go for ones
who look like you,
but I think
they'll make an exception.
You know what?
Since you clearly like
your little fucking friend,
how about I swap you out
for your pal?
How does that sound?
Ugh! Augh!
Ngh!
Oh, fuck!
God damn it.
Rrgh!
Kevin.
Get away from me!
- Away from me!
- Kevin! Kevin, it's me!
It's me... Bobby.
It's me.
Bobby.
You didn't leave me.
You didn't...
- Did he...?
- No.
Here, put this on.
She's still downstairs.
We need to get you
out of here, okay?
You have to help me
pull, okay?
One, two, three.
One more time.
Be right back, okay?
I promise.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Just trust me, okay?
It'll be all right.
J-Just back up a little bit.
Three, two...
Ow!
Oh, God!
Kevin, what...
Kevin, what is it?!
Come on.
Augh!
I have an idea.
N... No, no!
Don't leave me again!
Don't leave me!
Listen, listen!
Listen, okay?
Don't leave me again.
The worst thing that could have
happened to us already happened.
Just stay here.
I'll be right back.
Rgh!
Gah!
Rghh!
- Ragh!
- Augh!
No, let me...
Let me go!
Augh!
Ow! No!
Augh! Oh, God!
Oh, my God!
My finger!
You cut off my fucking finger!
You're dead!
Do you hear me?!
You little shit.
Bobby!
Just say something!
Come on.
Ough!
Fuck you!
Ungh!
Hey! We've gotta go!
- Mm...
- We've gotta go!
I can't.
What do you... Yes, you can!
Kevin, you have to go.
No! No!
You have to.
Do you know what you told me?
Friends till the end, remember?
This is not the end.
God...
Boys!
Okay.
Let's go.
Come on.
Guh...
Agh!
Hello?
Can anyone hear me?
Last unit,
please identify yourself.
Oh. My name is Kevin O'Connor,
and I need help.
Please send someone.
Sir, this is
a restricted frequency.
If you have an emergency,
please dial 911.
We don't... We don't
have a phone.
Um, she already killed
the other officer.
Please.
What is your location?
U-Um, I-I don't know.
It's a farmhouse,
and i-it looks far away.
I'm in a cop car.
Find a safe place to hide.
Officers are on their way.
Okay.
Here.
I got something.
Move your hand.
Okay.
Uh, here.
Don't move, okay?
- Okay.
- Three, two, one.
Agh!
Thank you...
We're still gonna go, right?
To California?
Yeah, of course.
They're gonna be here soon.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God, Oh, my God!
- We need to lock the doors!
- Please!
- What are you doing?! Please!
- No! No! No!
- No! What are you doing?!
- Please don't!
- No!
- No! No!
Please don't!
No!
Something's wrong.
Yeah.
No! No! No!
- No! No!
- No!
- No, no! Let me go!
- No! Let me go!
- Bobby!
No!
Agh!
Bobby!
I got something for ya.
Ungh!
Where do you think
you're going?
Stay down!
Say goodnight.
Gah! Ugh!
Ahhhhh!
Ugh!
Rgh!
How does it feel?!
Kevin!
It's okay.
Okay.
Boys?
Do you see her?
No...
Where are you?
Come on. Come on.
Where is she?
Is she still there?
I don't see her anywhere.
- Sit down.
- Agh...
Hey, I think she's gone.
Ugh! Agh...
Hrgh!
Agh!
Get away from him!
Agh! Gah!
- Get down!
- God!
Get off of me!
Augh!
- Guh!
- Ow!
Agh!
Grugh!
Gah!
Adam-2-4-4.
Shots fired, shots fired.
Suspect is down.
I got two in need
of medical attention.
Heading out.
A-2 checking out.
Detectives en route.
Take these boys to the hospital.
Let's get you two home.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/8e4mu
Help other users to choose the best subtitles