sync and corrections by awaqeded
www.addic7ed.com.
You kissed Olivia?
Damn.
Is it true?
- Yeah.
- You know they boning, right?
Wait. Is he the guy?
This isn't about me. It's about Ruby.
He's in love with Olivia.
- What...
- Can we just all take a moment
to appreciate the fact that, for once,
I was able to keep a secret.
You knew?
- Why would you sell me out like that?
- What do you mean, "Sell you out?"
And you? What type of friend are you?
- Jamal, it's always your fault.
- It's all about his trifling ass.
- What are you saying?
- Bitch, I got a brick in this bag.
You weren't even invited.
Y'all messed up!
We got business.
What about the lockdown?
It's done.
And y'all wanted to kill me.
Shame.
Bitch, that's my cue!
To think I made you
partner in my company.
God damn, that egg sandwich!
How the hell is this my fault?
They're always telling me to keep
my mouth shut, so I shut my mouth,
and now it's on me!
Baby, I just heard about the lockdown!
- A bomb went off.
- A bomb?
Yeah, but I wasn't the
one who dropped it.
It was a metaphorical bomb, but real.
Very real.
I'm still picking out
the emotional shrapnel,
and I... I will never, ever forget
the smell of that sulfur.
I think I might have PTSD.
People Telling Me Secrets Disorder.
- The "Me" is silent.
- But you're seeing okay?
Yeah. My eyes are fine.
In fact, for the first time,
my eyes are wide open.
I've never seen better
than I'm seeing today.
I'm woke AF.
- Don't be cussing in my house.
- Sorry, but the struggle is real.
You're 14. What struggle?
FIMS, Ma. FIMS!
Foot in Mouth Syndrome.
When I say something, I'm screwed.
When I don't say something, I'm screwed.
It's like no matter what I do, I can't
figure out how to unscrew myself.
Baby, you're looking
at the glass half-empty.
But you're seeing okay,
and your eyepatch is off.
That means you must be playing.
You're playing tomorrow?
Mom, no.
- Dwayne! Jamal is playing tomorrow!
- Mom.
- Dwayne!
- Damn it! I did it again.
Dude, we need to talk.
I have nothing to say, Judas.
Technically, Monse
sold you out, so she'd
be Judas. I'm just the
keeper of secrets,
- like the Vatican.
- No wonder I feel violated.
Look, I need you. I may
have inadvertently
signed my own death warrant.
Pray tell?
I had a FIMS flare-up last night
and might've told my mom
I'm playing in the game today.
You told your mom
you're playing in the game?
The game that's getting us
into the playoffs?
- Wait, we made it to the playoffs?
- If we win. You didn't know?
Dude, it's not funny.
Look, I need your help.
I need you to talk to Coach
and convince him
to let me suit up and sit on the bench.
Hilarious. I know.
But you... you... you are the master.
You are the wizard of words.
You can take any bad situation
and make it better.
You... are... Ruben!
Yeah, you're right. I did get Cesar
promoted and I wasn't even trying.
I also got Ms. Castillo
a tax credit on her fake boobs.
- So, you'll do it?
- Hell no!
You got two options.
Either come clean to your folks
or come clean to your folks.
Karma's a bitch, dude.
So... the truth is...
I lied.
I've been lying for months now and...
I know I was wrong...
and you're probably disappointed in me.
But there it is.
I throw myself at your mercy.
Would it help if I told you I loved you?
No.
I don't even let the water boy
sit on my bench.
Did I miss something?
When were you guys cool with each other?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Yeah, we're cool.
Interesting.
Hmm.
- You chilly?
- Not really.
Just thought it might be cool
under all that shade.
Oh, I didn't know there was pie.
- Cesar took the last piece.
- Yeah.
Cesar can't keep his hands
off other people's pie.
Happy?
- I don't want your sloppy seconds.
- I barely touched it.
Liar.
I'm done. Turns out I've had my fill.
You should have it.
It might fill that big mouth.
Am I the pie?
- It's complicated. We're dysfunctional.
- Understatement.
Talk later?
Stay?
- Aren't you mad at me?
- Why would I be mad?
That's the trend around here.
All right, you're still new,
so spoiler alert...
Can you please break
down what's going on
'cause shit's getting real weird
and I need the Cliffs Notes?
Where do I begin?
So, it's like this:
our friends are like a family,
if your family was full of pedophiles.
So like, you love your kids,
and your kids have kids
and you love those kids.
And your kids love their kids,
but maybe a little too much
'cause someone's touching the kids.
And you know who's touching the kids.
And you can't say anything
because you love them and they love you.
And it's all messed up
and always your fault.
And you never get any of the love.
Which is probs okay,
'cause you don't want to be diddled.
And this is a terrible metaphor.
Jamal, do you need help?
Yes! But not in that way.
Sorry. I'm only going off the rails
today 'cause I have to play football.
- I didn't even know you were on the team!
- Hence my dilemma, so...
now I have to figure out how to get
in the game, but not play in the game.
Can I ask you a question?
It's potentially sensitive.
Does it have anything
to do with a secret?
- No.
- Hit me.
Okay. I understand why Ruby
would be upset about my kiss with Cesar,
but why Monse?
Huh.
Monse is Monse.
There's no rhyme or reason to her crazy.
Unless there's some truth
to what Jasmine said.
Which would make sense,
because Monse mentioned
she hooked up with a guy over summer...
Stop! Ooh! Red light. Safe word.
This is starting to sound like a secret.
Please don't tell me.
- I don't think it's a secret.
- Okay.
Maybe it's a secret.
You know, it's probably a secret.
Christ on a cracker, woman.
I just told you not to tell me.
A secret.
You have a what?
I have a secret.
- And it came from Olivia.
- What is it?
- What are you gonna do for it?
- Nothing!
Because you owe it to me to tell
me a secret to replace the secret
that you didn't tell me
in the first place.
No. This is too juicy.
I would need something in exchange.
Something only Ruben can offer.
- I'm not talking to the coach.
- Then you'll be secret-less twice.
Was it about me?
Ha.
Good day.
Information manipulation theory.
Pray tell.
Basically, when I talk to the coach, I'm
going to confuse the crap out of him.
Now, I think there's some tea
that needs to be spilled. Spill it.
What if... Cesar really is
cherry-bombing Monse?
Boom!
That's it? Jamal, that's not a secret.
That's a question.
Oh, oh, oh. I forgot the other part.
The other part is.
Monse told Olivia that she was
hooking up with a dude this summer.
So? She went to camp.
It probably happened there.
Or... she boned Cesar before she went,
which is why he said what he said
in the first place.
And girls get
emotionally clingy post-coital,
which would explain why she still wanted
to be friends with him
even after he said what he said
and why she's so upset about his
kiss with Olivia now.
Coincidence? I think not.
Monse is a lot of things,
but she's not a liar.
Do you know how hard
it must have been for her to admit to me
- I was her first kiss in seventh grade?
- She told me the same.
In the sixth grade.
I feel so dirty.
We both feel so dirty.
Damn. Now we got to roll up our sleeves
and get dirtier.
Have you no shame?
What are you talking about?
You are a black man.
And isn't it true, good sir,
that you have a moral obligation
to see to it that this young black man
is afforded the same liberties
- as other black men in this school?
- What? He quit the team!
Yes, but did you ever ask yourself
why he quit the team?
- Don't care.
- And why not?
Isn't it your responsibility
as a leader on this campus,
as a leader within the community,
to wonder why someone
with so much potential
would quit the team?
So, he was reaching out to you,
pleading for you
to take notice of him and his pain.
- And you did nothing.
- Nothing.
- No, he didn't!
You did what the rest
of society has done
to every other brother
who has come before him.
You turned your back.
You closed the store. You shut the door.
Slammed it!
- You left him to run amok.
- Amok!
- Bamboozled.
- Bamboozled!
- Hoodwinked.
- Hoodwinked!
And led astray to become yet another
statistic on the streets of LA.
All he asks is just to get off
the streets and onto your bench.
- To give him sanctuary.
- Sanctuary.
- Safety.
'Cause I have a dream,
that one day, you will ask
not what Jamal can do for you,
- but what you can do for Jamal.
- Hallelujah!
Because if the helmet fits,
you must let him sit!
If I say yes, will you finally shut up
and get out of my office?
I need to consult with my client.
What are you thinking?
We accept.
- What's going on?
- You said we would talk.
Privately. As in sans the Santo.
It's cool. You all do your girl thing.
I'm gonna bounce.
But then you're gonna miss
seeing Jamal in the game.
- Jamal?
Told you Jamal's on the field.
How and why is this happening?
Me. Me is why this is happening.
Ruben made a special appearance
in the coach's office
- and got Jamal on the team.
- For what reason?
Isn't this exciting? Aren't you excited?
Yeah! Excited. Stunned. Surprised.
It's been a long time coming after
that record-breaking run of injuries.
I know. I thought we'd have
to put that boy in a bubble.
You still might.
- Come on! Go! Go! Come on!
- Go! Go! Whoo!
Whoo!
We're almost there guys.
Almost home free.
Yes! Yes! Yes, I like that.
Twenty-two! Twenty-two! Put in 22!
Oh, you heard the lady. Put me in.
No, no, no. Don't actually.
Don't actually put me in.
They saving me, Ma! They don't want
none of this Turner Classic.
So petty.
What's petty?
Oh.
So, now you're talking to me?
We've been sitting here four quarters,
you haven't said a word.
Like, "Hello. How was your day?
Your hair is looking immaculate."
- Or, "I'm sorry."
- I'm sorry.
- Really? That's how you're gonna do it?
- Well, I was waiting to do it one-on-one.
So your apologies are like your
betrayals. Stealth and untimely.
Hey, you guys want soda, candy?
It's on me.
- Nope.
Come on, Ruby. Can we not do this?
Not do what? Cat got your tongue?
Or was it Olivia?
That call was bullshit!
- Boo!
- Come on!
- Shame on you!
The ref is clearly biased.
That call was bullshit.
Bad ref!
Nice. Nice work, amigo. You got me.
...on the 36 yard line.
Excuse you. Why are you scooching?
I'm the injured party here.
I was just trying to protect you.
Really? Is that what that was?
'Cause I wasn't aware throwing your
friend under the bus was protection.
- Trust me. It was for your benefit.
- Or yours.
That bus was meant for you
and you pushed me in front of it.
Fight! Fight! Yeah!
- Fight!
- Break it up!
What bus?
The bus of truth.
'Cause I'm starting to question
whether that rumor you suggested
was just a rumor this summer
really wasn't just a rumor after all.
- Fake news.
- I have it on good authority
that you had a summer smash sitch.
And when you put two and two together,
it equals Cesar.
You're out of here! All of you!
Come on! Come on!
That's my whole lineup!
You can't eject my entire lineup!
Johnson, you're in.
Carter, get on the field. Nuñez...
- Which one?
- Both of you! Come on.
Turner! Turner!
No, God. No, God, if you're listening...
Time for the Turner Classic. Let's go!
Be aggressive!
It's time for the Turner Classic!
Your silence is your tell.
Now I know you lied.
- You're a liar and a puta.
- Go to hell, Ruby!
The game is almost over.
Let's talk this out after.
I can't wait that long.
You don't get to walk away.
I get to walk away.
Okay, maybe figure this out now.
There's nothing to figure out.
Monse and Cesar are backstabbing liars.
- Dude, drop it!
- Look! They're putting Jamal in the game!
If I don't? What're you gonna do, homes?
Put a green light out on me?
No, but I'll put you on pause.
I'm gonna watch.
Maybe even get in on it.
Enough!
You're acting like a bunch of kids.
If someone says one more thing,
I'm going to punch them.
All of you, behind the bleachers. Now!
Look, despite what may or may not
have happened, you love each other.
You are each other's family.
And now you've become my family.
So, whether or not you want
to work this out, you need to,
because every day
that you have together is precious.
Trust me. I know.
So, I'm sorry. This is my fault.
I'm the one that kissed Cesar.
So, if you're gonna be mad at anyone...
be mad at me.
Stop. You don't have to be sorry.
And no one is mad at you.
I had no idea one kiss
would cause so much damage.
This isn't on you. It's on me.
I've been lying to everyone.
And I need to come clean.
Huddle up. All right, fourth down, boys.
This one's for the playoffs.
It's do or die time.
We score or we're done.
- You don't have to do this.
- I do.
So, here's the truth.
I was into Cesar.
I had a big crush on him.
And before I went to my writing camp...
I... I told him.
And he didn't feel the same way.
- Say no more.
- We get it.
You don't, so let me make it clear.
After I told Cesar how I felt,
I bounced for the summer.
And Cesar told Oscar's homies
that we smashed to protect me.
He claimed me to keep me safe.
But that's it, that's all.
Nothing ever happened.
- 'Cause he's not into me.
- Monse...
Not like I was into him.
And I'm sorry that I didn't tell you
and that I blurted out that you kissed.
I was jealous and I reacted badly.
But it was fleeting, and it's over.
So, can we move on?
Can I stop embarrassing myself?
'Cause this hole that I've dug
is starting to feel pretty deep.
Heads up, secondary. Hike!
Sorry I called you a puta.
Appreciate that, pendejo.
You're amazing.
No, you are.
What the hell's going on out there?
I don't want to die! I don't
want to die! I don't want to die!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Yes! Yeah!
My baby! My baby!
All fall down! All fall down!
- Yeah, Jamal!
- Jamal!
- Yes, baby. Yes!
- Yes!
I know. Can you believe Jamal?
Oh, that was insane.
Your feelings aren't one-sided.
You could've told the truth.
- You didn't have to do that.
- No way.
You saw how one kiss
blew up the whole crew.
It was a kiss. One stupid kiss.
- Yeah, a kiss that didn't mean anything.
- Or maybe it did.
- It didn't.
- Then why did you kiss her?
We're not meant to be
more than friends, Cesar.
No, all I have to do is be honest
and explain why you couldn't.
Then they'll know the summer rumor
was true and I lied.
Then just come clean. I don't understand
why you can't just do that.
'Cause you're not a girl. For you,
screwing me gives you street cred.
- For me, screwing you makes me a whore.
- Not if we're together.
No! Then I'm just your bitch.
And you're only with me for one reason.
But I want to be with you, Monse.
- I want to be with you too, but I can't.
- Why?
Because Olivia's right, we're a family.
And if we're together,
- it might break the family up.
- It won't.
Do you know that? For sure?
Exactly.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying...
I'm good at being your friend.
So, I should do that.
And Olivia likes you, and I like her.
So, you should do that.
- Way to play.
- Thanks, man. Thank you.
- Hey.
- All right, brother.
Where you all going?
Out of here. Come on.
Nice game, homie.
You made the 'Ridge proud.
You need anything, I got you.
- Lil' Ricky.
- What?
Lil' Ricky.
- What about him?
- Where can I find him?
- What do you want with Lil' Ricky?
- You know, converse.
Chat. Chew the fat. Please?
I see you, homie.
1400 Forest Lawn Drive.
- Tell him Spooky said, "What up."
- Okay.
1400 Forest Lawn Drive.
Dad?
- When did you get home?
- I just got off the road.
Why are you in the dark?
You okay, baby?
- Do I need to kick someone's ass?
- No.
It's just stupid teenage stuff.
I was a teenager once.
Not that long ago.
Nothing's stupid if it's making you cry.
It'll pass. These things always do.
See, there you go again,
doing my job for me.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
I love you, baby.
You're the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
I love you too, Dad.
Do you ever think about Mom?
Of course.
Especially in moments like this.
Why?
Because she doesn't know
how incredible you are.
Or you.
Where do you think she is?
I don't know.
Last I heard, New York.
Are you good?
Yeah.
Are we good?
Any weirdness in the
air we should clear?
Nope. Totally clear.
You like Cesar. I'm cool with it.
I never wanted to hurt you.
You're not.
You sure?
You see, there's something called
the long game,
and that's what I'm playing.
So, fly along, baby girl.
You know, test the waters.
Enjoy your Cesar salad, and I mean that.
Because nothing is gonna taste as good
as this Ruben.
And you may not know it yet,
but I'm gonna be the love of your life.
So, good night, my dear.
Sleep well,
and dream about our wedding colors,
'cause I'm down with anything but beige.
Lavender.
- We going free ride. College scholarship.
- We going free ride. Going scholarship.
We going to the Super Bowl!
Way to bring it home, baby.
Ooh! You ready for the playoffs?
Ah! Yeah, so excited. Can't wait.
Gonna be epic. I quit the team.
What?
Months ago. And so you wouldn't find out,
I might have faked an injury or two.
Or eight. Today was a total fluke.
Ruby had to Jedi mind-trick the Coach
to let me sit on the bench.
I wasn't supposed to play,
let alone save the game.
I know this is shocking and sudden
and I've decimated
all your hopes and dreams,
but I just can't keep it
bottled up anymore.
My insides were feeling
like Coke and Pop Rocks,
and I don't want to be like Mikey.
So... I'm sorry.
And I throw myself at your mercy.
- So, you don't like football?
- Hate it.
Okay.
Okay?
You just got to do you.
So that's it?
That's all? You don't care?
We're here to support you, baby,
not hurt you.
We want you to find your passion.
And if it's not football,
you know, it's cool.
So, you don't care about football?
All this time...
all these lies, all those medical
devices, and you don't care?
This is really jacked!
We just want you to be happy.
I can't believe you. "Just be happy"?
I need a minute.
Alone.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yeah! Yeah!
What's up, Lil' Ricky?
I'm coming for you.