sync and corrections by awaqeded
www.addic7ed.com.
Hey.
My life is over.
Don't say that.
It's true.
I'm dead either way.
If I kill Latrelle, I'll be dead inside.
If I don't kill him...
I'll just be dead.
What if you disappear?
How?
With money.
A lot of money.
Twenty, seven, 42.
Do me right
and make my dreams come true.
You're heartless!
Come on, boo. You know I love you.
Those other boxes didn't mean a thing.
You're the real deal.
Am I interrupting something?
- Where've you been?
- I'm sorry.
I didn't see any of your messages
until this morning.
What's all this?
This is what Ricky left Chivo.
It holds the answers to RollerWorld.
I know it does.
That combo right there opened every box
and still nothing.
I've been searching all night
and nothing. Still nothing!
And there are dozens
of boxes left to go.
I think I have arthritis.
Would it be juvenile arthritis?
Am I still a juvenile?
Let me help you.
Woman, please! There's an order to this.
Bottom to top, left to right.
I hate you.
Let me see what you got.
What are you guys doing?
This is trespassing.
Um...
Is there anything you want to tell us?
About what?
That whole thing?
I was helping Olivia with a makeup test
for her quince when Jamal 911ed.
Right side's glamour, left side's chic.
Dude, I can't believe I'm saying this,
but...
you're beautiful!
Why is he here?
Because someone wasn't answering
my calls and texts.
My phone was dead and I'm here now
and that's all that matters.
I think the naysayer needs to go home.
I am not a naysayer.
And why do I need to go home?
- RollerWorld.
- I'm out of here.
RollerWorld is real!
So were the chupacabra bones
you found in sixth grade.
- It's the only way to save Cesar.
- Save Cesar?
Before he's forced to kill Latrelle.
Per usual, you're overreacting.
He's got a gun.
And he has to do it tonight
unless he disappears.
This is crazy. If he's got a gun,
then why don't we help him now?
Why can't he disappear now?
- To where?
- Anywhere.
That's not a plan.
This is the plan.
The guy who jacked RollerWorld
left this behind.
It's a clue to
where the money is.
- Ring around the Rosie?
- No!
The numbers up top.
They opened a combo,
then we found these numbers.
Now we have to figure out
what the new numbers mean.
This is ridiculous.
Do you hear yourselves?
Numbers leading to more numbers
leading to money
that definitely doesn't exist.
And if it did, somebody
would've found it by now.
Or not. It's our only chance
at saving Cesar.
I just put the numbers in my phone.
They're either lottery numbers
or extremely unique body measurements.
Well, only one is a prime number.
- What does that mean?
- I don't know. I'm just stating a fact.
I don't have a math degree.
Degrees!
These are coordinates.
- So what are we looking for?
- Anything and everything that jumps out.
Anything that marks the spot.
Maybe something
that could be from the '80s
after they pulled off the heist?
- I'll take the playground.
- I'll take the handball court.
And I'll babysit the bikes
and Google cheap bus tickets.
Sorry, I'm still not buying
into RollerWorld. You're all crazy.
And you look crazy.
Might want to wipe your face.
Sorry.
Ooh.
Mira. Hey, what's up?
I got a hit!
I'm just gonna wipe my prints off
and put this right back.
- I didn't find anything.
- Me either.
We might have enough
to get Cesar to Fresno.
- Then what? He lives on the streets?
- No.
The Central Valley produces
more than just meth.
Fresno's actually a bustling
agricultural community.
There's a plethora of
opportunity for him. See?
Wait. Get up.
No, I'm telling you,
Fresno's the answer.
If he doesn't want to pick fruit,
there's canning, curing, drying,
and the largest turkey farm...
That's it.
The game's afoot.
- Sherlock Holmes.
- Oh.
That makes total sense.
'Cause cholos love Sherlock Holmes,
homes.
Doy 823.8.
Doy. Doy. Doy.
Doyle! Sir Arthur Conan Doyle.
It's the Dewey decimal system.
I'm a survivalist.
Got to know your Deweys.
The library. Let's go!
Oh, great.
Oh, it's heavy.
Okay. All right.
I found the tip!
And the balls and the shaft.
- We don't have time for dick jokes.
- There's always time for dick jokes.
Cesar needs us. Stop dicking around.
You do know
that was another dick joke, right?
How do we know what we're searching for?
You'll know when you know.
Look at what I got here.
Okay, so we've
got four elements.
- What can we make with them?
- Uh...
A bomb.
To cause a distraction
to get Cesar the hell out of here.
Promethium, Phosphorus, Lanthium, Neon.
It's a compound.
Or it spells something out.
PM plane.
Night plane?
The Midnight Plane to Georgia.
- It's Midnight Train.
- And PM is noon, not midnight.
Midnight Plane to Georgia?
Your black card
should be revoked for that.
Uh, uh, uh, uh.
Halves cannot revoke
the black cards of wholes.
- Says who?
- All of me.
It's Pimp Lane.
It's Pimp Lane!
And only a local would know that.
Holy shit! This is real!
We got to go! We got to go!
It's Pimp Lane!
Oh, the game's afoot, bitches!
It's Olivia.
She's been blowing me up all day.
So, answer it.
And tell her what happened with Cesar?
No way I'm telling her about us.
Us? She's calling about Cesar.
Yeah. Right. You know what I mean.
I don't want her to worry. Here.
This is your phone.
I don't want in on this drama.
It's Olivia. Answer it.
Oh, hell no!
That's like giving Oxy to a junkie.
Hey! What's up?
Hey. I'm really worried about Cesar.
He's not picking up his phone.
I went by his house, he's not there.
- Is he with you?
- Me? No, why would he be with me?
I'm hanging with Ruby and Jamal.
Ruby is dying to talk to you.
Hey.
What's going on?
Uh...
We're working on a surprise
for your quince.
- Monse wants the phone back.
- No. I don't want it.
Yeah, it's a real elaborate surprise.
Lots of twists and turns.
Can I call you later?
Sure. If you see Cesar,
can you please tell him to call me?
Yeah, no prob.
I'll do that. Bye.
Bye.
What are you doing?
We're trying to figure out
if that's a boob or a butt.
A boob.
Can we get back to saving our friend?
Nothing.
There's nothing.
Except a lot of STDs.
That's why I didn't pull out
the black light.
We must have missed something.
So... you want the black light?
No, no. I'm talking about the elements.
We must've messed up the name.
It's not Pimp Lane.
But it's got to be Pimp Lane.
- Oh, I wouldn't sit there.
- Maybe we should go back to the library.
- It's closed.
- What do you mean it's closed?
As in not open. It's closed.
- Hey... it's a path!
- Why do you do this?
Every time I have an idea, if it
didn't come from you, you just go...
What do you want me to do?
Open the library?
You're insufferable. First you're
a non-believer, now you know everything?
Look, I'm right because I'm right.
Don't be a hater.
I found something!
That's a Santos cross.
But what does it say above it?
"En las sombras Del tiempo."
In the shadows of time.
Yeah, but what's six, four, seven, nine?
It's a sundial.
Chivo said Lil' Ricky loved them.
What do we do with it? There's no sun.
Ha.
Watch and learn, my
crab-infested friends.
Okay, so first, we take out a pen.
Then we need a light to be the sun.
So, a sundial is like a clock.
So, if I position my light
over the numbers,
it'll cast a shadow onto the letter...
Enough! Just do it.
Okay, you need to learn this
in case of the apocalypse.
What?
I'm gonna follow the numbers
to get a letter. Here we go.
Six o'clock: P.
Four: O.
Seven: O.
Nine: L.
Pool.
The money's at the pool.
But where's a pool?
- The community pool!
Lil' Ricky, you can suck it,
because nothing gets past us!
Our bikes!
What the hell?
Rookies? What, were you guys raised
in the 'burbs or something?
- Lock it or lose it.
- Read the room, Jamal.
How are we gonna get around now?
What are you doing at Pimp Lane?
Um...
How do you know about Pimp Lane?
Mijo, I wasn't always old.
I was once, what they
call, a sure thing.
- I think I'm gonna throw up.
- Don't slut shame me.
Abuelita, we got to get
to the community pool.
- ¿Por qué?
- We'll tell you on the way.
Ah.
Look how fast those fools
are drinking that lean.
They'll be faded soon.
Then you strike.
Too many ojos.
So what? Who cares who's watching?
I do.
And so would Spooky. We sit tight.
All right.
Jamal, what are you doing?
Look out!
Jamal, why
are you soaking wet?
I don't want to talk about it.
What just happened ain't right.
What's not right is
there's no Santos Cross here.
Every clue had a cross on it.
Google says there's 19
more pools in Freeridge.
Okay, so Jamal, you change
into the clothes I have in the back
and we'll check all the pools.
No. I'm doomed.
We're doomed. Cesar's doomed.
I haven't slept in days.
Julio's dead, and poor Juanita.
We're not doomed if we solve this,
so stop being so dramatic.
- I am being dramatic.
- We know.
Like Nicolas Cage dramatic.
Odd reference, but yeah, so quit it.
I'm so dramatic that I tried out
for the local production of Rent.
- That was a rip off of La Bohème.
- Whatever.
My point is I tried out
at the Robert Pool Theater.
The P-O-O-L Theater.
- It's a pool in the title.
- Oh.
Out!
Out damned spot! Out, I say!
One, two.
Why, then, 'tis time to do 't.
Hell is murky!
Fie, my lord, fie!
- There's nothing here.
- Keep looking.
I think this might be a dead end too.
...we fear who knows it,
when none can call our power to account?
Yet who would have
thought the old man...
Hear ye, hear ye.
Hast thou observeth
a crucifix of yonder year?
Circa the year of our lord 1980?
What?
Have any of you seen a cross?
There's a cross in the wings that
we touch before each show for good luck.
Been there forever.
"Find your center."
This doesn't make any sense.
Okay, so we started at the park...
and then we went to the library...
and then we went to Pimp Lane...
and then finally we came here.
And get dick.
Technically that
happened at the library.
Ta-da!
What is this?
This is finding your center.
The park.
The library.
Pimp Lane.
And now...
here.
Four points.
It's a cross.
Huh?
Now I really don't know
what you're talking about.
That makes three of us.
Do you know what's
in the center of these four points?
A place with muchos Santos.
Oh.
Stop praying. It's time.
Still too many people.
They'll hear it for sure.
Nah. Not when you got this.
Fool been crushing the lean all night.
So when he goes to take a piss,
you make your move.
God help me.
Are you praying for Cesar?
No.
For Sylvia.
Who's Sylvia?
Fernando's wife.
He poisoned her and her twin sister
after he woke up from his coma.
That's horrible.
She's talking about her telenovela.
Let's go.
Not here.
It's not here.
Is it just me or is that baby Jesus
throwing a gang sign?
He's repping the Santos!
There's nothing here!
- Monse, help me with this.
- Okay.
Hey! Have some respect.
- What are you doing?
This isn't just an altar.
It's a magic box.
Like Ms. Uyeshiro's box.
Don't you remember her box?
Come on, man, grow up!
But don't you remember her box
in the fourth grade?
It was like this intriguing,
impenetrable cypher.
- Dude, we don't have time for that!
- Okay.
Oh, so we got time for dick jokes,
but not box jokes?
You heard that?
- You heard that?
- Yeah.
Hey, Jamal, help me.
Here! Here! Here! Lift it. Lift it.
Hey, Nah. Hey, I'm about to go piss.
It's time, Lil' Spooky.
I'm faded, man.
This lean is something serious.
What the what?
I told you it was real.
We just saved Cesar!
This is surreal. We need to memorialize
the moment and send it to Cesar.
Okay, right.
It's chocolate.
Hell, yeah, we got chocolate!
We can buy chocolate, vanilla,
that new Tesla with the gull wings.
No, the gold.
It's not gold, it's chocolate.
Maybe it's only chocolate on the top.
Chivo.
It's Cesar.
- Hey.
- I got no more time. What do you got?
Um...
Nothing.
I'm so sorry.
Cesar?
Cesar, say something.
Oh, my God.
You better pray he's okay.
We'll get the money,
and he'll be safe.
We could've had him
out of town by now!
This is just a mislead.
A red herring. A MacGuffin.
Tell her, Ruby.
I told you we should've
just put him on a bus.
He needs money to get away.
RollerWorld is that money.
- We just got to...
- Got to what?
You live in a fantasy. Grow up, Jamal.
You just ruined Cesar's life.
He's never gonna be the same.
I didn't ruin his life.
He ruined his own life.
Cesar's in a gang! Okay?
That's the reality, all right?
And you think I'm living in a fantasy?
You're the one who's living in a fantasy
thinking you can save Cesar.
It's not going to happen. Ever!
Cesar was born a Santo,
he's gonna die a Santo.
So stop lying to yourself, sweetie.
I'm lying to myself?
Your whole life is a lie.
Those fake-ass injuries.
Bullshitting your parents.
The football team.
You're the biggest, fakest liar ever.
I hope I never see you again.
- And you never will.
- Jamal, Monse, chill!
No! I'm sick and tired of chilling.
And I'm sick and tired of y'all
telling me that it's always my fault.
So you can miss me with that crap.
Get over here!
Hey, hey, hey. ¡No más!
I can't believe I got played.
There has to be a way.
RollerWorld has to be true.
Jamal, for what it's worth,
I believed it too.
But... some mysteries
aren't meant to be solved.
Abuelita...
tell Olivia...
I can't make her quince.
Come on. Please, man. Please.
Don't do this, man. Don't do this.
We went to school together.
And you still pulled a gun on me.
I didn't shoot, man. But I didn't shoot.
You should've.