Enjoy Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
(SINGING) When you wish upon a star
Your dreams come true
(SIGHS)
Isn't that a catchy little tune?
Well, how do?
Cricket's the name.
Jiminy Cricket, to be precise.
And I'm here to tell you
one humdinger of a tale.
It's a story that begins a long time ago.
Actually, it's a story that begins
once upon a time, a long time ago.
That's right.
Much better. Much more precise.
Never understood that expression.
How can it be "once upon a time"?
Hey, who's telling this story? Me or you?
Well, who are you?
I'm you. Only older and wiser.
Really? How do you figure?
Because I'm the narrator
telling this story post facto.
I know exactly what's gonna
happen to you on this adventure.
Really? Well, let me ask you this.
Am I ever gonna be warm again?
Just keep walking. You'll find out.
(SCOFFS)
Some storyteller you are.
Shall I continue?
Go for it.
Narrate to your heart's content.
Thank you. (CLEARS THROAT)
Once upon a time, a long time ago,
my travels took me
to a quaint little village.
(WIND BLOWING)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHIRPS)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHIRPING)
"Mastro Geppetto. Wood-carver,
fabricator of clocks, toys, oddments."
Oddments, huh?
Sounds like my kind of place.
(CHIRPING)
(GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
(SHIVERS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
GEPPETTO: Hmm.
(SHUDDERING)
Huh?
(CLOCKS TICKING)
(MYSTICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
- (SMOLDERING)
- (JIMINY GASPS)
GEPPETTO: "Maybe something here
"A touch behind the ear
- "Not a boy. Just a toy for a puppeteer"
-(CAT YAWNS)
Huh?
(CHIRPING)
(CHAIN CLINKING SOFTLY)
GEPPETTO: "Thinking way back when
I'm missing him again"
(BLOWING)
(CHIRPS)
"Heart so young, songs unsung
"Oh, what might have been"
(CHIRPING)
(CHAIN CLINKING SOFTLY)
"I see him in my dreams
So perfectly, it seems
(PURRING)
"If I could only make
These dreams come true
"I may never find
"This vision in my mind
"Memory may hold the key
"To feeling how I felt
when he was here with me"
(SINGING) There was so much laughter
But we couldn't see
Happily ever after was never meant to be
If only this could be more than a memory
But memory will have to be
The way this old man's eyes can see
Just how it really was
When he was here
(FIGARO YAWNS)
With me
(MEOWS)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
Yeah.
Hmm. Not too shabby.
Whoa! (CLEARS THROAT)
Excuse me, ma'am.
(SIGHS) Well...
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Ha. Ah...
Figaro, all finished.
What do you think, huh?
(PURRING)
Oh, really?
Well, I think he looks very much like him.
Very much.
(KNOCKING ON WINDOW)
No, Figaro, it's Signore Rizzi again.
(GEPPETTO SIGHS)
(JIMINY CHIRPING)
(GEPPETTO GRUNTING)
No, Signore Rizzi, I'm sorry.
We have already closed at 6:04.
Precisely at sunset.
Oh, well, Geppetto,
I'm sorry to disturb you.
I saw your light was on and I thought
I would ask you one more time.
Please sell me the cuckoo clock
with the cute duck
and the little alligator on it.
GEPPETTO: That clock is not for sale,
as I have told you many times.
RIZZI: I will give you 20 lira. 30 lira.
Name your price, Geppetto, and I will pay.
They are beyond price, Signore.
I'm very sorry, but I cannot sell you
any of my cuckoo clocks.
But if you cannot sell your clocks,
why do you have a shop?
(SIGHS)
It's complicated. Perhaps a music box?
Good night, Geppetto.
I leave a disappointed man.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(GEPPETTO GROANS AND SIGHS)
They just don't understand, do they, Cleo?
My clocks, they mean everything to me.
(GLASS CLINKING)
- My clocks are my most special creations.
- (FIGARO MEOWS)
I made them for my beloved Constanza,
and she loved every one of them.
Every one of them.
Oh. (SPLUTTERS) But never as much
as she loved you, my dear boy.
Hmm.
My dear boy.
(FIGARO MEOWS)
(CHUCKLING)
No more of these sad thoughts, huh?
Time for some happiness.
This is why I gave you a smile.
So that you will always be happy.
What is your name?
(LAUGHS)
You should have a name of your own.
Yes, yes. Now, what should it be?
What should it be?
I carved you out of wood.
I made you out of pine.
You're a boy made out of pine.
Pine-occhio. Pine-occhio. Pinocchio. Huh?
Pinocchio. Yeah.
(LAUGHS) Uh...
Do... Do you approve
of the name "Pinocchio"?
Yes, yes.
(LAUGHING)
You see, Figaro. Do you love
the name "Pinocchio"?
- (FIGARO MEOWS)
- Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
- (LAUGHS)
- (MEOWS)
(AMUSING MUSIC PLAYING)
Ow! Hey! (GRUNTING)
Hey. (SCREAMS) No!
- (LAUGHING)
- (MEOWING)
(GEPPETTO SCATTING)
Oh, let's dance.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Whoa! Ow!
You call this music?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Don't you be afraid, Figaro. No.
No. Why? Because he likes you.
(LAUGHING)
Oh! Oh!
Figaro, no, no.
(GRUNTS) Even Cleo thinks
he's very, very handsome.
(WATER BUBBLING)
(GRUNTS) Figaro, come.
Don't be such a scaredy cat!
(MEOWING)
(SCATTING)
(CONTINUES SCATTING)
(MUSIC SLOWS DOWN)
- (MUSIC STOPS)
- (FIGARO WHINES)
Oh, Figaro.
- What?
- (MEWING)
Oh. Oh. Yes, yes. Almost time, but...
Wait for it. Wait for it.
(CLOCKS TICKING)
(CLOCKS RINGING)
(NEIGHS)
(QUACKING)
(CROW CAWING)
(RINGING STOPS)
Yes. Yeah.
(SIGHS) Now, it is time for bed.
- (MEOWS)
- Yes.
Good night, Cleo, ah,
my little water baby. (CHUCKLES)
(SOFTLY) Good night.
(YAWNS)
Good night, my beautiful birthday boy.
(KISSES)
(MEOWS)
(GURGLING)
(SNORES)
(SNORING)
(GEPPETTO GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(MUTTERS INDISTINCTLY)
Oh.
Oh, what a beautiful clear night.
Ah! Beautiful.
(LAUGHING)
Figaro, look at Pinocchio
there in the moonlight.
He looks almost like a real boy.
(CHUCKLES)
(GASPS) Look, Figaro. Look, look, look.
It's... It's the wishing star.
Oh!
I haven't seen one in so...
We should make a wish, huh? Yeah?
Star light, star bright.
First star I see tonight.
I wish...
Hmm.
(MUTTERS)
How do I say this?
(SOFTLY) I wish... I wish...
I wish...
(ENCHANTING INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GEPPETTO CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Figaro, do you want to know
what I wished for? I wished...
No, no. If I was to tell you,
you would think I was...
(CLOCK RINGING)
The problem with that one clock,
it talks too much.
(LAUGHING)
Get it? Get it? It talks too much.
Tick-tock, the clock tick-tocks too much?
(LAUGHING)
Ah. never mind. It's late.
(SIGHS)
(YAWNS) Still,
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
If my wish came true, Figaro,
that would be wonderful.
(SIGHS)
Wonderful.
(SNORING)
(MYSTICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(TICKING)
(TICKING SLOWS DOWN)
(CLOCK RINGS)
(MYSTICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(RATTLING)
(MYSTICAL NOTES PLAYING)
(ENCHANTING INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)
(GASPS)
Jumpin' jeepers. He's alive.
(SNORING)
(PURRING)
(CHIRPS)
Now see here. What's this all about?
(GASPS)
- Holy moly. You can walk.
- "Holy moly. You can walk."
Shut my mouth. You can talk.
"Shut my mouth. You can talk."
- No, you can talk.
- "No, you can talk."
- I know I can talk. And so can you.
- "I know I can talk. And so can you."
BLUE FAIRY: All right, all right.
All right, all right, all right.
Everyone can relax. I'm here now.
What seems to be the...
Oh, yes. I see what the problem is.
As I live and breathe. A fairy!
You're not really real, are you?
Of course he's real! He's alive, isn't he?
- And who might you be?
- Jiminy Cricket.
Bug, boulevardier, flâneur,
man of leisure. And who might you be?
Oh, the good Geppetto made a wish from
the depths of his heart and so I'm here.
- I'm the Blue Fairy.
- "I'm the Blue Fairy."
- No, I'm the Blue Fairy.
- "No, I'm the Blue Fairy."
Oh, I see what the problem is here.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(MAGICAL NOTES CHIMING)
- Let's try this again. I'm the Blue Fairy.
- Hello, Blue Fairy!
That's more like it.
Yes, I'm the Blue Fairy.
- Now, what's your name?
- I don't know.
I heard Geppetto name him Pinocchio.
(CHUCKLES) My name is Pinocchio.
Sounds like your head
is made of white pine. Hence, Pinocchio.
The perfect name
for a boy with a wooden head.
- PINOCCHIO: I'm a boy?
- Well, a wooden boy.
Geppetto, who lies thither sawing wood,
he's the wood-carver, I assume?
Yes, I guess you could call him
Pinocchio's pops.
- BLUE FAIRY: "Pops"?
- Yeah, Pops. Pappy. You know, father.
I mean, that is, if Pinocchio here
was a real boy.
If Geppetto wanted a real boy,
why would he carve a puppet?
Well, sure, there are other ways
to make a boy,
but I don't think Geppetto gets out much,
and I guess it's the best
he could do with the tools he's got.
Of course, I'm just a talking cricket,
so I'm not one to pass judgment
on what's real.
- Ms. Blue Fairy, am I real?
- Yes, Pinocchio, you're real, all right.
A real, live, living puppet that's painted
to look like a real, live, living boy.
Almost what your father wished for.
So when do I become a real,
real, live, living boy?
Because it sounds like that's
what will make my father happy.
BLUE FAIRY: "Little puppet made of pine
Geppetto's wish went up the line
"But his feelings were tangled
And knotted like twine
"Then light from a star gave life to a toy
A marionette boy full of wonder and joy
"But to be truly real
He had to pass an ordeal"
(GEPPETTO SNORING)
Geppetto has done his part,
and I have done mine.
And to be real is up to you.
You have to prove that you are brave,
truthful and unselfish.
PINOCCHIO: How do I do that?
Well, by learning to choose
between right and wrong.
- Okay, but how do I do that?
- Your conscience will tell you.
"Con Shuns"? Who are they?
No, no. "Conscience."
Abstract, noun, singular.
A conscience is that still small voice
that most people refuse to listen to.
(GRUNTS) And that is the entire problem
with the world today.
Are you my conscience?
Huh? Me? No, I'm not a conscience.
I'm a cricket.
More of an insect than an instinct.
BLUE FAIRY: Would you like
to be his conscience?
Me? No, thanks.
I've, uh, got enough on my plate.
Oh, really? I see a lost soul,
an insect of no fixed address.
An aimless vagabond
hopping from hearth to hearth
with no direction, no job,
no prospects and no purpose in life.
Now look here.
Just because a fella sneaks into
somebody's house to warm his backside,
and sure, he might have gotten
kicked out of a place or two, but...
- (SIGHS) Okay, you have a point.
- BLUE FAIRY: Here's the thing.
Do you know the difference
between right and wrong?
You're darn tootin', I do.
I consider myself a bug
of high moral standards,
no matter what you may have heard.
Well, that settles it then.
Kneel, Mr. Cricket.
I hereby appoint you
Pinocchio's conscience.
- Uh, temporary conscience.
- Sure. Temporary conscience.
Until such time
as Pinocchio may grow his own.
Henceforth, you are the high keeper
of the knowledge of right and wrong,
and a trusted counselor
during moments of temptation.
(MAGICAL NOTES CHIME)
Arise, Sir Jiminy Cricket.
(WHISTLES)
- Hey! This is more like it.
- (BLUE FAIRY CHUCKLES)
"Let your job restore your pride
And let your conscience be your guide
"For now, my dear Pinocchio
The time has come for me to go"
Oh, boy. She's rhyming again.
Looks like we're about to be on our own.
Pinocchio, when a boy
is brave, truthful and unselfish,
it makes his father proud.
And the most important part about
being real isn't what you're made of.
It's about what's in your heart.
(SINGING) Fate is kind
She brings to those who love
The sweet fulfillment of
Their secret longing
Like a bolt out of the blue
Fate steps in and sees you through
When you wish upon a star
Your dreams
Come true
(GRUNTS)
What was that? I heard something.
(MEOWS)
I heard something.
(RATTLING SOFTLY)
Figaro, Figaro,
did you hear something, too?
I heard something.
(MUTTERS INDISTINCTLY)
You? Did you...
- Did you hear something, Figaro?
- (MEOWS)
I heard something. Yes, I did.
I heard. I heard something.
What about you?
Cleo, did you hear anything?
(WATER BUBBLES)
- Pinocchio, did you hear anything?
- I sure did!
All right. I heard something, too.
And now that you can talk...
Hello, Pops.
(GASPS)
- (SCREAMING)
- (FIGARO SHRIEKING)
(CLOCKS RINGING)
(GASPING)
(TRUMPETING)
- (SQUEALS)
- (BABY CRIES)
(RINGING STOPS)
(SHUDDERING)
It's me, Pinocchio!
- You talk!
- Yeah. And I can walk.
(GASPS)
How? How can you walk? How can you talk?
The Blue Fairy. She said you made a wish.
Blue Fairy? The Blue Fairy!
I did make a wish.
I wished... I wished that my...
I know. A real boy. But guess what?
I'm almost a real boy,
and I can become one.
All I have to do is, uh...
A bunch of stuff.
An almost real boy?
An almost real boy.
Uh-huh.
(LAUGHING)
(JOYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHUCKLING) An almost real boy!
(LAUGHING)
An almost real boy!
Look... Look at you. Look. Look at you!
You are an almost real boy!
We can be... We can be a family.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, an almost real boy! Oh!
We must have music.
(AMUSING MUSIC PLAYING)
Dance. Can you dance, Pinocchio?
(LAUGHING)
(SINGING) I'll design
The perfect wooden shoe
And then we'll sing and dance
The whole day through
If you get splinters
I'll be there with glue
I'll take care of you
(LAUGHS) Yes, I will
Pinocchio, Pinocchio
Holy smoke-io
My dear son made of wood
Pinocchio, Pinocchio
I think you...
(CONTINUES SINGING INDISTINCTLY)
May I? Thank you. Much obliged.
And you think it is good
And so Pinocchio became
part of Geppetto's little family.
And despite a few minor
blended family issues...
(GLASS BREAKING)
...they became a stable,
well-adjusted household.
Pinocchio!
(SIGHING WEARILY)
Pinocchio, I have been thinking.
Maybe it is time for you to go to school.
Really, Father? Really?
(PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
- Whoa!
- (MEOWING)
(GEPPETTO GRUNTS)
Father, what's that big shining thing?
Oh! That's...
That is the sun, my son.
It goes around the Earth once a day.
It's basic, simple science.
You'll learn all about it in school.
Ah! And here are your new schoolmates,
and, ah, Signora Vitelli. Buongiorno.
Geppetto.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
GEPPETTO: (IN ENGLISH)
Oh, oh, oh, Pinocchio! Wait, wait.
Figaro, yes.
It's been so long, I nearly forgot it.
This is your lesson book.
And this is an apple for your teacher.
Now turn around. Let me get a look at you.
Oh.
Very handsome, very handsome.
(CHUCKLES)
Now, Pinocchio.
This town can be very confusing.
There are many, many curving streets,
so pay attention.
And if you get lost, just remember
we are two streets down from the fountain.
I'll come straight home
right after school.
I will be right here when you get back.
And we will eat dinner precisely
at the stroke of 5:00.
Got it, Father. The stroke of 5:00.
(CHUCKLES)
(SOFT EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHUCKLING)
That's right. There you go.
(MEOWING)
Oh! Oh, no! No. Ah!
Figaro, Figaro, no. Off he goes.
My boy.
(SQUAWKING)
Ah! Well, buongiorno, Sofia.
(SPEAKS ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Ah! I have some
very good garbage for you.
Ah, there we are.
(GRUNTING)
Mmm. Yum-yum-yum-yum!
(SMACKS LIPS) Mmm!
- (SNORING)
- (LAUGHING)
You miss him already, don't you?
Yes. Well, yes.
- I miss him, too.
- (MEOWS)
Already, yes. Figaro, do you miss him?
Yes? Yes? Well, going to school,
it will be good for him.
(GASPS) School? Jumpin' jeepers.
What time is it?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
First real day on the job
and I'm already late!
- (SQUAWKS)
- (SCREAMING)
Don't eat me! Don't eat me! Don't eat me!
Calm down. I don't like bugs.
Too much work. I prefer garbage.
(SIGHS) Thanks, I guess. That's a relief.
I thought I was a goner for sure.
- Cricket's the name. Jiminy Cricket.
- Nice to meet you. I'm Sofia.
So you're new in town.
It's a great little...
Excuse me, Sofia. I'm sorry to interrupt,
but I'm Pinocchio's conscience,
and I overslept.
Could you do me a giant favor
and airlift me to the school?
Asleep on the job, huh?
Who knew they were
outsourcing conscience work?
- Back in my day...
- Sofia, I really need to get to him.
This little puppet is running around loose
on the streets without a conscience.
Can you imagine the trouble
he's gonna get into?
Well, I wouldn't want that
on my conscience.
Okay, Mr. Right or Wrong.
Hold on to your hat.
(SCREAMING)
(SCATTING)
(GASPS) Well, well, well. Stromboli!
So that old rascal's back in town.
Gideon, remember the time
I tied strings on you
- and passed you off as a puppet?
- (FLY BUZZING)
(LAUGHING)
Remember when he found out? How he beat...
- Oh. (SHUSHES)
- (KIDS LAUGHING)
Gideon, listen.
The merry laughter of innocent children
wending their way to school.
Their thirsty minds
rushing to the fountain of knowledge.
(SIGHS) School, a noble institution.
What would this
stupid world be without it?
Well, look at that. A wooden boy.
(GASPS) A wooden boy!
Look at that, Gideon. It's amazing.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
A living puppet without strings!
(FLIES BUZZING)
(SNIFFS) Ugh.
(YELPS)
(SCOLDING INDISTINCTLY)
(GASPS) Gideon, a thing like that
could be worth a fortune to someone.
Let me see. Who would pay for a living...
(GASPS) That's it. Stromboli! (LAUGHS)
He'll give his eye teeth for that thing.
I can't wait to get to school
and learn what all this stuff is.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Quick. We'll cut him off.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh! Oh, oh, God. Oh, oh, my, my.
How clumsy of me. I am terribly sorry.
- I do hope you're not injured?
- Injured?
Damaged, broken,
irreparably splintered beyond repair.
I'm not broken.
(SIGHS) Thank heavens. You must be
constructed of pretty sturdy oak.
I'm pine. That's why I'm called...
Yes, pine. Well, we can't all be
constructed of quality lumber. (LAUGHS)
Well, well. Quite the scholar, I see.
A man of letters.
I presume you're on your way
to lecture at the science academy?
PINOCCHIO: No. I'm going to school
so I can learn a bunch of stuff
to be a real boy and make my father proud.
A real boy?
Why on earth would you want to be real
when you can be famous?
- Famous?
- Yes, famous.
I'm speaking of the theater.
Bright lights. Music. Applause. Fame!
Fame? But I want to be real.
Yes, yes, my boy.
But did you know, many people say
that you're not actually real
until everybody knows about you?
Why, to be famous is to be real.
Until then, you're just a nobody.
Do you want to be a nobody?
No! Nobody wants to be a nobody.
Everybody who's anybody
wants to be a somebody.
But my father said I should go to school.
Of course he did. All parents say that.
But he doesn't recognize your genius.
Who needs an education
when one has such a personality,
such a profile, such a physique?
Why, he is a natural born actor.
Right, Gideon?
And not just an actor. An entrepreneur.
Nay, an influencer.
And won't your father be proud?
- Really?
- Oh, of course he will.
Why, he'll see your name in lights.
Lights six feet high!
- Say, what is your name?
- Pinocchio.
Pinocchio.
P-I-N-O...
Probably a K.
Never mind. Too many letters.
We need a simple, strong stage name.
Slab Oakley. Chad Log. (GASPS)
I've got it. Chris Pine.
No, it'd never work.
We are wasting precious time.
Do you want to make
your father proud or not?
- I sure do.
- Well, then?
- Okay, I'll be famous.
- Capital!
- (UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
- (SINGING) Hi-diddle-dee-dee
An actor's life for me
A high silk hat and a silver cane
A watch of gold with a diamond chain
Hi-diddle-dee-dee
An actor's life is gay
It's great to be a celebrity
An actor's life for me
Oh, there. I see him.
Straight ahead. 12 o'clock.
(HONEST JOHN SINGING)
(JIMINY SCREAMING)
Pardon me, folks. Pardon me.
Passing through.
(SIGHS) Thanks, Sofia.
(JIMINY YELLING)
(GASPS)
(HONEST JOHN SCATTING)
(JIMINY PANTING)
- (JIMINY WHISTLES)
- What?
Jiminy, what are you doing up there?
What? Who? Who are we talking to?
What is a Jiminy? Wait, wait. I can't...
It's where? Where are you looking?
Are you saying that...
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(GROANING SOFTLY)
(CHIRPS)
(THUDS)
Jiminy, guess what?
I don't need to go to school.
I'm gonna be famous instead.
And that'll make Father proud.
All right. Now calm down, son.
Remember what I said about temptation?
Well, that's him.
Oh, no, that's Mr. Honest John.
He's my agent.
Honest John?
Pinokes, as a rule of thumb,
when somebody calls themselves "honest,"
they ain't.
Especially, if they're an agent.
So having just been duly
assigned to you as your conscience,
I'm telling you, forget all these
big-headed ideas about being famous
and get to school.
That's what your father wants you to do.
But Honest John said
my father wants me to be famous.
Well, it's like I said, kiddo.
Honest John ain't.
But you said if somebody
says they're honest, they aren't.
- Who am I supposed to believe?
- Well, that is the age-old question.
But I'd trust the guy the Blue Fairy
assigned to the case. Wouldn't you?
- Jiminy Cricket, temporary conscience?
- Well, then, I want to go to school.
Now we're talking. (CHIRPS)
School's that-a-way.
- (GROANING)
- Hey, Pinoke. Drop the mallet.
(GROANS) Oof!
JIMINY: Hold up here, Pinoke.
(KIDS CHATTERING)
Boy, they ought to do something
about all the loose gravel on this road.
One of these days, a heavy wagon wheel's
gonna fling one of these rocks
and hurt somebody.
- What in Sam Hill do we pay taxes for?
- What are taxes?
Nothing you need to worry about,
now that you won't be famous.
But here's what you do
need to know about school.
One, pay attention.
Two, obey all the rules.
And three, do whatever
the teacher tells you to do.
- Got it?
- Got it.
(CHIRPS)
- Aren't you coming with me?
- Uh, no, Pinoke.
Most schools don't take kindly to insects.
They lump me in with wasps,
cockroaches and termites.
I'll be waiting for you here
when school lets out.
- Get you home by the stroke of 3:17.
- Okay, Jiminy.
Whoa! See what I mean?
(SCHOOL BELL DINGING)
(KIDS CHATTERING)
He's a good kid, right?
And here's the good news.
It seems Pinocchio is serious about
becoming brave, truthful and unselfish.
And he listened to his conscience.
I bet you were thinking
I dropped the ball.
But old Jiminy picked up the fumble
and it's smooth sailing from here.
HEADMASTER: Out! Get out.
- Get out and stay out.
- (KIDS LAUGHING)
School is for real children.
Not ridiculous puppets.
Puppets belong in the puppet show.
Ah, come on.
Well, I'll be.
(HONEST JOHN LAUGHING)
Hey. What's the big idea?
Get me out of here!
(GRUNTING)
Let me out.
(GASPS) This is an outrage, an atrocity.
I don't think that teacher likes me.
Oh, who cares what he thinks?
His pedagogy is completely outdated.
Is his curriculum child-led?
Brain-based for a growth mindset?
I think not. He makes no room
for different learning styles.
He said I didn't belong.
All the kids laughed at me.
Of course they did.
Puppets make people laugh.
Oh, you poor, poor misunderstood boy.
Don't you see?
You don't fit in a traditional
educational environment.
You are misunderstood, just like every
great actor who ever walked the earth.
School is for ordinary, humdrum,
common, boring, silly little children!
Not brilliant artists like yourself.
It's fame you want. Fame and fortune.
- But my father...
- Wanted you to go to school and you did.
You went to school.
You gave it the old college try.
And what did
the wise and learned schoolmaster say?
He said I belong in a puppet show.
(GASPS) Alas, a puppet show.
I rest my case.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
- Now we're talking! (LAUGHING)
- No!
To Stromboli's. Fame awaits!
(SINGING) Hi-diddle-dee-dee
An actor's life for me
A wax mustache and a beaver coat
A pony cart and a billy goat
Hi-diddle-dee-dum
-An actor's life is fun
-(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
You wear your hair in a pompadour
You ride around in a coach-and-four
You stop and buy out a candy store
An actor's life for me...
No. Pinocchio, don't listen to him!
- (HONEST JOHN CONTINUES SINGING)
- No! Don't listen to him, Pinoke.
No! Pinoke, no.
No!
(GLASS SQUEAKING)
- (CLOCKS RINGING)
- It's 5:00.5:00.
Pinocchio should have been home by now.
He must have lost his way and...
And gotten lost.
- Well, come on, everyone.
- (MEOWS)
Yes. You too, Figaro. Figaro.
I haven't left the shop since...
Well, but...
we have to find Pinocchio.
Ladies and gentlemen.
(FANFARE PLAYING)
To complete the performance
of my great show,
Stromboli the master showman
and the greatest theatrical maestro
on the face of the earth...
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
- That's me.
- (AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
And by special permission
of the management...
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
- That's me too.
- (AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
I present to you something that
you will absolutely refuse to believe.
Introducing the eighth
wonder of the world,
the only marionette who can sing
and dance without the aid of strings.
- (AUDIENCE GASPS)
- The toy who thinks he's a boy.
So it's true. Stromboli got
his grubby hands on a magic puppet.
(CHUCKLES)
You have my condolences.
Oh, do you want them back?
(CHUCKLES)
- You're sweet.
- I'm Pinocchio.
I'm here to be famous so I can be
a real boy and then make my father proud.
And I'm Fabiana,
and I'm never gonna be famous.
Not unless I can figure some way
out of this two-bit, small-time
sad excuse for a puppet show.
(SIGHS)
Never mind.
I'm just having a rough day. Sorry.
- Why do I have strings?
- FABIANA: Part of the show.
One of Stromboli's
last-minute brainstorms. See? Slip knots.
(CHUCKLES)
You haven't met Sabina yet, have you?
I think you two could be friends.
She looks like she has strong legs.
(CHUCKLING) Your legs look sturdy, too.
Are they made of pine?
Yeah. But soon they're gonna be real.
Give them a try tonight.
- Break a leg.
- (GASPS) Really?
FABIANA: No, not really.
PINOCCHIO: Oh.
(THUDDING)
Did you hurt your leg?
It's a long story,
but it gets better every day.
(STROMBOLI ANNOUNCING INDISTINCTLY)
The only marionette who can sing
and dance without the aid of strings.
- (DRUM ROLL PLAYING)
- The toy who thinks he's a boy.
The one and only Pinocchio!
- (AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
- (HISSING)
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
(PLAYING FANFARE)
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING
AND APPLAUDING)
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SINGING) I've got no strings
To hold me down
To make me fret, or make me frown...
- (GASPS)
- (AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(ALL LAUGHING AND APPLAUDING)
(STROMBOLI LAUGHING)
(IN ENGLISH) Stupid puppet.
(LAUGHING)
Once more.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SINGING) I've got no strings
To hold me down
To make me fret, or make me frown
I had strings, but now I'm free
There are no strings on me
Hi-ho, the merry-o
That's the only way to be
I want the world to know
Nothing ever worries me
I've got no strings, so I have fun
I'm not tied up to anyone
They've got strings
But you can see there are no strings on me
(AUDIENCE CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
(ENTHRALLING INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(UPBEAT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(AUDIENCE CLAPPING RHYTHMICALLY)
(YELLS)
(MUSIC INCREASES IN TEMPO)
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
(YELLS AND SPLUTTERS)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
(MACHINE POWERING DOWN)
(SINGING) There are no strings on me
(AUDIENCE CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
(COINS CLINKING)
(IN ENGLISH) Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
(STROMBOLI LAUGHING)
Grazie. Grazie. Thank you.
- (DONKEY BRAYING)
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
(STROMBOLI SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(CREAKING)
(FABIANA VOCALIZING IN DISTANCE)
FABIANA: (SINGING)
I may not be a ballerina
But I'll always dance
And I may not sway in partner
But I'll know romance
-Half-human, half-marionette
-(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
I'm practicing my pirouette
I'll move without apology
And every step will set me free
I will always dance and dream of my plié
They'll see with just one glance
Me land a grand jeté
They'll smile and they'll all talk
I'll still need help to walk
But I will always
-Dance
-(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Start with the tango and then the salsa
And there's the rumba
And then we cha-cha-cha
The Paso doble, the quickstep
The two-step, the foxtrot
Merengue, bachata, the mambo, the bomb a
The plena, the samba
The kathak, kabuki and more
All you need is your feet
And a beat and the floor
You'll find your flow
And that's when you let go
Let it go like a child
And be free and be wild
Just do can-cans, not can'ts
Like the girls do in France
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
- (STROMBOLI SHOUTS IN ITALIAN)
- (GRUNTING)
(IN ENGLISH) What's this nonsense?
- Nobody in my show performs for free.
- (GASPS)
Now pack. We leave in an hour.
And you...
Ooh, ooh, ooh. My little Pinocchio.
I was scared to death
you got lost or stolen.
And we wouldn't want that now, would we?
In an hour we go.
(YELLS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- There.
- Let me go. Let me out of here.
- This will be your home.
- Help!
- Where I can find you. Always.
- Oh, no.
No, no!
Yes, yes. To me you are belong.
Let me go. Let me out of here.
Help! Father!
Father? No parent
wants a bizzaria like you.
PINOCCHIO: No, no!
Parents want a real kid.
Jiminy. Father. Help! Help!
Oh, no. Help!
(WHIMPERING) Please.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) My little wooden gold mine.
(LAUGHS MALICIOUSLY)
(CRYING)
GEPPETTO: Pinocchio!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Pinocchio!
JIMINY: Geppetto.
I'm here inside this jar!
GEPPETTO: Pinocchio!
JIMINY: Geppetto! Geppetto!
Pinocchio!
(MEOWS)
Oh, Figaro, Cleo, where can he be?
Pinocchio!
JIMINY: Geppetto!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
FABIANA: Psst. Psst.
Pinocchio. Pinocchio.
I'm up here. In the ceiling.
Stromboli is a horrible, mean man.
But we're going to help you.
Leave me alone.
FABIANA: We're going to figure out a way
to get you out of that cage.
Did you hear what I said?
We're going to help you.
Pinocchio, look at me. You can trust me.
You're a real person, and the only
real person I can believe is my father.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING)
I like the way you dance.
We haven't been formally introduced.
I'm Sabina.
I'm Pinocchio.
Thank you for getting my nose unstuck.
Well, you know what they say.
The show must go on.
- You're a wonderful dancer.
- Thank you.
It's too bad we have to meet
under these awful circumstances.
Mr. Stromboli said I could go home
and tell my father I got famous.
But then he locked me up.
Ah!
So now you don't trust anybody?
Well, I trust you. Sort of.
Thank you. I'll try to be worthy of it.
You see that key hanging on the wall?
- That's the key to this cage.
- (KEY CLINKS)
We have to get it somehow
and get you out of here.
But that could get you in trouble.
Pinocchio, can I trust you with something?
When we get to the next village,
we puppets and puppeteers
are going to take back the money
Stromboli stole from us and escape.
- Escape?
- Yes. Run away.
And then we're going
to start our own show.
And we will treat all the members
of our troupe fairly and kindly, and...
- (DOOR OPENS)
- (GASPS)
What's going on in here?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GULPS)
(STROMBOLI LAUGHING)
Pinocchio. My little Pinocchio.
Are you okay? You should get some rest.
Tomorrow we have a big show in Siena.
The Sienese love puppets.
They will give us lots of money.
(LAUGHING)
(SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING)
Just to be sure
there is no funny business.
Except on stage.
Then lots of funny business.
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Well, I guess this is it.
This is how it ends.
Starving to death in a pickle jar.
No, sirree. I thought I'd live to be 103.
Of course, this never would've happened
if I hadn't gotten into
the conscience business.
As I live and breathe.
Stromboli's puppet show.
I wonder if Pinoke
ever got a chance to... (GASPS)
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (EXHALES)
Pinoke! Hey, Pinocchio.
Over here. It's Jiminy!
I can't believe it.
We're so close and yet so far.
- (CLINKS)
- Whoa!
(STRAINING)
(SIGHS)
Well, I'll be.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
Psst. Pinocchio. Pinocchio. Listen up.
Jiminy. Gee, am I glad to see you.
Stromboli locked me in this cage.
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
Locked solid. Well, Pinoke, I guess
this isn't what you signed up for
when you decided to be
a famous actor, is it?
It's not my fault.
I never wanted to be famous.
(NOSE SQUEAKS)
Sorry, kiddo.
That's not the way I remember it.
But I didn't want to be famous.
I wanted to go to school.
- Hey.
- It's true.
All of those people
cheering and applauding. I hated it.
- BOTH: Whoa!
- What's happening, Jiminy?
Looks like some sort of fairy magic.
Kind of on the nose, if you ask me.
But the point is, a lie
can really change a person, Pinokes.
Which is why I'm telling you
the 110% most honestly honest,
truthiest truthiness ever.
Believe me.
(NOSE SQUEAKS)
Oops. Okay, that last part wasn't true.
But everything I said up until then was.
(YELPS)
Jiminy, you okay?
More or less.
Now quit telling those whoppers.
Jiminy, you see that key?
Uh-huh. Yeah, I do.
That's the key to this cage lock.
Can you reach it?
(GRUNTING) Impossible.
No way I can reach that.
Hey, Jiminy. You want to know something?
I don't want to be a real boy.
(NOSE SQUEAKS)
- (GRUNTS)
- Ow!
(CAGE CREAKING)
Whoa!
(YELLING)
Oh, Jiminy, are you okay?
Yeah, but tell me,
was that a real fib or a fib fib?
Of course it wasn't a real fib.
I had to reach the key.
I'm sorry, Jiminy.
Pinoke, remember what the Blue Fairy said?
It's not about what you're
made of on the outside.
Being real is in your heart.
That's what being real is all about.
But thank you for the apology.
Jiminy, I'm sorry I didn't
listen to you outside of school.
- (GRUNTS)
- Gotcha.
Thanks, Pinoke.
Now, swing me towards the lock.
Almost. Bull's-eye!
Ah-ha!
Hot dog! We did it.
Yeah, hot dog. What's that?
No time to explain charcuterie, pal.
- Now, let's get you home.
- Yeah.
I've met some really nice people, Jiminy.
They helped me
and they didn't even have to.
Well, that's what friends do.
One of them was a puppet like me.
Her name was Sabina.
I see. A puppet friend. Sort of a peer.
So peers are friends?
Well, not all the time, Pinokes.
You've got to be careful, because
sometimes when peers get in a group,
they like to pressure...
- (GASPS)
- (SCREAMING)
Jiminy? Where'd he go? (SCREAMING)
- (CHILDREN CHATTERING)
- Ow!
Blimey! Look what we've just
fished up off the bleeding street.
A little wooden boy!
Look at him.
He's made out of wooden slats.
I'm Lampwick. What's your name, Slats?
- My name's Pinocchio.
- KID 1: Pinocchio?
- KID 2: Pinocchi-who?
- Pinocchio.
(CHILDREN CHEERING)
So what's your story, Slats?
Why you made out of wood?
Because I'm a puppet.
But I can be a real boy.
Oh, I must say, for a puppet,
you are very clever indeed.
Only the smartest young lads
know about the collection.
Collection? What collection?
The collection for The Island,
you blockhead.
You have to be
on a deserted crossroads after dark.
You were on the corner,
so you got collected. Come on.
Oh. Okay.
But I need to find my conscience.
- (CHILDREN CHATTER)
- (COACHMAN LAUGHS)
LAMPWICK: Conscience?
PINOCCHIO: What's so funny?
(LAUGHING) You.
Your conscience is the last thing
you want to take to Pleasure Island.
Pleasure Island?
Is that where you're going?
You bet your sweet patootie
that's where we're going.
It's the greatest joy joint in the world.
No cops, no parents, no rules.
You can tear the place apart
and nobody says a word.
(LAMPWICK AND COACHMAN LAUGHING)
COACHMAN: Did I hear you correctly?
You would like to be changed,
transformed, so to speak?
PINOCCHIO: Yes.
Well, it's very fortunate
that you're coming with us,
because Pleasure Island
will be the most life-altering experience
you will ever have.
You won't be a puppet anymore,
that's for sure.
Really?
Aye. Cross my heart and hope to die.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, Mr. Coachman, it sure sounds fun.
(CHUCKLING)
But I don't trust you.
(SCREAMING) What!
(YELLS)
- Ow!
- COACHMAN: What?
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
(CREAKING)
(CHILDREN MURMURING)
Well, kids, it seems we have
a doubter in our midst.
A killjoy who apparently
doesn't believe in having fun.
I mean, who doesn't believe
in transformative experiences?
Shall we all turn tail
and go running back to Mommy and Daddy?
CHILDREN: No!
Look, you kids go. I'll go another time.
Oh, I'm sorry. It doesn't work that way.
(SINGING) It's only peer pressure
Unless you're not a peer
If you won't be like all these kids
There's nothing for you here
Don't trust me Trust all of them
The time has come
Don't cut and run
It's sink or swim Do or die
Are you with us on this ride?
Now you must decide
Don't be a party pooper
Afraid of having fun
It's all for one and one for all
The game is on
Don't drop the ball
You take the fall
And ruin it for everyone
CHILDREN: Yeah.
-Real boys always want more
-CHILDREN: Always want more
And real girls always like
The real boys more
Talking all this nonsense
About a so-called conscience
You're not gonna need that anymore
(CHILDREN EXCLAIM)
(CHILDREN EXCLAIMING)
- (BRAYING)
- (CRACKS WHIP)
What a bore.
(SINGING) So play, play
Time to play
All your troubles melt away
Play, play Time to play
Now it's time to play
So tell us what you say
(NECK CLICKING)
(SHAKILY) Okay, then.
I say we all...
go.
CHILDREN: (CHEERING) Yeah!
All right, then. Pleasure Island awaits.
(CHILDREN CHEERING)
COACHMAN: Hyah!
(SCREAMING)
Whoa!
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(YELPS)
Pinocchio. No!
(ALL CHEERING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Welcome to Pleasure Island!
Come right inside.
- Enjoy the ride and see the show.
- LAMPWICK: Get on the boat! Come on.
COACHMAN: There's so much fun here
to keep you smiling.
And no one is ever gonna tell you "No."
Look at that, Slats.
Whoa.
- (CHILDREN CHEERING)
- (FIREWORKS BURSTING)
BOY 1: Root beer!
BOY 2: Root beer.
BOY 3: Look! Free root beer!
BOY 4: Root beer!
Here you go, gents. Have a tall one.
They're on the house.
Better yet, have two. Bottoms up!
BOY 5: So much root beer!
BOY 6: Yes! A life supply of root beer!
BOY 7: I know!
Look at all that root beer!
(LAUGHING)
(THRILLING INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, give me that root beer! (LAUGHS)
LAMPWICK: That kid's crazy.
Ouch.
(LAUGHS MISCHIEVOUSLY)
(ENTHRALLING INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
LAMPWICK: (CHUCKLING) Whoa!
Hey!
Whoo-hoo! (LAUGHING)
(CHILDREN SQUEALING IN DELIGHT)
Whoa! (CHUCKLING)
Great move, Pinoke.
(CHUCKLING) Whoa!
(LAUGHING)
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
(CHOMPING)
(GAGS)
(LAUGHING)
(GLASS BREAKING)
LAMPWICK: Look at them kids.
They're swiping everything
out of that joint.
Give me that.
Push it!
(CHILDREN CHEER)
Hey, Slats.
(GLASS BREAKING)
(FIREWORKS SHOOTING)
Whoa!
(YELPS)
That jerk got a fire lit under him,
that's for sure!
(CHILDREN YELLING INSULTS)
(INSULTING CONTINUES)
Hey, I like these guys.
(GONG SOUNDS LOUDLY)
(CHILDREN YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
Hey, Slats, we got to come back here
and bust up some clocks.
- (CHUCKLING)
- They look like my father's clocks.
Oh, yeah? Watch this.
Bull's-eye!
(LAUGHS)
- You're up, Slats.
- No, thanks.
Something tells me my father might not
be too happy if he knew I was here.
(SINGING) Talking all this nonsense
About a so-called conscience
You're not gonna need that anymore
So play, play
Play, play Time to play
It was wrong of me to send him
off to school like a real boy.
Never should have done that. Never.
What in blazes?
- Oh, Sofia, is that you? What?
- (SQUAWKS)
What does this mean?
"Pleasure Island." Pleasure Island?
- Is this where Pinocchio is?
- (SQUAWKS)
Oh, my goodness. This is a serious crisis.
A catastrophe!
Oh!
Now we're talking. Am I great or what?
It's awfully quiet.
Where do you suppose
all the kids went, Lampy?
They're around here somewhere.
What do you care?
They're all losers anyway.
Four in the corner.
- Oh! Look at that.
- (HICCUPS)
Another perfect shot,
if I do say so myself.
(BRAYING)
(DONKEY WHINING)
Huh. I wonder where everybody is.
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (CREATURES GROWLING)
(WHIMPERING)
(SHRIEKING)
(ROARS)
What the cuss is that all about?
Ap-cray! Scratched it.
Something wrong with the table.
It's tilted or something.
Okay, Slats. Your shot.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Hey, Slats. There's something
I've been meaning to ask you.
How come you didn't bust
any of them cuckoo clocks?
Any real kid would love
to smash those clocks.
It just didn't feel right.
(LAMPWICK LAUGHS)
Listen to Mr. Goody Two-Shoes.
Well, I guess you ain't transformed
into a complete jerk yet. (CHUCKLES)
I don't want to be a jerk.
I want to be a real boy.
(SCOFFS) The way you're going,
you might make it to half a real boy.
It looks to me like you still got
a conscience inside of you.
- (JIMINY CHIRPING)
- I wish I still did have a conscience.
Pinocchio!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(DONKEYS BRAYING)
(CREATURES GROWLING)
(DONKEYS WHIMPERING AND BRAYING)
What's with all the donkeys?
(BRAYING)
Oh, brother.
It's like I've dropped into
H-E-double hockey sticks.
COACHMAN: Let's move it, you scum.
The sooner these donkeys get to
the salt mines, the sooner I get paid.
- (BRAYING)
- (CREATURE GROWLING)
I still say it's not right to yell
right as somebody's about to make a shot.
Get over it.
Everybody knows psyching out
your opponent is a great strategy.
You gotta do what you gotta do to win.
You're wrong, Lampy.
I still call what you did cheating.
Come on. To hear you talk,
you'd think something terrible
was gonna happen to us.
(GASPS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
LAMPWICK: Conscience, right.
(FABRIC RIPPING)
What a crock.
Uh, Lampy, you might want to check your...
- Who do I look like to you? A jackass?
- (PINOCCHIO GASPS)
(BRAYS)
(LAUGHS) You sure are...
Hey, you sound just like a donkey...
(BRAYS)
Did that come out of me? (BRAYS)
Uh-huh.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WHIMPERING)
(BRAYS)
(SCREAMS)
(BRAYING)
Help!
Somebody help me. I've been
double-crossed. I've been played!
(BRAYING)
Help me, please! Anybody!
Anybody, please! Just call anybody!
Help me, please.
Mama! Mama!
(BRAYING)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Oh, no. What's happening? What do I do?
Help! Help! Jiminy! Jiminy!
Jiminy! Jiminy!
(SCREAMING)
Pinoke, let's get out of here.
The kids, they're all turning
into donkey... (GASPS)
Oh, no! You too?
COACHMAN: Oh. These brats.
(CREATURES GROWLING)
There's that wooden boy. Get him!
- (BRAYING)
- Whoa!
Jiminy, let's go.
You said it, Pinoke.
Let's skedaddle out of here.
(PIANO KEYS PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
There they go! (YELLS)
Faster! Don't let them get to the sea.
Whoa!
(SCREAMING)
Oh, no. We're trapped.
No, we're not. Positive thinking, Jiminy.
Go!
(JIMINY SCREAMING)
Bollocks. Wooden donkey would
have been worth a bleeding fortune.
(SPITS)
Somebody's dropped
a barrel of salt in this water.
You're in the sea, Pinoke.
Seawater is salty.
- Now swim. Swing those arms.
- Like this?
Attaboy, Pinoke. Now you're cooking.
Let's get out of here.
- We don't want to bump into Monstro.
- Who's Monstro?
A sea monster.
He sleeps on top of the water.
So big he looks like an island. Land ho!
Father? It's me, Pinocchio. I'm home.
Maybe he's asleep.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
Look.
All of his clocks are gone.
What do you think happened to him?
(SOFIA SQUAWKING)
He sailed out to sea.
- He sailed out to sea?
SOFIA: That's right. Sailed out to sea.
Am I not speaking clearly?
- Sofia, how?
- How do you think? In a boat.
He needed to get to Pleasure Island
to look for Pinocchio.
So he sold all his clocks
and he bought a boat.
Those clocks meant everything to him.
It's his life's work.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
Gee. He sold his clocks to find me?
That's right, kiddo.
You mean more to him
than his beloved clocks.
More than anything.
Let's go.
(HOPEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
JIMINY: I don't see Geppetto anywhere.
I hope I'm wrong, but that sure
looks like Stromboli's to me.
Quick. Under the pier.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SOFIA SQUAWKS)
Look. It's Sofia.
I got an idea. I'll paddle out and see
if she knows which way Geppetto went.
You keep out of sight.
- (THUDS)
- (GASPS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPS) Pinocchio. (CHUCKLES)
Sabina? I'm so glad it's you.
(GASPS) Look. (CHUCKLING)
You've got new ears.
Uh, yeah. And a new tail.
Pinocchio, we, the members
of the New Marionette Family Theater,
have a very important proposition.
- You started your own puppet show?
- (AS SABINA) We sure did.
Last night, the Carabinieri
arrested Stromboli and put him in jail.
- (YELLS)
- Wow.
The New Marionette Family Theater!
I like it.
But there's more. We would be honored
if you would consider joining our show.
Really? You want me in your show?
Yep, donkey ears and all.
(AS SABINA) And we want you
to be the headliner.
Really? I can't think of
anything more wonderful.
But... Uh...
I have to stay and find my father.
(MAGICAL NOTES CHIME)
Pinocchio, something tells me
the decision you made is the right one.
It sure is, Pinoke.
I'm proud of you, kiddo.
And look. Your donkey ears are gone!
Yeah. My donkey ears are gone.
And your tail.
They're both gone.
Well, we've got to get going.
Perhaps I'll see you next year when we
come back to put on a show in Siena?
I hope so.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Until next year.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHIRPS)
And, Pinocchio,
please give my best to your father.
And mine, too.
- When you find him.
PINOCCHIO: I sure will.
Holy moly! I almost forgot.
Sofia said Geppetto left
about two hours ago, headed south.
She agreed to airlift us
so we can search for...
Hold on one gosh-darn minute.
Let's get something
straight here, Mr. Cricket.
I said I'd airlift you, not him.
I can't carry a heavy block of wood.
No offense, kid.
- Well, what are we gonna do?
- I have an idea.
(INSPIRATIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
No boats, nothing.
Only water as far as the eye can see.
We'll find him. Positive thinking.
(WARBLING INDISTINCTLY)
What? Pinoke, what'd she say?
(IMITATING WARBLING)
Yes, I heard that. But what did you...
Sofia? Do you see something?
(MUFFLED) Yep, yep, yep.
(GRUNTING)
Pinoke, I see a tiny boat.
- A tiny boat?
- Yes, a dinghy.
- What's a dinghy?
- A tiny boat.
(MUFFLED) Geppetto! I see Geppetto!
"Gee-pee-to." Geppetto. She sees Father!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Geppetto. It's Geppetto!
Father. It's me, Pinocchio!
(IN DISTANCE) Father!
Father, it's me, Pinocchio!
(SIGHS)
Father, it's me!
- Did you hear something, Figaro?
- (MEOWING)
Silly me. I thought I heard Pinocchio.
(MEOWING)
I must be day-dreaming.
- PINOCCHIO: Father! It's me, Pinocchio.
- (MEOWING)
Father!
Pinocchio? Running on the water?
This is a miracle. Pinocchio!
Pinocchio! You're back.
Yes, Father, I'm back. I'm coming to you.
Wait. No. I'm coming to you.
(JOYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
It's a miracle. Look at this.
You see, Cleo?
Cleo, Figaro, look! He can run on water.
Well, of course he can run on water.
He's made of wood. I'm coming, Pinocchio.
Father, I'm sorry I didn't come home
after I got kicked out of school.
You got kicked out of school?
Yes, for being a puppet.
So I joined the puppet show
and became famous.
You became famous?
PINOCCHIO: Well, almost famous.
I danced in a puppet show
and made lots of money.
But then I got kidnapped
and was locked in a bird cage,
so I had to tell a bunch of fibs to Jiminy
so my nose would grow so I could escape.
But then I got scooped up
by a coach full of foolish kids,
and was taken to Pleasure Island,
where I learned to drink...
Uh, I forget what they called it.
But anyway, Pleasure Island was bad
because I grew donkey ears
and was chased by the vapor creatures
who wanted to sell me to the salt mines.
But Jiminy helped me and we jumped off
a cliff into the sea and swam to shore,
where we found out you
sold all your clocks to buy a boat
so you could look for me.
And now we're here!
You did all that in one day?
PINOCCHIO: Yes.
My goodness. I haven't done
a fraction of that in my whole life.
I'm sorry, Father.
I apologize for all the trouble I caused.
GEPPETTO: Oh, no, Pinocchio, my boy.
All is forgiven.
I'm just so happy to see you
safe and sound.
Now we can go home again
and we'll be all together.
We'll be one big happy...
(SCREAMING)
(CREATURE ROARING)
(SHRIEKING)
Monstro! It's Monstro! It's Monstro!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MONSTRO GROWLING)
Well, I'll be. He's asleep.
Wake up! My friend's in there.
Open up, you big blubber mouth.
(MONSTRO GRUNTING)
Father! Father!
(LAUGHS) Pinocchio!
Pinocchio, you got swallowed too?
Father! Father!
(JOYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Here. Grab this.
Oh, I just hit my boy of wood
with a piece of wood.
(MEOWING)
- Oh, Pinocchio. Pinocchio.
- Hello, Pops.
(LAUGHING)
Pinocchio. Pinocchio,
I'm so happy to see you.
Oh. So happy to see my boy.
(FIGARO MEOWING)
Figaro, you're here, too. And Cleo.
Yes, yes, we're all together again.
Isn't it wonderful?
(GRUNTS)
Although, yeah, it is a bit strange
to be inside the belly of a whale.
But we will make do.
It is a bit humid, though, isn't it?
Father, I see your boat still floats.
Yes, yes. That is a good little boat.
So as soon as Monstro opens his mouth,
we can sail out of here.
Well, I don't know about that, Pinocchio.
I mean, look at all this junk.
It looks to me like everything comes in,
but nothing goes out,
except the other way, presumably,
but that is not a good option.
(SNEEZES)
(MEOWS)
- Father, what's inside that lantern?
- Ironically, whale oil.
That's right. And I have an idea.
(SCRATCHING)
Now!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
We did it, Father. Look at all that smoke.
It's wonderful, I think.
Come on, Father.
Let's get our boat into position.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
Open up. I need to get in there.
Open up, I say!
Open sesame!
(MONSTRO GROANING)
Well, what do you know?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
Whoa. Whoa!
(SCREAMING)
No, no, no!
Oh, no, oh, no, no!
(MONSTRO GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
Father, look!
GEPPETTO: Oh, oh, oh. Whoa.
Oh, oh. Oh, oh!
(MONSTRO GRUNTING)
Oh, oh!
I think he's beginning
to get irritated by the smoke.
It must be tickling his nose.
(MEOWING)
JIMINY: Pinoke. Pinoke.
- (SCREAMING)
- Jiminy. Grab on.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING AND CHIRPING)
- GEPPETTO: Jiminy? Who's Jiminy?
- My conscience.
That cricket is your conscience?
I sure am.
And let me tell you, it's no easy job.
- (MONSTRO GRUNTING)
- (YELPS)
(GEPPETTO AND JIMINY SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
Get ready, Father.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHOMPS)
(TRIUMPHANT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL GRUNT)
GEPPETTO: Pinocchio!
PINOCCHIO: Father! Father!
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
No!
(COUGHING)
Figaro, Cleo, I've got Father.
(MEOWING)
(GEPPETTO GROANS)
JIMINY: Pinoke.
PINOCCHIO: Jiminy, thank goodness.
I thought you were a goner.
Look. He sneezed us back toward land.
- (ROARING)
- Here he comes!
Everybody, hold on!
(WHIRRING)
Whoa!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(ROARING)
(MONSTRO GROWLING)
Faster, Pinoke, faster!
Spin those clodhoppers.
(GASPING)
(ROARING)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
You're almost there, Pinoke.
(MEOWING)
(WHIRRING ACCELERATES)
(CRASHING)
Father? Father?
Pinoke, you made it.
Jiminy, Father looks like he's hurt.
I have to help him.
(PANTING) You go. I'll catch up.
Father? Father, talk to me. Say something.
(SOMBER INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Father, wake up.
(MEOWING)
Father, Figaro is here. And Cleo.
They're all here.
(VOICE BREAKING) Don't die, Father.
Please don't die.
(CRYING)
(HUMMING WHEN YOU WISH UPON A STAR)
(SOBBING)
(SNIFFLES)
(CONTINUES HUMMING)
(SOBBING)
(SINGING) When you wish upon a star
Your dreams come...
(SOBBING)
(MAGICAL NOTE CHIMES)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(SOBBING)
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
(GURGLES)
(WHEN YOU WISH UPON A STAR
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING)
Pinocchio. My boy, you're here?
Yes, Father, I'm here. We're all here.
- (GROANS) Oh.
- (FIGARO MEOWING)
- Cleo? Figaro?
- (MEOWING)
(GEPPETTO LAUGHS)
Figaro, Cleo, you're all here. (LAUGHING)
Oh, I had the strangest dream.
I dreamt that we had all
been swallowed by a whale.
Yes, Father. But it wasn't a whale.
It was a sea monster, and we got out.
Oh!
Yes! Yes, we did.
Now I remember. You saved us.
You swam faster
than any clipper ship could sail.
No real boy could ever do such a thing.
Oh, Pinocchio, you honestly
did try with all your heart
and that makes you a truthful boy.
And you know what else it makes you?
Unselfish and very, very brave.
Pinocchio, when you first came to me,
I might have made you think
I wanted somebody else.
But it was you I was wishing for.
You will always be my real boy.
There isn't a single thing
I would change about you.
I am so very proud of you.
And I love you so very much.
I love you too, Father.
(LAUGHING)
(JOYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Well, well, we have come quite a long way,
haven't we, Son?
We sure have, Father.
Now let's get you home.
Yes, let's get home.
(GRUNTING)
Come on, Cleo, Figaro. But...
Pinocchio,
do you know the way?
We'll follow that light.
(INSPIRATIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
JIMINY: So in the end,
Pinocchio did prove himself
brave, honest and unselfish.
(WHEN YOU WISH UPON A STAR
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING)
And since then many stories
have been told about him.
People say he was transformed
into an honest-to-goodness real boy.
Did that actually happen? Who knows?
But I do know one thing for sure.
In his heart,
Pinocchio is as real
as any real boy could ever be.
BLUE FAIRY: (SINGING)
When you wish upon a star
Makes no difference who you are
Anything your heart desires
Will come to you
If your heart is in your dream
No request is too extreme
When you wish upon a star
As dreamers do
Fate is kind
She brings to those who love
The sweet fulfillment of
Their secret longing
Like a bolt out of the blue
Fate steps in and sees you through
When you wish upon a star
Your dreams come true
Enjoy Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP