BASED ON A TRUE STORY
A FILM BY
DENNIS GANSEL
THE WAVE
Good morning.
Making sure the kids
don't smoke in the yard, huh?
Hi, honey.
Hey, my rocker!
You know we teachers are lazy,
don't spoil our image.
Just doing some copying.
You seen Mrs Kohlhage?
No, why?
She was looking for you.
Better see what she wants.
Autocracy? I thought there was a clear deal
that I'll do the Anarchy class.
Mr Wieland showed me his outline for the whole week.
It's well thought-out.
- I'd have done mine this weekend.
- A bit late.
Wieland?
Wieland doesn't have a clue about it.
I studied in Berlin.
I`ve lived five years in the last house in Kreuzberg.
May 1st demonstrations, always there.
I'm an expert.
If it's that important,
ask Mr Wieland to trade.
Couldn't you...?
Work it out between yourselves.
Mr Wieland?
Mr Wenger.
- About the project subjects...
- Yes, and?
Could you trade with me?
I'm doing autocracy.
Alea iacta est.
The die is cast.
You know I wanted to do anarchy.
A bit too much!
Project week is for showing the students
the virtues of democracy.
How to make Molotov cocktails...
maybe only in chemistry class.
Have a nice day.
I loved you. You betrayed me.
But I haven't forgotten
my dream of life, love and trust,
the dream that once was real.
I will build it with my fortune
by destroying you.
Hey, thanks for the daisies, babe.
They'll look great
when I'm lying in the box.
He's making a fool of himself.
Know what I'm sayin', babe?
"I'll take you to Capri in your coffin..."
- He's saying it wrong.
- It's what I want to say.
Ferdi, can't we do it right through for once?
You're the one who stopped.
First stage rule:
The show must go on!
Dennis, aren't we applying
the play's criticism of capitalism to today?
That's why I'm updating the dialogue.
Okay, but don't make a joke out of it.
He can't assert himself.
Yeah, we're doing Drrenmatt,
not Quatsch Comedy-Club.
I thank you for the wreaths,
chrysanthemums and roses...
Noble.
That sounds like shit.
No way I'm saying that.
Forget it.
If Ferdi doesn't stick to his lines,
I can't do it.
I've had enough. Are you coming?
It's a pity they're not taking it seriously.
It's no use if everybody does what they want.
Coming to the game today?
Lisa and I have to study for Spanish.
Not all afternoon?
What did you sign up for?
Sign up?
Project week.
- Are the lists up already?
- Sure.
- I was thinking of autocracy.
- Me too.
Gotta go.
- Will you sign me up?
- For what?
- Whatever you take.
- Okay.
See you later.
Pull yourself together, okay?
I wanna see some real play.
Watch your defence and counter man to man.
Got it?
Eight minutes left. We can do it!
Marco, that goes for you too.
Play as a team.
Let's go!
Mogli, move the ball up!
Nice, Marco!
Marco!
Sinan's wide open!
- Marco!
- Go for it!
What are you doing, damn it?
Sinan was wide open!
Don't you want to score?
Martin, you tell me...
What are we supposed
to rebel against nowadays?
Nothing means anything anymore.
We all just want to have fun.
What our generation lacks
is a common goal to unite us.
That'd just be the Zeitgeist.
Look around.
The most Googled name on the Internet
is Paris Fucking Hilton!
- No shit.
Hey, let it out,
it`ll be better.
Stolte.
You got the dope today?
Sure I do.
- This is the real thing?
- Sure is.
A buddy brought it from Holland.
Are you nuts,
carrying that much dope?
Cops have to catch me first.
What do you want for it?
- Nothing.
- What?
It's free for you.
You're my homeys.
MONDAY
Baby.
The water's great,
probably 16 degrees.
Don't you want to go for a swim?
It'd do you good.
Maybe later.
How's your shoulder?
It's okay now.
Don't overdo it.
Yeah, sure.
Coffee?
Sure, thanks.
Morning.
What's up?
- Okay, Rainer?
- Yeah.
- Morning, Rainer.
- Sinan.
I have to say I'm surprised so many of you
are interested in autocracy.
I'd have chosen anarchy.
- Lame Wieland?
- Your words, not mine!
So...
Autocracy. What does it mean?
Come on,
you signed up for this topic,
you must have certain expectations.
No hassles, I hope.
Jens, what do we mean
by autocratic government?
- Stuff like monarchy, I guess.
- Not necessarily.
Ferdi, what can you think of?
Autos that are crass!
That was pretty lame.
Lisa, don't let me down.
- Dictatorship, maybe?
- That's part of it. Karo?
I think autocracy is when an individual
or a group rules the masses.
Right.
Autocracy comes from the Greek
and means self-rule.
From auto, "self",
and kratia, "power", "rule"...
In an autocracy, the ruler
or a group of rulers
have unlimited power
to change the law as they like.
Can you think of any examples?
Come on, a dictatorship!
- The Third Reich.
- Not again.
I didn't pick the topic, but we have
to get through this week together.
I printed out some things for you.
All that stuff again?
It's an important topic.
The Nazis sucked.
All right, we get it!
Right, shit nazis!
- And it's never gonna happen here again.
- What about Neo-Nazis?
We can't feel guilty forever,
for something we didn`t do.
We're not talking about guilt.
It's a historical responsibility.
Me a Turk, man!
- Okay, we all know!
- What do we know?
Except for some idiot East Germans...
Hey, I'm from the East!
You know what I mean, skinheads.
- Rainer, can't we do something else?
- Like?
The Bush administration.
Wait, this is interesting.
You think another dictatorship
would be impossible in Germany?
We're way beyond that.
Marco, what do you think?
Beats me.
We'll take a ten-minute break.
What's the deal?
I changed the seating.
Now there's more room for everyone.
Bring your table behind.
Fortunately, we can do whatever we want
during project week.
I propose we loosen things up a bit.
Any objections?
Very good.
What are the requirements
for an autocratic system?
Dennis?
- An ideology.
- Good. What else?
- Control.
- Surveillance.
You're getting ahead of yourselves.
Unhappiness.
Interesting.
What does every dictatorship need?
We already mentioned it.
A Fhrer, man!
A Fhrer?
A word with lots of baggage.
But every dictatorship has a central figure.
Let's go through this.
Who would that be here?
- You, the teacher.
- Me?
Who else?
One of you, for a change.
I'll be the leader.
No way! Rainer, you do it.
Let's vote.
Who wants me as your project leader?
- What is this?
- Play along.
Who's against? Any nays?
Abstentions?
- Good.
- Heil Rainer!
Of course, a leader deserves respect.
So you'll address me as Mr Wenger
for project week.
- Mr Wenger...
- Is he a megalomaniac now?
We just voted on it, didn't we?
- East German commie!
- Get with the programme!
Don't tell me what to do, bitch!
Watch your mouth, scumbag!
Quiet!
Clear off your desks.
From now on,
no one talks without permission.
- Yes, sir!
- Did I give you permission?
No.
If you want to speak,
you'll stand up first.
- Isn't that going a bit far?
- Mona?
Isn't that going a bit far,
Mr Wenger?
- Feel anything?
- What?
Standing up gets your circulation going.
It's blood pressure.
If you stand up, you wake up
and your concentration improves.
You can sit down again.
Marco. You're tired from training,
but try sitting up straight.
Straighten your spine,
place your feet parallel and breathe deeply.
Feel the difference?
Marco.
Yes, Mr Wenger.
It's better.
That's right,
you can breathe better.
Let's all do the same.
Everybody get up.
- Come on!
- What is this?
Breathe deeply.
Up you get.
Breathe in...
and out.
- What's with you?
- No way!
Then leave, please.
No one's forcing you to stay.
Attendance is voluntary.
- Rainer, be cool.
- Mr Wenger.
Kevin, it's very simple.
Either play along or leave.
Well?
This is weirding me out.
Come on, Sinan.
Bomber.
Later daze!
You can sit down again.
What else is important for a dictatorship?
- Discipline, Mr Wenger.
- Very good, Tim.
Power through discipline.
Let's go shoot some pool.
I've got a better idea.
Man, what's that?
What happened to your M-class?
It's my mom's, a wedding anniversary gift
from my father.
V-8, 250 bhp, 150 mph.
Wanna take this baby
for a spin on the highway?
What's with you?
- I'm not coming.
- What do you mean?
I'm going back.
Have you completely lost your mind
or what?
I've already failed twice.
You know what happens
if I don't graduate?
You're no honours student either.
I'm glad you changed your mind.
Have a seat in the back.
Thanks... Mr Wenger.
We were discussing which social conditions
favour a dictatorship.
Lisa?
- Which social conditions are necessary?
- Could you speak up, please?
Well, like, if there's injustice....
and, like, people don't know...
I mean, no jobs and stuff.
Hey, Ferdi!
What's the big idea?
Lisa, please just sit down again.
Take a deep breath.
Think what you're going to say.
Keep your answer short.
I know you can do it.
Try it again, okay?
High unemployment and social injustice.
Excellent.
High unemployment and social injustice,
certainly would favour a dictatorship.
Tim?
High inflation, Mr Wenger.
Good. Inflation.
- Political disillusionment.
- Very good, Karo.
Nationalism.
We saw it during the World Cup,
there were German flags everywhere.
- But that was great!
- I thought it was revolting.
That's what rocked about the World Cup!
If Germans can't be proud of their country,
like anyone else,
it just leads to the reverse,
to hatred of everybody else.
I think Mona means extreme nationalism.
Can we agree on that?
That was awesome today.
Thank you.
Sr. Wenger?
After class call me Rainer again.
I really enjoyed it today.
Keep up your contributions.
Yes sir, Mr Wenger!
Watch it!
Why don't you watch it?
Be nice to your sister.
Just gimme a light!
- You shouldn't smoke.
- My dad says I can.
I've got a light.
Torsten just said it's up to you.
None of your business, anyway.
Ignore the little weirdo.
- Retard!
- You're the retard!
Don't you have a home of your own?
Hi, hon.
Hi, sweetie.
You thirsty, too?
Aren't you going to ask me how it went?
How did it go?
It was totally fascinating.
Mr Wenger taught us how to sit properly.
Upright, with your spine straight.
You know when you stand up quickly
and your vision goes all blurry?
That's because your pulse is low.
More roast?
Now we have to stand up to speak.
It's good for your circulation,
and our answers must always be
short and concise.
Good. Why don't you, then?
There was this bizarre energy,
everybody was caught up in it.
"Bizarre" is right.
What's that supposed to mean?
"Power through discipline"...
Karo, honey,
that's not how we raised you.
Maybe you should have.
Leon could use a bit of discipline.
Your brother needs to learn his own limits.
It doesn't work for everyone.
Why?
Kevin, for example,
I had to kick him out of class.
I'll kick your ass!
Get off it! Rainer's cool.
- You traitor!
- I'd have kicked you out too.
Besides, Rainer didn't kick you out,
Mr Wenger did.
He never liked me 'cause I'm not
in his faggy water-polo team.
What do you guys do there?
We practise hard.
I don't know why we're losing.
We have to beat Ernst-Barlach-Gesamtschule,
or we'll lose our league standing.
Come by sometime.
When's your next game?
Marco, let's go to my room.
We're watching the race.
We can watch it in my room.
We have our project assignment.
- What assignment?
- Are you coming?
Sorry, Torsten.
You go study for your project assignment.
Hey, my little honeybee.
What say we do our own
"project assignment"?
I hear role-playing
can be pretty stimulating.
I thought we were going
to do something else.
Here, check this out.
Here's where we'll go.
The hippest part of Barcelona,
only seven stations to the soccer stadium.
Isn't it a bit far?
Seven stations?
Barcelona.
It's beautiful, right on the sea.
An artist's city.
Wouldn't your family miss you?
They get on my nerves.
Torsten and Bine are cool.
Sometimes they're too cool for me.
Stop whining.
Come here.
I'm not in the mood.
You're not moving tomorrow.
What's the hurry?
I have to sign up soon.
Then sign up.
Come on, don't go yet.
I've got practice.
Wait, not here. Come on.
Man, what kind of shit is this?
What is that?
Damn it!
You can`t do everything you want in here.
When you´ll finally understand that?
- Listen, man...
- Leave me alone.
Let's play together.
Everyone will expect you to hog the ball.
I'll swim into the clear on the left
and pass back to you, okay?
Get out! Slo, you play.
Nice, Marco!
That's better.
Great move, with class!
Finally!
Hi, sweetie, I'm home.
What's going on?
I just want to print something.
Kiki and Alex are really a pain in the ass,
a real couple of teachers.
Are we like them?
What's all this for?
Just a few ideas I want to try out tomorrow.
I have a few ideas too!
Only if you wear a nurse costume.
We'll see.
How about an injection?
I've got an injection that's all ready to go!
- Really?
- Yes.
Let's see it, then.
TUESDAY
Here he comes.
- Morning.
- Good morning, Mr Wenger.
I have a feeling you don't
take me seriously, do you?
No, of course we do.
Everybody stand up, please.
Now do as I do.
These are a few warm-up exercises
to loosen up your muscles.
Especially the legs.
And now in unison.
Left, right...
What is this for?
I want to show you something.
Good.
You feel it?
We're becoming a single unit.
That's the power of unity.
- How long do we keep this up?
- Until we're in step.
You know that from dancing, Mona.
Left, right...
A rhythm like this
can cause bridges to collapse.
- Kaschi, you're out of step.
- Chill, man!
I think we get it, Mr Wenger.
I don`t think so.
- This exercise has another purpose.
- What's that?
Wieland's anarchy class is below us.
I want the plaster to fall off the ceiling
onto our "enemy" heads!
Excellent!
Have they gone crazy?
Unity is power.
You want to know
why I rearranged the seating?
To break up your usual cliques.
You all have your friends and groups.
That's important.
You can't get through life all by yourself,
but together, we are much, much stronger.
The new seating has a method to it.
Do you know what it is?
Anyone?
Karo, why are you sitting next to Jens
and not Marco?
Because Marco and I distract each other?
Oh, do you?
Wieland down there wants to foster his students
by making them lone warriors.
You know what I mean.
No one letting the other copy.
I say that leads to social Darwinism.
I'm convinced if we pull together,
we'll be much stronger.
So we can copy from each other?
If it means better grades, yes.
That's why I've checked your grades,
and seated the good grades
next to the bad.
I want you to help each other.
That's total nonsense!
- Mona?
- I don't believe it.
Please stand up.
You wouldn't embarrass us like this.
All the poor students are lined up
like ducks in a row.
I never said anything about poor students,
just poor grades.
There are no poor students.
For example, you're good in my class,
but you struggle in math.
Lisa, however, is a math whiz.
You could help each other.
There's another advantage.
The whole class would do better,
at least better
than the anarchists downstairs.
I know it's unorthodox...
but why not try something new?
Hey, Domi.
We were pretty loud, huh?
How's it going with Wieland,
our Bavarian?
I thought anarchy would be interesting,
but he just blows.
He is like a sleeping pill.
If you guys hadn't raised hell,
I would've dozed off.
What was that?
A little calisthenics to wake them up.
Calisthenics?
I thought the building was going to collapse.
You disrupt my classes.
My students are outraged, and justly so.
Can I help you kids?
We wanted to ask if we can switch
to the autocracy class.
Right away, if possible.
We were talking about group unity.
What are the signs of group unity?
Team spirit, Mr Wenger.
Good, but I meant visual signs.
Lisa?
- Dress, Mr Wenger?
- Exactly, a common way of dressing.
One could also say by uniforms.
Uniforms suck.
Dominik?
I mean, uniforms are totally fascistic.
It might be so,
but not necessarily military uniforms.
There are all kinds of uniforms everywhere:
McDonald's, stewardesses, meter maids...
even business suits are a dress code.
Your outfit is a kind of uniform too.
It indicates your social group.
Lisa?
Uniforms can serve another purpose.
They eliminate social differences.
Yes, they do,
but also they eliminate individuality.
Mona, please stand up.
Lisa, explain it more accurately.
Well, I mean, we all stress out
every morning over what to wear.
If we all wore a uniform,
we wouldn't have to.
Karo?
I've heard that in Hamburg they're talking
about reintroducing school uniforms.
Does that make sense?
Sinan?
Sure, but they'd have to be cheap enough
for everyone to afford.
Marco, why don't you tell everybody?
I was saying...
Stephon Marbury of New York Knicks,
made a basketball shoe that cost only $14.99.
The "Starbury One".
He was a ghetto kid and wanted a shoe
kids could afford,
instead of expensive Nike Airs.
A good example.
How can he market them so cheaply?
Because they're made
in Chinese slave factories.
No, they just do
without expensive ad campaigns.
Nike spends hundreds of millions on ads.
David Beckham got millions from Adidas.
What say we adopt a school uniform
for the duration of project week?
Like what?
Maybe a pair of jeans, a white shirt.
Everyone has that.
- I don't have a white shirt.
- Then buy one.
I'm not spending money for that.
Come on, how much can it cost?
Jens, stand up, please.
I've got two.
You can have one of mine.
That's what I call team spirit, Jens!
Very good!
It's decided, then.
- Two of the same?
- Right.
I just had sold a white one.
110, please.
Thank you.
- Bye.
- Your receipt?
- No, no, its okay, thank you.
- Okay, bye.
- Hello!
These must really be hip.
45, please.
Excuse me, but my things
may be in here, too.
Where are you going in that?
Why?
You look like you just went out
of the convent school.
Well, I like it.
WEDNESDAY
Where's your white shirt?
I didn't like it.
- Why not?
- I just don't look good in white.
So that's it, a matter of vanity.
I don't have to explain why I don't want to wear
some shitty shirt!
That's just what Mr Wenger
was talking about.
Pure egoism.
Karo, but we have already agreed
we all take part in this.
Mind your own business!
White does not suit her.
- Good morning.
Mona has switched classes,
but we have more newcomers.
Go ahead and find a seat.
We're definitely full now.
But Jules Barman and Frederick Claussen
wanted to join us too.
Unfortunately, full means full.
Dennis?
Now that we're so many,
we need a name, don't we?
Excellent. That was my next topic.
Any suggestions?
Sinan?
"Terror Squad".
Serious suggestions only.
Dennis?
"Visionary Club".
Marco?
- "The Wave".
- I expected that one from you!
- It's great. It fits.
- True. Tim?
"Tsunami".
That's overdoing it.
Kaschi?
"The Base".
"The Pact".
"The White Giant".
"The Inner Circle".
"The Risen".
- "The Centre".
- That's good too.
Anyone else?
No one?
Karo?
"The Changers".
"The Changers"?
That's quite a few.
I'll write some down.
"The Visionary Club"...
"The Base"...
Okay, last suggestion...
"The Changers".
We have a winner.
From now on we are "The Wave".
That's really good.
Helps me concentrate.
Honest.
I like it.
Why not design a logo for us?
- Yeah?
- Yeah. You design our logo.
That brings us to the next step:
Power by Action
What's the use of great ideas
if we don't actually do something?
I want everyone to contribute to "The Wave",
for the greater good.
I'll set up a profile on "MySpace" for us.
- Great!
- I always wanted to do that.
Do it together.
No, I'd rather do something
on my own.
Why don't you make a website?
We can make badges with the logo.
My aunt has a machine.
We could have tattoos, on our arms.
Postcards to hand out...
Hey, what's up?
A friend of mine is out of stash.
I heard you can get dope.
Hey, my money's good.
Go buy it on the street.
What's going down over there?
They're fucking with Stoltefuss.
I don't sell dope to anarchist lice.
What's that mean?
Check out his pretty shirt.
Mommy buy it for you?
Leave me alone, you fucks!
Hey, take it easy.
Everything's cool.
Is there a problem here?
- Two more weirdoes.
- What?
This a gang thing?
If you don't leave Tim alone,
we'll kick your ass.
Everything`s cool.
Fucking fascists!
Those anarchist fags tore my shirt.
Don't let those scumbags push you around.
- You got my back.
- And if we're not here?
Tim, listen, let me give you my number.
If those bastards trouble you,
you gimme a call, okay?
Sure.
What was that earlier?
I really don't know,
she's upset about something.
I can't get through to her.
I've noticed that too, recently.
It bothers me when she tells me what to do.
She makes plans without bothering to ask me.
Why should I even follow her to Spain?
Ten months from now she'll have some guy
named Juan or Miguel or whatever.
I'm scared I'll lose her.
Karo, this is Dennis. Where are you?
It's total chaos.
Call me back when you get this message, okay?
- Voicemail.
- Like I said.
But she knows we're rehearsing today.
No big loss.
I bet she's pissed off
because nobody voted for "The Changers".
I'm not sitting around all day
waiting for our little princess.
I'm going with you.
Hey, wait a minute.
Lisa, I'm going too.
If you leave now, we can forget the play!
Is that what you want?
I think we can create
something really great here.
A play that means something.
Not just entertainment,
but a message.
But not without Karo.
You wanted her to play the lead!
I was against that consensus rule
from the beginning!
I thought we should have real auditions.
We never really voted on it, anyway.
Could you all be quiet for a moment!?
Let's do it the way I say,
just once.
Your big break, Maja.
You're Claire Zachanassian.
- Cool.
- And Lisa, you play Maja's role.
Me?
Sure. You know the part.
Just go for it.
And Ferdi, stick to the text
and don't clown around for once, okay?
Yes, sir!
Man, I'm glad this day's over.
But Rainer has really showed us
cool stuff today.
You should join up again.
"The Wave" needs you, man.
How will that look?
You don't have to come to class,
just join us.
Hey, let us also in!
- What do you want?
- To skate!
You're that bitch Karo's brother.
- Got a problem with that?
- Your sister is a cunt.
Tell me something new.
The pipe belongs to "The Wave".
You want to skate, you have to join.
... sits in the forest for the last time,
full of cuckoos and howling winds.
Tonight, the congregation will assemble.
Dennis said I was really good.
You tricked me.
And now Maja has my role?
The dream of life...
Well, it was just to try it out.
once the real dream...
Where were you?
that I had not forget.
I wasn't feeling good.
I thank you for the wreaths,
chrysanthemums and roses.
And Ferdi's sticking to the text?
Dennis finally put his foot down.
You're all against me,
in your white shirts.
- That's nonsense!
- Since I wasn`t around, it's working now.
Just because we voted against your name.
What?
Can't you see that you are getting
on everybody's nerves with your way.
Are you nuts?
Has it ever occurred to you
Marco may not want to go to Spain?
- Why do you say that?
- He told me.
What else did he tell you?
How often we make it?
You suck, you know that?
I suck?
What if I talked to your boyfriend
about your relationship problems?
I have no relationship problems
since I don't have a boyfriend.
You don't even have a friend,
in case you hadn't noticed.
It's all about you.
You know what?
Maja was much better than you,
but you don't care about that.
You're pissed off because
you're not top dog in "The Wave".
A shitty feeling, isn't it?
Get used to it!
- Hello.
- Hi.
Wait a sec,
I want to show you something.
- Here.
- What is it?
You know what a computer junkie Kaschi is?
He made us a "MySpace" page,
we are already on-line.
- Cool, huh!
- Super cool!
- Honey.
- Yes?
Kaschi's totally motivated.
The kids are changing.
Sure, like all wearing white shirts!
Okay, I forgot to change.
They already talk about you
at the faculty.
Haven't they always?
Since when do you care?
I'm just saying.
- That's our sign.
- Cool.
As a "Wave",
we will flood the whole City!
It really rules on a wall, guys.
My respect!
What's he doing here?
What's your problem, retard?
Be glad you're in.
Peace, guys!
Anyone can join "The Wave"
who believes in the cause.
Tim's right.
Kevin bailed.
Why the change of mind?
Chill!
Kevin had 5,000 stickers printed.
That shows he's worthy.
Sure, sponsored by daddy.
I think Mr Wenger should decide
if he is still involved or not.
Mr Wenger taught us about unity.
Only together we are strong.
I don't know about you guys,
but I bet Mr Wenger wouldn't like us
hacking the whole town.
You're getting too uptight.
I thought we were here to have fun.
Well?
Okay, grab the stuff and let's go.
Everyone got stickers?
Here is the template.
I've got five pieces.
- Let`s go!
- Can we go with you?
Get into the car, we're moving!
What's going on?
Are you crazy?
Guys, wait a bit.
What's wrong, retard?
Lets cover up the anarchy clowns' scribbles.
Righteous!
Don't worry about it,
she could have come along.
- Speak of the devil.
- Leave it.
If you are always available to her,
she may become bored.
Trust me.
I'm a girl, I know how we think.
Come on Marco, lets go!
Know what would rock?
Spraying "The Wave" up there.
How cool would that be?
Lets move.
I'll do it.
What?
I'll climb up there.
Stop fucking around.
Forget it, man.
Give me your cellphone.
- Got video?
- Yeah.
This guy is so whacked.
Totally.
He even filmed his sister getting laid.
- He doesn't have a sister.
- What?
I know Stoltefuss from way back,
from camp.
When he was young, the first time
he tried alcohol he ended up in a coma.
He's got a older brother,
a computer geek at the university,
but no sister.
Tim!
Don't fuck up!
Shit, it's the cops!
THURSDAY
Mom.
You really made a mess!
I'd never have climbed up there.
I wet my pants on the diving board.
Heights don't freak me out.
- Here, guys.
- Thanks.
Nope. "Wave" members only.
What?
Just kidding. Go ahead.
Stick your shitty ice cream in your ass.
I'm in.
You know what the initiation is, right?
Don't listen to the retard.
Hey, Turk, you got a big mouth
in your white shirt.
Hey guys, what you think of this?
A really cool "Wave" salute.
Very simple.
As our salute?
All groups have their own salute,
like "Black Power".
- West Coast.
- East Coast, man!
That's Eminem.
No, this is Eminem.
- Hang loose.
- Or Satan.
Don't forget the Vulcans.
Okay, great.
Can you show me again? This way?
Not so high at the end.
Under the chest, here.
Okay, all together now.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Mr Wenger!
Be seated.
Our last point was "Power through Action".
- Fuck off! We won't let you in!
- Why not?
Because you don't belong to "The Wave".
Leon!
What's going on?
They won't let me through.
What's wrong with you,
are you crazy, or what?
Not without the salute.
What salute?
Good morning, Mr Wenger.
Can I have a word?
Karo, I've missed you in class.
- Do you have a minute?
- Sure.
So what did you do?
I persuaded him my way,
what else could I do?
I'll have a word with your brother.
- And what about "The Wave"?
- What about it?
What? You will just let it go?
You will just give it up?
There just one day left.
We'll see it through together.
Without a white shirt,
for all I care.
Sorry, Rainer,
but I think it's totally out of control.
I guess you'll have to switch classes, then.
Everything okay?
How're things here?
I didn't think you cared.
Mr Wenger, can I have a word?
In my office.
Sure.
Dr Kohlhage, believe me,
I have an educational goal.
You should see
how the students have developed.
- They are really motivated.
- I know that.
I just wanted to tell you
Mr Westerhoff called.
Jens is completely changed,
he is speaking about you in high regards.
I didn't want to say it directly
in the teacher's room.
You know, some of your colleagues
have a hard time with your style,
but you have my support.
Keep up the good work.
The next edition of The Scraw
is laid out. There's no room.
It'd take too long, anyway.
We need to send an e-mail to all students.
Give me everyone's address.
We can't. Privacy!
Oh, who cares? I'll help you.
Know what I think?
I think you're going overboard.
You wanna sit around and do nothing?
No, I wanna go to Kaschi's LAN party.
LAN party. Oh God!
Don't lose them,
I had to sign for them.
What do you say,
meet by the lake at eight?
Too early, say nine.
It's only project week, after all.
Ready to get your asses riped off?
- These guys?
- Yeah.
So you're "The Wave Nazis"?
"Wave Nazis"?
Are you a retarded?
- You're being brainwashed by Mr Wenger.
- Piss off!
You painted over our graffiti.
What are you talking about, fucker!
Tim, are you crazy?
Tim!
Don't fuck around, man!
Run or I'll blow your brains out.
Okay, no problem.
Okay.
Tim?
They're gone. Put the gun away.
Have you completely lost your mind now?!
How can you walk around
with that gun in your hand?
It only fires blanks. Calm down.
Got it off the Internet.
Simple as that.
STOP "THE WAVE"
The end justifies the means.
It's not true that they beat up the kid.
We want to stir people up, don't we?
Michael Moore does that all the time.
I'm sticking with the truth.
Great, then we might as well forget it.
Yes?
I've been looking for you everywhere.
- What are you up to?
- Nothing.
We're having a party by the lake.
Wanna come?
We? You mean "The Wave" members.
Yes, there will be few.
No, thanks. I won't feel welcome
without a white shirt.
That's just stupid.
Yes, it is stupid,
and that's why I'm not coming!
Oh, bad vibrations! I better go.
- You can stay.
- No, I have choir rehearsal.
Have fun at "The Wave" party.
- Bye.
- See ya.
- What you got against "The Wave"?
- Marco, open your eyes!
"The Wave" it's turning
into a really weird thing.
You are too much involved.
Oh, really?
Then take a look at this.
Look at that.
Yeah, Tim made it.
He tends to overdo it.
Here...
"Yesterday, some guy wearing a white shirt
pressed on me and said that,
"unless I join "The Wave",
I will loose all my friends
"because all of them would join in soon.
"I said I'll think about it
and he got nasty,
"saying it might be too late."
Too late for what, Marco?
Don't you understand what is going on here?
Students are being harassed.
That thread was posted anonymously.
- Could be a fake.
- A fake?
Leon hassled a six-grader
because he wouldn't do your dumb salute.
- Your brother was always a retard.
- But not only that,
I'm even treated like a leper
because I don't wear a white shirt.
Then why not just wear one?
Because I don't want to.
But I do,
"The Wave" means a lot to me.
Like what?
Community.
You know about that,
you have a healthy family. I don't.
Are you coming?
Can I help you?
- What are you doing here?
- Protection.
- What?
- I'm your bodyguard.
What for? Tim, go home.
What do I want at home?
They don't care about me.
Come to me if you have problems,
but I don't need a bodyguard, okay?
Come with me.
- Hi, hon.
- Hi.
What did Mrs Kohlhage want?
- Hello, Tim.
- Hello, Mrs Wenger.
- Rainer, can I have a word?
- Sure.
What's going on?
I didn't invite him,
he just showed up.
He's got nobody at home.
I had other plans too.
We'll have dinner,
I will send him home later, okay?
Mr Wenger, do you have any ginger?
That goes really well.
- Way cool here.
- Like I say.
- Say, what is up with Karo?
- Why?
She came to the newspaper,
totally stressing out.
About "The Wave"?
She wanted the mailing list
to send out e-mails.
- No way. Seriously?
- Yeah.
E-MAIL BEING SENT
EMAIL CANCELED
- NO LAN CONNECTION
- Shit!
First we thought about Paris,
and then Lake Balaton.
But Italy would be way cooler.
Good food, beautiful women...
What more could you want?
Why don't you come?
As a supervisor.
We'll see, Tim.
Tuscany. It'd be cool!
It's not Rainer's only decision.
I`m sure all the students
would be for it.
If not, we'll sign a petition.
This has been a nice evening, Tim.
But Anke and I would like to be alone,
we have a couple of things to discuss.
Sure thing.
Thanks Tim. See you tomorrow.
Heard about the "Six Wanderers"?
No.
My dad says that here,
where the great lakes meet,
there're still a half-dozen drowned corpses
floating around.
Divers see them and think they're recent,
until they notice
they're wearing 1980s clothes.
Most of them committed suicide,
and the weird thing is,
the current keeps returning them
to the spot they died.
As if they're looking
for redemption or justice.
The fishermen call them "The Six Wanderers".
Got it.
- May I?
- Sure.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- Cheers!
Beautiful here, isn't it?
I never wanna leave this place.
Who says you should leave?
Just the way it is.
Go away to college after graduation.
I don't even know what to study.
I could see myself getting a regular job,
marrying the right girl,
having two or three kids...
and living my life in some quiet neighbourhood
for the rest of my days.
- Does that sound stupid?
- Not at all.
Turn down the music and come here.
You back there too. Come here.
Where's Marco?
Marco!
Get over here!
- What is it?
- Come here.
Good! First of all,
it's really cool that you are all here.
Really great!
And second, tomorrow is our big game
against the "bulls" from Ernst-Barlach-Gesamtschule.
You all gotta come!
It would be really cool if all of you
come tomorrow and support us!
So, tomorrow, 3pm at the swimming pool!
You guys rock.
Bring everybody you know,
in a white shirt!
Everybody!
Our enemies will feel the power of "The Wave"!
- "The Wave"!
- Now party on!
FRIDAY
What does this Sign means?
Good morning, Mr Wenger.
Tim, what`s wrong with you?
You can't simply disappear all night.
Do you realise the position
you're putting me in?
Shit!
That was those goddamn anarchists.
Now do you believe you need protection?
- Hey, are you crazy?
- Yeah, calm down.
- We got 'em all.
- Good.
I think we all know
who's behind this smear campaign.
We've no proof.
Marco, please.
Marco...
You also want "The Wave"
to keep going on, right?
Sure. I'll talk to her...
but after the game, okay?
What should we do with all the flyers?
Destroy them.
What the...?
I don't know who did it!
I don't want to know,
but it was a dangerous stunt.
I screwed up in my days too,
believe me.
But this is going too far.
- Got it?
- Yes, Mr Wenger.
Sit down.
Write down your experiences with "The Wave"
over the past week,
and put them on my desk
at the end of class.
Get started.
Time's up.
See you later, Mr Wenger.
This doesn't mean I wouldn't appreciate
seeing you at the game.
We need your support.
Mr Wenger, I know who's responsible
for the graffiti on the town hall.
Tim, did I ask you to tell me who did it?
I don't want to know.
If I knew, I'd have to inform
the principal and the police.
It's called vandalism.
If you've learnt one thing this week,
it's the value of sticking together.
You of all people should take that to heart.
I'll be pleased to see you
at the game today. Okay?
Okay.
Come on!
Yes, now play forward!
Marco, go forward!
What are you doing?
Yes! Superb!
- I can't let you in.
- Why not?
Get yourself a white shirt,
there are still some left outside.
I don't want your shitty "Wave" shirt!
Everybody has one,
don't make a scene.
You're full of shit!
The right side is reserved for us.
You've all gone crazy.
Defence, get closer!
Go, forward now! Forward!
Excellent!
- What do you say now?
- Shut your mouth!
No mistakes now!
Now what?
I'm not giving up that easily.
Fall back! You're ahead!
Go, Go! Faster!
Go, Faster!
Piss off, man!
You bastard!
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Stop "The Wave"!
Had to be them.
Bring them all to me.
You're sick, go home!
Hey, sit down!
What's your problem?
What's going on?
Are you nuts?
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
Sinan, what's wrong with you?
Shit! I just don't believe it.
You got them on this trip!
Was it my idea for them to start a brawl?
- Of course not.
- What do you mean, then?
You relish the way they hang on
your every word.
Are you telling me you wouldn't?
You're a teacher too.
That's not the point!
They look up to you,
but you're manipulating them!
It's an ego trip.
Don't you see that?
I think you're jealous.
- What?
- Because they don't look up to you.
This minor-league teacher is showing you up.
You think that's the problem?
It's what you all think!
Because of my college,
physical education and political science.
- I never knew the wound was so deep.
- Oh, you didn't?
At least I don't pop pills every Monday
because I'm scared of going to school!
Anke... Anke, wait...
- I didn't mean that.
- You did.
You said it and you meant it.
You've turned into an asshole.
Just leave me alone!
Shit!
Karo, what was that back there?
You can't do that!
You think you're some kind of resistance fighter?
What's up with you?
What was the deal at the game?
- It was full for the first time.
- And the fight?
That was because of this!
You just don't get it, do you?
We'd have won if not for you.
That bugs you.
For once it was my show today.
You moron.
- Karo!
- Leave me alone!
Don't walk away!
Let go of me!
- Let go of me!
- Karo.
Get lost!
Marco, what are you doing here?
I screwed up.
Come on in.
What happened?
I hit Karo.
You did what?
- I hit Karo.
- Why?
I don't know.
We had a fight about...
This whole shit has totally changed me!
I love Karo!
But I still hit her.
All this pseudo-discipline,
it's totally fascist!
You have to stop it.
Rainer?
I'll think of something.
You have to call it off.
- Now!
- Don't tell me what to do.
Yes, Dr Kohlhage, I know that.
I know, I know, yes.
I won't downplay the seriousness of it.
I take full responsibility,
but I must speak to the students.
All I'm asking is for you
to trust me on this.
Hey guys, just arrived!
"Tomorrow, school hall, 12 o'clock.
"The Wave"'s future is at stake."
"Pass it on only to members and supporters."
Three exclamation marks?
SATURDAY
Mr Wenger, it's quarter past 12.
Lock the doors.
I don't want any interruptions.
Yes, sir.
I'd like to stay standing up here,
so I have a clear view of the room.
Go ahead.
All clear here?
Then lock the doors.
Mr Wenger doesn't want any interruptions.
Everyone inside!
"I always had everything I wanted:
clothes, money, whatever,
"but what I had most of was boredom."
That's mine.
"The last few days have been really fun.
"It doesn't matter who's the best-looking,
the most popular or successful.
"The Wave" has made us all equal."
"Race, religion and class don't matter anymore.
"We all belong to a movement.
"The Wave" gives our lives meaning,
ideals worth standing up for."
"I used to bully other students,
"but the more I think about it,
the lamer it seems.
"It's much better to be part of a good cause."
"If we all rely on each other,
we can accomplish so much more,
"even if it means personal sacrifices."
As you surely noticed,
they were excerpts from your essays
about the past week.
It's impressive,
what you got out of "The Wave".
We shouldn't just allow our project to end.
- Rainer, what the hell?
- Marco, sit down!
Yes, but... People think...
I said sit down!
Germany's been going downhill for years.
We're the losers of globalisation,
but the politicians want us to believe
the only solution is to work harder.
But the politicians
are puppets for big business!
They say unemployment's falling,
and we're still the world's export champions.
But in reality, the poor are getting poorer
and the rich, richer!
Our greatest threat is terror.
A terror we unleashed ourselves,
because of the injustice we permit
in the world!
And while we slowly destroy our planet,
a few of the superwealthy rub their hands
and build themselves spaceships
so they can watch from above!
Don't you see what he's doing?
He's manipulating you.
Marco, sit down!
You can't stop me speaking the truth, Marco.
"The Wave" is the real problem!
No. "The Wave" is the only answer.
Together, we can do anything.
We...
We have the opportunity to make history!
Your girlfriend turned you up against us.
That's your problem.
That's not true!
It must be.
She infected you with her attitude.
But you can't stop us.
"The Wave" will roll over all of Germany!
Anyone who opposes us
will be washed over by "The Wave"!
Right on!
Bring that traitor up here!
Marco, I'll ask you in front of everyone.
Are you with us or against us?
Are you totally crazy?
What should we do with the traitor?
Bomber, tell us!
Well?
You helped drag him up here.
Because you said so.
Because I said so?
Would you kill him if I said so?
Should we hang him or cut his head off?
We could torture him first,
so he agrees to our rules.
That's what they do in dictatorships.
Do you understand what happened here?
- You all right, Marco?
- Yeah, sure.
Do you remember the question
at the beginning of the week?
Would a dictatorship be possible again
in Germany?
That's what happened here.
Fascism.
We thought we were special.
Better than the rest.
And what's worse...
we excluded others
who didn't agree with us.
We hurt them...
I don't want to think
what we might have been capable of.
I owe you all an apology.
We went too far.
I went too far.
But now it's over.
What's this mean?
For "The Wave"?
It's over.
Just like that?
Yes, just like that.
No, it's not over.
Yes Tim, it's over.
But not everything about "The Wave" was bad!
We all felt it.
We made mistakes, but we can fix that.
No, Dennis.
That kind of thing can't be fixed.
I want you all to go home now.
I'm sure you have a lot to think about.
- Maja, I...
- Leave me alone.
Stop!
The doors stay shut!
Nobody goes home!
- Put it down.
- You lied to us.
"The Wave" lives. It isn't dead!
Say it, "The Wave" lives!
It only fires blanks.
Now you take me seriously, huh?
I know you were fucking with me.
You all were!
"The Wave"...
was my life.
Tim, calm down.
Calm down.
Put the gun down.
Come another step closer
and I'll shoot you in the face.
And then what?
There'll be no Mr Wenger,
no one to lead "The Wave".
Is that what you want?
Karo, come here.