Mr. Chow, the virus that has infected
the mainframe can't be cured.
It's threatening to wipe out
the entire system.
Chairman Chow, you must take
control of the situation immediately.
If this continues, our stock will
plummet when the market opens.
We'll suffer significant losses
in the EU market.
-Chow Lui, what shall we do?
-Pay them off.
If we do,
they'll come back for more.
Our computers are protected by a
world-class first-rate security system.
Clients invest in us because
we guarantee absolute safety.
It's obvious that our mainframe is
being attacked by an external virus.
If we don't pay them off,
our reputation will be ruined.
No amount of money
can compensate for that.
Something called the Computer
Angel is getting rid of the virus!
Thank God! We're fine again.
Find this Computer Angel for me.
Who is this Angel?
Someone we can use.
How can I help you, miss?
-I'm here to see Mr. Chow Lui.
-Who shall I tell him...?
-The Computer Angel.
-One moment, please.
You want to buy $20 billion
of Dragon stock.
I think this is crazy.
I won't sanction it.
-Have you thought about--?
-The Computer Angel is here.
May, show her up.
Right away, Chairman Chow.
Alice, please turn down Dragon
on behalf of Nunn.
Sister-in-law, let's discuss this
in my ofice.
Sure. Don't stay too late tonight.
Control Center to Mr. Yip. Over.
Someone called the Computer
Angel is in the lobby...
...claiming to have an appointment
with Chow. Do you receive?
I'm Yip, Chairman Chow's chief of security.
We have to perform a search.
-She doesn't have weapons on her.
-Thank you.
This way, please.
Chairman Chow is waiting upstairs.
Mr. Yip, please go with them.
This way, please.
I'm May, Chairman Chow's secretary.
Sorry about just now.
Mr. Chow rarely receives visitors nowadays,
so our security's a bit tight.
-How are you?
-How do you do?
Please have a seat.
Do you have a name besides
Computer Angel?
Computer Virus!
I'm both Virus and Angel. The invasion
and battle against your computer...
...is my organization's
best optical illusion.
We were simply manipulating
the images on your screens.
None of your data was affected.
The only things we disabled were your
portals and prevention systems.
That's why it looked so realistic.
So much for the opening speech.
What's your point?
You've amassed your fortune
through smuggling and drugs.
It's an evil fortune.
You're impossible to approach
unless it's at your own bidding.
So I've come here to...
It's such a pity that
you're so intelligent.
Even if you had a cannon you
wouldn't be able to touch me.
Why do you think I put the glasses in there?
That much cyanide would poison a quarter...
...of the rush-hour subway crowd.
All units, Chairman Chow's in trouble,
check it out! Do you copy?
I copy!
Target destroyed.
I'm leaving the scene.
The police have picked up the alarm.
They'll be there in 5 minutes.
The guards on the 87th floor
are forming into groups:
Two in the elevator, five by the stairs,
two are at the lobby elevators.
I'm corrupting the screens in dispatch...
...and cutting off their communication.
Look.
What's happening? What's going on?
Let's listen to a song.
-What's going on?
-What happened?
Why is there music?
Hey, what's going on?
Count to 20 and go down.
One, two, three....
They're about 80 meters from you...
...at 10:00, four men total.
Forty meters...
...30 meters...
...20, 10, 5, here.
--eight, nine...
May, what's going on?
Now count to 20 and go back up.
Five...
...four, three, two, one.
This image will play in a continuous loop.
You may vacate the premises.
Control Center calling all units.
Target is located.
She's in an elevator in section C.
Wait for her on the 40th floor.
I'll lock the elevator
when it arrives there.
Do you copy? Over.
Out of the way!
Here!
-No one's there!
-You're joking? Isn't she inside?
Don't forget the cake and candies
I ordered from the Orchid Bakery.
Cut!
Mom and Dad! I'm here again.
I have a complaint.
I'm Sue, I am 8 years old.
Come to Daddy!
Daddy, what are you doing?
Daddy is inventing something that will
change the course of human history.
If it works,
it will connect by satellite...
...all the CCTV systems in every
building in the world...
...and be able to see
what people are doing.
Wow! That's like the eye in the sky.
See, Mom, she always bullied me
and nothing's changed.
Gazing at your boyfriend again?
You're so mushy.
Spit out the gum. You're disgusting!
Do you remember me?
I come back every year
to visit my cousin's grave.
I thought I'd run into you
at the cemetery.
A few years ago,
you suddenly disappeared.
I asked lots of people,
but no one knew where you'd gone.
Something happened
to my family that year...
...so my younger sister and I moved.
Are you still working at that American magazine?
Nothing's changed?
Everything's the same with me.
What about you?
All right, I'm going to New York
tomorrow on the noon flight.
Here's my telephone number.
I hope I'll see you again before I go.
What are you thinking about?
The baker must have really upset you.
This job was so clean,
what are you worried about?
-What's the fuzzy thing?
-It's hair.
Is she that tall?
Hey, what are you doing?
-You're asking me?
-Yes.
I'm not tall enough,
so I need to climb up this ladder...
...to inspect the ceiling.
Perhaps a 0.5-inch-diameter hole
between 1.6 and 1.7 inches deep.
This is very interesting.
Why? According to my analysis,
it's very possible that the hole was made...
...by an outstanding pair of pointed
4-and-a-half-inch heeled boots.
The hottest boots on
the Paris catwalks this year.
No one's asking you what it is.
I'm asking you who you are.
Forensics. I'm new.
Oh, a rookie. Go, and come back
when you know a bit more stuff.
No problem, Sergeant Ho Chi-kwong.
How did she know my name?
-What's her background?
-Who knows?
I do. She is Kong Yat-hung.
She used to be with Criminal Psychology,
then trained in the U.S....
...and recently came back to Hong Kong.
Oh, really? And who are you?
Ma Siu-ma. I was with Traffic, but I did well,
so I was sent to train in Zhuhai.
Now they've transferred me back
to be Kong Yat-hung's assistant.
What are you doing here?
You told her to leave, but didn't tell me to,
so I'm still working.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Is she crazy?
Don't assume she's a fool.
I'll bet she can run circles around you.
Is she so great? Let me check her out.
She has exactly the same birthday as you.
No wonder she's so intelligent.
Officer Hung, I've discovered something.
Security said the killer's face
wasn't recorded on camera.
The guards were all shot in the leg.
This killer is quite something.
You know it's harder to shoot someone
in the leg than shoot him dead?
Those men had no time to fight back.
They said, "Ouch!" and passed out.
Why not say, "Argh," and pass out?
Why would they say "Ouch"?
-I'll show you.
-What? Ouch! What are you doing?
That's why.
This song jammed the communication system.
Let's listen to it for clues.
What are you doing?
Even though my cousin lives in New York,
he hates the cold.
I remember that year. I was young
but very happy as a college student.
I went with my best friend May...
...to a remote island for Christmas.
There, I met Yen.
The three of us spent all our time together.
Yen and I discovered
we had feelings for one another.
But we had an unspoken agreement
not to let May know about it.
So we hid what we were feeling,
all through the holiday.
May made a date with us to get
together again the following year.
But the day before Yen's return...
...she died in a mountaineering accident.
It was arranged that I pick Yen up.
We'd agreed to meet at the mortuary...
...but what happened later
changed my life.
I never thought I'd ever see him again.
Come in.
They've transferred the money
into our account.
-What are you doing?
-You know.
No way.
Why can't I handle cases on my own?
Why must I always be the assistant?
Because you're emotional and reckless.
You lack the skills.
Does that answer the question?
I'm not good enough?
I'll get you for that!
The Chow Lui case. The killer
is very accomplished in I.T., no?
He hacks in then destroys the security system.
This kind of killer is rare.
What does the Secret King do?
He was a secret agent. Now he's old,
so he's called the Secret King.
You've been back a month. How did
you know he exists? Even I don't.
It took me a week to get through
the local files for the last 10 years.
A week? Do you remember anything?
-Are you drinking that coffee?
-Can't you see me using the sugar?
You've put the sugar in the cream.
Your coffee is next to it.
I put the sugar in the cream,
then I put it all in the coffee.
Okay?
Are you feeling all right today?
-Enjoying your novel?
-It's okay.
-Shall I tell you the story?
-Sure.
This story is called
"Made For Each Other."
It's about a man meeting a woman
at a pier--
I'm not done yet.
I don't like it. Tell me another.
All right, there's one called
"We'll Meet Again."
-I don't like that one either.
-I haven't started yet.
It's old hat. They obviously
have feelings for each other.
They're seperated, then they
meet again at a bakery--
They meet at a nightclub.
That's worse.
The girl's become a prostitute.
Guess what? He became the prostitute.
It's the opposite.
-She was fine.
-Whatever. Anyway, it's all the same.
Okay, I'll tell you the best one:
"Meant For Togetherness."
Okay, tell me.
A guy makes a date with a girl
to meet at the pier.
And then he tells her:
"If you come, it means we're
meant to be together...
...and we'll treasure our relationship forever."
And if she doesn't--
Lynn?
-What are we doing at the airport?
-Looking for someone.
Someone picking someone up
or seeing someone off?
-It's our old neighbor, Uncle Chan.
-Uncle Chan?
You're too young to remember him.
He's leaving, so we're seeing him off.
Lynn!
If you hadn't come today...
...I'd no longer have the excuse
to come back to visit my cousin's grave.
How could I forget you?
This gentleman looks like...
...our old neighbor Uncle Chan.
I'm Yen, and you are...?
I'm your fourth great-aunt.
You are telling lies again.
Mr.Chow never told me to invest
$20 billion in Dragon stock.
Isn't it the same talking about it
with me now? If you--
In any case, I don't agree.
Let the board of directors decide.
All the board lacks is your vote.
I definitely won't agree to it.
We manged to do away with your brother,
we can deal with Lai Kai-joe.
Your brother forced us into this.
We helped him conquer the world...
...but as soon as he made his fortune,
he abandoned us.
I don't care.
I'll kill whoever gets in my way.
Mrs. Chow.
What's the matter?
Shit!
The old man Lai refuses to give in.
Ignore him. When the time comes,
I'll transfer all our stock to Dragon.
We'll be even stronger.
And then you can officially...
...become Mrs. Chow again.
Why's the Secret King so late?
Has he stood us up?
The hardest part of being an officer
is the waiting.
Usually I try to bond with my
assistants, and play...
...educational and interesting games
of communication.
What kind of communication?
-You bait me, I bait you.
-You bait--
I ask you something, back and forth.
-We can ask anything?
-Anything goes.
-Okay.
-You go first.
I'll go first. Okay,
how many siblings do you have?
None. At what age did you
begin jerking off?
What?
Fifteen. Do you have a boyfriend?
No. When was the last time you did it?
Yesterday, yesterday.
Yesterday?
You're working today and you
jerked off yesterday? Look!
-Wow, your eyes are really bloodshot.
-Don't ask me questions like that!
-You might ask if I have a girlfriend.
-If you had, you wouldn't do that.
-You ever played with yourself?
-Play with myself?
Certainly not!
No? I don't believe it. Do you
think I'm that naive? Nonsense!
Of course it's nonsense.
It's just a game.
Why are you so serious?
Look at you, you're cute
when you're stupid.
Why are you so secretive?
The older I grow,
the more secretive I am.
Hung, none of my colleagues know
who made the hit you talked about.
Someone who specializes in selling
high-tech goods says 15 years ago...
...someone bought a lot of satellite
equipment from him.
But the buyer was a middle-aged man,
not a woman, like you said.
Turn off the walkie-talkie.
I didn't turn it on.
-How do you think I gather info?
-You gather from our headquarters?
Where in the world would we be
without secrets?
Get out. Drive.
Hey, hey, hey.
Did you have to go so fast?
You trying to kill me?
The Secret King reminded me. We're
concerned with finding the murderer.
But it's impossible.
The security is so tight there.
But the Computer Angel
comes and goes as she pleases...
...shoots the guards and none
of the CCTV capture her face.
Do you think it's an inside job?
The head of security said
all their computer data...
...is accessible only if Chow Lui's
fingerprints...
...were placed on the scanner
and correctly identified.
But Chow Lui is dead, in the mortuary.
So how does access happen now?
That's why I have to prove that
my theory is correct.
The penthouse was Chow's personal
space, so it's not covered by cameras.
All of Mr. Chow's visitors would have
had to take this elevator up.
-Who was first on the scene?
-His younger brother.
I need to use the restroom.
Where is it?
-Over there.
-Women are so much trouble.
Hello, does a Choy Siu-ming
work here?
Yes. What is it, please?
-Mr. Choy, phone home urgently.
-What?
-Something happened to your family.
-Okay.
-What's up?
-Something's happened to my family.
-Is it serious? Go, if it's urgent.
-Don't walk off by yourselves.
Don't worry. We'll wait here.
-Remember, don't go off by yourselves.
-Don't worry, I won't.
Hung, he's gone, come out.
What's on your mind?
I wonder if anyone changed
the data that day.
Ridiculous! I wonder who would make
such a terrible crank call.
Just wait till I find out.
-Mr. Chow, Mr. Yeung.
-You're still here at this hour?
Officers are investigating the case.
They're in Chairman Chow's room.
You stole Chow Lui's fingerprints
from the coroner's laboratory?
This will very soon prove
whether my theory is correct.
Sorry, Mr. Chow. I was
with them originally, but...
It's true! Who made the changes?
-Who was first on the scene?
-His brother, Chow Nunn.
-Who stands to gain from his death?
-Chow Nunn.
-Officers, where were you?
-We've been looking for you.
-This place is so big.
-These are the officers.
What are you looking for?
Nothing in particular.
It's standard procedure. We're done.
See them out.
It seems the policewoman
is on to something.
If she finds any evidence of the killer,
we're in deep trouble.
When the Angel finishes off
Lai Kai-joe...
...we'll send the Angel herself
to heaven.
Tell the Angel we need her
for another job.
-Come in.
-On the phone with Uncle Chan again?
-What is it?
-Business.
People with sweethearts are selfish.
Go away!
Did you find anything?
I've checked the company's
outgoing e-mail...
...and pulled all the suspicious
messages. Here, take a look.
-Wait! Find out the recipient's address.
-What?
-I can't help you.
-You're kidding.
Should we report this
to our superiors?
What kind of e-mail is that?
What does kissing ass prove?
On what basis can our superiors
take action? Intuition?
-Take me to a record store.
-Why?
Remember Security said
the communication system...
...was interrupted by a song?
And what if you find it?
I can't let any clue
related to this case slip by.
I spoke to my mother about you
on the phone yesterday.
She asked me what you do.
I couldn't answer her.
If you don't want to tell me, then don't.
It's not that I don't want to say.
My job isn't easy to understand
or accept for normal people.
This is a robbery. Don't move.
Take out your things. Hurry, quickly.
-No, don't!
-Get out!
Now you know what I do.
Wait for me.
I've studied the terrain. I've even
picked the tools for you.
This rifle is perfect.
I want to cancel that contract.
What?
I think we should call it quits.
Do I get an explanation?
He's asked me to marry him,
so I don't want to do it anymore.
You told him about us?
Congratulations.
Get some rest, I'll cancel the contract.
Then you get some rest too.
Sue?
Stick them up!
You frightened me!
I'm listening to my new CD.
I'm going out to dinner.
Okay. Go, before Uncle Chan
gets desperate from waiting.
Lawyer Chan, enjoy yourself tonight!
It's the boss's birthday.
I'm getting completely drunk.
It's your birthday tomorrow. I've
reserved a table for lunch at Rosario's.
I've heard they do great French food.
What is it?
What are you thinking about?
She hasn't called me all day.
It's not like her.
-Who?
-My sister.
I'll just call her.
-No answer.
-Maybe she's in the bathroom?
I'll call later.
Cheers.
Happy birthday!
Boss, how's the stock doing?
Going up. Buy from me
and you won't have a problem.
I looked into Lai's room.
Those three girls are clean.
Still no answer?
Let me see.
No wonder she's not picking up.
These?
I have something to do. I must go.
Remember our date
for lunch tomorrow.
Lynn!
Why are the lights doing that?
The light show starts at 10
and repeats on the hour.
We're the only place in Hong Kong
with this design.
Miss, do you need anything?
I'll wait to order when my friends
arrive. Please go outside...
-...and close the door for me.
-Okay.
There's something wrong.
-What is it?
-I feel she's here tonight.
Boss, the policewoman from last time
is here.
In that case, we'll take care of her
at the same time.
Are your instincts right?
Will they show up?
Shit!
She's across the street!
Let's go check it out.
Let me do it.
We're the police. Which room
faces the Magic Ocean Disco?
Room 17, but two ladies
are already in it.
-Thank you.
-Let's go.
Don't hold the elevator for me.
Excuse me.
It's pointless for you to hold on
to him. I still have your partner.
I didn't plan to bring her with me.
They think they're better than they are.
Even if she didn't die today,
she'd be useless tomorrow.
Okay. I'll release her
and you release my man.