Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Name of the corpse?
I don't know.
What do you mean?
One of your workers, isn't it?
No, she's not.
Don't lie to us.
It's true. Never seen her before.
Whatever. Just get it out of here.
Don't leave it lying around here.
What do you think you're doing?
This isn't a fucking funeral home.
What's going on?
What's this?
You can't do that!
They stick cigarettes in rice in your
fucking country?
C'mon, get rid of all this!
What a bunch of freaks.
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?!
You're destroying the place!
For fuck's sake!
She wasn't your mother was she?
No, she wasn't.
Damn Yentowns!
We've never seen her before.
You will forgive me, won't you?
A Japanese funeral would've
cost a fortune.
It's OK, I bet your Mom's made it
to heaven.
Yuriko really stashed it away!
Give it me!
What for?
I'll settle with you later.
What do you mean?
I told you, didn't I?
We'll split it later.
Well it's no use to her now is it?
But I was the one who found it!
Look after yourself
Take care.
Don't you forget us.
Good luck!
How come I haven't seen you?
Drop by.
Hurry up, lazy!
She was trying to deal heroin.
Amateur. Didn't know what
she was getting involved in.
Selling stuff to anyone. No wonder
Shanghai Riuman was watching her.
Serves her right if you ask me.
Of course I wanted to look after her.
But things're hard enough already.
Would you help me out?
Would you please?
I'm begging you.
Please.
You're not the only one having
a hard time.
If she's too much of a nuisance,
you can do what you like with her.
Yeah, Yeah.
What's your name?
Y-o-u-r n-a-m-e?
I asked you a question!
I don't have one.
Bull shit!
Everybody has a name.
You really don't have one?
A pack of cigarettes costs 250 yen.
A pack a day, that's 7,500 yen
a month.
My old man's a farmer.
He makes 400 yuan a month.
If a yuan is worth 12 yen
then that's 4800 yen.
He couldn't even afford cigarettes.
I never manage to save much.
I never manage to save anything.
Saving money's so hard.
At this rate I'll never get home.
How many do you do in a night?
It's been really slow lately.
Economy's bad, what can we do.
I'm getting cobwebs in my pussy.
I came up with this great game.
I bet my customers they can't last.
If they come under 10 minutes, I win.
If they last longer, they win.
10 minutes. Sounds easy, huh?
Of course they all think they can last.
If I win, I double the price.
They win-they get a free trick.
If they come really quick- I triple it!
What do you think?
Great if they're quick-shooters.
I learned a trick from this
quack doctor.
There's a spot between their ass
and their balls.
Oh god, it works fucking great.
I brought you something.
You shouldn't have.
It was given to me anyway.
Hang on, it's downstairs.
I wonder what it is?
Is it big?
What's your name?
Mine's Glico.
Glico. Weird name huh?
Do you know what Glico is?
It's a kind of candy.
Japanese businessmen grow up
sucking on Glico.
Wonder what she's bringing me?
Are you Shizuko's sister?
I don't speak Chinese.
No Chinese?
You-are-Shizuko's-sister?
Then who are you?
You're so cute.
What's your name?
Doesn't have one, she says.
Call her anything you want.
Is that all?
Everyone has to get by
on their own.
Work hard so you get out'a
here soon
Shall we go?
Done this before?
Obviously not.
Something like this.
This would look great on you.
Look in the mirror.
I used to be a school teacher.
I was pretty good at teaching.
You can call me "teach"
Go ahead, say it.
Hey!
What, forget something?
I changed my mind
it isn't enough.
What?
I want more.
That's all I've got.
Then forget it.
Alright another 10,000.
How about 30? Wait! 30,000!
He said he's gonna pay.
Huh?
That man...
What? I didn't hear him.
That place is a shit hole.
Never let yourself go cheap.
I'm sorry.
Looking at this?
Butterfly?
You like butterflies?
Not really.
Japanese call these "Ageha"
...these butterflies.
I came here with my two older
brothers.
Ranki and Rankai.
We planned to save some cash
and go home.
Wasn't so easy.
We couldn't find work.
For a while we scavenged,
lived like rats.
We used to purse-snatch
downtown.
Ranki would rip them off,
throw to Rankai.
Rankai would run like hell.
He'd dump it all in a trash can
somewhere.
My job was to pick it up.
We made a little money.
But then one day.
Rankai was running with the stuff
and he got whacked by a car.
Dead before he hit the ground.
Split his head right open.
Then it got all crazy.
Ranki and I tried to reach him but
there was a huge crowd of people.
There was an ambulance and
a guy in a white coat yelling.
I guess he was trying to find out
if anyone knew Rankai.
We didn't know any Japanese
so we couldn't understand him.
Ranki and I tried to figure out
what to do.
Then the ambulance was gone
and that was it.
Still don't know what
happened to him.
Probably took him to the hospital.
He was just another 'Yentown'
no name, no nationality,
one more unidentified body.
It'll be the same for me when I die.
It's the same for all 'Yentowns'.
That's why I got this tattoo.
If I die this'll tell 'em who I am.
Kind of like an ID card.
Want one?
What about your other brother?
He's probably scratching
around somewhere.
You're still a kid so
you get a caterpillar.
There we are.
"Ageha"
Yep, it's your name.
"AGEHA"
Oh shit!
"AUTO EXPERT"
Fei-Hong!
What's up?
There you are.
Thank you very much.
Where did you pick this one up?
You're adorable.
What's your name?
She doesn't speak Chinese.
N-a-m-e.
How much do you want?
God created all men equal
It's time to go.
"Oh Glico, sunshine of our heart
who's are you tonight
our Yentown madonna"
Italian folk songs and
Chinese wine don't mix.
Got a towel?
Isn't there one there?
Oh yeah...
What are you doing in here?
The music's too loud.
I guess you're starting alone.
What are you doing?
It's OK I'll pay.
This one's different.
I said I'll pay.
I'm gonna call the cops!
The cops... oh yeah?
Call the cops, huh?
Now try and call them!
SALUTE!
Think you can?
You don't fucking get it do you?
A whore house is for
a good time, right?
Am I right?
Goddamn it, sit down.
Get over here and listen to me.
You too!
Go and get Arrow!
He's all squash.
Sing what?
Sing something!
What?
Sing something happy.
Sudo's disappeared?
We've been out of contact
for a week.
And our little item?
THE FUCKING TAPE!
It vanished along with Sudo.
What did you say?!
We are undertaking
a thorough search.
I can't sit around listening to this.
Why the hell are you still here?!
Goodness! Going home already?
Mr. Chairman this is from
the manager.
At least have a taste
before you go.
Who the hell are you?!
Mr. Chairman!
Oops, pardon me.
Son-of-a-bitch.
It's all on the house.
Put your gun away so we can talk.
Can't you hear me, "TAKO"!
Mao Foo, he's scary.
Shall I pop him?
No hurry, Wan.
Rio Ranki!
Hello, Mr. Bigshot.
So where has the rat
hidden himself?
I thought Rio Ranki was
a gentleman.
Don't give me that crap
you faithless fuck!
What?
The tape... the TAPE..."My Way".
What are you talking about?
You've got to be kidding.
How come you don't know
"My Way"?
It's worth a fortune to a collector.
What?
OK? I want it back!
Let's see your stomach
you fucking kangaroo!
Oh Mao Foo, I forgot my gun!
So, now it's two against four.
We're in big trouble Mao Foo!
Four minus two equals
two survivors, right?!
Listen Ranki.
So, two will be left standing.
Who wants to live? You, big shot?
You're fucking insane!
So how do we decide?
Scissor, paper, stone?
Say, I'm sorry but there's no
sense in having it out here.
Ranki, how about we make
a deal?
I don't deal with scum...
Why didn't you blow me away?
You think this is a microphone?
Or maybe it's a hair dryer?
Sudo has the tape.
I can't find him.
That's why I'm here.
Where is Sudo?
Where?!
We are looking for him.
What?
He ain't here!
He's been missing for a week.
He's split, gone, on the run.
When we find him, he's a dead man.
Lying sack of shit.
You can do better.
It's the truth.
We were just talking about it.
Kumicho, lying's no good.
It's the truth.
Let's try again, who took the tape?
Sudo.
Who gave the order?
Wan, get a bucket.
We're going to have a blood flood.
I did.
You did.
That's better.
Now where's Sudo?
I don't know.
Liars go to hell you know.
Into the fire, into the flame.
Please don't.
It's the truth!
Here comes the bucket.
Chop his head off.
It's the truth!!
Good boy, Kumicho.
Honesty brings salvation.
Chop his head off.
But it's true!!
He used to pick up Yentown
hookers around here.
This is a perfect place to hide.
Come with me.
I'm cheap.
Don't get many 'Yentowns'
in here.
He's not my type.
Never seen him before.
Here, buy yourself a hit.
He was all squashed!
Goddamn kids!
10,000 yen please.
Your looking at Sudo Kanji.
He is, or should I say was
a main man
in Katsushika Syndicate.
About a week ago
Sudo disappeared
and the "family" put on
a frantic search for him.
But now, the strange thing is
the whole gang itself has perished.
Gone, they're history.
What do you mean?
Kumicho and all the other
key people are missing.
Organized crime just can't work
without someone to organize it.
Now, here are your buddies!
Wan Shaun Shen and Mao Foo...
They're Shanghai Riuman.
You know, Chinese Mafia.
Mao Foo's one cold blooded
mother fucker
or as they say
"a frozen face killer".
For some reason they too have
been sniffing around after Sudo.
Why, Ran?
I thought I'd ask you to find out.
And their leader, "Rio Ranki"!
He's at the top.
I'm talking "RIUMAN KING".
Sitting pretty on his
beautiful Yen Town throne.
He looks pretty young to be...
He's only 28.
He was a punk selling "hot" cards
and worked his way up.
Before long people were
calling him "The Forger".
Rumor has it he is already, or
is planning on counterfeiting
Fukazawa notes...
I'm sure he's going to be called
"The Counterfeiting King".
So Ran, why are you so
interested?
I'm not.
These are the counterfeit notes.
In the city we've found nearly
10,000 in a matter of days.
Looks amateurish.
Actually it isn't.
Take a look at this.
This is the stolen magnetic data.
Rio Ranki, huh?
Kind of crude for his M.O., isn't it?
"Thousands of counterfeit bills
appear throughout city"
Oh, my god.
What a piece of junk!
This whole place is ours?
I don't have many properties
like this.
You were lucky.
You'll need a dummy owner.
Yentowns aren't allowed to
make contracts.
Owner? He's gotta be Japanese?
It's OK we'll find someone.
Now, about the staff...
Pick the ones you like.
They can start anytime.
It's not going to be
that kind of place.
Glico, stand here for a second.
Over here, right here.
What for?
You want me to be a stripper?
How's this?
Sing something.
Soon you can sing all you want.
We're opening a club.
Your place.
We'll have a band, a lot of
customers, and you'll sing.
They'll come to hear you.
Everyone will be talking about
this place.
It'll be standing room only!
Then we'll put out a CD,
it'll be a big hit
and a star is born!
You'll be the hottest singer
in Japan.
What do you think, great huh?!
I think you're full of shit.
Frankly, it's very rare for a live
venue to go into profit.
Make it a girlie bar.
Why don't you get up here
and sing.
They don't want me.
They don't want me either!
What's so funny?
Definitely a live music club.
Not a goddamn girlie bar.
If you want singing
have a Karaoke bar.
Mr. Fei-Hong may have a point.
Butt out!
A legit club could be a useful front.
Front, back, whatever.
It's a straight live music club!
That kind of life is behind us now.
Great, fantastic, you're hired!
Name?
Betty.
Real name?
Ikeda Yoshiko.
How long have you been doing this?
It's my first time.
Yeah right, Betty.
Experienced?
Not very.
How old are you?
I asked you, how old you are!
Twenty-three.
Liar...
What is your name?
Asakawa.
Your instrument?
I'm supposed to be the owner.
Very impressive!
Here's the paperwork.
All under Asakawa's name,
just a formality.
If the whole thing goes under,
his life is insured up to
one million yen.
Oh, he's an insurance agent?
So if the venture folds...
We're not even open yet.
But just in case he dies
you collect on the insurance.
Where did you get this guy?
Too many bad debts
he had to sell himself.
We're talking about you.
Did you buy him?
A huh.
We'll take care of any killing
so don't you worry about it.
Our deal is off if they find out.
We're talking about you.
You guys are Yentowns, right?
Yentown has its own soul, right?
How can Jap musicians play
Yentown soul?
That's right, I'm not.
Both my parents were American,
but I was born and raised in Japan.
Thanks to the shitty Japanese
education system.
I can't speak a word of English.
Funny? Well, it is funny.
So what am I,
American or Japanese?
The way I look I always get treated
like a foreigner.
The fact is I was born
and raised here
and nowhere else is home.
From the cradle to the grave
I'll sleep on 'TATAMI'.
It's OK for you guys.
You've got a country to go back to.
Yentowns have their own countries.
How about you, sweetheart?
Where were you born? China?
Japan.
So you think you're Yentown?
Yes.
No, you're not.
Did you come here
to make money?
You're second generation,
but the Japs don't care.
You're just another Yentown.
Strange, isn't it?
So...
There should be a special
name for us.
And I came up with one.
Wanna hear it?
"Third Culture Kids"
Good, isn't it?
And our music is called,
"Third Culture Music"
Your instrument?
I don't play an instrument.
He said "Why are you here?"
"Why am I here?"
Well,
you could say...
I'm a supervisor.
It's OK, just leave it to me.
I'll get you the best!
Just like the real thing!
Why don't you sing something.
Go on!
Wait, hold it.
Time out!
Let's ask our madonna to sing!
No way!!
Come on up, what would
you like to sing?
I can't sing.
What, is he kidding?
My grandfather's music.
That music has no soul!
Oh my God, he's really gonna do it!
Who said you could put those
up here?
This is our turf.
You wanna put those up,
you gotta pay.
No
You think I won't hit a girl.
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Told you I'm not messin' around.
Get up.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Are you OK?
Come on.
How about "Al-Nothi"
(All or Nothing)?
You know "Fre-Flo"
(Free Flower)?
"DORE-SECU"
Dream Security.
Mr. Kusunoki of Mash Records.
Good afternoon.
And Ms. Hoshino of Popland Music.
We heard your demo, it's not bad.
Where are you from?
Shanghai, China.
Difficult to sell foreigners in Japan.
Do you know Agnes Chan?
We used to have a band together.
How about Theresa Ten?
God rest her soul.
That's about it for foreign singers.
Would you become Japanese?
That would be an easier sell.
That's a bit tricky.
The policy of the 'Yen Town Band'
is kind of...
different from Japanese er...
The soul... is... is
Doesn't sound hip to me.
Hip?
There's no 'hip' in rock'n' roll.
Do you have a visa?
Do you?
You can tell the truth
we're not the police.
I don't have one.
What do you think?
We can make it work.
What're they saying?
Quit being Chinese become a Jap.
Otherwise I'II never sell.
How will I take a piss
when I'm a star?
What do you mean?
Will it be different?
You'll do it the same as you do now.
How about sex?
Will it be OK to have sex?
I think I'm gonna come.
Really?!
Almost.
I'm sorry.
Fly,
Fly, fly.
A visitor!
Wait, you little fuck!
Wait!
Stop!
Stop or I'll shoot!
I feel a little guilty.
Well, no he was just kinda cute.
Made these yourself?
You're gonna make a good wife.
Yesterday,
me, David and others went...
record shop.
We went to a record shop
and then...
we think to buy one CD each,
but no CDs there,
then we went to another shop,
but no CDs there either,
another man came into shop
and said...
"Shanghai Baby" please.
"What" please?
"Shanghai Baby"
The name of Glico's single.
The man in the shop said...
"Mai Wan La"
"Mai Wan La"?
Really? Amazing!
The customer said...
Sold out.
Sold out...
These are good sandwiches.
I'll make them for you again.
What?
Hey! Check it out!
You gotta see this!
What?
What is it?
Chai found something!
What?
Let's check it out.
Is it real?
Here, just a little.
No way!
But I found it, why me?!
Because you found it.
Stop it! All of you!
He doesn't want to do it.
Why don't you do it yourself?
Me? I'm not... I...
Are you scared?
I'm not scared.
Do it then, wimp.
Be a man.
You better not...
Feel anything?
Nothing at all.
Stop!
Help!
Help us please!
Fucking kids, get out of the way!
What's all this? Stop a minute.
Help us!
Please help...
Rio Ranki!
It's him!
Over there.
In here Mr. Ranki.
We melted this... and a needle...
What's going on Boss?
Get to the hospital!
It's a fad.
I came here with
my brother and sister,
you know, make some quick cash
and cut out.
My brother bought it in a car crash
and I lost track of my sister.
So... it's been years.
When we first got here we had to
think up Japanese names
called ourselves the "YAOHANS".
I was "TOYOTA YAOHAN".
Rankai, my little brother
he was "HITACHI".
Only Japanese words we knew,
my little sister Shaod'ei
I named Glico.
Shaod'ei was such a
little ball of energy.
You know that Japanese candy?
Japanese businessmen grow up
sucking on Glico.
That's Opium Street.
Opium Street?
Have you ever been there?
You're kidding.
Pushers, mafia, dealers
everywhere... no way.
Even the cops won't go there.
He's so cool! Rio Ranki.
Amphetamines was it?
I don't understand.
No larceny, no assault, no drug
offenses, looks clean to me.
Shanghai?
That's about 80,000 one-way now.
Got any money?
No.
Get some.
Where from?
Home.
Go on then!
Go home?
Clear out! Lots of people are waiting.
Get out! Go!
Get the fuck out of here!
Number 6-2-9
Un-fucking-believable!
Ageha!
He's back!
Mr. Fei-Hong.
Afternoon!
Grumpy bitch.
You got PMS or something?
Hey there!
What's going on?
Desperate for cash?
You piece of shit.
Blackmailing the manager?
Calm down!
Stay out of it!
Quit with the fucking English!
Somebody translate this.
We quit.
What is this?
Fuck it.
I've had it with this place!
Ageha get over here and translate.
Ageha translate.
What's this shit?
Give it back you punk.
Give it here.
It looks like a million!
How much did you sell her for?
I'll fire you all!
Out! Out! Out!
Speak Japanese you bastard!
Ageha tell them!
They say they're gonna quit.
They want to know how much
you made off Glico
and how could you be so greedy
Tell them.
Tell them!
He said "Glico was a
good resource" and
"What's wrong with making
some money?"
He really said that?!
Typical Yentown scum.
Everybody wait.
It's over.
Wait... please...
Good thing they got out
before it's too late.
You've been let off
the hook this time.
Look out! Be careful you idiot!
Hoan!
Hey boss!
Where are we going?
Opium Street.
I'm not going.
Are you scared?
No, but...
Why are you going there?
There's something I want.
They're illegal, homeless,
they have nowhere else to go.
He's dead.
That's opium.
Is this it?
Medical Center?!
"Urinary Organs,
Acupuncture & Tattoos"
Boss, you're getting a tattoo?
Wow! Great! Fucking great!
Ms. Suzukino, you have a visitor.
Where?
In the conference room.
I'm Suzukino.
May I ask your name?
Nice to meet you.
You write this column, don't you?
That's right.
I read it every week.
How may I help you?
Do you know a guy name
Sudo Kanji?
Look, this guy.
You wrote this too, right?
Oh yeah. Deputy of the
Katsushika syndicate.
I saw him killed.
What?
Fell from a window.
Glico's window.
Do you know her, Glico?
Doubt it...
I know Glico from that
Yen Town Band.
Oh, you do know her.
I suppose a customer
took this picture.
She used to be a prostitute?!
This would be quite a scandal.
How much do I get paid?
Can I have more?
Thank you.
I was lucky to get this gig.
I'm a big fan.
Ageha! Ageha!
Randy Heavens from Yoga.
Koichi from Suzugamori.
Chu Ba Jeh from Namamugi.
Shao Kampao from Gasu Bridge.
Chu-Bin from Tennozu.
They're a weird bunch, but
they can pull it off.
Hoan.
Is that your woman?
Who do you think you're talking to?
What do you want sweetheart?
Strictly a business proposition.
Business?
I'll pay a million yen each.
Boss that's too much!
What's the deal?
Listen up.
Wow great!
I don't believe it.
Here.
Next.
Is that all?
Stop complaining.
Next.
Come on hurry up.
They'd never know if we
pinched some.
If they found out,
you'd be in deep shit!
Come on.
Hurry.
Next.
Is that everything?
Let's have it.
Good job.
Thank you very much.
Next.
You did well to get so many.
It wasn't easy was it Chu-Bin?
No big deal.
It ripped.
What are you doing?
It was just one...
What do you think you're doing?
Got a problem with that?
What the hell are you doing?
Hello.
Nice to see you.
Glico's here.
Hello.
It's great to have you here.
Why don't you have a seat.
Yen Town Band's so popular.
Excuse me.
I'd like to ask a few questions
while you get ready.
Do you mind if I record it?
Am I the only one who's nervous?
New album's out on the 21st?
OK, let's talk about that first.
Yeah?
Would you move the blue Porsche?
Sure.
Excuse me for a second.
Oh, let me see.
This?
Wow! Nice tattoo.
Suits you're image.
Hey, it's just like this one!
This is you isn't it?
Dunno.
Don't know?
But it's exactly the same.
What is this?
I don't know what you're
talking about.
OK. Let me put it this way.
What did you do with Sudo's body?
You know, the guy who fell
out of your window.
Remember? Back when you
were a hooker.
Look! Stop bullshiting!
What are you doing?
What've you got in your mouth?
Spit that out!
Yuk!
Spit it out!
You can't swallow it!
Alright. Go ahead.
But this proves you were involved.
You're giving yourself away.
Aren't you?
Get it?
Give me back that soggy picture.
Don't be so childish!
She's back?!
Meet me out back... alone.
Excuse me.
OK. Let's get moving.
Sorry, I overdid it a bit.
But I had to get you alone.
I don't wanna print everything.
I'm just curious about you.
You know what I mean?
It's my job, like singing is for you.
I don't sing because I like it.
You don't like singing?
I hate it.
"The singer hates to sing"
That's a good one.
Why is that?
I don't wanna be the object
of your curiosity, thanks.
Guess I hit a nerve.
Can I help you?
Want a bullet in the face?
Hey you! Where's Sudo's tape?
Tell me where it is.
Just a second.
Do you understand?
I'm stuck.
Let me get the...
Cigarette... ah
GET DOWN!
Morons.
Do you know "TELEKURA"
(phone sex business)?
It's called "Lovely Friends".
Tsen's recommendation.
How about you?
I don't know.
Fei-Hong is that you?
It's Glico.
How are you?
Fine and you?
Good. How's everyone?
Fei-Hong...
Were you on TV the other day?
Fei-Hong listen...
Maybe it was someone else...
What did you do with that tape?
Tape?
"My Way".
There's some weird guys after me.
They're looking for that tape.
They have guns,
what should I do?
It's probably Riuman.
They'll kill us.
Where are you?
Where are we?
No idea.
We don't know.
Who's with you?
Fei-Hong...
If I get killed...
What're you talking about?
Forgive me.
For what?
Becoming a singer and
leaving you all behind.
Stop talking crap!
Forgive me.
Don't be stupid, everyone's
happy for you
If I get killed...
OK, OK. Just tell me where...
If I'm killed...
Who's gonna kill you?
I can't imagine you letting
anyone get away with that.
I may never see you again!
Don't worry I'll help you.
Where are you?
What's around there?
Fei-Hong!
Hello?
Wait for me at "Aozora".
Fei-Hong? Fei-Hong?
What is going on?
I would appreciate it
if you'd explain to me...
Just exactly what is going on?
Hey!
They're here.
I bet Mao Foo's having fun with
Glico right now!
All we got was the faggot patrol.
I thought that was right up
your alley!
Shut the fuck up!
Was she really a whore?
Did you all get to stick it to her?
'Course we did! Jealous?
Can't see through the blood!
Can't stop the blood!
What the fuck?!
Open up!
Oh shit!
My money.
It's not enough.
What's this?
What're you...
Mr. Fei-Hong?!
Go in! Go in!
What kinda jerk car jacks a taxi
and then pays the fare?!
Give it back!
Shit!
What are you doing?
"This bank note cannot be used"
Isn't this overkill?
Shut up! Mr. Ranki's orders.
Just for one little tape? Stupid.
Can't be helped, Mr. Ranki's orders.
This is no fun at all!
Aim!
Fire!
We're looking for it!
That's Glico!
What are you doing?
Stop that!
Is he gonna take us all on?
Curious-er and curious-er.
Hold your fire!
Worry about the tape later.
Mao Foo's on the warpath now,
he's a dead man.
How about one on one?
If you get me, we'll let you all live.
Mao Foo don't make
promises like that.
What is this, a war?
Sorry we're closed.
Oh it's you Ageha.
What brings you here?
What's all this?
I want to buy it back.
The Yen Town Club.
Will you sell it to me?
You may be a kid
but you do have cash.
Where did you get all that money?
It's a secret.
Did you rob a bank?
I forgot, it's been sold
What! To who?
It's too late.
I'll buy it off them.
You can't do that.
Why not? Yes I can.
I've got all this money!
Because I said you can't!
Go home. Take the money with you.
The one on the left is from
the forgery.
They match don't they?
It's the same guy.
Run a check on Rio Ranki's group.
We may get something this time.
Riuman King, I'm gonna get you.
Who hired you?
Don't play dumb with me.
Those forged bills are everywhere.
Did all that by yourself, huh?
Where'd it come from?
I found it.
He found it.
It hurts when you lie doesn't it?
Even Yentown scum can see that!
Or do you need a little
taste of death?
Hey, Yentown shithead.
Who's your boss?
Tell us and we'll let you go.
Is it Rio Ranki?
I don't know.
He doesn't know.
Want money?
Will you talk for money?
Yentowns do anything for money.
Talk!!
Yentown!
"Yen Town- that's the name of your
whole fucking Motherland!"
That's what he said.
Get up!
You bastard!
I'll get him back.
One day I'll kill him.
God, it hurts.
Un-fucking-believable.
I could've sworn I heard singing.
Singing?
"My Way"
You're right. He's dead.
What's the name of the corpse?
Fei-Hong.
What?
Hio Fei-Hong.
Chinese?
Fujian or Shanghai?
Yentown.
The caterpillar turned into a butterfly.
Hey! What are you throwing away?
How much was there?
Lots.
How much is "lots"?
I forget.
Shit!
Do you know about tonight's
main dish?
He's your buddy.
Riuman King.
We're checking now but...
We heard the Fuchen Riuman
were on the move.
The Fuchen are behind it?
It's hard to believe.
In any case Mao Foo and
the gang have vanished.
Police have got wind of the tape too
We should move quick.
Get the tape, make some money.
Think I'll go back to Shanghai,
or...
maybe buy this whole town
fix the place up.
Yen Town.
God, I hate it.
Stop!
You're looking well!
Not too bad.
We should be going.
Glico the hooker.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3m7a9
Help other users to choose the best subtitles