( van beeping )
nick cannon: If you're
desperate to conjure more clues
to our singers' identities,
your wish is our command.
Here at "the masked singer,"
we've obtained a rare artifact
that possesses the
most mysterious secrets.
All you have to do is...
- Rub? - ( squeaking )
last week's group c
premiere was enchanting
and full of hocus pocus.
- Oh, my goodness! - Ta-da!
- Wendy williams!
- ♪ Who is that?
Tonight,
the group c playoffs get magical.
- ♪ stay - whoa!
There's a chance that
you might be unbeatable.
- With spellbinding clues...
- Nicole: Whoa. Whoa.
- Is that a brain?
- Robin: It's a brain.
- It's not a brain.
- Aren't you a doctor?
I will take a bite to prove
to you that this isn't...
Daddy, don't eat it. No,
no, no, no.
- Oh, my god.
- No, no. No, don't eat... oh.
...And an unmasking that
will leave you mesmerized.
- Abracadabra. - Ken: Oh!
- Is that a lion?
- That's a tiger.
It's a tiger, magnum, p.U.
It's "the masked singer."
( squeaking )
let's do this.
( music playing )
♪ who are you?
♪ Who, who, who, who
♪ really, who are you?
♪ Who are you?
- ♪ who, who, who, who - whoo!
♪ Oh, I really wanna know
♪ who are you?
Oh, it's nick cannon!
Welcome, welcome,
welcome, everyone!
- Hi, nick.
- Welcome to the show that has your favorite celebs
doing exactly what you're
doing day in and day out.
They get out of bed,
put on a mask, and get to work.
Tonight is the big
group c playoffs.
We have mushroom, broccoli,
the squiggly monster,
and the jellyfish.
They're all fighting
to make it to the finals,
and each brings
something uniquely different.
And speaking of
stiff competition,
our panel is locked
in a battle of their own
with their first
impression guesses.
Sherlock scherzie and
cluemaster jenny are tied
after both correctly guessing
wendy williams last week.
- And I have some major news.
- Jenny: What?
We have a very
special guest tonight.
This singer is so
incredibly talented.
Put your hands together and
your remotes down for mr. Tv.
Season four is
full of surprises.
( music playing )
nicole: What's happening?
What?
♪ The way that you
cheer and sing for me ♪
♪ the applause,
applause, applause ♪
- oh, okay! - Oh, my god.
Jenny: Is it joel mchale again?
Definitely not joel mchale.
He can't move like that.
( music playing )
♪ here's to the
ones that we got ♪
♪ cheers to the wish you were here,
but you're not ♪
♪ 'cause the drinks bring
back all the memories ♪
♪ and the memories bring back,
memories bring back you ♪
who is this?
♪ Now my heart
feel like December ♪
♪ when somebody say your name ♪
♪ 'cause I can't
reach out to call you ♪
♪ but I know I will one day
- guys, who is this?
- Kenan thompson?
- Could be kenan.
- ♪ everybody hurts sometimes, everybody hurts someday ♪
♪ but everything'll
be all right ♪
♪ go raise a glass and say
♪ here's to the
ones that we got ♪
♪ toast to the ones
that we lost on the way ♪
♪ 'cause the drinks bring
back all the memories ♪
- is it jamie foxx?
- Sounds like jamie.
♪ Memories bring back you
♪ doo doo, doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ doo doo doo doo
♪ memories bring back,
memories bring back you ♪
- that was beautiful. - Wow.
There it is. Give
it up for mr. Tv.
- Wow.
- So they have no idea who you are.
So go ahead and
give them your clue.
My whole performance was a clue.
- I know who it is. - Who?
- I thought it was jamie.
- Jamie foxx.
- I think it's jamie foxx.
- If he can play ray charles, he can play a television.
Well,
we want to know who it is right now.
Audience, you know the drill.
( chanting ) take
it off! Take it off!
Nicole: Is it jamie?
- Get it! - Wayne brady!
The season two winner,
the fox himself,
and guest panelist tonight,
mr. Wayne brady.
Incredible job,
my brother, always.
- Brady!
- Now go ahead and take your place over there
- in the panel, man.
- I got it right, again.
He didn't. Ken,
you didn't get it right.
- Wayne brady! - The fox.
- Nicole: So exciting!
- Fox! Fox! Fox! Fox! Fox!
And, wayne,
I gotta say now that you're joining us,
the way you threw
everyone off a little bit,
it's like you're a
man of many voices.
That's the whole thing.
I love playing the game.
And the fact that I could come
out and lay another one down
and still not be guessed...
This game is amazing.
- It is, it is. - There it is.
Well, it is time to get
tonight's competition going.
We're kicking things
off with the mushroom.
If you're still stumped
over its identity,
here are some new clues about
this magical mystery megastar.
( music playing )
mushroom: You know,
mushrooms get a bad rap.
A lot of people don't
like the taste of us.
But I'm here to win the
world over one song at a time.
♪ All the things I
should've given but I didn't ♪
- oh, my god. - Nick: Wow!
Oh, I just want to eat you up.
Even as a young shroom,
I knew I was offbeat.
I often felt like I didn't
belong anywhere.
Compared with the other fungi,
I had totally different roots.
- You can't sit with us.
- Wow, so many "mean girl" references.
That was a broadway musical.
I was around strange
food and customs.
"black beetles." that's
a rae sremmurd song.
But then I realized
that under the surface,
we're all entangled
together as one.
And even a porcini or
cremini can be a prom queen.
Once I embraced being a nerd,
an outcast,
I could proudly
share my unique gifts.
"outkast." andré 3?
My weirdness has led me here,
and now it's time to
fetch the golden mask.
- Nicole: I am really excited to hear mushroom sing.
- Me, too.
Wayne, group c is,
like, our wackier group.
And then group a and b,
we have our powerhouses.
- That's for sure.
- Mushroom's gonna have a lot to live up to.
Right.
Nick: After the break,
the mushroom performs.
♪ Stay
- what?
- Plus more from the magical group c playoffs.
Get ready to get
your mind blown.
Judges: Oh!
And later,
someone disappears from the competition.
The singer with the
least amount of votes is...
Oh, my goodness!
Welcome back to
"the masked singer."
ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for the mushroom.
♪ If I could turn back time
♪ if I could find a way
my goodness.
♪ I'd take back those
words that hurt you ♪
♪ and you'd stay
♪ I don't know why I
did the things I did ♪
said the things I said ♪
♪ time's like a knife,
it can hurt deep inside ♪
♪ words are like weapons,
they wound sometimes ♪
♪ I didn't really
mean to hurt you ♪
♪ I didn't wanna see you go
♪ I know I said good-bye,
but, baby ♪
♪ if I could turn back time
whoo!
♪ If I could find a way
♪ I'd take back those
words that hurt you ♪
♪ if I could reach the stars
- wow. - Whoo!
♪ I'd give 'em all to you
♪ and you'd love me, love me
♪ like you used to do
♪ if I could turn back time
♪ if I could find a way
♪ and, baby, maybe, maybe
♪ you'd stay
what?
( holding note )
- what? What? - Nick: Wow!
- All right.
- We are in the presence of greatness.
That was hot.
Mushroom,
I think you might be unbeatable.
Absolutely. Last week he
focused more on his falsetto.
This week he sang in
his more natural belt voice
- and he totally switched it up.
- Totally.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, mushroom, you know what you're doing.
You are confident. Who is
going to touch you this season?
Well said. Now, mushrooms are
known for their magical properties,
so each singer tonight
will have a magic lamp
to reveal something
earth-shattering about their identity.
Men in black,
bring out the magic lamp.
- Ken: Oh, look at that. - Ooh.
- It's a magic lamp.
- You think will smith is gonna pop out?
All right, mushroom,
let me help you out.
I'ma rub it for you.
( chiming )
judges: Oh!
- Jenny: Wow.
- Snap. Dang. That was magical.
- Robin: Oh, wow.
- What is that?
- Is that a brain?
- It's a brain.
It's not a brain.
A mind is a terrible
thing to waste,
but it makes for a
pretty sweet clue.
So you're a zombie?
- Nicole: Hmm.
- Okay, get ready to get your minds blown.
Someone close to me from
atlanta is staring right at my eyes.
Donald glover,
my co-star on "community."
there was orange
juice in the package,
but I'm here to confirm
that it wasn't o.J. It was tang.
- 'cause donald, stay with me...
- I know where you're going with this.
...Got his childish gambino alter ego name,
true story,
from a random online
wu-tang generator.
- I'm not even kidding.
- As ridiculous as that sounds, that is the truth.
Thank you, daddy! And also,
that is not a red brain.
That is a red bone.
One of his most successful
singles. That's a red bone.
- Nick: Wait, when di...
- Donald glover.
- Aren't you a doctor? - What?
I will take a bite to prove to
you that this is not a bone.
No, no. No, don't... don't eat. Okay,
look, I was stretching.
Daddy, don't eat it. Daddy,
don't eat that. No, no, no.
- Daddy, I don't want you to eat...
- nicole: Ooh, it's jiggly.
- Oh, my god.
- Ken: No, no, no. I don't want... oh!
- Robin: Oh! - Nicole: Ahh!
- What... what flavor is that brain?
- Strawberry.
I don't know if
this is the person,
but I remembered seeing
something about queen, bee, proud.
Maybe it's somebody from
the lgbtq+ communities.
And not many people
can hold notes out like that
and who are that
technically talented.
So I was like,
it could be adam lambert.
Wayne: For me,
it's not adam lambert.
Adam has a weirdly,
freakishly surreal tone.
But just from the clue package,
"mean girls," high school,
being a bit different, I got willow
smith before the singing happened.
- Ah.
- And then I thought, okay, maybe it is jaden.
And there was the red brain.
Maybe there's a link to "red table talk,"
- which is intellectual conversation.
- Oh, my gosh. I like it.
- Yes.
- I'm thinking jaden smith.
I agree. After that vocal,
that's a very good guess.
And he has a new album, so this
might be a great opportunity for him
- to showcase his voice.
- Okay, that's good. Yeah, yeah.
One thing we all know is that
performance was outstanding.
- Yes. - Whoo!
Nick: Keep it going
for the mushroom.
Wait,
is donald glover that tall though?
Well, is nick cannon that
short? The answer to both is yes.
- Nick, can you give us a clue?
- No.
- I think nick knows.
- I'm surprised that you don't.
Did our panel's mushroom
guesses turn into mush?
Agree or disagree?
Just use that hashtag.
Mushroom: I've spent so
much time feeling like an outcast,
but I feel right at home
under this mushroom cap.
I just can't get enough of this weird,
wild experience.
♪ Who is that?
Hey, mush,
what do you say we form an alliance
and guarantee a spot
in our group c finals?
I got a few moldy pals that could give
the competition a real stomach ache.
That's a little extreme, broc.
Come on,
I thought you were a fun guy.
Okay, okay. Let's do it. I'm in.
♪ Who is that?
Welcome back to your favorite
madcap hollywood costume party.
It's "the masked
singer" group c playoffs.
- Yes!
- Last week, broccoli threw down the gauntlet.
If you've still got a lot of room
left on your crudités platter
for decent guesses,
here are some new clues
about the celebrity
behind the broc star.
( music playing )
- yeah, just like that.
- Broccoli: I love brocc-ing this costume.
I feel like I'm a success story
for "the masked
singer" diet plan,
coupled with it being
so steamy in this mask,
I've already lost weight.
But it's no sweat,
because as far back
as I can remember,
I've always wanted
to be a broccoli.
Okay,
"goodfellas." ray liotta? De niro?
I dreamed of being a superfood
that enriches people's lives.
"copacabana"? Barry manilow,
anybody?
And one night,
I got the opportunity to do just that.
I had dinner with a legendary friend,
the big cheese.
I need your help on one final
project before I grow moldy, capisce?
I raced home,
and after pulling an all-nighter,
I cooked up a beauty
that really packed a punch.
- I called the boss...
- Three, seven, two...
- Spit it out.
- I made something special,
but even I couldn't have
imagined the classic I created.
And all from one meal!
And tonight I'm gonna serve
up another side of my legacy,
the sultry side.
( music playing )
♪ I've been alone with you
♪ inside my mind
♪ and in my dreams
I've kissed your lips ♪
♪ a thousand times
♪ I sometimes see you
pass outside my door ♪
♪ hello
♪ is it me you're looking for? ♪
♪ I can see it in your eyes
♪ I can see it in your smile
♪ you're all I've ever wanted ♪
- ♪ these arms are
open wide - okay.
♪ 'cause you know,
you know just what to say ♪
♪ and you know just what to do ♪
♪ and I want to
tell you so much ♪
- ♪ I love you - whoa.
- I love you, too!
- ♪ I love you
♪ I love
♪ you
I just got serenaded
by broccoli.
- Wow. - Hello! Hello, hello.
It is you we are looking for.
Broccoli rocking the stage.
- Broc star!
- Nicole: Oh, my gosh.
Nick,
I usually go for the tall ones,
but broccoli has my
heart this season.
- Totally.
- Especially after he just serenaded me
with that little
broc fro of his.
All right, there it is.
Yeah. What I really liked about it
was the first time you performed,
it was all up tempo,
high energy.
And this week,
I feel like we really got to...
A sense of your sensitive side,
you know what I mean?
That maybe when you're at home,
you just be
looking in the mirror
singing lionel richie. I get it.
I've been there,
and I'll do it again.
All right, well,
let's grab broccoli's magic lamp.
Men in black,
bring out the lamp.
( music playing )
let's do this.
I'll rub it for you.
( chiming )
whoa!
- Nick: All right.
- Robin: Roulette.
- He's a player.
- Take this clue for a spin,
and you may land on my identity
if you're lucky.
Ooh, lucky. Okay, well,
we have the roulette wheel.
- Screams vegas, right?
- Yeah. Yes.
- Mr. Vegas, wayne newton? - Oh!
Nicole: Okay? There was
a guitar in the package.
Wayne plays guitar. Was
wayne in "goodfellas" or...
- No.
- Wasn't he in "the hangover"?
- I think "the hangover"...
- Yeah, there it is.
- No, it's fine.
- Ken was in that movie.
- Get out of here. - Yeah.
- Ken, do you know who it is?
- I've been wishing that martin short,
one of my favorite comedic idols,
that he could be on this.
Saw canadian
bacon in the package.
You know, one of canada's
best. The anchor for "captain ron,"
- his movie with kurt russell. He is the real deal.
- Ooh.
- He can do it all.
- Broadway star, too.
Yes, broadway star as well.
You know, this is my annual
wish. Martin short, please.
- All right. - Please be you.
Genie,
rubbing the lamp for martin short.
I agree completely with ken.
Nick, that's on the record.
The winner of "the masked
singer" agreed with my guess.
That's a first.
Um,
I think I unlocked a major clue.
- Okay.
- Okay, bear with me. Bear with me.
- We're ready for it.
- Okay, so first from the clue package,
and it was an
incomplete phone number.
So I broke it down,
and I got a bunch of different words.
But the one that hit was frank.
It spelled frank, those numbers.
- Are you serious, jenny?
- Nick: Jenny's really working over here.
And then I thought about this
broadway play called "the producers."
and jason alexander
was in "the producers."
and then I was like, well,
how does jason connect to frank?
And I realized frank costanza
is he dad on "seinfeld."
- ken: Wow.
- So maybe jason alexander.
- Nicole: Wow. That is great, jenny.
- Robin: Great job.
- I like it. I like it.
- Thanks. I'm exhausted.
- I'm gonna go to sleep now. Good night.
- Ken: Yeah. Good night.
Nick: Well, we can all agree
that we can't sleep on this guy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
one more time. Broccoli!
Did the broccoli pack
enough of a nutritious punch
to make it to the group c final?
Tonight I showed the
panel my mushy side
and they ate it up.
Especially nicole.
Things were getting steamy
between the two of us.
Nick: When we return,
things get heated.
- I refute everything that you just said, ken.
- Whoa! Come back!
And you don't want to
miss this epic unmasking.
- Judges: Oh! - Yes!
Jenny: I kind of love
this magic element.
Like, if we could make a wish
and I can make ken disappear.
If I had a magic power, it would be
able to see through the costumes.
- That's actually a good one.
- Robin, do you... would you wish for a magic power?
- What would your magic wish be?
- Oh, to comfort and console
- the ills of the human spirit.
- Wow.
Now I feel shallow.
♪ Who is that?
Welcome back to
"the masked singer"
and our group c playoffs.
We still have two
singers to hear from,
and the next one is a character
that has more eyes and arms
than a bus full of kids...
The squiggly monster.
If you're still fearful that you
don't have enough good guesses,
just watch these new clues.
( music playing )
squiggly monster: America!
The more time I spend
canvassing in this costume,
the more the squiggly
monster and I are becoming one.
And who wouldn't want
to be this sexy squiggly?
( belches ) oops.
But despite my
unbridled handsomeness,
I have to report an
inconvenient truth...
That while I have
a colorful exterior,
there's more than
meets the eyes.
Is that the white house?
As a little squiggle,
I was bullied for
being different.
And I was struck over and over
by a barrage of tragedies.
But through those tough times,
I found that laughter
was my best medicine.
So, tall and makes people laugh.
Because you may
get knocked around,
you may slip and fall.
You may get hit in
your piggly squiggly.
But the big picture is our
time on this green earth
is to short not to
embrace the silly daily.
Tonight,
my campaign strategy is to sing a classic
that you can't resist
singing along to,
and of course, get your vote.
( music playing )
♪ I can't get no
♪ satisfaction
♪ 'cause I try and I try
♪ and I try and I try
- ♪ I can't get no - whoo!
♪ Well, I can't get no
♪ when I'm driving in my car
♪ and that man
comes on the radio ♪
♪ and he's telling
me more and more ♪
- whoo!
- ♪ about some useless information ♪
♪ supposed to fire
my imagination ♪
♪ I can't get no
♪ oh, no, no, no
♪ hey, hey, hey
♪ well, that's what I say
♪ well, I can't get no
♪ I can't get no
♪ I can't get me no
♪ satisfaction
♪ no satisfaction
( vocalizing )
- nicole: Come on, squig!
- Ken: Yeah!
- Yay!
- Satisfaction from the squiggly monster.
Awesome job. Ken, you still over
there getting some satisfaction?
Yes,
I... very satisfying performance.
That might be the most just
fun performance of the night.
You're incredibly entertaining,
but tonight you showed you got some range.
- You can sing. You can really sing.
- Yeah.
Well, let's grab ahold of squiggly
monster's magic lamp to get another clue.
Men in black,
bring out the lamp.
Yeah, yeah. Clue, clue.
( music playing )
bring out the lamp.
Right, uh, squiggly,
I think you got a little too many hands.
I can rub this for you.
( chiming )
judges: Whoa.
I'm here to "bear" it all. Yes,
I said that.
And that starts with
this very cuddly clue.
Nick: All right,
you guys picking up on anything?
- Yes, I am, actually, nick.
- Uh-oh. Our clue expert.
You know,
I was thinking of this person,
and then that clue
made it say yes.
He said laughter is
the best medicine.
This man was a doctor
on a show called "becker."
- ooh.
- Also, there was a father figure reference
in the first package.
He was also in "three
men and a baby."
now the teddy bear
comes out. It's ted danson!
- Robin: Yeah. - Ken: I like it.
- Oh, go off, jenny.
- I like it.
Robin: Well, I'm thinking,
so the teddy bear,
now this guy was
in the movie "ted 2."
and there was a
pineapple in the package.
He was in "the spongebob movie,"
who lives in a
pineapple under the sea.
I'm gonna go with
david squigglehoff.
- Jenny: Oh! - Nick: The hoff?
- I'm gonna go with the hoff.
- The height is...
- He's a great singer. - I like.
All right, ken,
can you top that?
I just can't get politicians out
of my mind grapes right now
because everything... when he
was talking about inconvenient truth,
it could be former vice
president al gore. I'm just saying.
It could be just
someone... Hear me out.
Just trying to
connect everything.
Al gore, he had an oscar-winning
documentary "inconvenient truth."
- oh, okay.
- Lots of comedy clues.
Al gore once hosted
"snl" back in 2002.
Also, ted, teddy bear.
Al gore has given
many ted talks.
Former vice president al gore.
You know what? I'm gonna go
ahead and rock with ken... ken again.
- Again? - I feel it's the...
There's something
wrong here. Hold on.
In looking at the clue,
the first shot
was something that
looked like the oval office,
so you think politics.
Later,
you got the vibe that he is a funny person.
Likes merging the worlds
of comedy and politics.
There are people that do that. Trevor noah,
stephen colbert.
But the "inconvenient
truth" was such a big clue.
I'm gonna have to go more
so with al gore on this one.
- Jenny: Wow.
- Agreeing with ken for the second time.
- Twice. - Wait.
Hold on, hold on. Squiggly
monster has something to say.
- Ken: Whoa.
- Nick, I actually have something for you.
- I actually do. - Uh-oh.
- Because I love nick.
- Hey, I love you, too, squiggly monster.
- Yeah!
- This is for you. I know you love hats.
- I do.
- And I'm not just kissing up. I hope you love it.
- This is... - Aww.
- Oh, look at that!
- Nicole: Hey!
Ken: Wow! Look at that.
Mr. Squiggle, mr. Squiggle,
are there any clues that go with it?
I don't think it's a clue. I just
think he genuinely likes me.
Well, I think you guys are
looking for some more clues.
So, we've been getting a lot
of questions about our singers,
and one of our
fans wants to know...
Oh, yes, I'm married. But, nick,
I never got your wedding gift.
- Classic gore.
- Does that help anything?
- That narrows things down.
- Right. Not at all basically, nick, not at all.
Well, I appreciate my gift. Y'all keep it
going for the amazing squiggly monster.
- Wayne: Good job, squiggly.
- Ken: Good job, squiggly.
Nick: Are our panel's squiggly
monster guesses ghoulishly great?
Tell us what you think.
I just lived out some major rock star dreams
I've had since I was a little squiggle.
I just hope it was enough to get
me elected into the group c finals.
♪ Who is that?
- ♪ who is that?
- Welcome back to "the masked singer."
and we've arrived at the
final competitor of the night,
the jellyfish.
If you're still confused
over who the jellyfish is,
maybe these new clues
will be the perfect bait.
Check it out.
( music playing )
jellyfish: I'm
super competitive,
but my nerves got the
best of me last time.
Robin: I could hear a
little bit of the nervousness,
but beautiful vocal tone.
It was hard to hear,
especially because I'm usually
one of the best at what I do.
Also, I'm here without the
people who pick me up when I fall.
My family.
My parents are the sea's knees.
The uss big bird?
Sacrificing time
and their careers
so I could follow my dream.
There's my ride or die,
papa jelly.
He helped engineer
my whole world
and taught me
the best lifehacks.
Yoga mats. Oh,
maybe kate hudson?
For years he'd wake up at 3 am,
put me in the car,
and I'd wake up hours
later at gigs in faraway lands.
- Gigs.
- Maybe she's in a group?
Oops! How'd that get in there?
Tonight,
I'm gonna use my dad's wisdom
to help fight off the nerves.
Xoxo, papa j. Love you.
Aww.
You know,
last time she performed,
she was really, really nervous.
See,
I get that. Because being in that costume,
they're almost more naked
than when they are themselves.
- Ken: Right. - ( thunder )
( sighs )
( music playing )
♪ crazy
♪ I'm crazy for feeling
♪ so lonely
♪ I'm crazy
♪ crazy for feeling
♪ so blue
ooh.
♪ Worry
♪ why do I let myself worry?
Wow.
♪ Wondering
♪ what in the world
♪ did I do?
♪ Oh, crazy
♪ for thinking that my love
♪ could hold you
beautiful.
♪ I'm crazy for trying
♪ I'm crazy for crying
♪ and I'm crazy
♪ for loving you
yes! Yes!
I loved it, I loved it,
I loved it, I loved it.
Wow. Talking about crazy.
Amazing performance.
Jellyfish, last time you performed,
which was beautiful,
but you were very nervous.
You've already
grown into this role.
And I saw you hopping up and down
afterwards like you were proud of yourself.
You should be! 'cause
that was amazing.
- Robin: Yeah!
- Wayne: Yeah, I'm so floored by you.
I know from being in that experience,
if you keep evolving,
there's no doubt that we will not
be seeing you at the end of this show
- winning the competition.
- Nicole: Yeah!
Reverend wayne brady,
ladies and gentlemen.
- Wow.
- Nick: We love it. Well, it is time
to bring out the magic lamp.
( music playing )
all right, jellyfish, you ready?
( chiming )
- robin: Whoa!
- Nicole: Oh, ho, ho, ho.
- That was a big one. - Whoa.
- Robin: Roar. - What?
If you can earn your stripes
and pounce on this clue...
( purrs )
( purrs ) she was rolling that.
All right,
you guys picking up on anything?
I'm picking up on something. I was
thinking about in the clue package
how it said,
"my dad took me to gigs,"
and we're all
assuming it's her gigs.
Why couldn't it
be the dad's gigs?
- Ah.
- Robin: The dad's taking her to his gigs, right?
So, that kicked in
another idea. Is that a lion?
- That's a tiger.
- It's a tiger, magnum, p.U.
Robin: All right,
we're gonna say that's a lion.
That's lionel richie,
and you're sofia richie.
- Jenny: Oh! - Ken: Whoa!
Well, this is the lionel richie
pose on the album cover.
You had me on the brilliance of,
like,
( imitating robin ) "yes,
maybe the dad had gigs.
Is that a doggie?"
all right, ken,
then go ahead with your brilliant idea.
With pleasure. Okay,
I believe this is someone
from the popular netflix movie
"to all the boys
I've loved before."
lana condor. Amazing actress.
"xoxo" in the package.
She was in "x-men."
and name-drop, imdb alert,
I am attached to play
her father in a movie,
so winning the
golden mask trophy
will be the second best thing
to happen to her this year.
Also, big bird's in the
package. A condor is a big bird.
Wayne: The thing
that I'm worried about
is if anything that you just
said makes sense to me,
that means that I
need to be examined.
But you have agreed with
two of his guesses already.
But it will not be three,
my brother.
Let me break this down for you.
Okay, so, maybe they're
part of a show business family.
There was a family of four.
I'm thinking someone
like jamie lynn spears,
who has been in show
business for years.
But then I went,
"oh! Wait a minute."
from the opening
tone of the voice,
it could also be halle bailey,
who was one part
of chloe x halle.
She is going to be the new ariel in
the remake of "the little mermaid."
- nicole: Yeah.
- And her father is the engineer of her career.
And "xoxo" is a beyoncé song,
and she signed them.
So that makes sense. I refute
everything that you've said, ken.
- Whoa! - And that is a tiger.
Not a liger. Not a leopard.
- I'm out. Carole baskin!
- Go! Go off, wayne!
- Come back!
- We've lost total control,
but ladies and gentlemen,
keep it going for the
one and only jellyfish.
That was definitely the
performance of the night.
Yeah.
Nick: Did the
jellyfish swim her way
into the group c finals?
Tell us what you think.
Tonight,
group c brought the magic,
but sadly, someone is about to
disappear from the competition.
Studio audience, panel,
and our superfans at home,
time to vote for your favorite.
Only three will advance
to the group c finals.
The ballots have been cast.
The singer with the least
amount of votes will be unmasked.
( groans )
and that, my friends, is...
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
The singer with the
least amount of votes
headed home tonight is...
Squiggly monster.
- Oh, my gosh!
- ( all groaning )
keep it going for
squiggly monster.
The rest of you, congrats.
We'll see you in
the group c finals.
Come on,
squiggly. You just step down here.
- Robin: Squiggly! - Squiggly!
Squiggly, I mean,
you put up an incredible fight.
And there's a silver
lining right now.
Even though you're not
going to make it through,
we get to see who's behind the mask,
right?
- Yeah! - Nicole: Yeah!
- Ken: Yes. - But first,
let's retrieve the panel's first
impression guesses from the vault.
Oh,
my god. Do not bring these out.
Nick: Men in black,
bring 'em out.
If your first impression guesses
are correct, you get a point.
Oh, my gosh.
Jenny's first impression
was bob saget.
Jenny: Yeah, you know what?
That was my first
impression guess,
and then the clues on this show
can just screw with your mind.
So it was taking me in
all different directions.
I originally was thinking
maybe al franken.
Then I thought maybe ted danson
because, you know,
the teddy bear.
But then, you know,
I just... Going back to my initial gut.
Father figure,
"full house." and then I saw the dj.
- D.J. "full house." hello.
- Oh.
I'm gonna go back and stick
with my first impression guess,
- bob saget. - Nick: Really?
Mr. Robin thicke,
his first impression
was also bob saget.
- Wow.
- Robin: Yeah, but then, you know, the clues,
and you're wrong
so many times before
that you start
second-guessing yourself.
So I'm thinking of other
dads like ray romano
who are also stand-up comedians.
And then I went with
david squigglehoff
because of the teddy
bear and some other things.
But bob actually did this speech
at my father's rehearsal dinner
for his second wedding,
so bob and I go way back.
So it was the voice and the
sense of humor that gave it away.
I still think it's bob saget.
Ken, your first impression,
you said this is fabio.
- Nicole: Oh, my gosh.
- You used that as a joke in previous seasons.
Oh, fabio's no joke, my friend.
- Nicole: Oh, my god.
- So are you sticking with this fabio guess?
- No, I'm not. - Smart move.
I've been going
back and forth on this.
I thought dr. Fauci
for medicine.
And al gore,
I thought for "inconvenient truth."
but this is my
inconvenient truth.
I'm changing my guess,
if that's okay with you.
When I'm thinking from
all the clue packages,
and actually today,
the teddy bear clue
was for ted mosby,
or "how I met your mother,"
that bob narrated.
I think it's bob saget.
At least you got to
somewhere sensible.
Nicole,
your first impression guess,
one of the ying yang twins.
Good night, nicole scherzinger.
- Nicole, I love it so much!
- Do you lose an ear for that?
- I didn't know. I...
- this is my favorite guess ever on the show.
Wasn't it? And she didn't even make a
distinction between which ying yang twin.
Oh,
the one that got the hair like that.
Are you sticking with
your ying yang twins?
Of course I'm not.
I'm gonna have to
go with gary cole.
And that was "office
space." that was lumbergh,
- the character that you're doing an impression of.
- Thank you. Thanks. Yeah.
He was also the dad in
the movie "brady bunch."
- yes.
- Right? And also with the white house,
he was in "west wing" and "veep,"
so...
Pretty good guess.
Mr. Wayne brady,
who do you think this is?
Well, at first I thought it
was mystikal from no limit.
But, you know what? Everything
snapped into clear focus,
and I actually had
this guess myself
when I was writing
down stuff earlier.
I thought bob saget. What threw
me was all of the political stuff.
But then the football with the guy getting
hit in the junk and the banana peel,
I went, "oh,
that's like a clip show."
well,
the gold standard for those clip shows
and for every host that's come after,
it's bob saget.
And if we are correct,
I'm sad that we're
sending bob saget home
because he truly is
one of the funniest,
dirtiest comedians of all time.
Indeed. I'm a huge
fan of bob saget.
Okay, panel,
you've made your final guesses.
Let's see if any
of you are right.
Squiggly monster,
show us who you really are.
Audience, say it with me.
( chanting ) take
it off! Take it off!
- Take it off! Saget!
- ♪ who, who, who, who
♪ who are you?
♪ Who, who, who, who
- ♪ who - take it off, already!
- ♪ I really wanna
know - take it off!
- ♪ tell me who
are you - come on!
♪ You, you, are you?
- Saget!
- Nick: Television icon,
actor, entertainer,
comedian og, bob saget!
- Bob saget! - Ken: Saget!
Making so many people happy
as the squiggly monster, as you do.
We're so happy to have you here.
What you guys do here
is why I wanted to do this.
Because, you know,
we're all going through a tough time.
I get to be part of your
joy. And it's needed so bad.
They said,
"do you want to be squiggly monster?"
they sent me a picture. I said,
"yeah."
ken's been texting me, "hey,
would you ever want to come by?"
and I went, "no,
I'm really... no.
I'm really busy. I love you."
and, nicole,
I don't know what to say.
- Nick: Miss ying ying twin.
- I bet you never felt more street, right?
- Well, I am street. I am.
- Nick: He definitely is.
Ken: I know you won't
even remember this.
I was moonlighting
at the laugh factory,
going up and doing open mics,
and you actually saw my act,
like, 20 years ago.
- And you were so supportive.
- You can tell when someone
is special and someone is funny
and someone is a
comedian at heart.
And not only that, but you were a
doctor and you gave me your free exam,
- and I want to thank you.
- Right there in the club.
Right behind that red curtain.
What is the best part
about being squiggly monster?
- Taking it off.
- Great job.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's hear it one more time
for the icon
who is mr. Bob saget.
- We love you, bob.
- Love you, bob.
Thank you to our very own fox,
mr. Wayne brady,
for coming back.
- Whoo!
- Nick: And now,
here to perform unmasked
once and for all,
the artist formerly known
as squiggly monster,
the one and only bob saget!
♪ 'cause I try and I try
♪ and I try and I try
♪ I can't get no
♪ well, I can't get no
♪ no satisfaction
♪ whoa!
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org