Previously on "The
Walking Dead"...
You need to see a doctor.
I have a meeting with
Pamela Milton later.
Someone like me would
never meet Ms. Milton.
Why not?
You have to know
your place.
Hey! I did nothing wrong,
Hey! I swear!
Oh, my God! What did you do?!
Don't you know who that is?
Got something coming!
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
We're all friends.
They're here to help.
You've fallen on hard times.
I have an interesting
choice to offer.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Man, that's... that's enough.
Yeah, man. No problem, man.
Did great in there, buddy.
You were very brave.
H-Hey!
Don't worry, li'l
dude. You're home, see?
Safe and sound.
Apples?
Come on. Let's go take a look.
Improved By M_I_S
www.opensubtitles.org
DAY 30 IN THE COMMONWEALTH
Thank you.
I'll take a witch hat.
Good choice. Thank you.
Hey! You're one of
the new people, right?
I heard you all lived
out in the wasteland,
killing rotters?
Yeah, I guess.
Cool.
So, there's probably nothing
you're afraid of, huh?
Come on, I'll show you where
all the good candy's at.
And I'm Mei.
Jude.
Cool name.
So, uh, what do you think?
It takes a minute to get
used to all this, you know?
You know, this place
was up and running
long before we ever got here.
Maybe we don't have to do
anything to make it work.
No, there's always something
you got to do to make it work.
Want another one?
Oh, hello! Happy Halloween!
And here's one for you...
and one for you.
They're delicious, aren't
they? You like 'em?
And first place goes to...
dressed as our
very own Mercer...
Celeste!
And this year's
grand prize is...
10 lottery tickets!
Let's take some pictures.
Thank you all for
coming out today.
You all look fantastic,
and I'm so happy you're
out here for Halloween.
I always thought
she was so classy.
I never knew anything about her.
Mm, I used to read
a lot of tabloids.
Hey! You two look busy.
Connie's reporting
for the paper.
We've got a full day.
How's work?
"It's nice to be
reporting again,
but Commonwealth
news isn't exactly...
hard-hitting."
Have you, uh, met Pamela yet?
"I interviewed her once,
before the world fell."
Yeah, and you also got her uncle
kicked out of Congress, so...
That was you?
"We gotta go.
We have a lot to do before
the masquerade ball."
See you later.
You should ask her to dance.
I gotta get to work.
Hey. Catch up later?
Yeah. See ya later.
Thanks
for watching Coco.
I'll come by tonight
to pick her up.
You know, why don't I
just keep her overnight?
You're sure to be exhausted
after the late shift.
You sure?
Yeah, of course.
Okay, well, thank you.
I'll, uh... I'll get her
before your Bible study.
Okay.
Shh, shh, shh.
Aww! Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Thank you. Bye.
Hi. Hey.
How's the place? Getting
any better? Hell, no.
No, I think this place is
literally made out of paper.
You sleeping?
Nah. No, no.
Can't wait 'til basic's over
and we get new apartments
Worrying about money
again is so weird.
It's not forever.
Ready, set, go!
Tide's turning and
Ezra's back in the game!
Just when we
thought it was over.
There is no telling
how this ends!
Ezekiel, come play!
Nothing I'd love more,
but I gotta take care
of these little guys.
- Us too.
- Okay.
Okay, okay, let's thank Ezekiel
for letting us use
Shiva's collar, huh?
It was the cherry on top of
that sweet costume, right?
Sorry, bud. We
gotta give it back.
You know, Ezra...
your dad saved this from
Hilltop when it burned
because he knew how
precious it was to me.
But there's something
actually more precious,
and that is your family.
So this leash is yours,
on two conditions. One,
that it always makes you
as happy as it made me.
And two, that you
honor Shiva's memory
and always think of her
when you play with it.
You have fun, buddy.
Ezekiel, you sure?
Yeah, just be
careful. It's a chain.
Who's hungry? Yeah?
Looks like they had fun today.
Oh, I think it was
good for everybody.
Yeah.
How are you feeling?
Also good.
Excuse me. Mm.
How was your
doctor's appointment?
Fine. No changes.
Have you heard from
Maggie or Lydia?
I'm sure they're okay.
Are you?
On a beautiful day like today?
Never better.
Oh, gosh. I'm so sorry!
I'm... I'm such a klutz!
Carol?
What are you doing here?
Sorry.
Snooping.
I was worried about Ezekiel.
What do you want to know?
Well, I know that
he needs surgery,
and I know that he's in line.
How long before you
get to number 147?
Too long.
Patients aren't aware
of their place in line,
so can you do me a favor
and keep that yourself?
Mm-hmm. Of course.
Does Ezekiel know how
bad his chances are?
He knows the odds aren't good.
But he doesn't know
there's likely no chance
he'll get the surgery unless...
by some miracle
he moves up the line.
I'm sorry. I wish
I could do more.
Welcome to the kill house.
In this exercise, killing
is not your primary goal.
I'm looking for
speed and teamwork.
Two teams of two will start
the course simultaneously.
One team goes through
the house on the right,
the other team takes
the house on the left.
There's one weapon per
team that must be shared.
Your objective...
Get through the house
and all the rotters inside.
There will be a rotter marked
in red at the end of each house.
First team to take out their...
Red gets one step closer
to earning their stripes.
But fail to work as a unit...
see what you get.
Hart, you're with Thomas.
Espinosa, Green.
Quintana, Johnson.
Dixon, Daniels.
Team up.
You mind if I go with
Espinosa? We make a good team.
Did I ask for your opinion?
Espinosa, Green.
Dixon, Daniels.
You're up first.
We got this. I know
you're the fastest,
and I'm the baddest,
so we're good.
Let's do this.
Hey. I'm Jake.
'Sup, Jake?
Aah!
I got it!
Clear.
Move.
Take it!
Keep going!
Aah!
Espinosa!
Dixon!
And what was that?
He was good. I
was right there.
I said speed and teamwork.
Green, Espinosa. Nicely done.
Dixon.
You're with me.
Wow.
You have to get
this. It's so good.
I don't have any money.
Oh. Don't you
get an allowance?
Hey! Who's your friend, Jude?
Hi, Princess! This is Mei.
Oh, I see Mei got the
memo. I dig her already.
You guys need any help?
Um, I think I'm
ready to check out.
Oh, rock on. Good taste.
Well, pleasure doing business,
and come back anytime, ladies.
You didn't have to.
It's a gift. For a friend
Can I have the receipt?
Oh, don't worry
about paying me back.
I'd like it as a
reminder. Of a good day.
None of these are going to work.
Seriously? None of these.
This is ridiculous.
I'm not angry, I'm
just frustrated.
She wants something worthy
of tonight's guests.
That isn't it.
We did the best we could
with the time we had.
She knows you'll come through.
Aah!
Hi.
Espinosa, we don't
need you for this.
I volunteered.
Give her a bag. I
love volunteers.
Especially ones
that look like that.
Right here.
Alright. Let's see
what Santa brought me.
This supposed to be funny?
He gets the newest
ones for his drills.
Advanced military
training, Mercer.
Advanced military training.
It's fine.
Hey, careful with that one.
This toothpick?
Yeah. It's not worth my time.
You gotta swing all
the way through.
That thing is pathetic.
Belongs on a wall.
Alright. Release the rotters.
With me.
Two at a time, on my count.
Three, two, one.
Why did you do that?! You...
Are you serious?
Thisis the future soldier
of the Commonwealth?
You shouldn't have intervened.
He would've been fine.
Did I fail another
team-building exercise?
You're used to handling things
on your own. I get that.
But that's not how
it works around here.
Sometimes we have to set
each other up to win.
What does that have to do
with that little prick's ego?
This place...
is as good
as anything I've seen.
It'll give you a decent
life if you can cut it.
And I want you to succeed.
But you gotta get out
of your own damn way.
You get lost out there?
Sorry. Long line
at the kitchen.
Here you go.
How was your day?
What? How was your day?
It was great.
I made a new friend. Oh, yeah?
She got me a record.
You ever heard of Motorhead?
That's good stuff.
Here, boy.
Oh. Hi!
Daryl? Yeah?
Can I get an allowance?
Can we wait a little
while 'til my job settles?
Then we'll talk about it again?
So, we can stay?
Do you want to stay?
Even after Alexandria
is all cleaned up?
I do! Yeah?
It's nice.
I think as long as my mom knows
where to find us,
I want to stay.
Yeah, no. It's way too tight.
Tell Max we'll have
something by tonight.
How did you know?
My mother always taught
me to be observant.
So, you found a way to get
outside the walls, huh?
Mm...
What do you want from me?
I have a friend who's
waiting for surgery,
and I need you to get him
to the front of the line.
That's a big ask.
Difficult stuff.
Not for you.
First things first.
I need to make sure this
wine goes over well.
Oh, it will.
Mmm! I can almost taste it.
Shame, my kids don't
even know what mango is.
Well, maybe they'll
have some one day.
My kids?
Not anytime soon.
Thank you.
Want some wine?
We hear it's really good.
Thank you.
Cheers.
What's wrong?
Not really my scene.
You know, I was cool being
on the other side of this.
But this... This is
your world, not mine.
Okay. Just take it easy.
If this is how the
other half lives,
might as well enjoy it, right?
Mm. Thank you.
On your left! On your left!
- Shot over here!
- This way!
- Good to see you, sir!
- Enjoy the party.
- Quick photo?
One more look. This way, sir.
Wow. He hates you.
That was a hate smile.
Hey, Mercer! Echate pa ca!
Gonna need a translation.
I just wanted to say hi.
You look very handsome
tonight. Súper guapo.
It's not my thing.
Oh, it is. Trust me.
You know, uh...
I hate these big events.
Kinda boring.
You want to make it
more interesting?
Join me?
I would be honored.
Name?
She's with me.
There's a dress code.
Princess!
Pamela,
how do you like the wine?
It's fine.
If you'll excuse me, Lance,
I'm due for an interview.
Oh, and we need to get
a meeting on the books
about this Alexandria thing.
I have questions.
I have a pitch.
I'm sure you do.
Connie, so lovely
to see you again.
Kelly, nice to meet you.
I hope you're enjoying
the festivities.
"Such an eventful day.
But speaking on the record,
do you celebrate every holiday
with such grandeur here?"
Traditions provide comfort and
structure in uncertain times.
So, yes, we treasure
our holidays here.
But Halloween is extra special.
You may remember from my
father's time in the White House
that it was his favorite.
He always loved a
good masquerade ball.
"What would your father
say about the class divide
on display here?"
Well, we're lucky
you've found us.
We appreciate and celebrate
every single person
who contributes to
our vibrant community.
In fact, I want to
introduce you to someone.
Carrie is last year's
lottery winner.
This is her first
masquerade ball!
If you'll excuse me.
Excuse me, Pamela, I'm...
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Ms. Milton has a very
strict itinerary tonight.
That guy looks so familiar.
Yeah, I kicked his
ass in the train car.
That Trooper? Uh-huh.
Why is he serving food?
Testing, testing.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention
for a moment, please?
It is my honor tonight
to introduce someone
who needs no introduction.
Our esteemed leader,
the governor of
the Commonwealth,
Ms. Pamela Milton!
Thank you all for
coming out this evening.
Tonight, I have
the great pleasure
of giving you a sneak peek
at something truly special.
This is the work of the
brilliant Alexa Park,
who is here tonight.
Don't be shy, Alexa.
It took Ms. Park nine months
to lovingly create
this painting.
Like many of our citizens,
she sustained serious
injuries out in the world
before she found sanctuary
at the Commonwealth.
Thanks to my
father's sacrifices,
we are all here.
Brick by brick and
block by block,
we're putting the
world back together
the way it was.
My father would be so proud
to see what the
Commonwealth is today.
How much this place protects
and cares for all its citizens.
Bullshit!
This is bullshit!
Sir, that's enough... Does
anyone here really believe
the Commonwealth cares
for all its citizens?
Do you know who I am?
Sir, this isn't the time.
Please, you need to stop.
Don't come any closer!
I just want to talk.
Will you please
just talk to me?!
I would've died for this
place. What's my name?!
I don't know. But I'd like to.
Tyler Davis. I was a Trooper.
I tried and I
tried to reach you.
One mistake and I
lost everything.
I came here to talk to
you, to make you listen.
Tyler. I want to listen.
Let's talk, just
the two of us...
Don't lie!
Thisis what you care about.
Fancy parties and paintings.
Not people like me.
We're nothing to
you. Disposable.
You're wrong, Tyler.
I see you.
I see you're hurting
and I want to fix that.
But first, you have to promise
not to hurt anyone else.
Please put down the knife
and let my assistant go.
Her name is Max.
I'm like you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Did get hurt you?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Just gonna stand there?
Go after him!
Get him.
South wing and roof, all clear.
I need a status on Dixon.
Got nowhere to go.
You taking me in?
You gonna give me a choice?
Shit, I didn't mean to...
I just wanted to talk to her,
to get her to understand.
But that was never gonna happen.
Stop!
Don't do that.
I screwed up protocols
with a prisoner.
I got beat up.
Lost my apartment,
my spending card...
I have no way to help
my sister or kids.
You got a sister.
That means you got family.
A lot of us don't get
to have that anymore.
Don't take that away
from her. It's not fair.
Turn around.
Let's go.
You caught the bastard.
Finally did something right.
No.
No, you caught him.
Go ahead. Take
him to your mom.
He could have grabbed anyone.
Well done, Sebastian.
Remove him.
You think getting rid
of me solves anything?
There are thousands
more like me.
Resist the Commonwealth!
Visibility for workers!
Equality for all!
Are there thousands more?
No.
Make sure.
Inside, please,
miss. Let's go.
How'd the wine go over?
Great.
It was a good first step.
What's next?
I'm glad you asked.
Murphy, you're on the door.
Katz, Lewis, split
the wait staff.
Figure out how he gained access.
Did he have help?
I want answers.
Espinosa.
Your friend on the wait staff.
Yeah. See if she
knows anything.
Yes, sir.
So, did you work with him long?
No, we never even met.
Oh, really? It's such
a small crew here.
You think I'm lying?
I'm just trying to
figure out what happened.
I think it's pretty clear.
Didn't you hear what he said?
Yeah, that there were others.
What do you think
he meant by that?
No idea.
But for what it's
worth, I believe him.
This place is like
a city from before.
You remember.
Yeah, I do.
But you're doing this.
So, you don't know
how he got in?
Nope.
Great.
I wasn't expecting you.
Well, it's nice to see you, too.
Come in.
Thanks.
Oh!
Vintage?
Yes. I am a lady
of high caliber.
The highest.
Wasn't that something today?
Oh.
They really know how to throw a
party around here, don't they?
Kids had a blast.
Yeah.
He would've loved it.
I know that this was too
painful before, but...
This belongs to you.
You should keep it. No, no, no.
I want you to have it.
This place can be a fresh start.
If you want it to be.
How are you? Really?
Just great.
Still finding reasons to smile.
Well, then...
To fresh starts.
Mm.
It's not bad. It's
not bad at all.
You always took the
big glass. Mm-hmm.
DAY 33 IN THE COMMONWEALTH
You look awesome.
Thanks.
And you look official.
Yeah? You think so?
Hm.
I don't feel official.
Hey, I got you something.
Yes!
Clear!
Please open the door.
She's not there.
You think she was kidnapped by
the government or something?
Her only hope is for me
to expose them myself.
Governor Milton runs the city.
But I know how it runs.
You want to make a true
believer out of me?
I want you to be a part of it.
Something happened.
And they clearly have a reason
for suppressing the truth.
Come on, man, that's enough.
Hey, man. No problem, man.
In the teaser of this episode
we wanted this feel of,
like, it's a little surreal
for our people to... to
be at the Commonwealth,
for Daryl, he does not feel
at ease at a place like this,
because it just feels so fake,
and so I think the idea of
this, like, haunted
mansion where, you know,
the maze that they're
going through...
is like, wow, we've
just made zombies
kind of almost like a joke,
but it tells you that the
place is, like, really safe,
that they're not even,
like, afraid to have zombies
as part of an entertainment now.
And we wanted to show, like,
when they go out into this
festival, it's as much like
the old world during a holiday
as, like, they've ever had.
They treat things very,
very differently here,
and it is even more
unsettling than Alexandria was
for our people when
they first came in.
So, uh, what do you think?
Takes a minute to get used
to all this, you know?
Maybe we don't have to do
anything to make it work.
Nah, there's always somethin'
you gotta do to make it work.
The idea of two
people and one knife
came out of the writer's
room, 'cause we were tryin' to
come up with a challenge that
shows true partnership...
You have to be in sync.
And I think Rosita and her
partner actually pretty
seamlessly figure out like,
let's talk to each other.
- I got it!
- Let's take turns with
the knife, like, one
person's gonna cover
while the other person's
got the weapon, like,
we're gonna move
sort of as a unit.
They basically pass the test.
Green, Espinosa, nicely done.
Daryl is very, very good at
working with his friends,
but his partner is a little
bit weaker than he is, like,
terms of, like, skill set.
And so I think, like, Daryl
wasn't expecting that,
so when he's like, "You take
the knife, I'm just gonna, like,
do my thing here," he's used to
working with people that you can
give the knife and that's an
act of generosity, you know?
And, like, they're gonna do
their thing, and he's gonna do
his thing, and that's
gonna work out great.
Dixon!
When Mercer comes in and
he shoots the walker,
Daryl, like, honestly is very
surprised, 'cause he's kinda
like, "I was literally right
there," like, "I wasn't gonna
let that guy die."
But in Mercer's eyes, he's like,
"You have failed the
spirit of this exercise."
What I see is a guy that
doesn't know how to work with
his partner and he just goes
lone wolf and does his own thing
and doesn't communicate, so
I don't think either of them
are really wrong, but they
don't see eye to eye yet.
You're used to handling things
on your own, I get that.
But that's not how
it works around here.
Sometimes we gotta set
each other up to win.
This is the first time,
at the masquerade ball,
where you very clearly see that
only a certain
segment of society
is welcome to this event.
The celebration at the beginning
of the day was for everybody,
and now this is the special
celebration for the people
who are privileged
enough to be invited.
There's something odd for
our people like Magna,
who's working at the
party, to go like,
"Wow, all that old stuff that
we thought we left behind,
that we thought
didn't matter anymore,
actually has always
mattered here,"
and it's jarring for Magna,
who we had previously, like,
established, like, when we
introduced her, she said that
she used to be a
waitress, and it's like,
here she is, serving
food, and I think, like,
she never thought
that she would be
knocked back down to that again.
But I think for Princess,
who wants to be
amongst people again,
she's right there, like,
you know, she's right there
to, like, see everybody
kinda come in.
I think Lance really
wants to be loved.
He feels like, "Well, I'm really
pulling the strings
of this place,"
like, "this is my doing," right?
And I think, like, he really
wants the recognition!
But we actually talked about
the fact that we think that,
in this community,
somebody like Mercer,
who is this super soldier,
and, like, the bright suit
and all of that, he is kind of
a celebrity in the Commonwealth,
and I think for Mercer,
like, truly, truly, truly,
that is an uncomfortable
place to be,
'cause I think he is somebody
who always imagined that he'd
just be a public servant,
but for the Commonwealth,
optics are important to them
and important to Pamela,
and so he's accepted that that's
part of the way his job goes.
And first place goes to...
Dressed as our
very own Mercer...
Celeste!
But for Hornsby it's
like, right, the...
He's the popular one.
Right, okay.
All: Mercer! Mercer! Mercer!
As we were talking about, um,
this character Tyler Davis,
who we met in the
episode "Splinter"
in the season 10 extension,
we were like, "Well, what's
his experience, like,
after 'Splinter'
happened," and, you know,
he's a very complex
character, because, like,
I don't feel particularly sorry
for him, like, all the time,
'cause I'm like, man, he did
take this person hostage,
he clearly doesn't have
the coping skills, right?
He is an imperfect
messenger, and I think
that's what makes it
easy to discount him.
This is what you care about.
Fancy parties and paintings.
That's one of the things that
we'll start to see that Connie,
for example, is keying in on,
'cause she's got journalist
instincts, you know?
And I think in any society
there's always an underbelly,
there's always, like, people
who are gonna be pushing at...
Against it, for
better or for worse.
You think getting rid
of me solves anything?
There are thousands
more like me.
Resist the Commonwealth!
Visibility for workers!
Equality for all!
But how much of the truth is he
telling... are there thousands
of people that are part of this?
Is this, like, something that
he is imagining is gonna happen?
Like, we wanted to leave
that question hanging.
Are there thousands more?
No.
Make sure.
When Rosita comes into
that little secret room,
then she's kinda seeing the
things that he's been painting,
I think there's a part
of her that's like,
"Huh, maybe there's more
to this than I thought."
I think just a lot of things
are running through her head
at that moment, and it's
something for the audience
to watch, and you can just
see, like, so many different
thoughts, like, flitting across
her eyes, like, Christian,
she does such a great job in
that scene of seeing things
without saying things,
'cause I think, really,
this character feels like
she's at, like, this really odd
crossroads that she never
thought she'd find herself at.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/9mrp6
Help other users to choose the best subtitles