I said break it up. There's
enough food for everyone.
- One week.
- We just took in
two new communities.
We have no crops, no back stock.
I know one more
place... Meridian.
The place I lived before this.
Run!
Aah!
Go! Go!
Run!
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
Dog!
Gah!
No! No!
Let him go.
I said let him go.
I never thought
I'd see you again.
Yeah, I thought the same.
What're you doing out here?
You alone?
You see anybody with me?
I saw you out on the
road with the others.
Who are they?
You one of them?
Crossed a small
group on the road.
No. I ain't one of them.
I travel light, like always.
We're gonna go. Come on, boy.
Come on.
Well, that's funny.
What's funny?
I always thought he
liked you better.
Look, I don't know
who you're fighting,
but I am not part of it.
We're going. Come on!
Improved By M_I_S
www.Opensubtitles.org
Let's see if you're right.
I came back for you.
I looked everywhere for you.
I'm sorry you ended
up with these people.
These people are my family.
They never stopped
looking for me.
When they found me, I came home.
How about your family, Daryl?
The ones you told me about?
That who was out on the road?
My family picked the wrong
fight with the wrong people
a long time ago.
It's like I told you, I'm alone.
You're filthy.
Up.
Again!
The others.
Are they still out there?
Hmm?
Are they close?
I don't know.
Who's the leader?
Is it the woman?
I ain't one of them.
Bullshit.
Enough.
Shaw?
I said stop.
I'll handle him.
He'll crack. I just
need a little more time.
I've given you
enough time already.
I said up!
I need you to cooperate.
I told you everything.
You told us nothing.
Talk.
The one we answer
to won't be so nice.
I traded with them.
They gave me some food.
I hauled some gear.
I knew them less than a week.
Unh-unh.
Go ahead, kill me if you want.
I got nothing else to say.
Should've
never brought him back.
I know what I'm doing.
Yeah, you keep saying that.
Daryl?
Is that you?
The others? Are they okay?
I don't know where
your friends are.
I don't care, neither.
But I... But nothing.
Just 'cause we
shared a bag of grain
does not make me give
a shit about you.
Understand?
Whatever beef you have
with these people,
I want no part of it.
You hear me?
You need to shut up
and leave me alone.
Got it?
I got it, yeah.
I was right about you.
Shoulda let you starve.
Asshole.
I ain't telling you
bastards a thing.
Get up. Get up!
Let me go!
Just as stubborn as ever.
Is that what you think this is?
Hmm?
Me being stubborn?
Fine.
Hard-headed.
You need to tell me the truth.
I've never lied to you.
Never, Leah.
I'm not gonna start now.
Let's try this again.
What do you know
about those people?
I don't know shit.
I'd help you if I could.
You know I would.
Just give me Dog, let me go,
you'll never see me again.
Is that what you want?
What is it?
Found Bossie.
And Turner?
I tried. I
couldn't save him.
I tried. Pope: It's okay, son.
You did the right thing.
You brought him home.
Lord, we release
our brother Turner to you.
Please, hold him close.
In your name, oh Lord, amen.
Amen.
God is here.
He's angry.
I'm angry.
Do you feel that?
Hmm?
Go make them feel our wrath.
What happened?
One of my brothers is dead.
Michael Turner was his name.
We fought all over
the world together.
Pope brought him in
after our last tour,
when he started his company.
I thought you were soldiers.
We were.
Then we went private.
You didn't tell me
you were a merc.
Mm, does it matter?
I mean, it's the same damn job.
Except we could
actually pay our bills.
Michael was like me, you know?
He didn't have a family.
He was the little
brother I never had.
You know, the little
brother I always wanted.
And he's dead.
You know, we lost
a lot of people
here, and it's been hard.
Not like this.
This is the first time
I've lost someone close
to me in a long time.
Well
except maybe for you.
You didn't lose me.
I came back and you were gone.
You left me.
I asked you what you wanted.
You left.
I got scared.
Of what?
Letting go.
It doesn't matter. It
wouldn't have worked anyway.
Couldn't have been happy.
Not in a world like this.
Is that you talking
or your family?
Like you've never done things?
Killed people.
I know the things you've done.
You have no right to
judge, not at all.
This is me, Daryl.
The good and the bad.
All of it. It always has been.
I don't believe you.
Well, I can't help with that.
But I can help
you save yourself.
Because despite everything,
I still care about you,
and I don't want anything
bad to happen to you.
So, you need to
tell me something.
Anything.
'Cause if you can't, I
can't control my commander
or what he will do next.
He's angry about Turner,
and he wants someone to pay.
There's a woman.
She's the leader.
They were speaking in code
'cause I was an outsider.
There was a tall, skinny guy.
Never shuts up.
And a priest who
carries a shotgun.
That's their leadership?
Yeah. But they have the numbers.
And one of their
soldiers slipped up,
and he was gonna go meet
three dozen of their fighters.
That's way more than the
15 you got here.
Well, you've been doing
your work down here, huh?
I'm gonna get you out of here
so you can be more comfortable.
When do I meet him?
This Pope?
Soon.
Well, you were right.
He was hard to break.
He told me there are a lot
more out there than we thought.
More than twice the
force we have in here.
I think he'll be good here.
And we need the manpower,
with Turner gone
and Nicholls and
Montanio still missing.
Say something.
You know I hate it
when you do this.
Do what?
Freeze me out.
Not everything is
about you, Leah.
I never said it was.
Oh, no?
'Cause here we are.
Losing a day of
tracking our enemy
'cause you... you had to
go on a fishing expedition
with an old boyfriend.
So, go on, then.
Tell me.
You find what
you're looking for?
I told you he would be
useful, and I was right.
He's a lot like us.
Pain doesn't scare him,
death doesn't scare him.
Carver saw it.
Come on, you see it.
I just see a guy who wants
to get in your pants.
Fine.
Who couldn't stop gazing
at somebody he loved.
I never said he loved me.
Oh.
You could've ended
him out there today,
and you didn't.
Why?
At one point, he meant
something to me, yeah.
I've been open about that.
But it ended the
day you found me
and I chose this family,
and I have never once
regretted that decision,
and I don't want you to, either.
Do you?
I believe in you.
More than the others.
I know.
You think we can trust him?
Yeah.
Good.
Now, let me see for myself.
You got something to say?
Come on,man.
Don't be shy.You're about to meet the man.
Yeah, save that coy shit
for your girlfriend.
Aww, Shaw ain't
nobody's girlfriend.
I'm betting she wears the
pants with homeboy here.
Isn't that right?
You don't know shit
about shit, Carver.
Knock it off.
I guess I'll just show
my dumb ass out, then.
Pope is on his way.
Anything you wanna tell me about
this guy before I meet him?
Just follow my lead.
Hey!
Aah!
Here! Take it! Take it!
Here! Here!
Come on.
Forged by fire.
Ordained by God.
Welcome him!
Fortitudo Saludis!
You believe in God?
No. No, I don't.
Not anymore.
Guess I just believe in me now.
Hmm.
Well, that's a mistake.
Why's that?'Cause
you're not Him.
I passed your little
test, didn't I?
Whatever you want to call it.
Oh, and you think
that's the end of it?
What else
do you want from me?
I want...
I want you to understand.
Sit down.
We all met in the
Valley of Death.
That's what we call it, anyway.
Hills of Afghanistan.
We fought for our country,
carried our fallen
brothers off the field.
Carried so many, we lost
count after a while.
Politicians.
They wrote the checks.
We weren't anything to them.
Just props.
Props for their next campaign.
See, they... They
talked about God.
They didn't know God.
They never saw His face.
It's not like we did.
We saw God everywhere.
He was in the blood and
the horror and death.
He was there,
telling
us where to go.
Didn't have much else to hold
on to in those days but Him.
And each other.
You smoke?
That war...
damn near ruined
all of us for good.
Came home and my guys
had permanent injuries.
They couldn't sleep.
They couldn't find real jobs.
So
people called us mercenaries.
We did all the ugly, dirty work
nobody else wanted to do.
Got paid for it, too.
Handsomely.
The real dirty work
started after the Fall.
Never been in a war like that.
Never seen that kind of chaos,
and I had seen everything.
But this...
Oh, the things we did.
All that death, day
after day after day...
After a while, I started
to feel like you.
Wondering... Wondering
where God was.
Until He showed His face again.
See, politicians... they had
one last war to get behind.
This time, coming for us.
The bombs came thick and fast.
It did not stop.
We lost some of our own,
had to run through
the fire to save them.
Found this little church
at the edge of town,
and we holed up there
as everything...
And I mean everything...
Burned around us.
When the fires
finally died down,
I looked at my people...
I could not believe it.
Not a trace of blood.
No burn marks.
Not even a scratch.
And that's when I knew.
We were the Chosen Ones.
These men...
These men upon whose bodies
the fire had no power.
God chose you tonight.
I mean, you... You
came out of that fire
alive and whole.
And look at you now,
sitting right here.
Are you hurt?
Hmm?
Any burns?
A scratch?
I've been through worse before.
Are. You. Hungry?
You were right.
About this one.
Of course I was.
Give him some, Bossie.
Don't be greedy.
He's family now.
You know what he did, don't you?
He walked 10 miles with his
dead brother on his back.
10 miles.
The strength that took...
You have any idea
how grateful we are?
Turner will have
a proper burial.
Just did what any one
of us would've done.
Mm.
These still hurt?
Hmm?
You need anything?
I just have one question.
S-Sure.
Something's been bothering me.
Your wounds
are on your back.
Pope, it's been a rough day.
Just getting clarity, Shaw.
Where were you when
Turner was being attacked?
I-I was right there,
just like I told you.
Uh-huh.
Facing the enemy?
Yeah.
Leah: He's been through enough.
Human nature is to run
when you are scared.
You know what
that's like, right?
It takes divine strength...
to face your fear head-on
Risk everything
for someone else.
We all saw what you did.
Getting Shaw out
of the fire first,
and you felt it, huh?
How far he would go
just to keep you safe.
Today, God baptized
you in that fire.
Made you one of us.
You see
there's one thing I
forgot to tell you.
Never turn your back
on your brother.
God doesn't only use
fire as His baptism.
It's also His wrath.
Aah!
We are the Chosen Ones!
We run into the battle.
We run into the fire.
Always.
We can't stay.
We need to help our friends.
I want to help.
Are you sure?
This is our home.
We got to fight to save it.
The only way this works
is if we trust each other.
When we see the
Reapers, they're in these
crazy, scary masks.
Our inspiration for these
was sort of a mish-mash
of different influences.
Military can sometimes
have tactical masks.
And sometimes they do
have things like skulls
or interesting designs on them.
And then we were also just
looking at different kinds
of post-apocalyptic concept
art, video games, to just things
that are written about with
people in gas masks and stuff.
And, when we were thinking
about, like, what is the look
of this crew, they're
almost like these faceless
people that come in
like the Grim Reaper.
Because of Dog being
separated from Daryl,
he chases Dog and finds
the dog with this Reaper.
And it turns out
the Reaper is Leah.
We had always planned
for that to be the story.
This is not a story
we came up with
after that first episode
with Daryl and Leah aired.
And, also, a lot
of time has passed.
So, there's obviously a
story that has happened
in the interim and
when they kinda
crash into each other,
there's a whole lot
that's going on
through Daryl's head.
But the first thing is, "I
gotta lie to get out of it."
Like, whatever I have to say
to do to get out of this,
like, I'm gonna leverage
that little bit of trust
that she has in me,
to help my people.
Because as soon as he sees
her on the other side of this,
he's like, "Okay, maybe
I was wrong about her",
but I'm not really gonna hang
around to try to figure it out.
Look, I don't know
who you're fightin'
but I am not part of it.
The way that we always
thought about this group
is that they probably have a
series of things that they do
when they come across what would
be enemy combatants to them.
They were all, basically
like, military contractors
or what some would
call mercenaries.
And they were doing these things
at a time when there was a lot
of torture that was,
sort of, like, sanctioned
in the military, so
they've all learned
those techniques and
became very familiar
with them before the world fell.
And so for The Reapers,
this is just part of
what they have to do.
And I think Leah is a character
that she can't be seen
to be showing any
softness towards anybody.
She is part of this group and
she answers to somebody else.
So, she may be the
one, at least in name,
in charge of the situation,
but I think that question
sits out there, like,
is she really in charge
of this situation or
has she been asked to
carry out orders and she
feels that she needs to?
She doesn't love what
she's seeing, you know,
and she puts a stop
to it or a pause to it
when it feels like it's
going too far or too long.
So there's just a lot
of complicated emotions
that are running
through the whole thing.
The one we answer
to won't be so nice.
We got really fortunate
in casting Ritchie Coster
in this role as Pope.
He just had a take
on it right away.
When we were developing
this character,
one of the things that we
talked about is just this idea
of being chosen
and what that can,
in the most extreme
versions, cause people to do.
For Pope, we just felt
that it'd be interesting to
kind of illustrate somebody who
probably was a
brilliant tactical mind,
was probably a really
great commander,
and yet, became kind of
disgruntled by the system
and felt left
behind in some ways.
And saw people that he
felt were left behind.
There was this story, this
thing that felt miraculous
happened, which is
actually not that uncommon.
Which is that, sometimes,
you're in a building
in a raging fire and the
fire jumps your building.
That's when I knew we
were the chosen ones.
God had spared them all
for something important
and that made him feel
like he needed to go
throughout this after time
and grab what they needed
on behalf of his people.
And, you know, in
many ways he has been
an effective leader
of his people
in that he has kept
them safe and alive,
but at what cost
to anybody else?
This idea of a trial by fire
just felt like this divine test.
We felt like that was just a
very dramatic way to illustrate
the type of danger that
they're all in but Leah, too.
For whatever it's worth,
there is a kind of
a turning point for Leah
in that moment as well.
Because it's one thing to
be inside the circle of love
and to feel like she's
one of his favorites
and he sees her as a daughter,
but what kind of father
sticks their daughter in a
room and sets it on fire?
With, like, no obvious
way to get out?
That is super, super intense.
And so, for both of
these characters,
they kinda come out of this
and Pope intends for them
to come out feeling like
changed people and they do
but maybe not in the way that
he's thinking is gonna happen.
In this scene where he puts
Bossy's head in the fire,
we wanted to kind of
show a few things.
One is that, you know, in
the apocalypse we've seen
our characters,
we've seen villains,
we've seen a lot of them do
some pretty intense things.
And, the question is,
who are the people
that are gonna stand up to that
and who is just gonna
try to live with it
and who is complicit in
it who is cheering it on?
Daryl's just kind of
coming into this situation
knowing very little about
them and he's still learning
what all of it means and
where they all stand.
And the big lesson
out of this is
nobody's gonna stand
up to Pope easily.
I think for some of
them it's a wake-up call
to realize, like, how intense
the situation has gotten.
I don't actually
think Pope has killed
a lot of his own
people in this way.
I think it's always been, like,
"It's us against the world."
And now that he's put
Leah in a burning room,
just threw one of these people
that she considers, like,
a brother in the fire,
the equation is shifting.
And I think there's
a sense of unease.
For Daryl, all of this is
intel that he's taking in
and he's realizing, like,
I've gotta tread very,
very carefully here.
He's in a dangerous situation.
We are the chosen ones!
We run into the battle.
We run into the fire!
Always.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today