Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Who are the real-world Illuminati ?
Find out @ saveanilluminati.com
CERULLO SHOEMAKERS
SUPERMARKET - KITCHEN WARES
Mamma!
MY BODY IS MINE
FROM NOW ON WE DECIDE
My brother?
I haven't seen him in two months.
I don't know where he is.
What do you want from me?
Mamma!
Don't ever let go of my hand,
is that clear?
EPISODE 5 - TERROR
You know when a man says:
"You're mine"?
Yeah!
You know when we reply:
"Yeah, I'm yours"?
Yeah!
We are both telling the absolute truth:
we are men's property.
When we dare to disobey their rules,
they beat us, they kill us!
The time has come to put an end to it.
Never again will we reply:
"Yes, I am yours."
Let's learn to be completely
and utterly our own.
Our bodies are ours, our heads are ours!
You are yours, shout it out!
I am mine!
I have the power!
I am mine and I have the power!
To the male comrades
who are here today,
I want to say, very politely...
Go away!
The square is ours!
Out! The square is ours!
Go away!
WOMEN'S LIBERATION MOVEMENT
- Stop, it's unacceptable!
- We're here to help you.
Tremble in fear, the witches are here!
Don't run away again!
Don't you run away again.
Sit down for a moment.
Hold Elsa.
Let's go.
You don't take two small children
to a demonstration!
Mariarosa was supposed to come too.
I wanted her to see Dede and Elsa
but she missed her train.
Forget about my sister!
She's the last person you can count on.
Anyway, there were other kids.
Everyone takes their kids
to demonstrations.
If everyone does something stupid,
it's still stupid.
You were even sick.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is.
It's very true.
Anyway, that's enough,
I'll go where I want
and take my daughters where I want.
I'm not your third daughter and
you're neither my father nor my boss.
But I am Dede and Elsa's father!
You hear me?
And I'm also your husband.
I worry because I care about you.
You had so many interests once.
You're not writing novels,
or for the papers, nothing.
You read,
but it's only superficial reading.
You risk losing yourself.
WE SPIT ON HEGEL - THE CLITORAL
WOMAN AND THE VAGINAL WOMAN
You don't care about
my reading and my work.
You just want me to be
an affectionate mother and a wife.
You're already boring
and now you want to teach me
what to read, what to risk.
You get it.
Hello?
Yes, she's here.
It's for you!
Go and check on the pasta.
I'm going.
- Hello?
- Lenù, it's Carmela.
- Carmela, how are you?
- Not good, Lenù.
That's why I called. They killed Gino.
How did it happen?
They shot him at the pharmacy.
The police came to the gas pump.
They were following leads,
they think Pasquale's involved.
But I haven't seen him in months.
- Has he come to see you?
- No.
Why?
A while back he asked
for your phone number and address.
If you know anything, tell me.
I don't know anything, I swear.
You think I wouldn't tell you?
In the neighborhood it's war,
comrades gotta watch their backs.
The fascists even
threatened me and my husband.
They say that Pasquale set fire
to the MSI branch office
and the Solaras' supermarket.
And what do you think?
I'm scared.
Pasquale is at the top
of the fascists' list.
I'm scared they'll kill him.
- Have you asked the police for help?
- No.
They're more fascist than the fascists.
If you hear anything, please call me.
Sure.
Say hello to your husband.
And give the girls a kiss from me.
Take care.
Hello?
It's me.
Lenù, what's up?
Carmela called me.
- She told me they killed Gino.
- I heard.
You know they pinned it on Pasquale?
Of course they took it out on Pasquale.
I'm sure it wasn't him,
but even if it was, I'm on his side.
What?
The cops should take it out
on the dead guy,
he only ever did bad things.
Not on a communist worker.
Lila, Carmela's beside herself.
She said the fascists
want to see Pasquale dead,
they blame him for torching
the Solaras' supermarket.
Carmela's always beside herself.
But why did she call you?
Pasquale needed my advice
and asked for my number.
Anyway, let's change the subject.
I would have called you.
I wanted to ask you...
Can I leave Gennaro with you
until school starts?
Why?
I have to work.
I have to take the girls to the beach.
Can't you take him too?
I'm going to Viareggio.
I hardly know the boy,
only if you come too.
You promised you'd look after him.
If you were ill.
Who says I'm not ill?
Are you ill?
No.
Why not leave him
with Stefano or your mother?
Will you do me this favor or not?
All right.
Bring him to me.
Enzo will bring him.
Thank you, take care.
Are you coming to eat?
The Brescia bombing...
- Pietro!
- What is it?
Eight people have been killed
and over a hundred wounded.
Here is a dramatic recording
of the moment of the attack
and the ensuing moments
in Piazza della Loggia.
Stay calm!
Do not leave the square!
The police are cordoning off the square.
Workers!
Do not leave the square!
The police!
Good morning.
Does Elena Greco live here?
Yes.
Can you tell her Pasquale
and Nadia are here?
Elena!
Pasquale and Nadia are here.
Come in.
Hi.
I nearly didn't recognize you.
Hi, Nadia.
What are you doing here?
Traveling.
Come in.
- Nice to meet you, I'm Pietro.
- Sorry, I didn't introduce you.
This is Pietro.
- Hi, Pietro.
- Hi.
Have you come for the demonstration?
Demonstrations are just a waste of time.
Have you come from Naples?
No, we were in the area.
Are you going back?
No.
So tell me, how are you?
Good. We're...
Yes.
Dede, come here.
These are two friends of mine.
She's Nadia and he's Pasquale.
Pasquale and I have been friends
since we were little.
- Weren't there two?
- One's sleeping upstairs.
Upstairs...
- In a terrorist's pocket...
- Leave it!
..was found a map of the locations...
Turn it down.
I haven't seen you for ages
and we're going to watch TV?
The roadblocks have been reinforced.
Concerning the traffic flow
for the summer exodus,
the authorities anticipate
traffic delays exiting the cities
on all major highways
and ask citizens...
Turn it off.
We were about to eat.
Would you like to eat with us?
Yes?
- Shall I put on the pasta?
- Yes, please.
Dede, go and wash your hands.
I'll go and help Elena.
Dede!
Come here.
What kind of name is Dede?
Cat got your tongue?
Well?
Will you tell me?
Are you scared of me?
Is it my beard?
Don't be scared, I'm good.
And if anyone tells you I'm bad,
you gotta say: "No, I met him.
He's good."
What did you say to her?
I convinced her to wash her hands.
Is there any wine?
I'll go get it.
Is the kitchen here?
Yes.
Nadia, do you want something to eat?
No, I don't feel like it.
Sure?
Sit down.
There was no wine, I got a beer.
- Don't you drink?
- We never drink at lunch.
Does she understand Neapolitan?
I couldn't get her
to tell me why you call her Dede.
I don't know if she understands it,
but she doesn't speak it.
Don't you mind?
No.
So why don't you
come to Naples anymore?
You don't see anyone anymore,
not even your friend.
I'll come.
Lila and I speak a lot,
we spend a fortune on phone calls.
Do you ever see her?
Occasionally.
How's Armando?
We don't speak anymore.
All I know is
his wife left with the kid.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
She was right to do it.
This is a beautiful house.
It's like a castle.
Who lives here?
It's a quiet house.
It's a quiet area for posh people, right?
Everyone who lives here works.
And what do they do?
Lawyers, architects?
Dentists?
Aristocrats?
- Is this house yours?
- No, we're renting.
Renting.
Anyway it's two stories.
I'm taking a rest now...
I've worked.
Give me your hand.
Feel how rough my hands are, professor.
If these hands weren't like this,
not even a chair could exist.
A car, a building.
Not even you.
If we workers suddenly stopped working,
everything would stop.
The sky would fall in,
the earth would leap into the sky,
the plants would take over the cities.
The Arno would flood your houses again
and only those who've
always worked could survive.
Whereas you,
with all your books,
the dogs would eat you.
That's so old!
I've heard you say
these things a thousand times.
Here's the pasta.
Give it to me.
For you.
It's really good.
Thank you.
Bon appétit.
Thanks.
- What's wrong?
- I have to go to the bathroom.
Let's go.
We're going to the bathroom.
She really loves you.
She's little.
When she grows up
she won't love you anymore.
No, I hope she will
when she's grown up, too.
Who are they?
Friends of Mamma's.
My mother spoke about you all the time.
You were her student, but you seemed
more like a daughter than me.
I hated you.
Also because you stole Nino from me.
He didn't leave you for me.
Who cares,
I don't even remember
what he looks like.
When I was a girl
I wanted to be like you.
Why?
You think it's nice
being born with everything set out?
Well, you don't have to work as hard.
You're wrong.
It seems like it's all been done for you
and you don't have
a good reason to work.
You feel guilty for what you are,
that you don't deserve it.
Better than feeling guilty
because you failed.
Is that what Lila says?
No.
I prefer her to you.
You're two pieces of shit
and will always be.
But you act friendly,
Lila doesn't.
- Let's go take a shower.
- I don't want to.
You don't want to?
Let's go.
Is it this way?
Now you'll explain who those two are.
- What do they want?
- I don't know.
You don't know?
You don't know...
Even though Nadia
had mortally offended me,
I felt Pasquale was fond of me
but he wasn't able to express it.
In fact, he was odious.
The fear Pietro might snap
and they'd fight, muzzled me.
So, as everything precipitated,
Pietro and I remained silent.
Remember this song?
Professor, you need to face facts.
You're all dead and you don't know it.
Everything about you is dead.
The way you live, how you speak.
Your conviction that you're intelligent,
democratic and on the left.
But how can I explain this
to someone who's dead?
Pity, it's cold.
Folks, we'll get out of your hair.
Take care, Signora Airota.
I wanted a chat with Lenù,
but maybe Lenù wasn't at home.
Or time's passed and people change.
And we had nothing to say
to each other anymore.
See you.
Bye, Dede.
Professor...
I never want those two
in my house again.
Someone who talks like that
about intellectual work
is a fascist, even if he doesn't know it.
She's a type I know all too well.
There's nothing in her head.
What are you saying?
You're talking about people
and things you don't know.
Everything you are
you owe to your parents.
It's easy, you just say Airota
and all the doors open to you.
You need to shut up.
I wasn't hurt by that slap,
I'd already had so many.
I wasn't that different
from the neighborhood women,
but Pietro had never slapped anyone
or been slapped.
Meanwhile, the hot weather arrived,
and the news of terrorist acts
and the alarm that spread throughout
the country really affected me.
Is this any time to go away?
Yes.
What changes?
With everything that's going on,
it's like we're at war.
And we go to Viareggio?
If we stay in Florence, what can we do?
Here they are, they've arrived.
Come, Dede.
Gennarino, now remember
what Mamma said.
What is this, the woods?
- Hi!
- Lenù!
- How are you?
- Well, you?
Everything's fine.
- Hi!
- You're not going to greet Aunty Lenù?
Good morning.
He wants to shake hands!
It's normal, he doesn't remember.
Come in.
- Is all this stuff yours?
- No, we're only renting an apartment.
Here we are!
- Hi!
- I'm Pietro, it's a pleasure.
Enzo, the pleasure's mine.
- The trip?
- Fine, there wasn't much traffic.
Gennarino! My pleasure.
This is Dede.
Let's go.
- I'll stay for a bit then set off again.
- No, stay overnight.
We've prepared the beds and dinner,
go back tomorrow.
I don't want to put you out.
Remember what Mamma said?
Signora Elena, this is for Dede
and this is for Elsa.
Thank you!
Here.
Actually, my name's Adele
like my grandma.
That's my sister Elsa,
like Elsa Morante.
We gather these files,
information, in the system.
And then the system manages
the accounts, payroll, suppliers' orders.
- How does the system work?
- With perforated cards.
Cards that we make holes in.
Lila and I prepare the system
to perform complex operations.
- And if it makes a mistake?
- What do you mean?
The computer.
No way, it doesn't make mistakes.
If it goes wrong,
then Lila and I have made a mistake.
When machines replace men,
many jobs will be lost.
At Fiat, robots already do the welding.
Lila says it will be a good thing,
for her humiliating jobs
that frazzle you must disappear.
If Lila is so clever,
why is she your helper?
What can I say?
We're still in a world of male bosses.
Papa, can you bring me some water?
Dede's woken up.
She's calling you, go.
We're in a world of male bosses...
- I'm off.
- Bye, Pietro
- Good night, thank you.
- Good night.
I like the professor.
Tonight he spoke more than usual,
he must like you.
- Sit down.
- Thanks.
Tell me the truth.
Why was Lila in a rush
to send me Gennaro?
- What's going on?
- Lenù, nothing's going on.
We work a lot and school's over,
he has nothing to do.
Lila thought he'd be better off with you.
- If it's a problem, I'll take him back.
- No.
I heard from Carmela,
she told me about Gino.
She's very worried about Pasquale.
She says he's in serious trouble
and the fascists want to kill him.
The fascists want to kill everyone
who doesn't think like them,
including me.
Pasquale came by.
He was strange, he didn't seem himself.
I didn't really understand
what he wanted.
He didn't tell me where he'd been,
where he was going.
Do you know anything?
You think we speak? He never calls me.
As I said, all we think about is work.
We don't see anyone
and it suits us just fine.
We mind our own business,
we don't bother about others.
Lila has other things on her mind.
What things?
She didn't tell you about Michele Solara?
Does she have problems
with the Solaras?
No, the opposite.
He wants to take the system
and use it for all his businesses
and he wants Lila
as the head of technology.
- She didn't tell you?
- No.
She doesn't want to disturb you,
you have your own life.
If she says yes this time,
it would be a huge leap for her
and a lucky break for both of us.
Together we'd make 750,000 a month.
And Lila?
She has to give her answer
in September.
What's she going to do?
Have you ever known in advance
what's in her head?
No.
What do you think she should do?
I think what she thinks.
Even when you don't agree?
Even then.
I don't know.
Lila working with the Solaras?
What's behind it?
Let's turn in, I'm tired.
Enzù, tell me the truth.
That is the truth.
Tell me the truth.
What Enzo told me
thrust me back into that world
I thought was moving away
and yet it was still there.
Gennarino, there's hot cornetti ,
I'll give you one.
- He already had breakfast.
- For a snack.
- Come on, let's go.
- I want the cornetto.
See? He wants one.
Go get it.
Tell them I said it's okay.
You want a coffee?
You said no when I offered you
200,000 lire a month
to develop new ideas for me.
You said no to doing the books
for the new Vomero store.
I found you a job as secretary
to an important politician.
But you know I'm stubborn,
I won't give up.
You know where I work?
At IBM. You know what it is?
They hired Enzo too.
They took us because we studied,
because we're smart.
How much do you earn?
Not much, but it's clean money.
- Thank you, Michele.
- Let's go.
I'm stubborn, you know it.
- I'll wait for you for eternity.
- So, wait!
- Just call and I'll run.
- Thanks again!
One day something odd happened.
Gennarino disappeared,
he was nowhere to be found.
Kids!
- Have you seen Gennarino?
- No, I'm sorry.
We haven't seen him.
Marinella!
Have you seen Gennarino? My boy!
Have you seen Gennarino?
Gennaro!
Where the fuck were you?
Where were you?
I've been here all the time.
That's enough now, tell me.
Tell me the truth.
You won't solve anything like this.
I said tell me. What happened?
I wanted to be by myself.
What happened?
That's not true!
Lila, will you calm down?
I'll go to that asshole
and show him what for!
- Where are you going?
- Let go of me!
Calm down!
Lila!
- I'll kill him!
- Calm down!
You're not going.
If you stay here nice and calm, I'll go.
Stay here.
Lila feared it was Michele's way
of getting to her.
She felt that Gennarino kept quiet
as he'd bonded with Michele Solara.
Gennarino trusted him
more than his mother.
Michele, was it you?
You crazy?
Dunno what you're talking about.
Gennarino's like my son,
I'll kill anyone who touches him.
Rather...
Why don't you let Lila work with me?
She's very intelligent.
Why don't you come, too?
I know you work for IBM.
I'm opening a data processing company.
Think about it.
I need someone like you.
After all, things were good
between Enzo and Lila,
even though she was always on the go
and he couldn't swallow the fact
Lila was still married to Stefano.
Now there's divorce, it doesn't
make sense to stay married to him.
I couldn't care less.
Maybe Stefano does.
He wouldn't even know there's divorce.
I don't want to waste time.
What do I care if I stay married to him?
I'm with you,
I sleep with you.
That's the fact of the matter.
But maybe we could get married.
But aren't we already fine like this?
If we get fed up,
each can go their own way.
What are you doing here at this hour?
I was looking for the bathroom.
It's over there.
Thank you, good night.
Night.
Good morning, Lenù.
Good morning.
I made coffee.
Thank you.
Times change.
We want to live peacefully too,
without worrying about
making ends meet.
And if he wants to take her from you?
I'll kill him.
But he doesn't want that.
He has a mistress
and everyone knows who she is.
Who is she?
Marisa.
He got her pregnant again.
Marisa Sarratore?
Alfonso's wife.
And Alfonso?
Alfonso couldn't care less.
They say he's a faggot.
Anyway, thank you,
a vacation will do Gennarino good.
The doctor said the sea air
is good for tonsils.
I better go, or I'll get back too late.
- Hello?
- Lila.
- What is it at this hour?
- Why did you send Gennarino here?
Are you worried about him?
- You didn't tell me he disappeared.
- Why would I?
In your life
the Solaras matter less than zero.
You want to be nice? Take Gennarino
to get some sun, to swim.
- I gotta go.
- No, explain it to me.
That's enough, take care.
Fuck you!
The more I tried
to draw her into the open,
the more she took refuge
in the shadows,
like a full moon
when it crouches behind the woods
and the branches scribble on its face.
Whereas I had become a vacationer,
with a house at the beach
and three children,
a front-row umbrella,
menthol cigarettes
and the sun making me blonder.
Elena!
Wasn't it called Soccavo,
the factory where Lila worked?
Yes, why?
Come here a minute.
Dede!
Get out of the water!
There's an article by Nino Sarratore
that says they killed the owner.
GANG WAR RAGES ON
Is it him?
I have to make a call.
Go on.
You're not as fast!
Mamma, can we go to the tree?
Yes, but don't go too far,
I need to see you.
Hello?
- It's me.
- Lenù.
Everything okay with Gennarino?
Yes, everything's fine.
Did you see they killed Bruno Soccavo?
I didn't know about it.
- Haven't you read the papers?
- No.
They burst into the factory and shot him.
What horrible news.
Call someone,
find out what happened.
And see if there's someone
to send a telegram to.
What telegram?
I'm out of touch
with the factory people.
Nino wrote
that it was a political murder.
Political how?
It woulda been for other stuff, you get
killed here for a thousand reasons.
Cheating, misdeeds,
one glance too many.
Put Gennaro on, I'll say hello.
No, I'm at the café, he's playing.
- So, we'll speak later?
- Bye.
- Have you seen Dede and Gennaro?
- No.
Dede!
It's nothing bad, in the neighborhood
all the girls want to see it.
If you're curious,
you need to satisfy it.
Dede!
Come here!
Are you crazy?
I've been looking everywhere!
And you're older, too.
What were you doing?
We weren't doing anything.
Not doing anything...
that stuff isn't for kids, okay?
You're mean, Mamma.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-