Jack says just a few more weeks and
you will be free.
Stories about you come up
the canal.
Once you walked fine alone,
now you need a stick.
You stay clean for two weeks,
I'll write Linda another letter.
Have you recently suffered seizures?
It is Tuberculoma, I am
afraid it is inoperable.
MUSIC: Lawman
by Girl Band
Watch Movies, TV Series & Live Sports
www.admitme.app
Mr Shelby.
I only gave opium to your brother
because he give me big trouble.
He attacked my wife.
I would like a pot of green tea,
please.
It has taken me ten years
to build this business.
Your business will be safe,
if you do what I say.
How much opium do you have in
your cellar?
Five pounds.
Bring it to me.
Four minutes against the clock.
As member of Parliament...
..for this constituency...
..it is my duty to take
responsibility for the welfare
of my constituents. Mr Shelby,
the clock is still ticking.
The consumption of opium is very
prejudicial to health.
Women give it to their children
so they can leave
them untended while they work
in the factories.
Men lose their jobs when they
become addicted.
From now on, you will sell
only cigarettes, cake and tea.
If I hear that you are selling
opium again,
time will indeed run out very
quickly for you. Do you understand?
Yes, I understand, I will stop.
Mr Shelby, the clock
is still ticking.
Please tell...
..your suppliers and your
customers...
..that from now on...
...there will be no more opium...
..in Small Heath or in Bordesley.
Thank you for the tea.
BOMB EXPLODES
You can let them through now.
Yes, sir, Mr Shelby.
You tell the pub and cafe owners
in Montague Street...
..if there is any further trade
in powder,
there will be no more Montague
Street.
I will have it demolished
and replaced by apartments.
By order of Birmingham Urban
District Council.
Sorry I'm late, they closed Montague
Street.
There's a gas explosion or...
Right. Well, it would be nice if
just one thing
could happen in Birmingham that
wasn't our fault.
I have gathered you all here today
because there is news
and it is of interest to the whole
family.
First of all,
I would like to welcome Finn's new
wife Mary to the family.
Right. Well, I'm very glad I dragged
myself out of bed for this.
There is...
..one more item of business.
Johnny.
Tom.
Come on, come on, hurry up.
Everyone...
..this here is Erasmus.
Nobody calls me that.
They call him Duke.
20 years ago, at Appleby horse
fair...
..I met a girl.
We shared the shade of a hazel tree.
Nine months later this lad was born.
This is my son.
His mother died on the road.
Up until now I never tried
to find him.
But I am trying to look at life in a
different way.
A child is a precious thing.
So I am bringing him...
Into the fucking family with
a snap of his fingers.
No, I am bringing him into the fold.
He'll have to earn membership of
the family.
For the moment, welcome, son.
You have a seat.
Go on, sit down here.
There are some mistakes I've made...
..that I can never address...
..and some I can.
Some wounds I can try to heal.
And new wounds you can open up.
Anyway...
..that's the business of the day.
Is it too early for whisky?
There you go.
Shelby breakfast for you, son.
I don't drink.
And I'm not a Shelby, all right?
I'm a Duke.
Ooh, hoo, hoo, hoo.
You're a fucking Shelby, all right,
don't worry about that.
Mm, I think we will need Curly
and a strong rope to break this one
in, Tom.
Arthur, open up the shop,
put the kid here on the blackboard,
writing up the odds.
I can't write.
Put the kid on the blackboard,
wiping off the chalk.
Go on, son.
Come on then.
Lizzie, come on.
My father was the Duke of the Saxon
Shore.
My mother was a Romany Queen.
Who told you that, your mum?
I don't allow people to talk about
my mother.
Good for you.
So let's get this right then,
you can't read,
you can't fucking write,
there's nothing wrong with that.
What can you do, eh?
I can tell the time.
You can tell the time.
Here, he can tell the time.
Ain't that clever.
It's a lot more than you can
fucking do.
What did you just say to me?
What time is it, Mr Shelby?
That's what I can do.
You little bastard.
Here, keep it.
Stop you from being late in
the future.
Is there forgiveness in your heart
for Arthur Shelby?
No.
But maybe there will be forgiveness
from God.
And you will do God's work?
God is interested in you as
well, Tommy.
And God will be with you on your
journey every step of the way.
He may not need to take many steps.
Tell me this, Linda...
..is God interested in me...
..or in my money?
I believe you run a foundation
and that your foundation has many
missions across the world
but in these times of financial
crisis,
funding is hard to come by.
So perhaps your God's plan is
a practical one.
Perhaps he would like me to make
a donation
to your foundation
and in return, he would like you
to help my brother on his road
to redemption.
Now, I know that in a place of
worship such as this,
you would never ask how much.
So I will tell you plainly.
I will write your foundation
a cheque for £10,000...
Praise the Lord.
..if you agree to look kindly on
Arthur and to help him.
I need to look after everyone in
the family.
Do we have a deal?
Your money will be spent to do good
around the world.
And a mission will be named
after you.
But I am only agreeing to help
him...
..not sleep with him.
No.
Now, I imagine the negotiation for
that particular favour
would take a considerable amount of
time...
..and I have an appointment.
God bless.
Apologies for the initial
misunderstanding.
My brother dealt with it.
For the care you took.
Even though I succumbed
to temptation.
Part of the reason my brother is
back dealing with it,
is down to you, you spoke to him.
As a comrade.
The beating is still owed to you.
Do you still do that kind of work
yourself, Thomas Shelby, MP?
Mr Stagg, see, I can use men like
you.
I have friends that are in need
of guns.
Soon, there will be a shipment
of Thompson sub machine guns
coming here from Boston.
And I need you to unload
and store those weapons.
There will also be ammunition...
..like this.
You have a good look.
And I need you to take better care
of the guns and ammunition
than you did of the powder.
You understand?
Previously,
all of my import and export
went through Belfast docks.
Now we're dealing with Boston...
..I am considering shifting
my supply line to Liverpool.
You'll be a very rich man.
Don't you ever say thank you?
Thank you.
Is that why you do it, Mr Shelby?
Is that why you keep all this going?
To have people say thank you?
You could close all this down.
You could leave the sport behind.
You could live like
an ordinary mortal man.
On your gravestone -
"an ordinary mortal man".
But, instead,
you still go round collecting
"please" and "thank you"
and "sorry"
and "forgive me, Mr Shelby."
Is that what it's all for?
You want to know?
You want to know
why I've carried on...
..all these years?
It's so I can do this.
And then...
..do this.
Feel it?
I feel it.
Junk doesn't even come close.
Soon, Mr Stagg...
..when my last piece
of business is done...
..I will indeed...
..be an ordinary mortal man.
You have a good day.
Arthur,
we've got a problem with a referee.
He's not taking the money.
He's fucking religious
or something.
Jesus Christ.
With Tommy away, you're in charge
of gambling, Arthur,
what shall we do?
"And this they said to him,
"that they may have some charge
to bring against him."
Arthur,
this referee, he's threatening
to go to the police.
"Jesus...
"..bent down,
"and with one finger,
he wrote on the ground..."
Arthur, brother...
..people are laughing at you.
So I just phoned
our Holy referee - again.
He basically told me to fuck off.
Not even basically, actually,
he literally told to me
to fuck off.
Is that right?
So, do you know?
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Do you know what he wrote
on the ground? Hmm?
No. Do you know? No.
You don't know, do yer?
No, I don't. Billy, do you know
what he wrote on the ground?
I... Hmm?
Do you know what Jesus wrote
on the ground?
He bent down,
and with one finger,
he wrote on the fucking ground.
You know?
Do you know what he wrote?
Come on, Billy. No.
Arthur, what should we do?
Go and get me the referee.
Bring me the fucking referee.
I know she's here with us.
Always.
But still, it's just you and me.
I thought it would be good
if we were in a different place.
I hate that house now.
I wish I could blow it up.
There was a time when we'd say
nothing afterwards
because we didn't have
to say anything.
But now we've got nothing left
to say.
There's business.
What business?
The American.
He's coming to Birmingham.
He's stopping over
on his way to Liverpool.
He is staying with us
tomorrow night.
Frances knows.
She's making up a menu.
And then...
..we have to make a move.
Do you want to know
what that move is, Lizzie?
No.
I know enough.
Your book of regrets.
23, 24,
52, 55.
The combination to the safe.
Regrets.
And I'm on there.
I'm on the list.
On the very top of the list.
Yep.
Yes, you are.
I regret marrying you, Lizzie.
Cos I've put you through
so much.
I've put you through all of this.
Ruby.
Everything that is to come.
When you married me,
you married a man
and you married a curse.
You have shared my fate.
That is my regret.
But know this, Lizzie.
In this moment,
in this room...
..I love you.
You sound like
you're ticking a fucking box,
and I don't know
what's inside the box.
Never have you let me in.
Even though I know
the combination to the safe.
Oh, this is him, is it?
The one who likes
to be fucking difficult, eh?
When I leave this place,
I am going straight to the police.
You are?
This man pointed a gun at me.
Who, him there? Yeah.
Well, let's phone the police, eh?
Don't worry. We'll have this
sorted out for you.
Hello? Yes, get me the police.
Reports of a man with
a revolver on Watery Lane.
There you go.
And you ask for Inspector Moss.
Chief Superintendent Moss.
He's in charge of Watery Lane
and Bordesley Green.
That's right.
And you see this?
That's his betting credit with us.
He makes a lot of money
from football matches.
Because we give him
the results before the match.
On Saturday afternoon,
you take this whistle,
and you blow.
You give a penalty
to Birmingham City
in the final minute.
The goalkeeper will let
the penalty go by him,
and Birmingham City will win 1-0.
All you got to do is...
HE CLEARS THROAT
WHISTLE BLOWS
HE SNORTS
No.
I won't do it.
If the police won't listen,
I'll go to the newspapers.
I'm not afraid.
I was in France.
Phone Tommy, Arthur.
You shut up.
I am not phoning fucking Tommy.
I am dealing with this, OK?
I'm leaving.
You are going fucking nowhere.
It's time one of us stood up
to you people.
It's not right
what's been happening.
I will not take money to cheat.
Fucking hell.
In France, I ran at the wire.
And I was not afraid.
I am not afraid.
I won't do a bad thing.
I have seen too many bad things.
A beating will make no difference.
I know that,
cos I can see
it in your fucking eyes.
HE SIGHS
Fuck.
In the bleak midwinter...
Holy Mary, mother of God.
Ah!
Right, Billy Boy.
You've been in the family
long enough.
Yeah. It's time for you
to get bloodied.
Arthur, you can't. Arthur, please.
You've been with us long enough.
Arthur, fuck, Jesus Christ.
I can't be that man. Arthur, please.
Either two men die today, Billy...
..or one. You fucking decide.
You hate him, Billy. You hate him.
You don't know him Billy.
He's fucking laughing at you.
Come on, hate him.
Look him in the eyes, man.
Look him in the eyes.
I can't. I can't.
I'm sorry...sorry.
GASPING
Aaaaah!
GURGLING
Enough. Enough, enough, enough.
BILLY SOBS
All right. Billy B, come on.
Come on, sh...
Sh, sh...
It's all right. It's all right.
Look at you. Look...
Look at you, look.
Huh?
You're bloodied now, Billy.
You're bloodied now.
You're not going to heaven no more.
They won't let you in.
Isiah, you take him to the foundry.
And you ask for Mr Patches,
all right?
You tell him
we got some fuel for the furnace.
FOOTSTEPS
WHISTLING
FOOTSTEPS APPROACH
Who the fuck are you?
Ah! Ah!
I hear... Please.
..you're the informant
inside the Shelby organisation.
And who the fuck I am...
..is the man who you now work for.
Please, please...
I have some things I need you to do,
and I want to impress upon you...
To IMPRESS... Ah! Ah!
..upon you
the seriousness of my intent.
Cos, you see, I used to do
this kind of thing for a living.
And sometimes I kind of miss it.
Just like Mr Shelby,
I miss the...the wave
of electricity you get
under your scalp.
I miss the taste like metal
on the tip of your tongue.
I am about to give you
an instruction.
You do as I say,
you stay a man.
Fail,
and I will send people
to serve your balls to you
on a china plate.
I'll do what you say.
A decision has been taken.
My associates are going to take care
of Tommy Shelby.
And you are going to give us up
his brother, Arthur.
Do you understand?
CORD CINCHES
Yes...Yes. Fucking yes. Please.
Only information leading
to the murder of Arthur Shelby
will save you from an Italian death.
Cos it was the Italians
that taught me that
above God, above children,
above his wife
and above his mother...
..most of all,
a man loves his balls.
BILLY WHIMPERS
BILLY HUFFS
BILLY SOBS
DOOR CLOSES
Oh...
Hello, Arthur.
I think we should pray.
That's how we begin this.
You'd like to pray?
The prayer I have chosen is
the Act of Contrition, version two.
So, you're Catholic now, Linda?
You're Catholic.
Quakers don't pray.
Bow your head, Arthur,
and close your eyes.
And recite the prayer.
You know it well
from when you were boy.
Oh, my mind's all dried up
with junk, though,
and shot full of fuck...
Shot full of holes.
Linda, please.
It's in there somewhere, Arthur.
It's like a song.
Yeah.
Somewhere.
Together, we'll find it.
Digging for the words
will help clean your soul.
I'll begin it.
Forgive me my sins, oh, Lord,
forgive me my sins.
The sins of my youth.
The sins of my youth,
the sins of my age,
the sins of my soul.
The sins of my body.
The sins I know,
the sins I know not.
The sins I have concealed
for so long.
For so fu...
For so long.
I caught him stealing a car.
And he's got a stack of cash
from the betting shop.
Steal from who you want,
but don't steal from me.
Here you are.
Get a train to wherever
the fuck you want to go. Get out.
I don't ride trains.
Is that a fact?
Well, Curly has a two-wheeled wagon.
What am I, a tinker?
I need four wheels.
And a horse for the hills.
Which hills?
All of them.
All the hills of England.
TOMMY CHUCKLES
Why do you want to leave?
I didn't take to that work
in the betting shop.
Well, you heard him, Charlie.
Get my dad's old four-wheeled wagon
and two strong ponies.
Right.
Curly! Get here.
Before you go,
do you want to know the truth
about yourself?
No. Who does?
Well, I am going to tell yer.
That spring at Appleby Fair,
your mother stole
my watch and chain.
You're from a long line of thieves.
The watch had the words
"Saxon Shore" carved in it.
I stole it myself
from a drunk when I was a kid.
I imagine she told you
your dad was
the Duke of the Saxon Shore.
Well...
..I am the Duke,
it was my watch.
I am your father.
That's the truth.
When her dad found out,
he shot me in the chest
with a squirrel gun.
A scar and a stolen watch
and a story she made up.
That's all you need to know
about yourself
before you get on the road.
Esme told me the spirits favour you.
That the spirit is in you.
She tried to sell me like one
of those horses, didn't she?
How much did she pay for me?
I have no use for gold any more.
But if you're a horse,
you're in the right place.
Curly!
Curly. Hurry up.
This boy has hills to climb.
I remember that watch.
Oh, yeah?
She used to wear it over her heart.
We buried it with her.
Tom. The old wagon's
right front wheel is fucked, Tom.
It's standing in the wet.
Put a new one on, Curly.
Yeah.
They fix wagons here.
Good families
come from the New Forest
to have their wagons fixed
and get fresh horses
before the fairs.
Yeah. Yeah, I like it here.
I like it better than
that betting shop.
Why?
People.
People piss me off.
There are a lot of people
in that betting shop.
So far, here I've only counted two.
Uh-huh.
Charlie and Curly,
the rest is dogs and horses.
Curly's half horse himself.
Dogs are OK.
Horses are better than people,
mind you.
There's work here
for a man who knows horses.
Unknown.
I want to remain
completely unknown.
Well, you'd be in the right place
for that as well.
No-one knows anyone here.
Hey, mister.
Save that wheel a minute.
Where would I stay?
Stables, with the other stallions.
Now that Finn is married off,
there are plenty of girls
round here.
Their fathers
are mostly unarmed.
I have a future for you, Duke.
You already have a son.
My business has two sides.
Light and dark.
I'll need someone for each.
And I'm dark, am I?
I have realised we don't get
to choose which one we are.
Dark knows dark.
And my affairs,
both light and dark...
..will need settling soon.
Curly? Find a shovel for
the Duke of the Saxon Shore here.
Get him shovelling shit.
HE SNORTS
And put some petrol in the boat.
I'm off to meet a lady in Solihull.
# One silver dollar
# Bright silver dollar
# Changing hands, changing hands
# Spent for a beer he's drinking
# Worn by a gambler's lust
# Pierced by an outlaw's bullet
# And lost in the blood-red dust
# One silver dollar
# One silver dollar... #
Take a look at her.
Now imagine ten people
living on side.
Step on. Have a look inside.
I've had a response
from the Guinness Trust
about building charitable housing
at two sites
along the canal network
between London,
Birmingham and Liverpool.
This lock here would be
the one of the sites.
I have the permission.
We just need the finance.
I know that you and your husband,
Bryan Guinness, are estranged,
but I understand
you still have influence
in the Guinness family.
Your support might help them
make their decision.
Will you help me?
I've booked a suite in a hotel
a mile from here.
My chauffeur will take us there.
You look quite the thing
dressed like that,
dressed like a working man.
They'll probably show you
to the coal house
to make your delivery.
Yep, they probably will.
Oswald has fucked your wife,
so my suggestion is
about balance and proportion.
It would be only fair.
Can I assume...
..I have your support?
This isn't about charitable housing,
this is about changing the world.
It's about a different kind
of trust.
Absolute trust.
We have important work ahead of us.
It's much harder to lie
with your body
than with your words.
This, I have learnt.
Mostly, I do
whatever I want to do.
Sometimes, I do things
for the cause.
In this case, it's both.
Come.
In the interests
of absolute clarity,
that is simply
the English aristocracy's way
of shaking hands.
So...
Welcome.
MELANCHOLY MUSIC
# Come under my wings, little bird
# Come under my wings... #
HE GASPS
# Unmade
# I swear that there's nothing
# Up my sleeves
# And then back again
# I swear there's nothing
# Unmade
# There's no faces
# Won't grow back again
# Broken pieces... #
POLLY: If you do this thing...
..the possibility of war,
you have to consider.
MICHAEL: It was the ambitions
and strategies of one man
that caused this.
POLLY: There will be a war
in this family.
And one of you will die.
# I swear there's nothing
# Won't grow back again
# I swear there's nothing... #
We need to leave early to catch
the first train to Liverpool, yes?
Yep.
So eat early, finish early.
You changed the combination
of the safe.
Why?
Have you got new secrets?
With the new business at hand,
there are some things
that I cannot share.
What things?
What are those tablets?
The doctor gave them me.
Pain killers?
Yeah. What pain?
Any pain that comes, Lizzie.
When you're ready, I want you
to tell me everything
that's going on.
It's like
the clock's stopped ticking
and I'm waiting
for the bomb to explode.
We are in that quiet minute.
Tommy?
That's where we live now.
When I know everything...
..I will tell you everything.
Oh, no, Gina's running wild,
y'see.
Harrods, dope, amphetamines,
lords and ladies,
you know, the whole
English aristocracy thing.
Fuck wine - whiskey.
Shelby, you having whiskey?
I'll stay on wine.
Fuck wine, more whiskey.
I'm celebrating.
Celebration, you know.
Getting off this fucking island.
You see, the thing with England,
the currency here,
it's not money.
Nah. You got bored of money
a long time ago.
Cos you know anyone
can have money,
you can fucking...
..you can fucking find money
in the mud.
You can forge money.
Mr Shelby, you can steal money,
am I right?
The currency here, it's blood.
And Mr Shelby knows that
better than all of them.
Blood here is like wine,
like the vintage wine
in that bottle. It's the label,
it's the terroir,
it's the grape that makes the wine.
Who fucking cares
about the glass around it?
And you, my friend,
you're an American.
You fucking smash the glass,
you spill the blood
and you spend their currency
to get what you want.
Am I right?
When you come to America,
I will show you things.
You're going to America?
To Canada, Lizzie,
to collect payment for the shipment.
I need to do it myself.
And who will be going with you?
Michael will be there
to watch his back.
Another journey, Tommy?
$5 million, Mrs Shelby.
It's worth a little cruise,
don't you think?
You know whiskey does talk,
Mr Nelson,
and sometimes
whiskey is...very eloquent.
But $5 million, Mr Nelson...
Now, that is a legacy.
And when I come back,
I will know everything.
I see myself so clearly
in you, Thomas Shelby.
You are a man with a bright
and glittering future.
DOOR OPENS
Mr Shelby,
there's a car coming up the drive.
A Rolls-Royce.
Were you expecting more guests?
No.
Excuse me.
We were on our way
to my constituency in Smethwick
and I heard our American friend
was in Birmingham
and that he was coming here,
so we came
to say one last farewell.
Champagne.
We have much to celebrate.
It isn't that I wasn't sure
Mr Shelby would give you
an excellent send-off,
I just felt,
since telegrams and wires
and letters can so easily
be intercepted,
we might confirm all that
we've achieved during your visit
over champagne.
It is remarkable how quickly
our relationships have developed.
So many triangles in this room.
Everyone except from Mr Nelson
is the point of a triangle.
How am I part of a triangle?
Mr Nelson,
you have all that you came for?
I have confirmation
that the future of Europe is in
the hands of men like yourselves.
And that urgent conversations
between Washington,
Rome and of course Berlin
can now begin.
A two-week visit that may have
changed the course of history.
We have all got what we wanted.
Yes.
And I got what I have wanted
from the moment I set eyes on it.
Elizabeth,
you are a very lucky woman...
..to have each day
what I have only sampled once.
Forgive us, Mr Nelson,
that was a necessary bit
of housekeeping.
Thomas.
We do so hate to be indiscreet,
but we have told you many times,
if you are to seek power
in these days of shiny magazines
and society photographs,
sooner or later,
you will have to find a spouse
who is more suitable.
A woman with Lizzie's past
and personal history
really isn't suitable.
She doesn't deserve you, Mr Shelby.
You know the thing is, Mosley...
..you're right.
You're right,
she doesn't deserve me.
She doesn't deserve what I am.
She doesn't deserve
what I will become.
What will you become?
The truth is, I belong here,
at this table.
With fuckers like you.
She doesn't.
For all I try to hide it...
HE SCOFFS
..I'm just one of you.
Could there be a sadder ending, eh?
# Take a little walk
to the edge of town
# And go across the tracks
# Where a viaduct looms
like a bird of doom
# As it shifts and cracks
# Where secrets lie
in the border fires
# In the humming wires
# Hey, man
# You know you're never coming back
# Past the square
# Past the bridge, past the mills
and the stacks
# On a gathering storm
# Comes a tall, handsome man
# And a dusty black coat
with a red right hand. #
I'm here on behalf of your wife,
Gina, and Jack Nelson.
Mr Nelson's prepared
to get you out of here.
But first he needs an answer
to the question.
If the answer is yes...
..you'll be released.
If the answer is no...
..you'll stay.
I have consulted my mother.
Your mother's dead.
Never the less,
I have consulted her.
And yes.
When I'm released,
it is my intention
to kill Tommy Shelby.
# He's a god, he's a man
# He's a ghost, a guru
# And they're whispering his name
# Through the disappearing land
# But hidden in his coat
# Is a red right hand
# You don't have no money?
# Well, he get you some
# You don't have no car?
# He get you one. #
Watch Movies, TV Series & Live Sports
www.admitme.app