Previously on "For the People"...
Your client tried to blow up the
Statue of Liberty, Sandra Bell.
We the jury find the
defendant, Mohammed Fayed, guilty.
You could be a good lawyer.
If you tried. You're just not trying.
My tradition is now to eat with you
every night before
the first day of trial.
Can I get your number?
I like you.
This could never work.
We'd be lying in bed,
and I'd be infuriated.
My takeaway from that is that
you've thought about us lying in bed.
How is it that your first time on duty,
you get him?
I'd like for you to come by
my office this afternoon
so we can discuss some things.
- It's a date.
- It's not a date.
- Do you miss him?
- Sometimes.
This is the United States District Court
for the Southern District of New York.
Are you worthy?
Do you hate me?
Why would I hate you?
It wasn't that bad. I mean, it wasn't...
No, not that.
I mean, you said we'd end up
in bed next to each other
with you hating me.
Oh, yeah, right.
Well, yes. Give it time.
But for right now...
it's fun.
Have you been working here all night?
I was in the kitchen from 2:15 to 3:00.
I think I broke the toaster.
Did you finish?
Yes.
How do you feel?
I feel like I shouldn't have
lost the trial
in the first place.
I'm thinking about getting a unicycle.
- No.
- I am.
But this was going so well, you and me.
I think it'd be cool.
You are mistaken.
You really do that every morning?
Every morning.
She walks across the
Brooklyn Bridge every morning.
- And back. What are you doing here?
- Me?
You're not just loitering around
the clerk's desk, are you?
No.
Because you know I wouldn't like that.
'Course I know that.
What's to like about that?
What are you doing here?
I am here because I am on duty.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Duty?
Yep.
Okay.
Here's your case.
Cool. No problem.
Shouldn't be if you're on duty.
And it isn't. Because I am on duty.
No problem.
Huge problem! I can't do this.
Where did you get this?
- I picked it up on duty.
- You're not on duty.
You know, this is a great point.
I like this point.
Oh, so smart, Sandra.
Eh, see, I like that less.
What is the problem?
Ohhh.
- Ohh.
- Oh.
Kate Littlejohn.
You'll be fine.
No. I will not be fine.
Do you realize I have an actual fear
of fluorescent colors because of her?
Because of the tabs!
A clinically verifiable phobia.
I have been treated
for this... unsuccessfully!
- Brainbridge.
- What?
Oh, sorry... Bainbridge.
I keep mixing that up.
Bank robbery. Government's gonna
offer a favorable deal.
Alice Huang. Staff hydrologist
with the U.S. Geological Survey.
She's being charged with downloading
and transmitting sensitive
scientific data
about water distribution systems
to the Chinese.
You okay?
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
She was up all night on the Fayed appeal.
I slept, like, 11 hours last night.
I can totally switch.
It's okay. I'm okay. I got it.
Okay, well, good morning, everyone!
Let's make this a great day.
This is one of those mornings
where I wonder
what it's like across the street.
Grim and quiet,
plotting death and destruction all day.
Good morning, everyone!
How was everyone's morning?
Littlejohn?
My morning was great, sir.
I am glad to hear it.
Mine too.
Excellent.
I would say excellent, as well.
- And I would say, for me...
- Okay. Let's get started.
Mr. Oliver, this is a case
I was gonna give to Mr. Knox,
but I knew he would complain about it,
and I knew you'd smile and say,
"I appreciate the opportunity,"
and then mumble something
under your breath about me.
No, sir. I do appreciate the opportunity.
Always giving me the worst...
Broti. Your wine informant has gone AWOL.
This is a problem.
Ms. Littlejohn,
a parent at The Whitley School
has apparently been found
with MDMA in her car.
This is now your problem.
Since when is this a federal prosecution?
Since two other parents at the
school called their good friend
the United States Attorney
for the Southern District
of New York Douglas Delap
and asked his office to handle it.
And I want you to keep those parents
up to speed on this case.
Speaking of parents,
Mr. Knox, your mom is in town.
I know this because you
tried to put lunch
for the three of us on my calendar,
and I took this off my calendar.
And in case anybody is not yet aware,
Leonard Knox's mom
is a United States Senator!
And, finally, Ms. Chavez,
you are up against Sandra Bell.
Some of the other attorneys here
will have negative things
to say about that,
but I am not a negative person,
and I encourage everybody else
to be kind and respectful
to our adversaries.
Thank you all. It's been a great pleasure
spending time with you this morning.
Sandra Bell is a total pain in the ass.
- Sandra Bell is sanctimonious...
- Crush Sandra Bell.
I'm not a spy, Ms. Bell.
Why don't you tell me
about Mr. Hua Lin...
how you were first introduced?
In the summer of 2015,
I was visiting my parents in Beijing.
My former professor introduced
me to Hua Lin at a party.
We talked about fluid mechanics,
streamflow response...
things we both care about...
and from there, it grew.
Personal.
I visited him three times in Beijing
over a two-year period.
I visited his office at
the Ministry of Water Resources.
We stayed together in a hotel.
That's where I gave him
two flash drives full of data.
Which I did not have access to.
Lin didn't ask me for any of this.
I offered it.
Because we were scientists
trying to solve a problem.
That was the real reason.
But the personal side,
it just complicated everything.
And by the time the FBI
showed up at my desk,
I had deleted so many e-mails,
lied about so many things...
I-I couldn't tell the truth.
We are both married.
And we both have children.
I know how it looks.
How it always looks.
Whenever I spoke Chinese
on the phone at work,
with a family member,
people would make these comments.
What about?
Wen Ho Lee. Chi Mak. Greg Chung.
People made jokes about
Chinese-American scientists
who had been accused of espionage?
I just let it pass.
We do that.
But... now I'm here.
The courthouse where I was arraigned...
that's where I became a citizen.
I love my new country, Ms. Bell.
My children are Americans.
I've built my life here.
Can you help me?
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Good to hear from you. How's it going?
You know, working a lot.
Tried oysters for the first time.
Don't totally understand what I'm eating.
Is that the body?
The head?
W-What is this little lump exactly?
I just... don't think about it.
I had this friend in high school,
he wouldn't eat anything with eyes.
So, a lot of scallops, clams, oysters.
Potatoes?
Yes.
That's a good point.
You wanted to...
tell me something?
Really, I wanted to have coffee with you.
But yes.
Your wine forger client? Toby Mahler?
He missed a tasting with the FBI.
They're getting a warrant.
You didn't hear it from me.
Thank you.
For real, though, please
don't use this against me.
I would never.
Again.
All right. I got to go deal with Toby.
Thank you.
For all of this.
Oysters are amazing.
You clearly had the wrong ones.
I'll take you somewhere good.
You'll see.
I know all your clients
probably say this,
but I have no idea how those
things ended up inside my car.
You'd actually be surprised
how many don't say that.
I've never even tried drugs.
I feel like I'm living in some sort of
horrible alternative universe.
I can't sleep.
I'm trying not to let my son
see how terrified I am,
because if something happened to me...
If you plead guilty,
I can probably get you probation.
No jail time.
But that would mean pleading guilty,
and if you insist that you're not...
What about William?
His scholarship?
It's hard for me to imagine
that he'd stay at the school.
Do you know who called the police?
Told them to search my car?
It was an anonymous tip.
This sounds crazy, but...
there's a mother at the school...
a lawyer.
Dana Gallagher.
And I ran against her this year
to be head of the Parents' Association.
I won.
She and her husband have three kids
that go to The Whitley School.
And they never liked me.
I don't know why.
Maybe if you're paying tuition
for three kids,
you're bound to hate the person
whose kid goes for free.
William worked so hard
for that scholarship.
At his old school,
there were these kids that...
He had a rough time.
How do I tell him
he has to go back there?
Let's take it one step at a time, okay?
Maybe you won't have to.
Webb Flynt is stepping down
as Solicitor General?
I thought he'd die in that chair,
but apparently he wants to fish
and play with his grandchildren.
- Whatever.
- So, what's the word?
Who's the AG looking at as a replacement?
Me.
You're not leaving the Senate.
He's looking at me for names.
And I only gave him one...
you.
Me?
Yes.
Solicitor General of Texas?
- Yes.
- That's in Texas.
Well, at least we know you'll
be able to find your office.
Is it too soon? I just
got to the Southern District.
Barack Obama had just
gotten into the U.S. Senate
when he ran for President.
Opportunity is opportunity.
- This...
- Is an opportunity.
You did your time in New York.
You come home to Texas.
Accept the Attorney General's
appointment as Solicitor.
You do the job we both know you can do.
Then you use it to launch yourself
into the United States Senate.
I'm really settling in at this office.
Some of the people I work with,
we're starting to click.
I'm sure they'll forgive you
when you invite them to the White House.
Because that's where you're headed.
This job is mine if I want it?
That's the question...
do you want it?
Do you want it?
You look kind of...
- I'm fine.
- Oh?
Well, obviously,
selling drugs to children
is an abhorrent offense,
but the good news is,
we're willing to negotiate.
Now, given the amount of MDMA that
was found in the defendant's car
and factoring in
her intent to distribute...
Nancy Martin's not a drug dealer.
Really? Just like
Adam Dyle wasn't a scam artist?
- It's not the same.
- Well, you're the same.
Still willing to believe
whatever your client says...
willfully ignoring the evidence.
Look, that evidence
could have been planted.
Nancy's fingerprints weren't on it,
she left her car unlocked...
The principal of The Whitley School
confirmed there were already
numerous rumors going around
that Nancy sold drugs.
Rumors? Mm.
An anonymous phone call...
Is that a Lego brick?
I have a statement here
from two parents at the school,
Michael and Dana Gallagher.
They're both attorneys,
and they will testify
- that Ms. Martin has had a...
- Wait. Stop.
The Gallaghers are driving this?
Nobody drives our prosecutions.
Oh, yeah. Right.
The Gallaghers hate Nancy Martin.
She beat out Dana for the head
of the Parents' Association,
and what's worse, she's poor.
I think they're playing you.
I think you're the one
who's being Adam Dyled here,
Kate Littlejohn.
I think that's it for today, Mr. Simmons.
Why don't you call me when
you're ready to be reasonable.
Thank you for having us in.
Roger says you're one of the good ones.
We are so relieved to hear
the government's
taking this case seriously.
Oh, we take every case
seriously, Ms. Gallagher.
Now, I am sorry that I don't
have more to report right now,
but my hope is we can
have a deal in place by...
I'm sorry, a deal?
A deal with jail time.
This is Ms. Martin's first offense.
You know I'm a litigator, right?
So was Dana before the kids.
We know what an excuse sounds like.
It's not an excuse. It's a simple...
Maybe we should call Doug.
You don't need to call Mr. Delap.
This woman is ruining our school.
Okay? Do you understand?
So you can sit there
and defend her or you...
I'm not defending her. In fact, I'm...
Listen to me,
you twenty-something-haircut.
Nancy Martin needs to go to jail.
Okay? She's been fooling everyone
with her "I'm such a good person" act
and trying to shame
the rest of us into giving up
the Foundations of
Western Civilization curriculum
or trying to set a limit on how much
the kids can spend on their prom night...
it's prom, for God's sake...
when she should just shut up
and be grateful
her kid's even at the school
in the first place.
And now this?
Selling drugs?
I want that woman locked up.
I really don't like those people.
Lucas and Amy?
- He does do that thing with his nose...
- The parents who brought this case in.
- She called me a "haircut."
- I don't know what that means.
- Should I talk to Roger?
- I doubt he knows. He's such a...
Should I talk to Roger
about how awful they are?
Dana Gallagher used to work here.
I wouldn't.
I need some help.
Remember that first day here,
when I told you
I didn't want to be the help desk
for every man in this office?
That was so long ago!
Okay, so, here's the thing.
I think I have feelings for this girl...
- Allison.
- Doesn't matter.
And I want to tell this girl...
- Allison.
- How I feel.
How do you feel about Allison?
Not sure.
I mean, I loved her. Then I didn't.
But now, seeing her,
it's different, and I just...
I don't know.
Seems like a sweet thing to say.
- Well, I mean, I'm confused...
- Yes. Look.
If you have feelings,
I think you should tell her.
I'm a big believer in being honest.
For example...
I would like you to leave now.
Well, this was great.
Thank you.
Hey.
Hey?
Where have you been?
Flavigny-sur-Ozerain.
What?
It's in France.
Please tell me you're joking.
For real. It's a village
in Burgundy. Check the map.
Toby, you can't leave the country!
That's part of the deal.
I was meeting with producers,
tasting new vintages.
I can't help the FBI track down forgers
if I'm not experiencing the latest wines.
Is this about the meeting
I missed on Monday?
Yes. And I will prepare
a statement, but...
No, I think Gerald already
called over to that Broti
or whatever her name is.
- Who is Gerald?
- He's my lawyer.
I'm your lawyer.
You were my lawyer.
But now that I can afford
a lawyer, I have a lawyer.
- Wine?
- What?
To celebrate.
No. No wine.
- It's not fake.
- That's not the point.
You said you couldn't go out
on a date with me because
I was your client.
Now I'm not your client.
So there's no reason
we can't see each other.
There are other reasons.
Such as?
Look, if the answer's no,
I'll respect that,
and you'll never hear from me ever again.
But before you make up
your mind, just know...
I like you.
A lot.
You're smart and charming,
interesting, beautiful.
I like being around you.
So, now that you're not my lawyer...
will you at least consider it?
And you said?
I don't know. Something ridiculous.
Because he's ridiculous.
Ly hot.
But I am enjoying Seth.
What is happening here?
- Oh, a cone of depression.
- What's that?
It's a conical shape produced
in a piezometric surface
by the extraction of water
from a well at a given rate.
It's also the place defense lawyers go
when they're about to lose a case.
Don't say that.
I don't think Alice Huang is a spy.
I truly don't.
But this stuff she downloaded
sounds alarming.
"Quantitative Precipitation Forecast."
"Site Specific Hydrologic
Prediction System."
A jury is gonna hear this
and they're not gonna have
a clue what it means.
They're just gonna think it sounds bad
and she shouldn't have been
giving it to the Chinese.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless a jury doesn't hear this.
- A bench trial?
- Yes.
You want to try this in front
of a judge and not a jury?
- Yes.
- Why?
Because the jury's gonna get lost
in the technical jargon of this case.
This is about hydrological engineering
and flow capacities
and moisture state variables.
Is that what this is about?
Or is this about Mohammed Fayed?
No.
About a jury looking at your client
and not at the evidence.
I understand why you're nervous
about taking this to a jury, Sandra.
I do. Juries are scary.
Because they're made up of people.
With blinders and biases
and real human limitations.
But a jury is the best chance you have.
Because you have 12 chances with a jury
and only one with a judge.
If you think they need to understand
this evidence in order to acquit Alice,
then help them understand the evidence.
That is your job,
and you are good at your job.
Don't run from it.
I think we should talk.
The voice. Everything.
It all seems so real.
May I come in?
I think there's something odd
about this case.
Yeah, me too.
Like, I guess for me, it seems
a little odd that...
- Nancy Martin was framed!
- Yes.
And that the Southern
District of New Y...
Wait, did you just say yes?
- Yes.
- Yes, you said yes?
- Okay.
Can you just nod?
Yes.
- Nngh!
- Okay, look.
I think the Gallaghers might
have had something to do
with the situation Nancy is in right now.
Then arrest them and drop
the charges against Nancy.
There are issues here that make
it difficult for me to do that.
I need your help.
What else do you know
about the Gallaghers?
- Just what I told you.
- We need more than that.
So put some agents on it.
Like I said, this is complicated.
Do you have an investigator here?
Uh, one. For the whole office.
I've heard that there is more than
one agent in the FBI, though.
Is that true?
Maybe there's more history,
an earlier altercation between
the Gallaghers and Nancy.
Right. Those rumors
about Nancy selling drugs.
If we can find out who started them...
But didn't the principal say
there were multiple sources?
So we ask other parents,
maybe even some kids?
Wait, are we arguing or agreeing?
I have no idea.
Arguing.
I'll call the principal.
See if she can help us
set up some interviews.
This was productive,
if highly unpleasant.
Mr. Davis, what is your occupation?
I'm now retired, but for 27 years,
I was a special agent with the FBI.
Did you have a particular area
of expertise within the Bureau?
I worked in counterintelligence,
with a focus on threats
to critical infrastructure.
The government alleges that Ms. Huang
jeopardized national security
by downloading site-specific PMP values.
What is a PMP value, Agent Davis?
Possible maximum precipitation.
Essentially, it means the chance of rain.
Ms. Huang also allegedly downloaded HMRs.
What is an HMR, Agent Davis?
A hydrometeorological report.
Weather forecast.
How about an RVI?
It basically is a report
on the amount of ice formed
on a particular river.
That's it?
Yes.
Huh. Okay.
Agent Davis, in your view,
would the distribution of any
of the data Ms. Huang downloaded
from the National
Water Distribution Database
jeopardize national security?
No.
Agent Davis, you have familiarity
with the Chinese government's
espionage efforts
in this country, correct?
Objection. Mr. Davis is here
to testify about infrastructure.
Mr. Davis was put up as an
expert in counterintelligence.
I'm entitled to ask him about that.
I'll allow it. Sir, you may answer.
- Yes.
- Isn't it true, Agent Davis,
that when China cultivates
someone residing in this country
for use in espionage programs,
it is generally someone born in China,
fluent in the language and customs,
and who still maintains
broad and deep ties to China?
Yes.
Isn't it true, Agent Davis,
that newly cultivated spies often begin
with more mundane kinds
of intelligence-gathering
in order to test their
capability and visibility?
Yes.
So the mere fact
that this scientific data
might have been
of relatively minimal value
doesn't necessarily tell us anything
about whether Ms. Huang
is operating as an agent
of the Chinese government?
Objection! Prejudicial!
Your Honor, Ms. Chavez is making
the outrageous suggestion...
- Overruled.
- That just because
Ms. Huang was born in China...
Overruled.
You may answer.
That is correct.
I do not know if Ms. Huang
is an agent of the Chinese government.
I suppose she could be.
How's it going
with your fancy private school?
I don't know if I like these parents
or opposing counsel less.
Do you have to choose?
I guess not.
I brought you these.
Silver.
- You okay?
- I have a job offer.
You were going after Max Gillespie's
job in Public Corruption.
In Texas.
What?
Solicitor General.
Y-You have an offer
to be the Solicitor General of Texas?
I'm only a few years younger than
Ted Cruz was when he had the job.
And I think I'd be better.
So you're gonna take it?
I don't know.
What do you think I should do?
I... think you should do
what you want to do.
Yes, but what do you think I should do?
Honestly.
I have no opinion about it. Honestly.
But I'm happy for you...
if it's what you want.
Well, I just wanted to let you know.
Congratulations, Leonard.
Do you want to toss it, or should I?
You okay?
I should get up.
Have you been here all night?
I broke the microwave at 4:15.
It was intentional.
I'm sorry.
- You need to get some sleep, Sandy.
- Mnh-mnh.
I am going to lose.
You're not. Stop saying that.
I am.
I am going to lose.
Because this jury
is going to look at Alice
and they are going to listen to Alice
and they are going to think,
"Spy. She is from China. She's a spy."
And it doesn't matter what I say,
because what I'm saying,
I'm not saying very well,
because I'm pissed off...
Listen to me.
It's okay to be angry.
But it is not your fault that Alice Huang
shared data that she wasn't supposed to.
It's not your fault that she
lied to the government about it.
And it is not your fault that
Mohammed Fayed was found guilty.
It is my fault. Don't say that.
Please don't say that. Because it is.
It is my fault.
I was there to protect him,
and I did not!
I did not protect him!
I Di...
It's wrong, Al.
What's happening to her.
She is being treated unfairly.
So tell them that.
Tell them that, Sandy.
Ms. Cappelli, you had
the cubicle adjacent to Alice's
at the USGS Water Science Center?
That's right. For over two years.
When she asked you for the
password and login instructions
to the National Water Distribution
Database, did you give it to her?
- Yes.
- Was that a difficult decision?
It wasn't a decision at all, really.
People share these passwords
all the time.
I borrowed one
before I had one of my own.
It wasn't considered a big deal, until...
U-Until when?
Until Alice used it.
Mr. Jorgensen,
what is your area of expertise
at the Geological Survey?
I'm the Deputy Assistant Chief
of Engineers.
And you've worked closely
with foreign governments in this area?
Primarily Norway.
I was born and educated there.
In the past 18 months, how many
trips have you made to Norway
in a professional capacity?
Four trips.
Did you ever share any data
from the National
Water Distribution Database
with the Norwegian government
on those trips?
Yes. A lot.
Was the USGS aware of this?
Yes. I was given a commendation
for the work I did with Norway.
As Chief Security Officer, you enforce
all United States Geological
Survey rules and procedures,
as well as maintain all IT records?
That's correct.
According to your records,
how many USGS employees
have downloaded data from
the National Water Distribution
Database in the last year?
67.
How many have been investigated,
to your knowledge?
One. Alice.
Is this a bad time? I... I can come back.
Is everything okay?
I hope so.
What I'm about to do is...
unprofessional...
- Okay.
- Inappropriate,
and has a high likelihood
of making me seem like a fool.
You're not really selling it.
I love you.
Seth...
I'm not scared of you
beating me in a courtroom.
I don't think you're controlling.
I think... I was insecure,
and you wanted me to be a better person.
And I am now.
I've done the work. I have changed.
A lot.
Except for the fact that
I'm still in love with you.
- This is a lot.
- I know.
And I'm not trying to overwhelm you.
I'm not proposing.
I'm not saying
we should move in together.
I'm not saying we should do anything.
I just want you to know how I feel
and that I'd like you
to give me another chance.
This is what I wanted to say.
How do I look?
What?
Do I look like a prosecutor?
You know? Tightly wound. Judgmental.
Huge stick up my...
Principal Hatcher! Nice to meet you.
I'm so sorry to keep you waiting.
Minor crisis with the new kiln.
Please.
We're hoping you can shed
some light on the relationship
between Nancy Martin
and Michael and Dana Gallagher.
The Gallaghers?
They... Hm.
How do I put this?
They hated her?
Well, "hate" might be too strong a word.
But they certainly didn't want her
to be head of the Parents' Association?
Well, you have to understand,
Michael and Dana both
went to Whitley themselves.
They're very invested in its identity.
And the head of the Parents' Association,
well, for all intents and purposes,
that person becomes
the face of the school
for the period of their tenure.
What's wrong with Nancy
being the face of the school?
Well, she'd have a great deal
of contact with our funders,
most of whom are alumni.
And alumni appreciate
a certain history of the school.
A culture.
Nancy Martin, while she did manage
to charm quite a few
of the other parents,
did not reflect that culture.
The rumors about Nancy dealing drugs...
do you think there's any chance
they were started by the Gallaghers?
I can't imagine.
Let me just say, Nancy Martin was the one
who had the ecstasy
in the back seat of her car.
Even if the Gallaghers
did help spread some rumors,
obviously, they weren't unwarranted.
Why don't you suggest some families.
We can dig them up. We're good.
I mean, we can't just sit here and
badger the woman all day, can we?
She's got a job to do.
- I ha...
- Come on. Up, up, up.
Thank you, Principal Hatcher.
Thank you.
Hey.
What the hell are you doing?
Did you hear that?
She said ecstasy was found
in the back seat of Nancy's car.
Uh-huh. It was.
And how did Principal Hatcher know that?
Because that information
hasn't been publicly released.
It wasn't in the indictment.
Nobody knows that. Except us.
You think she planted the drugs?
I think she planted the drugs.
Are we gonna hug?
God, no.
Okay. Cool.
Alice Huang grew up in Hebei
province in Central China.
She studied at Jilin University,
moved to the United States
when she was 20,
got her M.Sc. with
a concentration in Hydrology
at Stony Brook...
and fell in love with America.
She is a mother of two boys.
She's a board member
at her local Boys & Girls Club.
She likes Drake.
She's a long-suffering Knicks fan.
She is a New Yorker.
She is an American.
Why is she here?
Why are you here?
Is it because Alice borrowed a password?
You heard the testimony
of Jennifer Cappelli.
Passwords are shared
all the time in Alice's office.
Is it because Alice downloaded data
from the National
Water Distribution Database?
66 other people downloaded
the same data last year.
Why is she here?
Why are you here?
Is it because Alice
exchanged scientific data
with a colleague from another country?
Jonas Jorgensen exchanged
the exact same data
in the exact same way.
He was rewarded.
She was arrested.
Why is she here?
Why are you here?
One of the great misunderstandings
of the American criminal justice system
is that it is a search for the truth.
It is not.
When the judge gives you his instructions
and you head back to that jury room,
you will not be asked
to return with the truth.
You will be asked only
to return with a verdict.
"Guilty" or "Not guilty."
Did the Government meet
its burden of proof or not?
I believe the evidence
is clear that it did not.
I believe the evidence is clear
that Alice Huang is not guilty.
But the truth also matters here.
So let's tell the truth.
The truth is, she is here,
you are here, we are all here,
because she is not from here.
That is why we are here.
That is the dark truth.
And what you do...
here, now...
that will either be
a light out of this darkness...
or this is where we will stay.
Hey.
The indictment against
Principal Hatcher. Just filed.
Excellent!
I don't have to defend her, do I?
Unlikely.
But if you did, she'd be in good hands.
- That sounded like a...
- I always thought you'd be
a good lawyer if you tried.
You're trying.
There's something about the way you talk
that makes me feel bad inside.
And yet, I like it, too.
I guess... that's just honesty.
I understand you've reached
a unanimous verdict.
- Is that correct?
- Yes, Your Honor.
In the case of
United States vs. Alice Huang,
we the jury find the defendant,
Alice Huang,
not guilty of espionage
against the United States.
I told you you were gonna win.
I told you.
You never told me that.
Well, I thought it.
What are you still doing here?
Come on!
I didn't win.
That's a win. Trust me.
Fayed.
No.
Not that.
You still might.
I should've done better. More.
This proves that.
If I could do it over again...
If you could do it over, Sandra,
you would probably lose again.
Because this job is hard,
and you need to find a way
to give yourself a break.
This relentlessness, this intensity,
this quest for perfection...
it is what will make you truly great,
but it can also break you.
Do not let it break you.
Okay.
Listen. I've been doing
a lot of research about Texas,
and here is what I know about Texas.
First, you will have to live in Austin.
- Everybody loves Austin.
- Precisely my point.
It's one of the fastest-growing
cities in America.
- Is that a positive?
- It's exhausting.
People in Austin spend more time
waiting in line for food
- than any other city in America.
- You're insane.
Well, maybe I should
move to Austin, then,
where thousands of insane people
stand on a bridge
waiting for bats
to fly out at dusk every night.
Now, look, I like animals
as much as anyone. But bats?
Here is a list
of other things I know you hate
that you can expect a lot of in Austin.
100-degree days... Austin had 73 in 2011.
No pro sports.
Very few black people.
Cricket swarms.
The never-changing reality
that it is surrounded by Texas.
Also, the worst cities
are the ones that also double
as people's first names.
Think about it.
Seven presidents have come from New York.
Three from Texas.
You'd be much better off
starting your political career here.
Listen, you've always trusted me
to help you weigh decisions,
to guide you,
give you cold analytical...
analysis.
And... you should stay.
There is one more thing on this list.
The truth is, this...
could have been the entire list.
I will miss you...
so much.
I already said yes.
To the job.
- If I had known...
- No.
No.
It's a good decision.
It makes sense.
You can... forget all this.
Will you stay?
We never really made a tradition
out of Hand Pulled Noodle House #3.
I have to go.
Don't tell me you love me.
I don't.
Good.
You do look fine, though.
I will say that.
Sorry, it's just...
I could really use someone to talk to.
It's okay.
Allison?
Yeah.
Oh.
I, uh...
I understand.
Have you seen "Rocky IV"?
- No.
- It's the best one.
Okay. Sure.
You okay?
You are worthy.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com