I think I'm losing my mind.
Hello, Shadow.
There are bigger sacrifices
one might be asked to make
than going a little mad.
What's in Chicago?
The hammer.
If I lose, I will go with
Wōtan and do what he ask...
And if you win?
I get to knock your brains
out with my hammer.
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Right there.
Okay.
Mmm.
Mmm. Perfect.
It's too good for them.
Eight grandchildren,
each one smart as a table.
Assaf with his music.
He sounds like you. Yeah.
No, it's too early
to fry the onions.
Assaf likes them crisp.
No, no, it's not perfect.
More cinnamon.
Assaf? I told you
no come before 5!
And no more bringing me
your laundry!
I tell you I am done
being your maid--
You are in wrong floor.
Black people family is upstairs.
No mistake.
You are to come with me,
Mrs. Fadil.
You have died, Mrs. Fadil.
And it is time for you
to come with me.
I have company soon.
If you are here to rob,
then rob.
There is a television,
and I-- I have a phone
my grandson says
is also a camera.
I wish I was but a thief.
I am not.
I am of Death.
You are dead, Mrs. Fadil.
- That is me?
- That is you.
Your family will come soon
and find you.
They will do right by your body
and bury you as is proper.
They will be sad for a time,
then they will find
happiness again.
Your Assaf will marry in a year
and name his first daughter
for you.
A bullshit middle name?
A bullshit middle name.
This is how they will find me?
This is a Muslim home.
Why does Anubis hold out
his hand for me?
It is my thanks.
You were once a girl
with your own Tita.
Who taught you
the ways of Egypt old,
of when the Nile
was full and flooding.
She told you stories
of the Wolf and the Jackal,
the Red Wind,
and of the Child of Bast.
- I remember.
- You do.
For that,
I bring you to the Scales.
Come.
My family will find me.
They will not try it.
You taste.
It is perfect.
Sixty-eight years.
It's not much for America,
but... more than my Tita
ever prayed for.
Come.
This is not Queens.
I was using that.
We shall see
if you have used it well.
I was unkind
to the first boy who loved me.
I stole a doll once
from my cousin.
I-- I tried...
my best.
Your best is good.
Each will take you to the Du'at.
The Du'at has many worlds.
Choose.
Which has my father?
He beat me,
and I would like not
to see his world.
Choose.
You are a kind boy.
You choose for me?
Are you sure I do this with you?
Follow the wrong god,
I do not see my Tita again.
Careful!
The Buffalo is waning tonight.
You're Zorya Poluch... ch...
the sister that was sleeping.
I am Zorya Polunochnyaya, yes.
And you are called Shadow.
What are you
looking at up there?
I was looking at that.
See?
The Big Dipper?
Odin's Wain, they call it.
And the Great Bear.
It is a thing.
It's not a god.
Like a god.
It's a bad thing.
Chained up in those stars.
If it escapes, it will eat
the whole of everything.
So we watch the sky...
all day, all night,
the three sisters.
If he escapes,
the thing in the stars,
the world is over.
Like that.
And people believe that?
A long time ago.
You're not cold?
Cold doesn't bother me.
This time is my time.
My sisters,
they're of their times.
When is your time?
Your birthday?
No, I-- I don't want
my fortune told.
My fortunes are the best.
Virgins have the advantage.
And now we have something.
Oh.
No.
You have nothing.
You believe in nothing
so you have nothing.
You are on a path...
from nothing to everything.
You had something recently.
You lost it.
- My-- my wife.
- Not your wife.
Did you sell your head
to Czernobog?
Yeah.
You keep giving away your life.
You don't much care
if you live or die, do you?
The world's not
what I thought it would be.
You'd rather die
than live in a world
with bears in the sky.
I can help you.
- First, you must do something for me.
- What is it?
Gotta fight you?
Play checkers?
You have to kiss me.
I have not ever been kissed.
I don't know if I like it.
We do this now.
I--
Kissing is disgusting...
but-- but in a nice way,
like, uh, bleu cheese or brandy.
Take the moon.
What?
Just take it.
Here.
Don't lose this.
Don't give it away.
You've been given
protection once.
You had the sun itself.
I can give you the moon.
It's the daughter,
not the father.
Now...
you wake up.
Is not sunrise yet.
Enjoy your time.
How about another game?
Same terms.
How can be same?
You want me to kill you twice?
Right now you only have
one blow.
One is all it takes.
That is...
the art.
How long has it been...
since you last swung a killing
hammer in the stockyards, though?
It's gotta be, like,
what, twenty years?
Thirty?
I think you got used
to the bolt gun.
I think you got weak, and I don't
think you can kill me with one shot.
You could just leave me
brain damaged,
a drooling piss bag reminder
that you got old.
That's not gonna do
either of us any good, is it?
If you're gonna
smash my brains in,
I'd rather you finish the job.
I win, you come with me
and Mister Wednesday,
you'll still take your shot
when we're through.
But you win...
come sunrise,
you'll take your second swing,
if you need it.
No one needs to know but me.
Okay. Another game.
You are light, I'm dark.
Enough visiting.
Go to bed.
I'm trying to.
You deserve better than this.
You no like it,
you sleep on floor.
Is good enough for me.
You only learned
to live with less.
There is food, there is roof.
What more do you need?
A court to adore you.
In the old country,
you were draped with pearl,
loved, feared, waited upon.
Excess suits you.
Things will be better
again soon enough.
Ah.
Your turn.
Mm-hmm.
Bye-bye.
In old country,
I opened the gate
for my father at dusk
when he returned to us,
then climb into
black satin sheet.
Here, I tell pretty fortune
for dollars.
Now, you've never told me mine.
This thing you want to do.
You will fail.
And they will win.
That's only my fortune today.
Come. Walk with me, hmm?
It will rain now.
Boy, will it ever.
Since when were you afraid of
getting a little wet, hmm?
You're playing
the same game, old man.
Only get to fool me once.
Shut your mouth.
Still so beautiful.
I thought I told
the pretty lies.
You want fortune
or you want truth.
Oh, I want knowledge
over comfort,
over all things, always.
They will kill you this time.
Ahh...
Do you remember
when we were young?
Barely.
Well, let me remind you.
What have you done?
I can taste you on the rain.
What else can I taste?
War.
All right.
I'll go with Wōtan
to his Wisconsin.
Then I'm gonna kill you.
Is good?
Is good.
Oh, you're up.
This is good.
- Storm died.
- No, it hasn't.
We're gonna rob a bank.
You want some coffee?
You best be getting on, son.
Jack's Crocodile will take
a bite outta you.
You won't shoot.
You'll try,
but the gun will jam,
or worse it'll backfire
and you'll lose two fingers.
Don't push your luck.
♪ ...special on my mind ♪
Hey, there.
You look like you've
seen better days, friend.
- You okay there?
- I am not.
- Where you headed?
- Wisconsin.
Take you as far
as Madison. Get in.
- You a rapist?
- No.
- Murderer?
- Not recently. You?
I got seats that tip back
if you want a good sleep.
♪ Something tells me
I'm into.. ♪
Eleven years sober,
but I remember being
on your side of the highway.
♪ We only danced for
a minute or two ♪
♪ But then she stuck close to
me the whole night through ♪
♪ Can I be fallin' in love? ♪
I'm not a drunk.
Okay.
Got a sack of cranberries
on the floor.
♪... and she held my hand ♪
♪ I knew it couldn't be
just a one-night stand ♪
Don't try to touch my knob.
Not my style, friend...
and not my type.
But when you wake up,
I might extol
- the virtues of the program.
- Yeah, you do that.
♪ ...I'm into something good ♪
♪ Something tells me
I'm into something good ♪
Ah, that's some crazy bad luck.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck.
Watch it!
It's 11:35.
My appointment was for 11.
Mr. Blanding knows
you're here.
Excuse me.
Can you perhaps
call Mr. Blanding
and tell him I am still waiting?
He's at lunch.
When will he be back?
He won't be coming back.
Excuse?
Mr. Blanding.
He won't be coming back today.
Can I make an appointment
for tomorrow?
You have to telephone.
Appointments only by telephone.
I see.
Why are you smiling?
A salesman is naked
in America without a smile.
Tomorrow I will telephone.
Peak Hotel, please.
Fuck! Fuck! Shit! Fuck!
Been driving this Allah-forsaken
taxi for 30 hours.
It's too much.
I spent the day
waiting to see a man
who will not see me.
My brother-in-law hates me.
I have been in America
for a week, and it
has done nothing
but eat my money.
I sell nothing.
Hmm.
What do you sell?
Worthless gew-gaws
and baubles
and tourist trinkets.
It's horrible, cheap,
foolish, ugly shit.
- You try and sell shit.
- I sell shit, yeah.
And they will not buy it?
- No.
- Eh, strange.
'Cause when you look in the stores
here, that's all they sell.
Shit.
Take Eighth Avenue.
We'll go uptown that way.
My grandmother...
once swore that
she had seen an ifrit,
or perhaps a marid,
late one evening,
on the edge of the desert.
We all told her that it was
just a sandstorm,
a little wind,
but she had seen its face.
And its eyes, like yours,
were burning flames.
Grandmothers came here, too.
Are there many jinn in New York?
No.
There are angels,
there are men
who Allah made from mud.
Then there are
the people of the fire,
the jinn.
They know nothing
about my people here.
They think all we do
is grant wishes.
If I could grant a wish, do you
think I would be driving a cab?
Once I had a man shit
in the back seat.
I had to clean wet shit
from that seat.
Tell me, is that right?
That's not right.
Keep the change.
I'm in room 318.
Going to 76th and Madison.
I wish you can see what I see.
I do not grant wishes.
But you do.
This is the bank
I'll be robbing,
so let's go say hello.
Are you outta your goddamn mind?
Have a little faith, son.
Hell, no.
Well, how about faith
in a higher power
wanting me to succeed?
Fuck, no.
Oh, fuck, yes.
You're my bodyguard, huh?
That means you guard my body.
Is that not right?
Not when you're robbing a bank.
At the moment,
my body is going to the bank.
It's not robbing it.
Come on, learn.
It'll be fun.
All right, look.
We had a compact or whatever
the fuck you called it.
Okay? I'm not doing
anything illegal.
Oh, you're not.
Well, apart from maybe
a little aiding and abetting,
and, of course,
receiving stolen money.
I'll tell you what,
at the end of this,
you're gonna come out
smelling like a rose.
Fuck.
Excuse me. Could you tell me where
the deposit slips are, please?
Right out the front door
on the wall.
And if I needed to make
an overnight deposit?
- Same forms.
- Oh, thank you.
Oh, you do not look happy.
I am five days out of prison,
you're fixing to put me
back in by six.
Do not bleed before
you are wounded, huh?
Would you like me to
get you a hot chocolate?
Yeah, come on!
Let me buy you a hot cocoa.
Jot that number down.
Got you marshmallows
in your cocoa.
You like marshmallows?
Why are you talking to me
about marshmallows?
Like I'm worried
about marshmallows.
Yeah, I like marshmallows.
What we need is snow.
Hard, driving, irritating snow.
I want you to think "snow."
Think "snow."
- Snow?
- Snow.
Yeah, snow.
See those clouds
over there to the west?
Concentrate on making
those bigger, darker.
Think about dark skies
and driving winds
coming down from the Arctic.
- Think "snow."
- Okay.
- And how's this gonna help?
- Might not do anything.
But at least it will
concentrate your mind.
Snow, snow.
Snow.
We're here.
Well, I'm here.
You're somewhere else.
Just thinking about snow.
That woman thinks Jesus
suffered for her sins.
They're her sins.
Why should Jesus do
all the suffering?
'Cause his dad sacrificed
his ass.
Don't blame the parent.
Plenty of suffering
and blame to go around,
although that White Jesus, well,
could stand
a little more suffering.
He's doing very well
for himself these days.
And how many colors
does Jesus come in?
Why, you got your
White Jesuit-style Jesus.
You got your
Black African Jesus.
Brown Mexican Jesus.
You got your swarthy Greek Jesus.
You've got--
Well, that's a--
That's a lotta Jesus.
There's a lotta need for Jesus,
so there's a lotta Jesus.
Now, the Mexican Jesus came here
the same way
a lot of Mexicans do.
- Illegally.
- Oh--
No, that's not being racial.
You can ask Him.
He'll tell you.
He waded across the Rio Grande,
his back as wet
as the epithet suggests.
Next customer.
Good afternoon.
I want to insta-print a couple
of sets of business cards.
And I may need your assistance
with printing some posters.
Snow.
I think that's enough.
Enough what?
Snow.
Don't want to immobilize
the city.
- I thought of snow.
- And it snowed.
What do you know?
I love this place.
Food's not particularly good,
but the ambiance--
...unmissable.
Come on, eat up.
Can't rob a bank
on an empty stomach.
No, I'm not hungry.
Who says you have
to be hungry to eat?
Wasn't supposed to snow today.
Wasn't even supposed to be cold.
So, you're perfectly
okay believing
that tiny people on television
can predict the weather,
but you crinkle
with consternation
at the mere suggestion
that you could make it snow.
One of those things
is science, okay?
The other is fantasy.
You're talking about it
like it's apples and oranges.
It's not apples
and oranges, okay?
It's reality and fantasy.
Oh, so that's how
the world works!
It's either real
or it's fantasy?
Yeah, that's how
the world works.
Yeah, says the man
who hasn't seen it.
Shadow, at best, you suffer
from a failure of imagination.
We're gonna have to fix that.
Uh-oh, look what
the goat dragged in.
- Cat.
- Goat.
Big, rank, stinking goat.
Mad Sweeney, you look like a man
who's fallen on hard times
from a great height.
Thought I wasn't gonna see you
until Wisconsin.
I'll never make it to Wisconsin,
not with the current
state of my luck.
This cunt's got my coin.
Give me my coin, cunt.
- The coin you gave me?
- Witness. He has a point.
I gave you the wrong coin.
The one I gave you
was my lucky coin.
Well, you can't afford to be too
careless with a lucky coin.
Something like that,
you wanna hang on to.
Tell you what, I'll give you
your lucky coin back
when you tell me how you
plucked it out of thin air.
I plucked it outta thin air
is how I plucked it outta
thin air, ya bug-eatin' nonce.
Now give me my coin.
I threw it away.
Where did you throw it away?
Eagle Point, Indiana.
So, if you want your
lucky coin back,
make your way
to Parkview Cemetery.
There you will find
my wife's grave
with your coin on top.
Oh, you fucker.
Suppose I'll just be one more
in a long line of men
to climb on top
of your dead wife.
Be nice.
- I'll see you in Wisconsin.
- Yeah.
Good luck, Mad Sweeney.
I'll see you back at the car.
Just make sure
he doesn't steal it, huh?
Now, you're gonna do a little light
shopping at the grocery store.
Pass a little time
at the phone booth.
If anybody asks you
what you're doing,
well, you're waiting for
a call from your girlfriend.
Her car broke down.
Here.
- Who the fuck is this?
- You the fuck is this.
"A. Haddock, Director of
Security, A1 Security Services."
Yeah, that's you.
But what's the "A" stand for?
Alberto? Alphonse? Augustine?
Ambrose?
It's entirely up to you.
"Asshole" is what I feel like.
Nice to meet you, Asshole.
I'm James O'Gorman.
Jimmy to my friends.
I got a card, too.
Okay. Let's get outta here.
I'm gonna leave you
with one question.
If at the end of this night
you do not end up in jail,
will you believe in me?
Don't answer that question.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck!
A1 Security Services.
Can I speak to A. Haddock?
Uh, this is Andy Haddock.
Mr. Haddock,
this is the Chicago Police.
You've got a man
at the First River Bank
on the corner
of Market and Second.
Uh... yeah.
That's-- That's right, Officer.
It-It should be James O'Gorman.
Is there a problem?
No problem, sir. Just wanted to
make sure everything's in order.
- Well, thank you.
- We're just concerned,
because something like this really
ought to be handled by two personnel.
Oh, tell me about yet.
B-Better yet,
you tell those stingy bastards
down at First River Bank about it.
I mean, these are my men
I'm putting on the line.
You know, they're good men.
You know,
you sound like a bright
young man, Officer...
- Myerson.
- Officer Myerson.
If you ever need
any extra weekend work,
you just give us a call.
You got my card?
Yes, sir.
Hang onto it.
You call us.
Yes, sir.
Have a good evening, sir.
So that's what you do
to make money.
You believe in me now?
I believe you exist.
Oh, I think I deserve a
little more faith than that.
Are you back in jail?
All that whining
about going back to jail,
and you haven't, have you?
Not yet.
This is the
only country in the world
that wonders what it is.
You've been to a lot of
other countries, have you?
No. No, never,
just this one.
Just that the others
know what they are.
I mean, no one wonders
about the heart of Norway
or goes searching
for the soul of Mozambique.
Mozambique knows what it is.
They all know what they are.
Americans know who they are.
They pretend they know.
But it's still just pretending,
like I'm pretending now.
Just like you.
What am I pretending?
You are pretending you cannot
believe in impossible things.
Uh, I'd be genuinely deluded
if I believed that shit.
If you are deluded,
I believe it's genuine.
You don't strike me as
the disingenuous type.
Okay, let's go.
Huh?
Did I make snow?
Did you make snow?
Well, if you choose
to believe you made snow,
then you get to live the rest
of your life believing
that you can do things
that are impossible.
Or you can believe
it's a delusion.
No, see, delusions
feel real, okay?
That's why it's a delusion.
None of this feels real.
It feels like a dream.
What a beautiful,
beautiful thing
to be able to dream
when you're not asleep.
I've-- I've crossed
enough paths
to know that one in four
people are rock stupid.
Even the smart ones have got some
kind of delusion they believe in,
whether it's gods or ghosts.
Do you believe in love?
Yeah, I believe the shit
out of love.
Did you always?
Not before Laura.
So you didn't believe
till you did,
and then the world changed
because you believed.
Belief is only a product
of the company we keep
and how easily we scare.
And you do not scare easily.
And my company is questionable.
Always has been.
The only thing that scares me
is being forgotten.
I can survive most things
but not that.
Very best part of memory is
it's mostly about forgetting.
We remember what's
important to us.
I wonder what'll be the first thing
that drifts through your mind
when you look back
on this evening?
Snow, I bet.
Room 55.
Hi, puppy.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
♪ I went down to
St. James infirmary ♪
♪ I heard my baby moan ♪
♪ And I felt so broken hearted ♪
♪ She used to be my ♪
♪ My very own ♪
♪ I went up to see
the doctor ♪
♪ She's very low, he said ♪
♪ I went back to see my baby ♪
♪ Good God, she's
lying there dead ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org