Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Fuck being bosses.
We gonna be kings, Tee.
Kings of the motherfuckin' D,
man.
[dramatic music plays]
- [gunshot]
- You need to leave
all this shit alone.
Just focus
on the business, Meech.
Taking care of the motherfucker
who popped my brother,
that is my business.
Ruffle his feathers,
nothing else.
Don't do me like this.
Don't, man.
- [gunshot]
- What the fuck you do that for?
[Lamar] Zoe, look, come back.
I just want to talk.
What do you want?
I want Zoe to know
that I'm her father.
Terry lying up in here
with a gunshot to his head
all because his brother
pulled him into this.
You need to let Meech go.
[groans]
You got to do whatever it is
that you got to do
to protect your shit,
'cause the vultures
and the wolves
are comin', nigga.
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
[electronic music plays]
[♪♪♪]
[sizzling]
Hey, are you making me
and Nicole a burger?
Ain't nothing wrong
with your hands.
Hold on.
[♪♪♪]
Oh, hell no.
Man, how you gonna
make yourself
a triple-meatloaf sandwich
and leave us enough
for a meatball?
Should have got up earlier.
I'm sick of your selfish ass.
You cuttin' that shit in half.
Man, move.
- What you doing, man?
- What's wrong with you, man?
Ah, shit!
You done fucked up now.
I'm about to kick your ass.
[♪♪♪]
[loud crashing]
Ooh, y'all gon' get it!
We gotta do something.
Why? Man, they still
gon' beat our ass.
Not if we Krazy Glue
everything back together.
[Older Meech]
Trust: it's the foundation
of all relationships.
All right, bro.
[Older Meech] You gotta trust
a person you're with
as much as you do yourself.
[Lucille] Which one of you
broke my damn china?
[Older Meech] Me and Tee
always trusted each other,
no matter what.
Moms ain't no dummy,
and just like I predicted,
she whupped our asses.
Told you to keep
your hands off the china!
[Older Meech]
But we stuck it out together.
And even the times
we did lose,
having him beside me
always cushioned the blow.
[R&B music playing on radio]
[♪♪♪]
[tires screech]
Fuck.
[music stops]
What the fuck is going on?
Something wrong
with your phone?
Oh, look, Pat.
I know we behind.
I'm disappointed in you, Meech.
[Meech] Come on, man.
You know I've been dealing
with Tee's shooting.
Rock, tell Wonder Boy here
what I call personal problems.
Excuses.
[Pat] And just like assholes,
everybody's got one.
[tense music plays]
[♪♪♪]
[breathing heavily]
[Pat] You paying
a-fuckin-ttention?
Yo, Pat, me and Tee ain't
never stiff you before, man.
Yeah, you ain't never been
behind like this either.
Listen, this your alarm clock.
If I don't get my loot
in six days,
this motherfucker gon' ring.
Six days?
And I'm taxin' your ass
ten points for being late.
Now get the fuck out my car.
[car door closes]
You know he ain't never
gonna climb out of this.
That's the point.
I keep my foot on their neck,
they stay where they are.
Under me.
[tense music plays]
[Charlie] ♪ I got everything
On the line ♪
♪ I'm out here
I'm on the grind ♪
♪ Trying to get mine ♪
♪ At least you could
Wish me luck ♪
♪ A nigga move the weight ♪
♪ Trying to get the cake ♪
♪ I'm in and out of state ♪
♪ At least you could
Wish me luck ♪
♪ Too many niggas fake ♪
♪ It's hard to tell a snake ♪
♪ One more flip
And I'm straight ♪
♪ At least you could
Wish me luck ♪
♪ I don't go hand to hand ♪
♪ It go gram after gram ♪
♪ Yeah, holla at me, man ♪
♪ At least you could
Wish me luck ♪
♪ Too many niggas fake ♪
♪ It's hard to tell a snake ♪
♪ One more flip
And I'm straight ♪
♪ At least you could
Wish me luck ♪
[50 Cent]
♪ The D's ain't that good ♪
♪ These niggas is ratting ♪
♪ They tell them
What's going on ♪
♪ That's how they know
What's happening ♪
♪ I'm riding
With the top down ♪
♪ Trunk full of yola ♪
♪ Ghetto pharmaceutical ♪
♪ I move that Coca-Cola ♪
♪ Thousand grams of pure ♪
♪ Though I fuck
With the weirdos ♪
♪ They snort away the pain ♪
♪ Bang their dope
In their vein ♪
♪ Shorty crying
Christmas ain't coming ♪
♪ Her pop's locked up ♪
♪ When it hurts the worst ♪
♪ Your ace find out
She knocked up ♪
♪ Welfare ain't an option ♪
♪ When the Feds
Come knocking ♪
♪ It's all fucked up
So wish me luck ♪
[Charlie] ♪ At least
You could wish me luck ♪
♪ A nigga move the weight ♪
♪ Trying to get the cake ♪
♪ I'm in and out of state ♪
♪ At least you could
Wish me luck ♪
♪ Too many niggas fake ♪
♪ It's hard to tell a snake ♪
♪ One more flip
And I'm straight ♪
♪ At least you could
Wish me luck ♪
♪ I don't go hand to hand ♪
♪ It go gram after gram ♪
♪ Yeah, holla at me, man ♪
♪ At least you could
Wish me luck ♪
♪ Too many niggas fake ♪
♪ It's hard to tell a snake ♪
♪ One more flip
And I'm straight ♪
♪ At least you could
Wish me luck ♪
♪ Wish me luck ♪
♪ At least you could
Wish me luck ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, wish me luck ♪
♪ Wish me luck ♪
♪ All you got to do
Is wish me luck, yeah ♪
[hip-hop music plays]
[Lucille] Thank you so much
for taking time
out of your busy schedule
to come and pray with us.
[man]
A family that prays together
stays together, sister.
It's always my pleasure.
Shall we pray?
Boy, you can't pray
with that boy in your hand
in your condition.
Nah, Mama, I'm fine.
I told y'all I'm ready for
things to get back to normal.
Fine or not, you still gotta
stay in the house
for the next few days,
doctor's orders.
Yes, sir.
Matthew 18:20 says,
"God is present
whenever two or more
are gathered in his name."
[Lucille] Yes, Father. Yes.
- Yes.
- Bow your heads.
[Lucille] Mm.
[pastor] Dear heavenly father,
we love you.
We come to you asking
that you bless this oil.
Cleanse it of all
of its impurities, Father.
- [Lucille] Mm.
- [pastor] O Father God,
we ask that You bless
Brother Terry...
[Lucille] Yes.
[pastor]
...so he can see clearly
that you would have him do
the work for Your glory.
[Lucille] Yes, Lord.
[pastor] And this we pray
in the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
- Mm-hmm.
- [Terry] Amen.
[Lucille] Amen, amen, amen.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Pastor.
I fixed that railing
at the church.
I'm willing to walk you out
any time.
Brother, God
has smiled on y'all.
Brother Terry, he survived,
spirit is right,
and he's doing a lot better.
Well, his eye got
a little worse
after the second surgery.
What did the doctor say?
He flopped like a wet suit.
They're doing
the best they can.
[pastor] Hmm.
Mistakes, that's human.
But it'd be a sin
if your son lost his sight
due to negligence.
My niece Karen, she just
graduated from U of M Law.
And she'd be happy
to take a look at your case
on a contingency basis,
meaning...
I know what contingency means,
Pastor.
[pastor] Brother Meech!
- Pastor Swift!
- [Swift] Praise the Lord.
[Meech] Praise the Lord.
How you doing?
What you doing here?
[baby fussing]
Came to check on Terry.
Okay, but let me see
them keys first.
See, now you can knock
like everybody else
that don't live here.
Mmm. Is it me,
or is the Lord in the kitchen
cooking up some of that bacon?
Smell like the Upper Room
up in here, sister.
[laughs] Come on, Pastor.
Let me make you a plate,
all right.
Thank you, sister.
And thank God
for this breakfast
we about to partake in.
[hip-hop music plays]
[♪♪♪]
[singer] ♪ Yo, yo, yo ♪
♪ Makin' a livin'
Off little giving ♪
♪ Talented, charismatic,
And also a little driven... ♪
Yo, yo. Why you lettin'
the fuckin' smoke out, man?
Close the door.
What the fuck is on your mind?
Maybe we should start
splitting profit 50/50.
I shed my own blood
for this shit.
Nigga, we got bigger fish
to fry, a'ight?
Pat just gave us six days
to pay him back,
and he taxing us 10%.
Six days?
How the fuck we gonna do that
when we only pulling 30
off the rec center?
Guess we gotta hustle
around the clock.
But, yo, there was this article
that dropped at the Free Press
about all that drug use
at these plants.
Now, them factory niggas,
they ain't scraping
for dubs, dimes, and nicks.
They want that high quality
A1 shit that we got.
[Meech] So you on
that factory shit again?
Ain't the worst idea
I've heard.
I'ma put B-Mickie on it.
Speakin' of that nigga,
what up with him?
He ain't even come holla
at me at the 'spital.
He's straight...
just like yo' ass need to be.
Now you need to go home
and get some rest, man,
so you can ease back
into this shit, a'ight?
I'm gonna catch you later.
I'm out.
All right, then.
[hip-hop music plays]
[♪♪♪]
Jay-Mo missing.
Filmel got beat
to a inch of his life.
[♪♪♪]
We at war.
The 50 Boyz got somethin'
to do with this.
I say we go head-up
at Meech and Terry.
Nah, them piss-colored-ass
niggas, man,
they already dead.
I don't want to just hang 'em
by their rat tails, man.
I wanna take 'em
for everything they got
once they pockets is full.
Shit, I'm always down
to make some more paper.
'Cause first, you gotta cripple
their business,
then you take over.
As they're struggling
for breath, nigga,
you snap their fuckin' necks.
How the hell
we gonna do all that?
Ah, don't be questioning shit,
young blood.
Lamar been running
these streets
since y'all lil' niggas
was in your daddy's nut sack
trying to find a way
to the promised land.
You feel me?
So I guess you want us
to fall back
while old school
work his magic?
Damn right.
Maybe for the sake
of being in step.
But we only doing this
'til Filmel get back.
[singer] ♪ That's why every day
I'm getting hella paid ♪
♪ So every day I elevate ♪
[♪♪♪]
[man] I'm waiting for the war
man, for real.
♪ So every day I elevate ♪
[♪♪♪]
I guess you chief rocka now,
huh?
[♪♪♪]
[singer]
♪ So every day I elevate ♪
[baby fussing]
You put them drops
in your eyes, boy?
Yes, sir.
[Charles] What now?
We out of time with the bank.
Look, I'm doing the best I can.
This is not a problem
that can be fixed
by adding a extra shift
here or there, babe.
[doorbell ringing]
[Charles] Who's that?
[Bryant] Okay, Terry,
now that you've had
a chance to recuperate,
can you remember
anything that happened
on the day you got shot?
No, not really.
Still kind of a blank.
What about the person
who shot you,
like what they were wearing
or maybe something they said?
You were seen arriving
at the hospital
in a black Mercedes-Benz
with the windows shattered.
Whose car is that?
Teens don't usually get shot
in luxury cars at close range
unless they're
in the drug game.
I asked you a question, boy.
It's mine.
My Uncle Troy got it for me
as a baby shower gift.
Does Uncle Troy
have a last name?
My son is a stellar student
and a young father
who is the victim
of a violent crime.
Why are you talking to him
like he's a suspect?
I'm sorry, Mrs. Flenory.
We are all
on the same team here.
It's just
that the fact-finding process
can get a little sticky.
I understand that,
but as far as I'm concerned,
this interview is over.
[door slams]
You wanna tell me
what that was back there?
Mama bear protecting her cub.
I'm talking about you.
Me? What? Okay, here's an idea.
Why don't you say
what's on your mind
instead of acting like this
your first day out the academy?
You barely pressed that kid
about who shot him
when the whole thing
looks retaliatory.
And that bullshit
the girlfriend tried
to sell us about the Benz?
Come on.
The boy was scared.
He's not gonna talk
if he doesn't feel comfortable.
That's interrogation 101.
What is it about
the Flenory boys
that has you acting
like some kind of priest?
Look, motherfucker,
I was working patrol
while you were still figuring
out how to aim for the toilet.
Insult my integrity again,
I'ma beat you
like you stole somethin'.
Now get in the fuckin' car.
[hip-hop music plays]
[singer]
♪ Clockin' This money ♪
♪ You know, what, uh-huh ♪
♪ You-you want it? I got it ♪
♪ Then come get it ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey
You want it? I got it ♪
♪ Then come get it ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ You want it? I got it ♪
♪ Then come get it ♪
[Kato]
It's slow as shit out here.
[B-Mickie] Look, getting
a new spot to pop
is like hopping
on a new horse, a'ight?
You gotta break 'em in
slow and easy.
You got one rule
for all horses?
What if you get a stallion?
Shit.
The wilder, the better, right?
[both chuckle]
Yo, you goin' to Terry's
surprise party?
Mm, I don't know.
I don't really do bowling.
Oh, come on.
I was looking forward to seeing
you in that bowling shirt.
Bet you got your own shoes
and balls and all that shit.
Nah, but I can knock down
all them pins, though.
[security guard] Hey.
Y'all have been here
for over an hour.
And I already told you,
no loitering.
Yo, this is
a public street corner.
Listen.
You might not dress the part,
but there's only one reason
a girl like you stands
on a block like this,
so you and your pimp
need to get moving.
Yo, did you just call her a ho?
If the corner fits.
Nigga, I will fuck you up.
Keep playing with me.
Yo, B. Come on. We don't need...
If y'all are still here
when I get back,
I'm calling the police.
[♪♪♪]
[singer]
♪ I said hold my paper ♪
♪ Got all my... waiter ♪
♪ You want it? I got it ♪
♪ Then come get it ♪
[soft R&B music plays]
[♪♪♪]
Take these, and...
Why don't you just build
on your own property?
Because you got
the best corners.
Look, how about this?
Um, we'll do a deal.
I'll even throw a railroad
in the pot.
Hmm?
Mm, no.
- [Lamar] No?
- Give-give me.
- [Lamar] No, no.
- Give me.
No, no.
You can't... you can't have it.
Come on, Zoe.
It's time for you to do
your homework.
Are you gonna come to
the tennis practice tomorrow?
Stop stalling
and give him a hug.
[♪♪♪]
Mm...
Bye, Dad.
You hear what
she just called me?
[pager beeping]
You need to take that call?
I didn't even know Zoe
was into tennis like that.
[Monique] Yeah, she took it up
a few months ago.
Her guidance counselor said
that he thought
it was a good idea
to keep her mind right.
Well, she any good?
Lamar, what are you doing?
I'm just trying to get to know
my daughter better.
I mean, it was cool
you came to see Zoe,
but if you gonna be
coming around on the regular,
I'ma need to know
you gon' be here.
That's not gonna be a problem.
[Monique] I mean, 'cause what
if you get sent away again?
You don't need
to break her heart twice.
Monique... I promise you,
I ain't gonna let anybody
hurt you or Zoe.
And I ain't going nowhere.
My place
is right here with y'all.
[♪♪♪]
[Meech] Y'all ain't sold
a single bag yet?
Man, the robo-cop's
been rolling all day.
Did y'all at least try to find
a store to post up in?
[B-Mickie] Do you see
any stores around here?
Why am I just now hearing
about this,
given how pressed we are?
[B-Mickie]
I'm not finna alert you
every time the wind changes,
a'ight?
I'ma handle shit.
Obviously, you not, nigga,
blowing a whole fuckin' day.
[tense music plays]
[♪♪♪]
[tires squealing]
[factory horn blares]
[♪♪♪]
[mellow hip-hop music plays]
Hey, my man.
You ain't going to the factory?
I'm not paying $500
for a permit
to get on that damn lot.
What'd you say your name
was again?
David, but everybody
call me Fonzo.
[♪♪♪]
- [phone ringing]
- [indistinct chatter]
James Williams' mom hasn't seen
or heard from him in days.
Who the hell is that?
Street name is Jay-Mo.
Leader of 12th Street,
and you don't know him?
Boy, that's weird,
considering you've been
running this roost since, uh...
you said something like...
"Since I was learning to hold
my dick and take a piss."
I don't know this kid.
Yeah, well, Jay-Mo
just happens to be
the Flenorys' biggest rival.
You two, in the war room, now.
I reviewed the Flenory file.
You make this about
your own personal fiefdom,
hoarding intel and witnesses.
Oh, it's not your fault.
It's the walls,
it's the institution,
how you were trained.
All that ends right now.
Detectives Bryant, Lopez,
this is Commander
Marceline Beckwith,
Michigan State Police.
She's your new division head.
Every one of our drug cases,
including the Flenory file,
it goes through her now.
[Marceline] Good evening,
detectives.
What Captain Ward means
is that the state police
has initiated
the Downriver Area
Narcotics Operation,
which we're calling DRANO.
Ecorse PD will be joining me
and officers
from local jurisdictions
to ID and dismantle
drug organizations in the area.
But we're making progress
on our own.
Don't wanna to get
a mixed metaphor,
but we're still in the weeds.
This will give us
a bird's-eye view,
help us connect the dots.
For the next 18 months,
you will have more resources,
more reach, and more respect
than you ever dreamed of.
And you'll still be taking out
bad guys from your old cases.
What is not to love?
Not a goddamn thing.
Welcome to the team, gentlemen.
[dramatic music plays]
[♪♪♪]
[Older Meech]
I'm a history buff,
so let me put y'all up
on game.
After the '67 riots,
white folks fled the city
for the 'burbs,
making the D "Chocolate City."
In 1973, Detroiters elected
their first Black mayor,
Coleman Young.
I issue open warnings now
to all dope pushers,
to all rip-off artists.
It's time to leave Detroit,
hit 8 Mile Road.
And I don't give a damn
if they're Black or white,
if they wear Superfly suits
or blue uniforms
with silver badges.
Hit the road.
[Older Meech] So in the '80s,
when the State Boys
joined the drug fight,
Mayor Young wouldn't let them
patrol inside city limits.
So the state
did the next best thing,
they united law enforcement
agencies all around the city.
Remember, Detroit
was the murder capital
of the world in '85 and '86,
right when me and Tee
jumped in the game.
Even though we from the D,
we started off
making our money
in River Rouge, Ecorse,
and all the other
Downriver communities.
That put us directly
in the crosshairs of DRANO.
[upbeat music plays]
[♪♪♪]
Hey, this shit
is a roach coach for real.
Hey, watch your mouth.
Tell me what
the hell y'all want,
'cause I know that damn permit
ain't come for free.
[Meech] Say yes
to us using your truck...
...and you gonna get
this same stack every week.
[♪♪♪]
What y'all selling?
Rocks.
- [Fonzo] Ain't interested.
- Shit.
Guess you won't be needing
this permit then.
Hey, what'd you say your name
was again?
Friends call me Fonzo.
You can call me David.
All right, Fonzo.
Why the fuck are you cooking
out of this roach coach?
Call my truck that again.
- [Meech] Chill out.
- No, no, no. Go ahead.
Look, we ain't trying
to disrespect you
or your livelihood, a'ight?
We're really just
trying to help you.
By selling drugs outta my truck?
[Terry] Obviously, you like
to cook, right,
but you just don't got
the resources to do it.
[Meech] Look, my brother and I
used to cut out pictures
of everything we wanted.
Cars, shoes, chains, anything,
and then we used to talk
and dream about those things
until they actually became
our reality.
So I'm asking you, Fonz,
what you want
your reality to be?
[♪♪♪]
I mean, I do own
my own restaurant.
Yo, you gonna be making
so much money,
you can open
your own shit downtown
instead of working out of a...
out of a tightly
confined space like this.
Damn.
All right.
But on one condition.
[Terry] What's up?
You gonna have to apologize
for insulting my truck.
[♪♪♪]
Fuck you, nigga.
That's close enough.
[siren wailing]
[monitor beeping]
[indistinct chatter]
[uneasy music plays]
[♪♪♪]
Peek-a-boo.
[muffled screaming] Help! Help!
Nurse! Help!
Help!
[breathing heavily]
[groans]
[♪♪♪]
Crew do miss you, man.
I can't say I feel the same.
But it does pose
one question, though.
[♪♪♪]
What are you gonna do
when you get out of here?
Please, leave me
the fuck alone.
[Lamar] A'ight.
You know, America
is a beautiful country.
It'll be a shame if you didn't
get to see all of it.
[♪♪♪]
What you say, Filmel?
[Filmel groaning]
When the doctors let you go,
how about...
you get in that
janky-ass car of yours
and you take a road trip
for the rest
of your fuckin' life, huh?
- [groans]
- Huh?
You gonna take
that trip, right?
Nigga, I said you gonna take
- [screaming]
- Hmm?
[groaning]
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Good boy.
[♪♪♪]
Friends do a lot of things.
But a sponge bath
ain't one of 'em.
[♪♪♪]
[siren wails in distance]
[indistinct chatter]
[emcee] Come on, gentlemen.
Let's show our ladies
how much you love 'em.
[indistinct chatter]
Guys, who's ready
to give you a lap dance?
[upbeat music plays]
Destiny to the main stage.
[Meech] Damn, girl.
Keep doing that shit.
I need a favor, though.
Cool, but... I'ma need
some more money.
That ain't nothing. Don't trip.
I got you.
[emcee] Come on, gentlemen.
Reach into those pockets.
Don't be cheap.
These ladies are beautiful.
Show 'em your love.
[dancer]
Well, then I got you too, boo.
[♪♪♪]
[emcee] And joining
onstage now...
[Terry] What the fuck
are we doing here?
- [emcee] Poundcake.
- [Terry] Hey.
[emcee] Show her some love,
fellas.
Show her some love.
[laughter]
How the hell you plan
on getting out of this hole
when you blowing all this
damn cheese on this bitch?
Man, you gotta spend money
to make money, Tee.
Damn, you see
them factory dudes in here?
They come in here after work,
like to blow steam
off their backs, you know,
make more bang for their buck,
cheaper shots,
and longer lap dances, nigga.
A'ight, I tipped baby girl
to let us know
which factory dudes in here
like to smoke and get high.
[Pat] I guess y'all
ain't trying to get
my paper back for real, huh?
Y'all blowing my shit up
in this raggedy-ass titty spot.
Y'all could have at least
went to TJ's
or the Black Orchid
with my shit.
Y'all got time to fuck off?
Cool.
I'm moving y'all delivery date
up a day.
[Meech] Come on, man.
You can't do that shit.
I can do whatever the fuck
I want to.
I'm God. Remember?
It's good to see you
on your feet, Tee.
Maybe you can get
your brother back on track.
I don't know, but y'all got
three days, straight up.
Wasting my motherfuckin' time
in this stinkin'-ass spot.
Go get my scratch.
[♪♪♪]
Where the fuck did he
just come from?
Hey, I don't fuckin' know, man.
Nigga been hawkin' us
for days, man.
[Terry] Let's stop fuckin'
around with his money
and get him paid.
Motherfucker,
are you listening?
Yeah. Give me a minute.
[singer]
♪ When I walk in the club ♪
♪ They know my name ♪
♪ This is my city ♪
♪ This is my fame ♪
♪ This is my clout
This is my dope ♪
♪ Got that fam
Knockin' at my door ♪
♪ I'm settin' up shop
Gon' play at the table ♪
♪ You got my money... ♪
Damn, I think
the thick one's into you.
Do I know you?
No, but you should.
Man, I heard you like
to have a good time.
I got some party favors that'll
blow your fuckin' mind, dawg.
That's for you right there.
That's on the house.
Yeah.
If you diggin' it,
spread the word.
Let everybody know at work.
Tomorrow, you can find me
by the food trucks.
All right. Good lookin' out.
Already know, so...
[♪♪♪]
- [car alarm blaring]
- [dog barking]
- [baby fussing]
- [Charles] Hey!
Hey, hey. There he is.
My grandson.
How you doing, Lawanda?
Let me hold the little man.
I'm good. I'm good. Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
Get any sleep?
No. [chuckles]
He be keeping me up all night.
That sounds about right.
I used to put Demetrius
and Terry in the car.
Something about rollin' around
with them put 'em right to sleep.
You should try it.
I mean, who can't fall asleep
in a Mercedes, right?
[laughs]
Here, let me grab him
back really quick.
Oh, yeah.
Been meaning to ask you
about your uh, your uncle,
the one that bought you
the car.
Oh, yeah. Uncle Troy.
Yeah. He from around here?
No, he lives in Pontiac.
[Charles]
Oh, out by the Silverdome, huh?
Yep.
You know, the only time
I get to see him
is when we go
to a Pistons or a Lions game,
which is why
he bought me the car,
so we could take little TJ
to see him more often.
Hey, what's going on?
[Charles]
Just catching up with Lawanda.
She was telling me
about her uncle,
the one who lives out by the...
Oh, by the Silverdome.
Troy, right?
Yeah.
I'd love to meet him sometime.
Where you been, boy?
Ain't you supposed to be
sitting around the house
all day?
Uh, Terry Jr. needed
some baby formula.
Yeah, and they were
actually out,
and my head started throbbing.
So I came back to see
if Lawanda could go.
All right, y'all take it easy.
[hip-hop music plays]
[♪♪♪]
[singer] ♪ Yo, yo, yo ♪
Oh, shit.
[singer] ♪ Talented
Charismatic ♪
♪ And also a little driven ♪
♪ Been driving with this mic ♪
♪ By my side like
A little pip ♪
♪ And I know I'ma make it ♪
♪ Guess you could
Call it intuition ♪
♪ I'll back it up
I told you my game ♪
[♪♪♪]
I told you about smoking
outside this house like that.
[Meech] Well, I got
nowhere else to go.
You kicked me out, remember?
Well, that's the bed you made,
Demetrius.
[Meech] You right, Ma.
Crazy part is,
I just paid a mortgage
on a place
I'm no longer welcome.
Your father and I told you
not to do that.
It was the right thing to do.
No, you did that
to make yourself feel good.
No, I did it because our family
needs a place to live in, Ma.
What's more important?
Doing good with dirty money
or being homeless
and holy out on the street?
You had no right to go
against our word.
No right.
How the hell am I supposed
to tell your father that?
I'll tell him, Ma.
You don't got to do it.
Boy, hush, hush, okay?
And don't you say nothin'
to nobody
until I figure this out.
You hear me?
You are my heart,
and I love you to death,
but one of these days,
you're gonna need to learn
to listen to somebody.
[singer] ♪ Let's go back
To the basics ♪
♪ Let's go back
♪ Let's go
Back to the basics ♪
♪ Back to the basics ♪
♪ Back to the... basics ♪
[truck horn blaring]
[Meech] You remember
what it's called, right?
Yeah. Burger Stone.
No, Stone Burger.
That's right.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
- Mm-hmm.
[Meech] Let's get it.
[B-Mickey]
You sure about all this?
Get your fuckin' head
in the game, man.
Everything straight?
Yeah.
Obviously, something going on
between you and Meech.
Just wondering if I need
to be worried.
About what?
I want to run with a crew
that's gonna last,
where I can move up.
So I mean,
if it's some trouble...
Any trouble Meech and I got,
that's between fam, a'ight?
We fight, curse,
whatever we do,
but, shit,
at the end of the day,
that's still my nigga.
[factory horn blaring]
[indistinct chatter]
[Meech] Big Dog!
What's up?
Was that shit A1 from day one?
Hell yeah.
Where can I get some more?
Right here. Step up.
Tell him you want
a "Stone Burger," all right?
- Stone Burger.
- He gonna you up.
All right, cool.
Good lookin' out.
One Fonzo bacon burger special.
I'm looking for something
called a Stone Burger,
but I don't see it.
[Kato] Yes, sir.
It's on our secret menu.
Okay, cool.
Let me get five of 'em
and five fries
in separate bags.
[Fonzo] Five Stone Burgers
and five fries coming right up.
Thank you.
[Kato] Next.
Yeah. Can I uh, get two of them
Stone Burgers, please?
Comin' right up.
[indistinct chatter]
[funky music plays]
[♪♪♪]
[person] ...same shit I had
earlier this morning.
[Older Meech]
Let me explain two things.
The 50 Boyz never went to cars
to sell drugs.
And we never, ever,
under any circumstances,
sold to white people.
Don't look at me like that.
You gotta understand.
Detroit was damn near
all Black in the '80s.
You saw a Shay Whitey
in the hood,
you knew it was the po-po.
Or they was gonna attract
the po-po.
And this motherfucker
up there
lollygagging with them.
No, sir.
What the fuck is you doing,
man? Huh?
What the fuck you kick me
like that for?
Man, focus up, nigga.
What the fuck
is you fuckin' doing?
Ay, everybody, huddle up.
Come on, man. Let's go.
[♪♪♪]
Hey, look, we got two days
to sell the rest of this shit,
so I need everybody
out here to focus up.
And I got a Rolex for whoever
sell the most in the next 48.
Oh, that's mine.
That's what I'm talking
about, baby.
Yeah, we gonna see.
So let's get to work, niggas.
[Older Meech]
Cracking the whip ain't always
about beating
on the motherfucker.
It's about knowing which
buttons to get people to do
exactly what you need
them to do.
[hip-hop music plays]
[♪♪♪]
[singer] ♪ '80s crack era ♪
♪ CdawgVA
Bubblegoose, black leather ♪
♪ Stack mad chedda
Drop chedda ♪
♪ Gucci watch
With the sweater ♪
♪ My bop better ♪
♪ Wave top, it's the texture ♪
♪ Women wanna feel on me
Feel free ♪
♪ With north beat
I'm still on key ♪
♪ Me and Clee shine through
The cloud like sun ♪
♪ The fair one ♪
♪ Haters wanna ask how come
Allow none ♪
♪ Move like ninja in dark
Body cloth ♪
♪ Cartel shells, the real
The body parts ♪
♪ Can't stop what's unseen
Young king ♪
♪ For you clowns
I'ma say one thing ♪
♪ M-O-N-E-Y, stay fly ♪
♪ M-O M-O-N-E-Y, stay fly ♪
♪ Stay fly
Stay-stay-stay fly ♪
♪ Stay fly ♪
♪ Three-way hopper ♪
♪ Deep state dropper ♪
♪ Any sound systems aside
A bass knocker ♪
♪ Que pasa? ♪
♪ Never played
With a mobster ♪
♪ Straight rocker
Old Bay over lobster ♪
♪ Living like this won't end
No friends ♪
♪ Feel our firsts on ten
Chrome rims ♪
♪ Camouflage
Close to the cut ♪
♪ Stay fly, stay fly
Stay-stay-stay fly ♪
♪ Stay fly ♪
[♪♪♪]
Yo, the food trucks
and the rec center got us
on target to hit Pat back
and have some leftovers to cop
some of our own shit.
I told you can't nobody stop us
when we work together.
Well, speaking of teamwork,
- we can start splittin'...
- Scoot!
Po-po!
Assume the position.
Put your hands on the car.
Keep 'em where I can see 'em.
[Meech] What?
Put your hands on the car,
and keep 'em
where I can see 'em.
Nigga, hurry the fuck up.
Nobody's seen or heard
from Jay-Mo.
Please, please, tell me
you ain't do nothing stupid.
Man, I smacked him up a bit
and sent him on his way.
A'ight, shit, he probably
at Cedar Point
somewhere with his girl.
He been missing since I dropped
him off to you.
Man, I don't know
where that nigga at.
Clearly somebody is making
a play for 12th Street.
And it sounds like it's more
internal than external
if you ask me.
[ominous music plays]
New drug task force
being formed.
Watch your back.
What?
That's what we got you for.
[Bryant] I ain't gonna have
much wiggle room.
So you know, this here,
this your heads-up.
[♪♪♪]
Ey, yo, what the fuck
happened to Jay-Mo?
[♪♪♪]
[Meech sighs]
B-Mickie smoked Jay-Mo, bro.
No. No. There's no fuckin'...
why the fuck would he do that?
Nigga, I don't know.
I pulled out trying to see
if he shot you.
And I wasn't sure,
so I ain't fired.
Then that nigga did.
So y'all just been lying
in my face
this whole time, Meech?
Where the fuck is the body?
B-Mickie put it somewhere
in the river, man.
I don't fuckin' know.
You weren't even there?
Oh, my God.
Meech, if that body shows up...
yo, 50/50 ain't even
a discussion no more.
From now on, we equals,
or you could just start
running shit with B now.
Nigga, quit being overdramatic.
We on or I'm out.
[tense music plays]
A'ight, man. Fuck it, man.
Damn.
All right then.
See, the first shit
we need to do is holla
- at B-Mickie's ass about...
- Nah.
First thing we got to do
is ante up our loot,
so we can pay Pat back.
Then I'ma ask him
for some supplies
so we can start
cookin' up our own shit.
[Terry] Fuckin' dickhead.
[♪♪♪]
[dramatic music plays]
- [bell ringing]
- What's poppin', Meech?
Ain't shit. Ain't shit.
The old man in?
Yeah, he's in the back.
Make sure you knock first.
A'ight.
[Rock] Him and Junior
in the back
with a couple honeys.
So ain't no tellin'.
But uh, I'll buzz you in.
[light R&B playing
from jukebox]
[♪♪♪]
[door buzzes, clicks]
What's crackin', Pat?
Oh, shit. Meech.
My young boy.
Ah!
Yeah, my man, 100 grand,
always comin' through.
Always.
Nigga. Hell yeah.
That's what's up, my nigga.
What's up?
You want to celebrate
with us, man, have a drink?
Oh, no. Shit, I got to go home,
go to Terry's party.
I'ma be late,
but I'll catch you this week.
Oh, for real, man?
A'ight, nigga.
That's what it is,
later though.
Later. That's cool.
That's cool. That's cool.
I'll see you next time.
That's what's up.
[♪♪♪]
Hell yeah. Hell yeah.
[LL Cool J's "I'm Bad" playing]
♪ Ah ♪
[LL] ♪ No rapper can rap
Quite like I can ♪
♪ I'll take a musclebound man
And put his face in the sand ♪
♪ Not the last mafioso
I'm a MC cop ♪
♪ Make you say go LL
And do the Wop ♪
♪ If you think you
Can out-rhyme me ♪
♪ Yeah, boy, I bet... ♪
- [person] Ooh!
- Whoo!
[Terry] Lucky motherfucker, man.
[Sockie]
Let me see y'all do that shit.
I'll put 100 on it
you can't do that shit again.
[Lawanda laughs]
You know, you look kind of cute
with that patch on.
Yeah?
In, like, a Slick Rick
kind of way.
Cute ain't really something
I associate with him,
but thanks.
Why you gotta hate
on Slick Rick?
Hey, buddy. How you feeling?
Hey, Mr. Ryan.
I'm still recovering, you know?
Just glad to be home.
That's great.
- This is Monica.
- [Terry] Hey.
I brought all your assignments
like you asked.
Oh, wow. I appreciate that.
Thank you.
Y'all bowling, right?
Well, we didn't bring our shoes
and balls for nothing.
[both laugh]
- It's good to see ya.
- All right.
Did you just have your teacher
bring your homework
up here for real?
It's called gamin', Lawanda.
Yeah.
Brown-nosing's more like it.
Yo, give me a sec.
What up doe?
How'd it go with Pat?
Let's talk
about that shit later, man.
Nah. Are we going or we not?
Where the fuck B-Mick at?
Hell if I know.
I ain't that nigga's keeper.
The hell you just say to me?
Man, chill with that shit, Tee.
Hey, go on, Kato.
No, fuck that shit.
I'm tired
of all you motherfuckers
treating me like a ho.
And I'm not just talking
about Kato either.
I'm talking about yo ass,
B-Mick, and the motherfucker
that shot me.
I'm a fuckin' boss.
From here on out, I'm ruling
with a iron fist, Meech.
I ain't doing
that bullshit no more.
[♪♪♪]
They're out of paper.
You know they out
of paper, right?
Anybody see you come here?
Come on, puddin'.
You know I can slither my way
in and out when I want to.
Speaking of which,
you been working
with Meech and Terry
for a while.
Lamar, don't fuck me over.
They're just starting
to trust me.
I don't renege
on good-faith deals.
So you tell me everything
I wanna know,
and I'll make sure
we both get paid.
There's something going on
between Meech and B-Mickie.
When I say I wanna
know everything,
I wanna know everything.
Who's holding.
Where they keep they weight
and they money.
Now, you know a good-faith deal
goes both ways, right?
And I don't grant exit clauses.
[tense music plays]
[♪♪♪]
So start spilling.
[record scratching]
[man] Put that shit on
the motherfucking table, nigga.
- [overlapping chatter]
- [person] Money's on strike.
[singer] ♪ Let me
Tell you a story ♪
♪ About this boy right here ♪
You in the mix with DJ Kutz.
Welcome home Southwest Tee!
What's up to Big Meech
and the 50 Boyz Crew.
Puttin' this song.
Let's rock out!
[Lawanda]
Come on, we should go.
My mom's with the baby.
I ain't ready to go yet.
But here, here.
Come on!
[hip-hop music playing]
[man] Nah, nah, nah, redo.
Double of nothin'.
♪ Lemme tell you a story about
this boy Raheem ♪
Hey, ain't that nigga
Tiny from 12th Street?
♪ He would bring me flowers
and chocolate ♪
♪ Tell me I'm the only girl
he wanna be with ♪
Hell yeah, that's that nigga.
♪ Gold BBS' goin' hard ♪
Shit, I guess we know who
running 12th Street now.
Probably the one
that stomped out Filmel.
And that's probably the nigga
that popped me too.
- Ah, fuck that.
- Ah, chill, Tee.
Look, we gonna see
about this motherfucker, man.
All we got to do
is be smart about it.
We gon' get that motherfucker.
Fuck that nigga, man.
- Fuck y'all.
- Fuck you talking about.
[♪♪♪]
[rap music plays]
[singer] ♪ We shot callin' ♪
♪ We straight ballin' ♪
♪ Everybody ain't no solvin' ♪
♪ This for the family ♪
[pins clattering]
[soft R&B music playing]
What's up, babe?
[♪♪♪]
Sick of you treating me
like shit!
Yo, what the fuck?
You act like I just made you
take the bus home.
You drove in a brand-new Benz.
Man, I don't care
about that shit.
- Then what's the problem?
- You didn't even have
the decency
to walk me to the car, Terry.
I'm the one who lied
to the police for yo' ass.
I lied to your parents.
I'll lie to your-
your fuckin' brother
and do whatever the fuck else
I gotta do
to make sure you win,
'cause when you win,
our family does too.
But you keep treating me
like I'm fuckin' disposable,
and I'm not.
I am the mother of your child.
I'm your fuckin' partner.
So you better respect
that shit.
Look, look, look. You right.
You right. You right.
Come on, get the fuck off me.
Look, look. I'm sorry.
And I promise, I'm never gonna
take you for granted again.
[♪♪♪]
Wait, wait, wait.
It's still too early
for me to have sex.
Ain't nothing wrong
with your mouth though.
When was the last time
you ate my pussy, huh?
[Terry]
Yo, come on. You was pregnant.
With your baby, nigga.
I told you that's
against my religion.
Oh, okay.
But sucking your dick ain't.
Such a hypocrite.
You really meant
what you said, though?
Hell yeah. Every word.
[♪♪♪]
Hey, babe.
Hey. I went to the bank
to try to make a deal
on this mortgage,
and they told me
it had been paid in full.
You went to Pastor Shifty...
No.
[Charles] ...after I told you
I don't need no outside help
providing for my family.
Now call the church and put
a stop payment on that check.
I can't.
[Charles]
Oh, you can and you will.
No, really, Charles, I can't.
Well, fine, you give me
the number and I'll call.
Meech paid the mortgage.
I didn't know he'd done it
until it was too late.
How long have you known?
How long?
We not takin' it.
How we gonna un-pay something
that's already been paid?
[Charles]
I don't care how it happens,
but you gonna do
what I tell you or else...
Or else what, Charles?
What are you gonna do?
[Terry]
Hey, hey, hey. Come on, guys.
Stop fighting like this.
Stay out of this, boy.
Now you gonna do
what I tell you.
No, you are my husband,
not my daddy.
I don't take orders from you.
Ma, Dad, chill.
You want Meech to be the man
of this house so bad?
Fine.
Give him the key.
You let him come and go
as he pleases.
I'm outta here.
- [Lucille sobs]
- Come on, Pops. Ma.
Ma.
[door slams]
[tense music plays]
[♪♪♪]
[knock at door]
What's crackin'?
I've been calling
to page you all day.
So you just thought it was
a smart idea
to pop up unannounced?
What you talking about?
We need to rap.
Look, I ain't got time
for this.
[Meech] Man,
I don't give a damn
if you got company in there.
Look, we need to talk
about this motherfucker Lamar
right now.
Bye, Demetrius.
[Meech]
It's for your own protection.
- Here I go, nigga.
- Hey.
You best push on before
you get your head cracked.
Come step outside, then,
if you're so bad, nigga.
[Lamar] Nigga, you ain't
gotta say nothing
but a fuckin' word, nigga, huh?
Oh, okay.
Really, Meech? Zoe's in here,
and you pulling out
a fuckin' strap?
Ey, yo, get the fuck away
from my house
before I call the police.
A'ight, fuck it then. We done.
Nigga, you been done.
Get to stepping, nigga.
Nigga, fuck you,
charcoal-ass nigga.
Fuck you talking about?
Fuck out of here.
You ain't bad.
[Lamar] Young-ass nigga.
Shut the fuck up.
[dramatic music plays]
[♪♪♪]
[Older Meech] The foundation
of all relationships is trust.
If you don't trust the one you
with, they become a threat.
And threats can take you out.
You gotta see people
for who they really are.
And I was just starting
to get a clear picture
of everyone.
[funky hip-hop music plays]
[♪♪♪]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Watch Movies, TV Series & Live Sports
www.admitme.app