Master Philip,
Don McCorkle, FBI.
If you wouldn't mind,
I'd like to ask you
a few little questions.
So, that shithead was
an FBI agent.
Tells me, "You're a red,
you're a communist.
You're marked."
We are planning
for the upcoming visit
of Herr von Ribbentrop,
the German minister.
We would represent
the U.S. Department of Interior
at the dinner.
We would in no way be endorsing
the Nazi policies
- that affect our communit...
- Can we bring Sandy?
I'm here for my son.
Herman, Lindbergh wants to meet
our Sandy.
- He's a Nazi.
- Charles Lindbergh is a hero.
You are a coward,
and you're dragging everyone
down with you!
Now, we open the country
to a permanent migration
of Jewish families.
To be clear, the Homestead Act
involves voluntary participation
- in the program, correct?
- How could it be otherwise?
Boys, your father is home.
You finished
your collections early.
Why are you always
messing with my things?
Sandy,
I didn't touch your things!
What's the matter?
Stay on your side.
Stay out of my stuff.
I didn't do it. I didn't!
Then how else did this
move over there?
- When did you get this?
- Yesterday.
I tried to find out more before
I rattled everyone, but...
it seems to be real.
The company's
already signed off, so...
This is my sister...
and the rabbi.
I'm no fool,
this is just revenge.
I saw Karl.
He said the request
that specified me
came straight from
the Newark office of the OAA.
I don't know what we can do.
- Hey, Dad.
- Philip, go back upstairs.
Bess.
He has a right to know.
Philip, where's Sandy?
In our room.
Sandy!
Come down.
I gotta dry off.
Come on, Alvin, let's blow.
- Settle, Shush.
- Yeah, settle where?
All the grifts and rackets
in Philly or Camden
or down in Atlantic City,
and my uncle dumps us here
with the spare change
and broken pieces.
Yeah, to start.
He tells us to show up and do
whatever Mr. Schapp needs.
So... we do as we're told.
- Pinball Billy Schapp.
- Uh-huh.
Who gives a goddamn
about this shit?
I need a sit-down
with my uncle...
You had a sit-down
with your uncle,
and he put us here.
We're on the payroll.
We have nowhere to go but up,
so sit your own ass down
and show some patience.
Like Mack here.
Hey, Mack, how long you
been hauntin' this warehouse?
- Eleven years.
- See?
That's not so long.
I'll bet Mack gets promoted
any day now.
It's easy for you to make jokes,
Alvin,
but I had a good ride
running numbers for Abie
in Newark.
I'd still be there
if not for you.
No, no... if not
for Longy Zwillman, you mean.
Wh... Can I help it
if that asshole throws you over
- just for knowing me?
- It's not like I'm a red.
Yeah, well, me neither, Shush.
But I think that Lindy
and Hitler are both shitbags,
and that's close enough,
ain't it?
Sorry, Shush.
You got dragged, too.
Grab the dolly
and bring it around.
Mack, you got a paperclip?
Yeah, look over there.
John Gaver...
Said after last year's
Triple Crown, Eddie knows best.
No, that truck's going
to Delaware.
Come on, move, guys.
Where'd you learn that?
I'm from Jersey.
See these scratches?
I'm not the first
to pop this baby open.
Come on, Shush.
It so happens
that the Levin family
has been selected to be
participants in a new program,
Homestead 42. Which is...
"designed to give us
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
to move to a region of America
previously inaccessible
to city dwellers like us."
And once there,
chances are good
that we will be able
to afford to buy
a place of our own,
where you two will have
separate bedrooms
and a big backyard to play in.
On the other hand,
you will be changing schools.
And we will be saying goodbye
to Summit Avenue.
Where are we moving to?
Danville, Kentucky.
It's the county seat
of Boyle County.
I know where that is.
It's a town near
where the Mawhinneys live.
It's nice.
It's quite a coincidence.
Of all of the towns
in all of America...
What is the population
of Danville?
Uh, it is 6,700.
And how many Jews...
in Danville?
Well, they don't provide
that information, but...
you already know, Bess.
- Is there even a synagogue?
- A synagogue?
I'm sure there isn't a minyan.
- They cannot just...
- Boys.
This is a big surprise,
and we're all
a little dumbfounded, so...
Ask whatever's on your mind.
And never mind Evelyn,
I cannot believe the company
would do this to you.
With all the work that
you have done for those people,
all the hours you put in,
the effort.
It's not the company, Bess.
They're not the ones
that are forcing this.
They aren't?
They picked seven Jews.
The entire government
of the United States
is leaning on them.
The administration
of a popular president
is telling them to cooperate
in a new program
of national importance.
You think
a life insurance company
can stand up
to Charles A. Lindbergh,
the big man in a little plane?
We have rights.
Yes, we do. I can quit my job.
Short of that, the Metropolitan
Life Insurance Company does
what the President
of the United States asks.
That's how this happens.
Everyone is afraid.
How could she?
I lost my head with your sister
and that goddamn rabbi.
This is all to punish me.
You were angry.
Your son was being pulled away.
I'll go see her...
apologize.
Don't you dare.
You did nothing wrong.
You will not apologize.
Who do people in Kentucky
root for?
Excuse me?
Dad and Sandy root
for the Yankees.
I like the Dodgers, but we could
also be Giants fans.
What's the team in Kentucky?
Seldon, you hungry? Can I
get you something for breakfast?
Oh, I just ate earlier
downstairs.
Thank you.
Philip, I'll wait for you
- on the stairs, okay?
- Mm.
- Morning, Seldon.
- Good morning.
Dad, who do they root for
in Kentucky?
Uh, baseball? Um...
Cubs or Cardinals, probably.
Maybe the White Sox.
They're all in Kentucky?
No, they're all
a couple states away.
It's the best they can do.
- What's the Klan?
- Excuse me?
The Cooducks Klan?
Ku Klux Klan.
Yeah. That.
Are they in Kentucky?
- No.
- Yes. They are.
They are in Kentucky and Ohio
and Indiana and Missouri
- and all over that part
of the country.
- Bess.
What are they?
They are a group
that doesn't like Negroes
or Jews or even Catholics.
They, uh...
They're certified idiots
that you don't need
to worry about, Philip.
But if we move to Kentucky...
Eat your breakfast, Philip.
I don't want to go.
Why can't we stay here?
Because the company
is transferring your father.
Why?
Did you do something wrong?
- No.
- Such a baby.
It's just a part of working
for a big company
like Metropolitan Life.
Well, it's wrong.
Yes, because everything right
with America
is right here
in Newark, New Jersey,
and everything wrong
is somewhere else.
Ignore him, Philip.
Until your brother learns
to be civil,
we will just continue
to ignore him.
Come on!
Okay, stop.
No, there he is.
Don't say anything stupid.
You got a minute, Mr. Schapp?
What can I do for ya, kid?
Uh, we're hopin' to do for you.
Uh, Shushy and me, we just went
to six of your bars, um...
South Philly, West Philly,
Center City...
And I'm paying you for this?
Uh... maybe.
But that's up to you. Shush?
- I've seen one before.
- Look at the keyhole.
No, look.
You see those little scratches?
So what? They're from the key.
No, the key doesn't make
marks like that.
Sorry,
Mrs. Lewis isn't available.
May I take a message?
I got it.
Come on.
What are you telling me?
You're leakin' silver.
Papa, I found those invoices
- that you need...
- Minna.
Got a phone call for ya!
Meet the smart little macher
from Jersey
who's telling your old man
he's being robbed.
Alvin...
- Levin. Uh, sorry.
- Minna.
Pleasure.
Phone call for you! Phone call.
I apologize.
Bess, you have said nothing
for which you need to apologize.
Herman was understandably angry.
He was, but that's
of little moment
to what's happening.
Bess, we haven't gone
to the trouble
of recommending the Levins
for Homestead
because of any dispute
between us.
I'm not so petty as that,
and neither is your sister.
Please. Don't do this.
Herman has worked a long time
in New Jersey,
working his way up
at Metropolitan Life,
he knows these neighborhoods,
he has regular clients.
- Bess.
- And our boys are happy
at their school.
They've come up year after year
with the same classmates.
- Please, Bess...
- And when we are gone,
Evelyn will regret this.
As angry and hurt as she is now,
she will have sent away
her only sister
and her nephews, who she loves
and who love her.
And there will be no way
to repair...
Bess, your sister realizes
that this is an opportunity.
You will not be set back
in the slightest.
You'll be given
a government stipend
to cover the cost of the move,
and with Herman's salary intact,
the cost of housing
and other living expenses
are such in Kentucky that
you will soon be homeowners
and saving off
your every paycheck.
We have enough money.
And the personal growth inherent
in getting your children
out of the insulated culture
of Weequahic?
Insulated?
- We are Jews.
- As am I.
We are comfortable living
among other Jews.
And I am comfortable living
anywhere in this country
with anyone.
And isn't that...
the purpose of this program?
In fact, isn't that the essence
of the American experiment?
Our family is an experiment
to you, Rabbi?
Sit.
Bess...
Your family was also selected
because Herman has come to
the attention of law enforcement
for sheltering a young man
who went overseas
in violation
of the neutrality laws.
Now, this move...
will do much to mollify the FBI
and their current concern
about the Levins.
It's true, Bess.
In so... many ways,
what is happening here
is for your own good.
And in three months...
you will be writing
your sister from Kentucky
to thank her for opening
a new world to you.
You will see.
Above all, you and your children
are always welcome in my home
anytime.
In fact, Evelyn and I hope
to see you all at the wedding.
And my husband?
I'm sure he and I
will speak again.
I'll meet you
wherever you wanna go...
the place just right
around the corner.
You're gonna need
some form of identification.
- Looks good.
- Thank you.
Yes, Mr. Elia.
Right, I understand
what you're saying...
because we don't
have enough information.
But we need to
have the documents.
Aunt Evelyn!
Oh my God, Philip!
I am so happy to see you.
This is Leroy.
This is my nephew Philip.
Pleased to meet you.
- I'll take care of this.
- Okay.
Let me look at you.
You have grown at least an inch.
Did you come from school.
Is your mom with you?
I came by myself. On the bus.
All the way downtown?
I'm impressed.
Come on. Let me show you
this way into my office.
Got it.
In here.
Can you keep a secret?
Oh. Yes!
I went alone
to the Newsreel Theatre
to see you at the White House.
What was it like to eat dinner
with the president?
Well...
This is the reception line.
On your way to a state dinner,
the guests file past
the president
and the first lady,
and when you're introduced,
they photograph you,
and then the White House
sends this to you.
Russ! Line two.
Did the president say anything?
He said, "It's very nice
to have you here."
Did you say anything back?
I said, "It's an honor,
Mr. President."
I saw you dancing
in the newsreel.
Yes, I did dance.
Evelyn Finkel of Dewey Street
at the White House.
Isn't it unbelievable?
Sure is.
Aunt Evelyn...
Do you know that we're moving
to Kentucky?
Uh-huh.
No thanks.
I don't want to go, Aunt Evelyn.
I wanna stay at my school.
Who sent you here, Philip?
Sent me? Nobody.
You can tell me the truth.
Nobody sent me.
Can't Seldon and his mother go
instead of us?
Seldon? Is that the boy
from downstairs?
His father died.
His father also worked
for the Metropolitan Life
until he got sick.
And now,
his mother works there, too.
How come we have to go
to Kentucky and they don't?
Did you father send you here,
Philip?
Nobody evens knows I'm here.
Please send Seldon to Kentucky
and not us.
Philip...
You can't go through life
being afraid of things
that are unfamiliar to you.
I mean, suppose I'd been afraid
of going to the White House
or of meeting
the foreign minister?
Hey. I don't want you to grow up
and be frightened
like your parents.
You won't do that, will you?
You promise me you won't?
- Not you, huh, Marty?
- Not me.
And it's not like
I'm foolin' anyone
with the last name of Lefkowitz.
So, who did I piss off?
Montana?
- You're kidding me.
- Missoula, Montana.
Compared to that,
Kentucky's gonna feel like
you're working
the Manhattan office.
This is so fucked up.
How does a government tell
a private company
where to send its employees
based on their religion?
It's no help to Met Life.
Who's gonna do a better job
of selling and collecting
on policies to Jewish families
than you guys?
Or the colored?
You guys do better
in the colored neighborhoods
than anyone.
I'm sure the cowboys in Missoula
will love Sy Hershberg
making his home
where the buffalo roam.
I almost forgot,
I have a treat for you.
It's an after-dinner chocolate,
a chocolate wrapped
in gold paper.
And see what's on it?
That's the presidential seal.
It's what's waiting for you
on the tables
at the White House.
When I saw it, I thought,
"Who is the boy I wanna make
most happy in the whole world?"
Here.
Seldon's last name is Wishnow,
right?
- That's right.
- And he's your best friend?
- What'd he say?
- He said one more week.
You sure you don't got
the shell shock?
My dad got it from the war.
Ma said he was never right
in the head again.
Head's fine, Shush.
It's my leg.
I don't know, Alvin. I saw ya
eyeballin' that little mouse.
- That mouse?
- Yeah.
You're talking
about the boss' daughter.
I don't care if she's
Pharaoh's daughter,
she's not for me.
Besides, you already made
a splash with that thing
- about the coinboxes.
- Trust me, Shush.
I know what I'm doin'.
Damn!
All that walkin' yesterday
broke down
the fucking stump again.
I sure miss Philip.
He figured out how to wrap
the bandage so tight.
Better than the Canadian nurses
ever fucking did.
That little pisher.
Please
justify the increased spending
on the considerable resources
it took to move them...
Secretary, apologies. The trains
are all delayed this morning,
a problem on the tracks
in Baltimore.
Not to worry, Rabbi.
We tabled the reports
on Just Folks and Homestead
until you arrived,
and Mr. Stedman here
was just concluding
the quarterly reports
on Park Service
and Fish and Wildlife.
I'll just conclude
by referring everyone
to the quarterly status reports,
uh, for licensing and parkgoing,
which show us as staying
in the black
through the third quarter.
Here, here.
Rabbi, you have the floor.
Well, I won't waste
anyone's time
on what is working well...
because what is working well
requires considerably
less attention,
and the Just Folks program
is a national success.
Voluntary participation
now involves
more than 8,000 teenage boys
in 34 states,
and the numbers are growing.
This summer,
we may see increased enrollment
of more than 50 percent.
City youth are being connected
to the values
and authenticity
of the heartland.
Cheers.
On the other hand,
I would be remiss
if I claimed that Homestead 42,
as the second phase
of the president's initiative
to absorb American Jewry
into the mainstream,
has found similar favor.
- There are problems?
- There are.
The fact that the program
is not truly voluntary
has led
to some considerable dissent.
This was anticipated. We sought
to overcome any skepticism
by ensuring
that the transfers came
with fundamental
economic incentives,
but thus far, what Congress
has approved is only a stipend
to cover the cost of the moving.
Salary increases
for transferred families
were omitted from the bill...
We can hardly expect
a Republican Congress
to pass legislation that has
government mandating raises
for private employees
just because their companies
transfer them
to different posts.
- Right.
- But without that...
And speaking as a businessman,
I can hardly expect
private companies
to pay employees more
for doing the same jobs
at new locations.
But Secretary Ford, sir,
absent an actual
economic incentive,
what we are then asking
of these families
is to accept
an involuntary transfer
to another city or town
with no benefit to them.
Involuntary in what sense?
Well, we're moving them
and they get nothing,
save for the fact
that their salaries
go a little further
in more rural economies.
Well, that's meaningful.
- Secretary, sir, I was told...
- Rabbi.
When I build an auto plant,
- I build it where I want.
- Right.
And if the workers
want those jobs,
they come to my plant.
Or they don't.
Now, if the Jewish people
want to keep these jobs,
they have the opportunity
to move to where the jobs
will now be.
Or not.
That seems voluntary to me.
I'm telling you,
this guy's right hand...
- Go on.
- Hey, Mack.
These?
- Yeah, that's all of 'em.
- Yeah?
No, no, no, I got it!
- I got it, I got it, I got it.
- What?
- Oh.
- Uh...
- Where's it go?
- To the, uh, the office.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Oh, geez.
Are you okay with that?
I'm fine.
It's just every now and then...
I just forget
that I'm a cripple.
Oh. I don't think
you're a cripple.
Oh. That's sweet.
But, um... when my stump
breaks down, I'm a cripple.
What do you mean it breaks down?
- Uh...
- What... You... you got it?
Yeah, yeah, no, I got it.
Uh...
Every now and then,
if I overdo things,
it gets swole, and then the...
prosthetic doesn't fit right,
and then it gets more swole,
and it's just...
- 'round and 'round like that.
- Yeah.
Yeah. You... You should soak
your stump in Epsom salt.
It makes the skin tough.
- Yeah.
- Epsom salt.
I'm gonna go to the power room.
These are a little bit higher.
Boys not home from school yet?
School just let out.
My bus must've been early.
Bess.
Where exactly is the company
sending you in Kentucky?
- Danville, near Lexington.
- Danville...
In today's mail.
Why would they send two of us
to the same little town
in Kentucky?
Why send me at all?
I'm not a Met Life agent.
My husband was.
I'm drawing on his pension
and insurance
and working part-time
in the regional office.
Why bother with me at all?
The one thing I can think,
the one blessing,
is that Seldon and Philip
will still get to be together.
At least there's that.
The first thing will be
to apply for an injunction
in U.S. District Court
to see if we can stop
the transfers
while the case is adjudicated.
Because that will take a while.
What are our chances?
Well, better if we go in
with plaintiffs
from a variety
of New Jersey corporations.
You three will be suing
for relief from Met Life,
but I'd like to dig up
plaintiffs from Hess Oil,
Prudential,
as many of the other companies
that are cooperating
with the OAA.
How long might that take?
Give me a week before I file.
If we sue, can Met Life
go hard at us?
Could we be fired?
I can't prevent your company
from being punitive
if they want to be punitive.
In the event that we prevail
in court,
they would be liable for damages
if they go that way.
If we prevail.
Any lawyer who claims
a guaranteed outcome
in a civil action
is a liar, Mr. Levin.
I'm out.
I'm in.
Fuck Montana.
In.
This is still America,
and I want my day in court.
Glad you're with me, Sy.
Levin.
What now?
You've failed to contact
the OAA field office
and confirm your transfer plans.
If you want to keep your job
at Met Life,
the deadline's this week.
Why wait?
I dunno.
Keeps slipping my mind.
How's your nephew doing?
We haven't seen him around
lately.
- Limping right along, I'm sure.
- We done here?
Have a fine evening.
But if I was you...
I'd save the time and money
taking things to court,
and I'd report to OAA.
Sandy.
Is Philip with you?
No, he's outside playing.
Good. I wanted to talk to you
alone.
What did I do now?
You knew your aunt
was sending us to Kentucky.
You knew before your father
even opened that letter.
Don't lie to me,
I know you knew.
I'm not lying to you.
Okay.
But you did know, right?
Aunt Ev said
it was for own good,
that she was protecting us.
Protecting us from what?
She said we were already
in enough trouble
from the government.
Because of Alvin, because of him
coming to live with us
after being in the war.
And what did you tell her?
Did you tell her Seldon
is Philip's friend?
No, I... I don't think Philip
even likes Seldon all that much.
Well, someone said something
because now the company
is transferring the Wishnows
to Danville as well.
Mom, it wasn't me.
So...
We've started modifying
the coin boxes.
And at some cost.
Meaning I hope you're right,
and I hope like hell
I see a profit.
I am, and you will.
Is that all you're gonna do?
What do you mean, kid?
Well, they've been
robbing you for years.
So they should all pay.
Jack up the price.
A Lincoln per pinball
and vending machine,
a Hamilton on each slot.
Ain't that easy, kid.
I raise the rent,
and they'll kick up a stink.
Then make an example
of one of them.
I'm not into rough stuff.
And if I go to Margulis
and cry help,
he'll have to get the okay
from Waxey Gordon.
And then, both of them will take
a bite out of my ass
for making it happen.
That's how things work.
Just point to the mutt
with the loudest mouth.
Me and Shush'll do the rest.
My take goes up, I still gotta
ante up to Margulis and Gordon.
Yeah, but now,
you got the whole pie,
so how you slice it
is up to you. Farshteyn?
You don't rattle, kid.
Let me give it a little thought.
I see you
sniffin' around my daughter.
Is that a problem?
You got intentions?
It's too soon to know.
Well, that's it for now
from the editorial room
of the Jergens Journal
and yours truly,
Walter Winchell.
That's a month.
And not one word
about Homestead 42.
God, I hope they haven't
bought him off.
I'm sure they haven't.
He still attacked Lindbergh
and Wheeler.
Yeah, I know, but still.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna write to him.
Tell him we need him
to speak out.
I mean, the government
telling companies
where people of this race,
that religion,
where they can and can't work?
You let them get away with that,
what's next?
That's how fascism works.
You're sitting there,
writing to Winchell?
- Walter Winchell?
- Yes, I am!
And you're predicting
that these people
will stop at nothing
once they know what they can get
away with,
and yet, you don't think
they can do what they want
to the mail?
Come on, Bess, it's one letter.
It's not just one letter.
You're also planning
to sue the government.
As you said, we have rights.
How can you see
what these people are
and have so little sense
of what they are capable of?
We have already had FBI agents
harassing us,
we have had our children
questioned!
Let someone else
write to Winchell.
Someone else?
- The next guy?
- Yeah.
Let the next guy step up.
And I just sit here on my ass?
Keeping quiet,
waiting for the worst to happen?
No. I don't see Shepsie
sitting around
writing letters,
waiting for the worst to happen.
- Not Canada again.
- Yes, Canada.
This is my country!
Not anymore! It is Lindbergh's.
It is the Jew haters'.
It is the America Firsters'.
It is the people who chase
children down the street,
asking questions,
and then deport
their families to Kentucky.
It's their country.
And if we run? If we quit?
Then they win.
And they do not get to win.
- Herman.
- We have done nothing wrong.
Mrs. Lindbergh.
I just wanted
to congratulate you personally,
as the president and I
will regrettably not be there
on the day.
Oh, so kind...
As it happens, we'll be flying
down to Caracas that week
for
the Pan-American Conferences,
but it was kind of you
to favor us with an invitation.
Oh, not at all.
You both have
our very best wishes.
Rabbi,
I'm sure we will talk further.
I'm sure. Thank you.
Thank you.
Well, that was unexpected.
Yes, when she heard
you were outside,
she wanted to
give her regrets personally.
Oh, so kind. She's so gracious.
- Mm-hmm.
- And did you see the president?
I did not,
but as you can surmise,
I had a good bit of time
with the First Lady.
And as I suspected,
the opportunity
to push more funding
through Congress
will have to wait until
after the midterm elections.
What would appear to be
salary bonuses
for relocating Jewish citizens
are...
for rather obvious reasons,
politically untenable
before then.
But the promise I made
to people will be kept.
I am assured.
As you know,
we applied for an injunction
in US District Court.
Unfortunately, we were denied.
But, as we drew
a conservative judge,
I saw merit
in immediately appealing
to the Third Circuit.
How long will the appeal take?
I will do what I can
to expedite on my end,
but the reality is,
at least a year.
There's only so much I can bring
on this first trip down.
Once you're settled, we can send
the things
you don't have room for.
Or, when we come, we can bring
some of your things.
I suspect Herman's going to hire
a moving company.
Herman's made the decision?
Not yet. But for all his years
at Metropolitan Life,
I don't see him walking away.
And you? What do you think?
What do I think?
Does it matter what I think?
More and more, he yells.
He doesn't talk.
If he wants to fight, he fights,
and if he wants to quit,
he quits.
And the powerful Russian offense
pushes back against
the German assault
on the Crimea.
Finally, the Russians learned
how to fight.
They stopped them outside
of Moscow in December.
- Remember that?
- That was the winter.
Either way...
the Russians are the only ones
making it hard on Hitler.
The British, too, in Egypt.
It's a sideshow.
That's a couple of divisions
running around the desert.
The Russians are making
the bastards bleed. Thank God.
And back beyond
the invasion's starting line
of three years ago.
Herman, we gotta get outta here.
All of us.
The Soviet
Separate Coastal Army sweeps in
and takes back
the ancient city of Kerch.
You sure you got enough room?
Car's already packed
to the brim.
You, Estelle, and the kids
need to fit in there somewhere.
We'll manage.
Oh, Herman. Uh, Benjamin here's
gonna be taking over for me.
Happy to meet ya.
Can I, uh, give you a hand?
No, no, no.
You stay and mind the store.
Marching in this haul here
are Germans and Romanians.
They surrender easily
and completely,
with their weapons...
So. Winnipeg.
Yeah, it's quite a trek.
Estelle is putting the youngest
in his pajamas
so we can drive
right through the first night,
get over the border
before we stop.
My brother says Winnipeg's nice.
He's an idiot,
but that's what he says.
Seriously, though, Herman...
you gotta think about things.
If you go to Kentucky,
you don't know
what you're getting into.
And if you don't go,
if you refuse...
Then the Cossacks come for me.
They came.
When Alvin was staying with you,
didn't they?
They questioned you, the kids.
They leaned on your brother
until Alvin was gone.
Yes, Herman, there are Cossacks.
There are. They're out there.
Travel safe, friend.
Next year, in Jerusalem.
- Or Saskatchewan.
- You mean Manitoba.
Nu, there's a difference?
Oh.
Can I see?
No, not yet.
You're so serious.
Look.
Wow. This is...
It's beautiful.
I don't want to go to Kentucky.
Do you want to go to Kentucky?
No.
Good evening,
Mr. and Mrs. America,
and all the ships at sea.
Let's go to press.
Flash. The phony moniker
for phase one
of organized Jewish persecution
in the land of the free
is Homestead 42.
- Give 'em hell, Walter.
- Aided and abetted
by the most respectable
of America's robber barons.
Item: 225 Jewish families
have been told
to vacate their homes
in America's northeast cities
in order to be shipped
hundreds of miles
from family and friends.
This first shipment has been
kept strategically small
so as to escape
national attention. Why?
Because it marks the beginning
of second-class citizenship,
if not outright persecution,
for the four and a half million
American citizens
of Jewish descent.
That lying prick.
How can you listen to that shit?
- This is the great US of A...
- Not in this house!
Instituting illegal actions
against its natural-born
and naturalized citizens.
And who's next,
Mr. and Mrs. America,
now that the Bill of Rights is
no longer the law of the land?
And who's next
under the Wheeler-Ford plan
for government-funded removals?
The long-suffering Negroes?
The hard-working Italians?
The last of the Mohicans?
- Stay with me...
- Good night, Mr. Winchell,
and good luck
finding a new career.
Why do you say so?
Because that guttersnipe
just accused me
of persecuting my own people,
of making them
second-class citizens.
Well, he didn't name you.
He slandered my program.
Well, what are you gonna do?
Well, it's been a while
since I've written a sermon
from scratch,
but at this moment...
I feel the fire.
A sermon? For Saturday?
For tomorrow.
And a newspaper page
is going to be my pulpit.
Are you sure, boychik?
Yeah. I made up my mind.
Then, geviss.
It's done.
You change your clothes,
be there by nine.
Hey, Monty...
thanks.
This is family.
They're putting them in for ya.
This one going
to Secaucus or not?
Aw, shit.
Soak 'em in Epsom salt.
That'll toughen 'em up.
Saul, my brother's been wearin'
a suit too long. You got soft.
Come on. It's my first day,
don't bust balls.
- Thanks for taking me on.
- All right. Come on, come on.
You smell like tomatoes.
Hey, will you get yourself
some gloves?
- This is goodbye.
- All right...
- Goodbye, Selma.
- Thank you.
Write when you get there.
Please write.
I will write
as soon as I'm settled.
- Drive safely.
- I will.
Seldon. Goodbye. We'll miss you.
Don't forget to stop and eat.
Please take care.
- Goodbye.
- Wait!
Mom, make them wait.
- Philip, what are you doing?
- Wait! Just make them wait!
What in the world?
Is he all right?
Philip!
You don't have to do that.
Yes. Take it.
Take it!
- Thank you, Philip.
- Thank you.
All right, c'mon, let's go!
Do you just
take the leg off first?
What, you want him to go
lopsided on you?
I'm just askin'. I never been
with a one-legged guy before.
Hey! I still got two.
I mean, used to be three,
but you know...
- After you.
- Thank you.
You got somethin'
to drink at home?
If you buy me a bottle, I do.
These fucking guys.
Ooh! One ain't enough.
Well, you assholes
can't leave a guy alone
for a minute, can you?
Are we goin' or what?
What's that all about?
Fucking G-men.
Always lookin'
for another pound of flesh.
Mazel tov!
Poor hands.
They'll toughen up.
I'm gonna clean up,
hit the sack.
You want me to fix you a plate?
No, Bess.
I just need some sleep.
Sandy.
- How are you?
- Okay.
Good.
Wake me up in an hour.
I've decided
I'm gonna go see Winchell.
Herman.
Herman, please.
Not now, Bess.
For my sake.
What's the matter?
Why didn't we just go
to Kentucky?
Because your father felt
it was the wrong place
for you and your brother
to grow up.
That's crazy.
I went to Kentucky.
The Mawhinneys don't hate Jews.
But there are others who do...
and this, Sandy, is our home.
I wouldn't wanna
have you as my enemy.
Me neither.
Not half a day after your piece
in The Times,
and Walter Winchell
is out of a job.
Can you believe he then had
the unmitigated gall
to climb up on a soap box
in Union Square the next night
and announce he would run
for president?
- What a farce.
- A radio provocateur
- against Charles Lindbergh.
- Lindy's a hero.
And two years out
from the election.
- Hmm.
We aren't even
at the midterms yet.
- It's ridiculous.
- Nuts.
Well, here we go!
- Mazel tov.
Hey!
Don't do this.
What are you saying, Bess?
I can't stand up
for what I believe?
They burned him in effigy
on Long Island last night.
The Bund showed up,
they're making threats.
You want me to run and hide,
Bess?
Rabbi.
It's a glorious night.
Mazel tov.
Can you spare just a moment?
Of course,
there's always a moment
for the synagogue officers.
What can I do for you?
Oh, nothing tonight, of course.
Tonight belongs to you
and your bride, but...
if it's possible
to meet with you
before you return to Washington?
Oh, what's the matter?
It's just that the membership...
We've been shedding
some families.
More than 100
in the last few months.
They're been complaints
about your political involvement
and a feeling on the part
of some...
Gentlemen,
this is my wedding night.
-Yes, of course...
-And whatever problems
you think you have
with congregants
who differ in their views,
I can assure you that there are
more prospective members
who will be joining our shul
as a result of my work
with the government.
Now, I will thank you to leave
the rest of the evening
to its purposes.
Good to see ya, Fred.
Harry. Peter.
Good evening,
Mr. and Mrs. America!
First of all...
First of all, pay no attention
to Mr. Hoover's men
over on my left...
- with their cameras
and their dark suits
and their intimidating tactics.
Because this is not Berlin,
and they are not the Gestapo.
No. This is
Paterson, New Jersey!
This is the United States
of America!
- This is our right to assemble...
- Fucking Nazis!
Easy! Easy.
No violence. No violence.
Do not give them an excuse.
Don't do it.
And second of all,
I want to thank you
for coming out
on this, the fourth whistle stop
on what I promise will be
a two-year grassroots campaign
to take back America
from those who want to turn us
against each other,
those who no longer remember
what it is
that America stands for,
who use the cry
of "America First,"
who promote nationalism
and isolationism
to make enemies of hardworking
American citizens
who build and continue
to build...
Goddamn Bund!
Get lost,
you fucking Nazis!
Reds go home!
We agreed no violence.
No excuses for violence.
Do something!
Who are these guys?
- All right. Easy.
- You don't belong here!
- Please stay calm.
- Fuck you, you commies.
- Hey! Stop!
- Who are they?
Officers! Stop that.
Officers... No violence!
Please! Stop!
- Come on!
- Everybody calm down.
It does not need
to be like this.
Leave us alone!
- Please!
- Get away from us!
- No violence.
- Where are the police?
Stay calm.
Stay calm! Please!
- Stop it!
- Fucking Jew!
- Get outta here!
- Yeah, you little pinko!
What began earlier
as a political rally
in the downtown section
of Paterson, New Jersey,
has since resulted in
an evening of violence
and rioting.
At ten o'clock,
the controversial
radio personality
and presidential hopeful
Walter Winchell
took to a makeshift stage
for his fourth campaign speech
and repeated the need
to take back America,
thus provoking his hundreds
of supporters in attendance
to lash out at the small group
of residents
peacefully observing from
the outskirts of the crowd.
Dozens from both sides
are injured,
and one man has died
from his injuries.
The mayor has enforced
a curfew, which is largely
being ignored,
as reports
of escalating violence,
rock throwing, window breaking,
and fires perpetuated
by Winchell's mob
continue to multiply
within Paterson city limits.
A downtown hardware store owner
told police earlier today
that several men wearing
Winchell buttons
bought handsaws,
ice picks, and hammers.
When another group entered
to make similar purchases,
the owner called the police.
We return you now
to this hour's program.
You... You can't do this.
Not to us. Not to our lives.
If you do, I will go to Canada.
I will go to Canada,
I will take the children,
I will leave.
This just in.
The Colombian Broadcasting
News Bureau.
Anti-Jewish disturbances
are now being reported
by authorities in both Cleveland
and Indianapolis.
Fellow Americans, concerned at
the civil disturbances
that followed Mr. Winchell's
speaking engagements,
this president will do
all within his power
to prevent any further harm
from coming to the citizenry.
- We have to get out.
- They've closed the borders.
I thought that Lindbergh
would be good for everyone.
For the Jews, for everybody.
I thought...
The riots are not because
of Lindbergh.
I believe he is a good man.
Does it bother you at all
what's happened in this country?
Well, the question seem to be
whether you're still willing
to act on that?
We only think we're Americans.