Transcript by Addic7ed.com
Enjoy Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP
Can't find that in Sheboygan.
Huh?
Why don't you help me out here? Yes, ma'am.
Oh... Oh, hey, Ryan.
I, um, didn't see you there.
Yeah, I didn't see you, either.
That's so weird that neither
of us saw each other.
You remember my boyfriend Drew.
What's up, bro?
Oh.
We're going to put some burgers
on the grill later.
Maybe crack some brews?
Yeah, you should come.
Sounds fun.
Here comes the corny nickname.
See you then, Ry-Guy.
And here comes the part where he carries her
into the house like a
Viking on a rape quest.
No! No! Come on.
He's going to wreck that, mate.
I know how you feel about Jenna.
Stop pretending this whole Drew
situation doesn't make you sick.
I'm surprised you still have an appetite.
What am I going to do?
She's dating Drew,
and he doesn't seem like such a bad guy.
Mm. Not a bad guy, huh?
Have you any idea what it feels like
to have someone come into your house,
treat you with no respect
and act like they own the place?
Did you eat my sandwich?
Oh, I get it.
Because I'm a dog, right?
I can only imagine what
you'd say if I was black.
Hey, Ryan. Wait for it.
Yeah! Ry-Bread!
Hey, Drew... a blank.
Ha! Burgers will be up soon.
Have a seat, bro.
Uh...
I-I don't... I don't mind standing.
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
Hey, Wilfy, down.
Go on.
That's it.
You love your Big Daddy Drew. Yes, you do.
Now, sit.
In the dirt? Wilfy, sit.
Ah! That's my boy.
Wow. Never seen Wilfred so well-behaved.
Oh, he's always like that with Drew.
I think it's the sound of his voice.
He's got a pack mentality.
Dogs want to please their alpha,
so they like to know who's in charge.
Look, I live and breathe
Sheboygan Lager sales,
so when I find out this Milwaukee's Brew guy
is talking to my clients, here's what I do.
I go into his territory,
and I take 15 store managers
out golfing in one week.
And before I know it,
my sales are up 40%.
About a month later,
I see this Milwaukee's Brew guy at a bar.
He's looking all drunk and depressed.
Turns out he lost his job.
Aw. So I bought him a beer.
A Sheboygan Lager! Come on!
Yeah!
Don't you think that was
a little harsh, Drew?
Insert moronic sports metaphor here.
When it comes to beverage sales,
you either swing for the fences
or you get off the field.
Nauseating.
I don't understand, Wilfred.
If you hate Drew so much,
why do you do everything he says?
I don't know, Ryan.
Why do you do everything I say? I don't.
- Hey!
- Aw, drop it.
Now.
Dogs shouldn't eat from the table, Ry.
Makes 'em think they're our equals.
But that doesn't mean we can't have
a little fun, now, does it, Wilfy?
Do that again, and I swear to... What?
Careful, Drew.
Oh, it is on.
Oh. Wilfred loves to wrestle.
Here we go. Bring it on, bitch.
I'm going to punch those perfect
white teeth down your throat.
Great guy.
He really is.
I just wish he wasn't so competitive.
You fur ball!
Got to be competitive to
be good at sales, right?
Yes, but sometimes he takes it too far.
You know, like last Christmas,
my dad beat him at Wii Golf,
and he got so angry
that he threw the controller
through the window.
I was so upset, I didn't
talk to him for a week.
Well, nobody's perfect.
Well, that's true.
And Wilfy's just crazy about him.
I'll bite off your ears
and box the bloody holes that remain!
And he's got a good heart,
and... he makes me really happy.
All right.
I think the big fella's all tuckered out.
Your death... will be... my holiday.
Hello?
Ryan, it's me.
Wilfred, what's wrong?
Back-to-back-to-back-to-back-
to-back orgasms.
That's what's wrong.
I'm hanging up.
What?
Ryan, it's me again.
We can't sit by and let this caveman
get his naughty-boy on
with the love of our life.
Or maybe you need some more convincing.
We have to get rid of Drew.
Wilfred, Jenna's in love.
I don't want to do anything
to hurt their relationship.
Why not? Because it's wrong.
Stop bothering me.
I will not stop bothering you until...
Wilfy, quiet!
Gotta go.
JENNA Yeah! Oh!
Bring it! Oh!
Put your legs up.
Put your legs up, please.
Come on. Come on, Bear.
Work with me here.
Aah! What's the use?
You see what Drew does to me, Ryan?
I'm so emasculated, I can't even
raise a fence post for stupid old Bear.
I need your help.
What you're asking me to do
goes against my conscience.
I couldn't live with myself. Really?
But Drew sex-punching
Jenna for hours on end--
you can live with that?
Look, we just have to be patient.
Long-distance relationships
almost never last.
And from what Jenna tells me,
it sounds like they've got other problems.
From what Jenna tells you?
So... so you guys are,
like, girlfriends now?
No.
This is how it started with Jenna's
old college chum, Bobby "Blue Balls" Davis.
The only scoring he did was
the triple letter bonus
on their nightly Scrabble game.
You want to go down like that?
You're running out of time.
Hey.
You here to pick up Wilfred?
Actually, I was going to ask you
to keep him a little longer.
We're going out to dinner to celebrate.
I'm coming to L.A., bro!
I'm moving in with Jenna!
Looks like you better start brushing up
on your seven-letter Scrabble words.
Here's a few for you.
Sexless.
Flaccid.
Dry-dick.
Shall I go on?
All right. Here's what I'm thinking.
We wait until Drew is asleep,
and then we put his hand in warm water.
Then, just when he starts to pee himself,
we take a rock and crush his skull.
That's your plan?
Well, how would you kill him?
What's the one thing Jenna
hates most about Drew?
Vaginal tearing from his huge cock.
He's a sore loser.
Look, all I have to do
is beat him at something
and make sure Jenna's there
to see him lose his shit.
That is the stupidest, most ridiculous...
Actually, that's pretty good.
Except for one thing.
Drew's a born winner, and you're... you.
That may be true, but there is
something I'm really good at.
Ah. Here we go.
What the hell is that?
My old chemistry set.
"Little Suzy Baker's Oven."
What are you going to do,
challenge Drew to a Bake-Off?
That was my sister's.
Behold...
the instrument of Drew's destruction.
My Ping-Pong paddle
from when I was All-State
Table Tennis champion.
So chemistry, baking and Ping-Pong.
I guess my only question is:
how were you not blow-jobbed to death
by the entire cheerleading squad?
The beagle has landed.
Wilfred!
I'm sorry, man.
I tried to get him in the house,
and he ran over here.
You crazy mutt. Going somewhere?
Oh, yeah. Some play downtown.
Jenna's almost ready.
You're a Ping-Pong guy, huh?
I dabble.
Yeah, I used to play.
Used to?
Yeah, I kind of promised Jenna
I'd lay off competitive sports for a while.
Sometimes... I get a little too intense.
Oh. That's cool.
You don't seem like the
Ping-Pong type anyway.
What do you mean?
Well, you're a big guy.
Usually, Ping-Pong players are quicker.
I'm pretty quick, bro.
I guess I'll just have
to take your word for it.
You know what? What the hell?
One game won't kill me, huh?
Let's set it up.
Well done, Ryan.
Don't screw it up.
I got this.
Oh, I got lucky.
Yeah, you did.
Get him a body bag! Yeah!
Wilfy, quiet!
Ryan, serve.
There you are.
Right on cue. Drew, what are you doing?
The show doesn't start till 3:00,
babe. We'll be quick.
But we had a deal. Oh, come on.
It's just a friendly
little game, right, Ryan?
Totally, bro.
Oh, yeah! Get some!
I probably should have warned you--
back at the break room at
Sheboygan Lager, I was 192-0.
Oh, yeah! 43-43.
- Tied again.
- Bloody hell!
Come on, Drew. We're
already a half hour late.
Okay, can't we just say
that next point wins?
Hey, those aren't the rules, Jenna.
Uh, I think that's a good idea.
Fine. Whatever.
Your table, your rules. Next point wins.
I thought you said you were good.
I've seen more aggressive ball play
in an airport men's room.
Geyour head in the game!
No!
Yeah!
Sheboygan Lager, bitch!
That's how we do!
That's... how... we... do!
Yeah! Yeah!
Whoo!
All right, babe, let's go see that play.
What?! I'm not going to the play with you!
I'm not going anywhere with you, ever again!
Wait, Jenna!
That... was... awesome!
I've never seen Jenna so upset.
You don't think that pains me, too?
But that's the price we
pay for true love, Ryan.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go tear a new asshole
in the back of Bear's neck.
Hi, Ryan.
Do you wanna come in?
No, thanks.
I'm actually just waiting
for a cab to the airport.
Jenna broke up with me.
Really?
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, uh,
I just wanted to come over and apologize.
I'm embarrassed.
Well, we both got a little heated there.
It's like, I know what I'm doing is wrong,
and I just can't help myself.
Like with that Milwaukee's Brew guy...
I didn't actually buy him a Sheboygan Lager.
I bought myself a Sheboygan Lager.
Then I spit it in his face and
told him to lick my balls.
What's wrong with me?
Something.
Yeah.
And now it cost me the most
important thing in my life.
I just wish I was more like you.
You seem so...
in control.
Anyway, take care, man.
You, too.
That... was... hilarious!
Did you see how destroyed he was?
Uh, yeah. I feel bad.
That's just your conscience
being a total gaylord.
He's gone, Ryan!
The tyrant is exiled!
He was on the wagon and we
threw him under the bus.
We need to fix this.
The only things that need fixing are
your tangled transportation metaphors.
We got exactly what we wanted!
No, you got what you wanted.
You always do this--
you manipulate me and you
don't listen and you push
and push and push
until I finally give in and
do something I know is wrong.
I don't like your tone, Ryan.
Why?
Does it remind you of someone?
You know, you may not have liked Drew,
but at least you respected him.
Blah, blah, blah. Shut up and
go make yourself a sandwich.
I'm hungry. And this time,
don't put so much--
Did you just...?
You can't just...
All right, Ryan.
Point taken.
I guess you're in charge now.
Yeah, yeah, I guess I am.
So, what, what would you have me do?
I want you to help me
undo the mess we've made.
That's gonna take some thought.
Um, is it all right with you
if I go and comfort Jenna
while I ruminate on that subject?
Yeah.
Sure.
May I be excused?
Hi, Jenna, it's Ryan.
Look, I'd really like to talk
about what happened with Drew.
Give me a call back when you get a chance.
Hello?
Hello, Ryan.
Wilfred, what's going on?
Just calling to see if you'd
followed your conscience yet.
Any luck getting Drew
and Jenna back together?
I'm working on it.
Oh, good!
I'm very happy for you.
Too bad you won't be around to see it.
What are you talking about?
Did you enjoy your brownie, Ryan?
What? How did you know it--
I made it just for you.
I hope you like my secret ingredient.
What did you put in it?
Oh, nothing really.
Just a powerful neurotoxin
that is coursing through
your bloodstream as we speak.
What?
Did you really think I'd
give up my alpha status
without a fight?
I wonder what your outlook is, Ryan.
"All signs point to...
dead!"
Where are you?
I'll never tell!
And if you think you'll find me,
then you've vastly underestimated the depth
of my brilliantly... Oh, hey, Ryan.
What's all this about poison?
I didn't manipulate you
into getting rid of Drew
just to let your conscience screw it up.
I had to poison you.
I don't believe you.
I don't believe you'd do that to me.
That's just the neurotoxin
eating away at the part
of your brain that allows
you to believe things.
Are you feeling weak?
Is your heart racing?
Is your mouth getting dry?
You think you're more powerful
than me, don't you, Ryan?
Well, I have news for you!
Give me that! Never!
But I will let you have it!
Are you all right?
You... saved me.
Why did you save me?
It was the right thing to do.
After everything I did to you?
I will never understand humans.
But this is the reason why we
will ultimately defeat you.
Wilfred, focus.
What did you poison me with?
Theobromine.
Oh, my God!
You've heard of it?
No, but it sounds terrible.
I still can't believe you poisoned me.
I still can't believe
you bopped me on the nose with a newspaper.
Bopped, Ryan!
I never wanted to dominate you.
I just didn't wanna be dominated by you.
Oh.
If I make it through this,
I'm gonna start listening to my gut more,
and you're just gonna have to accept that.
Understood, mate.
Hell, maybe you're onto something
with all this conscience stuff.
I'm even starting to
think I should stop doing
that god-awful thing to your mouth guard.
What thing? What did you do? Shhh.
Conserve your energy, mate.
WOMAN Dr. Kakel, call the operator.
Well, it looks like you're okay, Mr. Newman.
Your blood tests showed zero toxicity.
But I ingested a large
quantity of theobromine.
So did I, at lunch,
when I had a Hershey bar.
Theobromine's just a
chemical found in chocolate.
So, it's not poisonous?
Only if you're a dog.
Chocolate?
Ask him about the raisins.
I put raisins in there, too.
Well, it's official,
Jenna forgave Drew.
They're back together.
I'm sorry to hear that, Ryan.
I'm sorry for both of us.
If it's any consolation,
I promise not to try to kill you again.
I appreciate that.
I wouldn't drink that if I was you.
I'll get you a fresh beer.
I'll just pour this one out.
Ah! Ah!
Ah...!
Ah!
What's wrong, mate?
I'm still thinking about Jenna.
I know what'll cheer you up.
Bear, come here.
I want you to meet my friend Ryan.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net
Enjoy Movies, TV Series and Live Sports
Signup Here -> WWW.ADMITME.APP