Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Based on actual events.
USSR, June 1985.
It's uncommon to see welding and
not to hear its sound. I love her sound.
Shykhshyhshyh?
You're good at it.
Excellent welded.
Only melted pieces remain on
metal. You see, they come to the opposite side.
I see.
There is not much film left. Light, smile.
A pair of historical frames.
You look great.
Guys, let's round off already.
You are 4 hours 10 minutes in open space.
- And what about the Earth?
- We will enter the zone in a couple of minutes.
We begin to gather slowly.
That's interesting,
if one day one has to leave
Earth, can he live in space?
Continue your family, raise children,
find a livelihood, fall in love?
Make love in outer space.
Probably, someday and such
the experiment will be conducted by mankind.
Invent some kind of simulator for
preparing cosmonauts for ... love
"Cosmonaut Ivanov held a record
amount of time in the simulator »
- Yes, there will be a new space record.
- Enough is enough.
So, fellow cosmonauts,
what kind of simulators are there?
By the way, you weld
in outer space.
Dawn, we're done. Going back.
So go back to the station.
What about oxygen?
There are 15 more minutes.
I thought we were out of communication.
It was awkward.
I thought so too, but I decided to give
possibility of cosmonaut Lazareva
personally present the project
for management's consideration.
The idea was accepted for consideration,
Next year we will start preparing.
Comrades, a woman for the first time in open space
- and she jokes, laughs, speaks of love!
I would applaud the cosmonaut Lazareva.
In the MCC, by the way, she is already applauding.
- Ay!
- What's the matter?
Light, freeze! Do not move!
- What happened?
- I pierced the glove.
- Hold your hand, do not move.
- I am doing my best.
Burr from welding through the glove
pierced. And sticks on both sides.
"What's the pressure?"
- It's falling.
You, the main thing, do not twitch.
"Volodya, can you cut the metal neatly?"
"It's already being done."
"How's the pressure?"
- 0.7 atmospheres.
Normal pressure. Hand come on.
And let's go quietly,
as for a walk. As in the Arbat.
That's right, past the house of the book.
Opposite the restaurant is Prague.
We turn to the boulevard.
Light, talk to me
I'm talking with you...
"Volodya, you do not have more than two minutes for everything."
- It's OK, we'll be in time.
Well, recall how silver
according to Mendeleyev's table?
- What?
- Silver on the table ...
- Argentum.
"And mercury?"
- Hydrargyrum.
- Right! I always confuse them with each other.
- Guys, I do not see you. Where are you?
- Getting close.
We are going to the cinema?
Oh sure.
There are very few left.
We can go to the "Autumn Marathon".
"Are you coming in?"
- Yes, we are.
- Do you like the Autumn Marathon?
- I Love ... "Autumn Marathon" ...
Hold on, Light ... Hold on, dear ...
That's all.
How's the pressure?
Are you coming in?
Lazarev! Fedorov!
Are you online? Reception!
Guys, are you inside or not yet?
What's happening?!
It's hard for me to explain this
from the point of view of the laws of physics.
Vladimir Petrovich, you yourself
think how it looks from the outside.
Astronaut Lazarev almost died
from the fact that you saw the light,
and he eclipsed your consciousness.
If I write so in the report,
It will greatly affect your future
in the space detachment.
Maybe they were angels?
How do you like this answer?
Are you joking?
If I were joking, you would laugh.
When you flew by the Soviet Union,
Have you thought about Olya and me?
Uh-huh.
Everytime?
Everytime.
What, 16 times a day?
Even more.
I did not think about you only,
when flying over Madagascar.
And what were you thinking about Madagascar?
I thought it would be if I was from outer space
I'll land in Madagascar.
Probably, the local Papuans will see,
as I fall, find me
and make the leader of his tribe.
And I'll tell them about space,
about the stars, about the universe ...
... and a little about what
I had a life in the USSR.
And what was your life like in the USSR?
Well, tell me.
I love you.
I want you back.
to life on Earth.
I'm trying to.
- How is it?
- Volodya, here is the Earth. Here, objects fall down.
- Let's go to.
- Wait, it's awkward ...
Something at me the signal was gone.
Renouncement!
The telemetry system does not work!
- The temperature sensors cut down!
- And radio electronics too!
The battery packs do not respond.
I see, I see, the failure of all systems. Calmly,
without panic! Reboot the system.
"What could have happened to it?"
"The signal is gone."
"How much communication is there?"
- Three hours and almost six minutes.
Come with me. All with me!
Valera, photos from telescopes on Gagarin.
I can not see a damn thing. Either she, or not she.
- Maybe her Americans were shot down?
- Yeah, hell they're going to hit her ...
And if this is their SDI, if
"Star wars" launched?
You call the Ministry of Defense?
No, I want to cancel shish kebabs for tomorrow. So,
connect me with the Ministry of Defense!
The Russians completely lost control
over its orbital space station.
Salyut-7 turned into an unmanageable
a space object weighing 20 tons.
While no one can determine how long Soviet
The station will stay in orbit in this mode.
According to experts in the near future
the station will begin to fall precipitously.
When and where is the Soviet space
will the station drop to Earth?
There is a high probability that she
can fall on the United States,
The fall of the station to the locality
will lead to numerous victims.
When falling to the ground, the station
can destroy a whole region.
We hope that the Russians themselves
will be able to solve their problems,
but we, too, will not waste time in vain,
we will develop our action plan ...
Comrade Shubin, how could this happen,
that in the midst of the Cold War,
we, suddenly, lose the most important
a strategic object in space?
We, unfortunately, do not know yet,
what happened, we try to understand.
If you do not know what happened, respectively,
you do not know what to do. This is true?
We know what to do. You need to fly
to the station, and there already to understand.
Well, when will you fly?
The station will be in orbit for another three months.
We will prepare.
"We do not have time for this."
- And what's the rush?
We received information,
that NASA has designated a start
Challenger for 30 number.
That is, after 22 days.
Take a look.
This is our station Salyut-7.
Weight 20 tons. The size is 15 by 6 meters.
And this is the American shuttle "Challenger".
The size of the cargo area is 15 by 6 meters.
The capacity is 20 tons.
Funny coincidence, is not it?
And here's another funny coincidence.
This is the new member of the Challenger crew.
Our Frenchman Patrick De Bonel.
I flew with Fedorov to Salyut-7.
Still friends with him, and even parcels
he sends it. With chestnuts and smelly cheese.
Patrick knows Salyut-7 as well
as our guys.
And if the Americans seize our
station, is that what will be, the invasion?
Not just an invasion.
We will have to answer.
Valery Petrovich, you understand that we can not
allow the Americans to land at our station.
If you are not ready to fly, we
will be forced to knock it down with a rocket.
If you destroy it, then the fragments from this explosion will lead to
All satellites that are in orbit are out of order.
We will lose space. Well, 10 years at least.
We can not destroy the cosmos.
Valery Petrovich, prepare the crew.
Today marks fifteen years
Since the moment of entering the first orbit
space station "Salyut".
Now a new modification of this station -
"Salyut-7" successfully works in near-earth orbit.
Her flight is on schedule
program in automatic mode
without the crew of astronauts.
The whole system is monitored
from the Earth Center for Flight Control.
The station rotates on two axes.
Approximately 1 degree per second
- How can you dock with her then?
- Fedorov would have docked
Manually docked only
Lazovoy, Fedorov, and Plakhov.
Astakhov has many hours of training.
But why guess? It is necessary to plant
guys on the simulator,
and work out the docking
with a rotating station.
Yes, we must try.
We call Valer, Fedorov?
For Fedorov, the space is closed by doctors.
We try the rest.
- Something does not bite.
- Maybe the fish had a hibernation?
We must start warming up. And then I have
now, too, winter hibernation will begin.
It's with pleasure.
Victor Petrovich! Comrade Alyokhin!
We are looking for you everywhere, you
urgently call in the detachment.
Now!
"Well, we must get ready."
"Why do you need them so urgently?"
The medical commission must have passed.
Volod, pick up the fishing rod, please.
And what about the medical board did not say?
So what can I say?
How many times have I been dragged to this
medical board, and then in duplicates.
- Thought I would be upset that they did not call me?
- To be honest, that too.
You ohrenel, Vyt?
You decided that I would be upset,
that you are called, but I do not?
Decided to pity me?
And you know, you're not an astronaut at all,
you were not even in outer space.
You're an engineer in a spacesuit.
Be healthy.
- Hello, Vit.
- Kind.
- Listen, and what is your wife's time then?
"Thirty-one weeks and three days."
- Four days.
- Four...
Four days, yes.
"So this is about to begin, is not it?"
- Yes.
Wow, we've transferred you from backups
in the main crew.
Thank you.
We want you to fly to the Salute.
- So I'm ready.
"Only this is not a planned flight."
- What happened?
- It happened, Vitya.
We lost contact with the station.
We do not understand what happened to her.
You did it with your own hands,
so you know her better than anyone else.
"And who is the commander?"
- And who would you like to fly with?
With Fedorov.
Do not make sudden movements. Repeat the trajectory
movement of the docking unit. Well and further on sensations.
Wahler, come on like this. Docking -
with you a bottle of cognac.
- Dock - from me a box.
- Have agreed.
We stick together ...
Yes b ...
"Gene, try not so fast."
- Go.
We modeled the visual
micromodel of station rotation.
The ship will have to repeat exactly
the trajectory of the station's rotation and so to dock.
Theoretically, of course, this is possible,
but, I'm afraid, only theoretically.
Come on, come on, come on...
We remove one seat. Instead of him
in addition we load fuel, food, water.
In space, each gram is worth its weight in gold.
Less food, water, less oxygen.
And there will be fewer casualties, if that, yes?
Guys, well, it's impossible.
No, Valery Petrovich, it will not work.
Imagine that you stop by the garage.
Here, it's going to be a car.
And the gate you first so,
then so, so, still so ...
You're more pampered with her, well,
as with a woman!
Valer, I'm with a woman who rotates
on all its axes, have not tried it yet.
I'm not sure that someone will do it.
Well, who is our next commander?
The commanders ended up with me.
The entire detachment was tried.
Hello, Volod!
"Oh, Valer, she's well."
- How are you?
- Nothing, nothing. How are you?
- Yes, it's okay like it.
Heard, we have difficulties
with sending the crew to the "Salute"?
Docking can not? I heard.
Do you think this is even possible?
- Does it rotate strongly?
- Strongly.
More degrees on all axes.
Valera, you're a pilot.
You know everything.
Okay. Glad to see.
I'm going to teach young people.
Volod, if you had to fly?
Everything is complicated there ..
It fits me
Tomorrow morning to the medical board.
I will only replace one light bulb
and immediately back. At once.
And someone else can not
to send a light bulb to change?
I'm the best engineer. You know.
You are deceiving me. The best engineer
Do not just send a light bulb change.
- My little?
- You're hiding something.
That's what I'm hiding from you, what?
That something had happened there.
Something serious.
That all refused to fly,
and only you, the fool, agreed.
So ... Pregnant that you can not do?
You can not be nervous.
- What are you doing?
- I'm nervous.
Stop, please. Oh please.
Well, do not be nervous.
Here, fly, take with you.
- Into the space?
- Yes.
- Honey, well, we do not go skiing on skis.
- So, without talking!
There is.
Two hats! Come here.
Give the menu, please.
- They say that Gorbachev introduces a dry law.
- Yes I know. I'm a little bit.
For what we drink?
I'm flying tomorrow to Baikonur with Vitya.
Are you kidding?
- In a week into space.
- You're written off.
It happened.
They can not cope without me.
You need to manually join.
Everything will be fine. Do not worry.
Come on, you know where!
Nin ...
Tell me what's wrong with you
this cursed cosmos,
on what did you exchange us with Olya?
I confirm the readiness of the spacecraft to launch.
The spacecraft is switched to onboard food. Seventh.
The report of the seventh was adopted, the first
First, there is a farm break
lateral blocks, the seventieth
The report of the seventieth was adopted, the first
Start is enabled.
Bleed one.
Purge. Bleeding 2.
The key to drainage.
Inflating.
Earth-board. The mast has departed.
- Start!
- Ignition!
Preliminary.
Intermediate.
The main thing.
Climb!
Good goes, beautiful!
How are the fluctuations?
The oscillations persist.
The car goes rigidly, but surely.
Tangazh, yaw, rotation - normal.
Management System Parameters
the launch vehicle is normal.
There is a reset of the DAS CAC.
There is a department of the first stage.
There is switching off the engine of the side blocks.
There is a deactivation of the side blocks.
Stabilization of the product is stable.
Pamirs, and what is that you have there dangling?
It's an Olympic bear, Dawn.
My daughter gave me.
- Talisman?
- Indicator of weightlessness.
For good luck!
There is a branch of the head fairing.
There is a department of the main stage.
There is a shutdown of the main engine.
There is a tail drop.
Well, guys, you're in orbit! Congratulations!
Congratulations, Dawn!
Today at seven in the morning Moscow time, came out
into orbit the Soyuz-T-13 spacecraft.
Daddy flew into the sky.
The crew of the ship is to be carried out
docking with the orbital complex Salyut-7,
carry out planned studies
and experiments
for the benefit of the world and all Soviet people.
In the Khabarovsk kravo
Komsomol organization ...
- I do not see her yet.
"She's still in the shadows."
Soon it should appear in about 90 degrees
right on the pitch and somewhere around 10 degrees in the yaw.
We wait.
Not yet ...
There she is. I can see it.
Well, turn the ship around.
Let us take a look.
I'm taking aim.
Here it is, dear.
And we see.
Let's go quietly.
1600 meters. Approximately through
5 minutes we will be at the station.
Fly at a distance
Two hundred meters and there hang.
There is.
- Can we start to extinguish the speed?
"It's early yet."
Gashu the lateral speed.
I give 2 meters per second for braking.
Dawn, you see her?
We see.
Rotation by pitch approx.
1.5 degrees per second.
This is even faster than we expected.
Dawn, pay attention, solar panels
deployed in different directions.
Yes, we see.
- Stepanovich?
- It's not clear yet.
Sash?
"We'll have to take pictures." Then we will analyze.
- We do.
Pamirs, with fuel more poetic.
There are no more than three attempts to join.
I understand you, Dawn.
- Still back on something you need to return.
- Yes. Well, with God?
So, Pamirs, start docking!
Go.
"We're going to the mooring."
- I put forward the docking rod of the docking mechanism.
The distance to the site is 32 meters.
We go to the dock.
Lead, crash!
No docking.
- Lead, lead!
- I see, I'm taking them away, I'm taking them away! Calm down!
- Strongly collided?
- Not much. We almost braked.
So, Pamirs, you are now
go into the radioten,
rest better.
And we'll confer here, we'll think about it.
Until the connection.
"I understand you."
- There is.
We'll take a look at it externally.
So. If you start moving from 11 meters
at a speed of 35 centimeters per second,
it will be exactly a quarter of a turn.
And, in principle, we will be able to catch the knot.
- What are you doing?
- I'm trying.
I select the speed. You suggested it yourself.
- You can not go without a team.
- Nothing. We will rehearse a little.
Did you hear what the earth said?
"Let's do an external inspection of the station."
- I understood.
By longitudinal station
rotates in one plane.
Estimated docking speed
15 centimeters per second.
This is not enough for the ship
adjust to the station and catch its rotation.
Let's try to catch the movement.
Let's take a closer look, as they say.
Recheck the readiness of the docking systems.
This is just a rehearsal.
At the same time we'll take a closer look at the station.
So you do not need to reduce the speed, you need it
increase the opposite. A minimum of 3 times.
At least to 35 centimeters per second.
- Is the system ready?
- The system is ready for docking.
Let's go quietly.
110 meters. The speed is 34 centimeters.
Speed ??35.
At this speed, if not coincide, slow down
just do not have time, and this is a guaranteed collision.
35 ... We'll break the ship.
We must return them, damn it.
It's dangerous, Volodya!
You understand, Vitya, every inch here
important. Literally every centimeter.
A little left-right, up-down, forward-backward,
back and forth ... and not a fig. Do you know what I mean?
"We're taking a risk, Volodya."
- Quietly, quietly, quietly ...
Well, dear, will we kiss?
Gashi. Gassy speed! We'll crack!
There is a docking. There is a mehzahvat.
We begin the contraction. Victor!
Now let's calm down.
Why do we have to go around uselessly?
You're crazy crazy!
We docked.
I refuse to continue the flight
together with you, you hear!
Whither, where will you get to?
Valery Petrovich! Valery Petrovich, connection.
Pamirs, reception.
Dawn, I'm Pamir-1. I hear you.
- How are you feeling?
- Excellent.
Pamirs, look. Generally,
we are here to consult ...
Earth, do you already have an image?
Not yet.
We docked.
I mean, did not you understand?
Docking of the Soyuz-T13 and
station Salyut-7 produced successfully.
The contraction is complete.
Reported by the commander of the ship Pamir-1.
Your mother.
Ready to test for leaks
and to the transition to the station.
How do you hear me, Zarya? Reception.
Well, guys, you give!
And we were afraid.
And you need to change your shirt.
Pamirs, I congratulate you, you fellows.
But let's somehow the next time together.
- There is. Accepted.
"So, comrades, we are preparing for the transfer to the station."
We entered the docking station.
Ready to go to the station.
Here is the order.
Open the hatch?
- Valery ...
- Wait a second.
Vitya, you know, like in Georgian, well, wait?
Wait, well!
- Pamirs, reception ...
"Dawn, welcome." The Pamirs are in touch.
Pamir 1 does not enter, Pamir comes in. 2.
Dawn, and what's the matter? Why can not I?
- Can not. The Pamir comes in. 2.
- Guys, give it up. We go in together.
Volod, if something happens to you,
Vitya will not be able to drop the station into the ocean.
This is a necessity,
which we must fulfill.
There is.
Close, Vov.
Come on.
Guys, if, with me, suddenly what will happen,
drown me in the Indian Ocean.
From childhood I dreamed to be there.
Coconuts, bananas ...
"Put off the coconuts!"
- There is.
- Open the pottyhonechku.
- I'm opening it.
Pamir 2, the pressure?
670 mm.
Spits a little.
The pressure drops.
I continue to open.
550 mm. Continues to fall.
- Valera!
- A?
- Critical. It is necessary to close!
- To open? Open it!
- Where to open ?! Close it!
- Vitya ...
- Victor!
- Pamir - 2!
Earth, Earth, I can not hear you.
My ears have been poured from a differential pressure.
Pamir-2?
"Where are you?"
- The Earth, I'm Pamir-2. I'm at the station.
There is no depressurization. But there's ice all around.
In the sense of? What do you mean?
What ice, Vitya?
It is very cold in here.
And what about the instruments? What data?
- On the manometer 530.
"Try the lights on."
Why are you silent? What is there with the light?
Pamir-1, Volodya? Reception
Brothers, yes, there's a knockout.
"Volod, are you at the station?"
- Yes, I'm at the station.
- Well, what is it?
"She's all in the snow."
Do not understand. In what snow?
Are you laughing?
The most ordinary snow.
In places in a centimeter thick.
Guys, but can you see the inside of the panels?
Inside the panels is ice. This is not a station,
but a freezer.
Where did the ice come from?
It looks like "Spring" jerked.
What is the temperature?
Yes, the devil only knows.
The gradient is electronic.
Spit.
"You're cold?"
"It's frozen."
Where did you spit on the porthole?
He spat at me. But I did not.
So, Pamirs, listen to me carefully.
Fly while back on the ship and hang up.
You did not sleep well for a day.
There is.
Well, hello, home.
"Welcome". Did you write?
No, Sveta wrote.
Well, comrades, what thoughts?
- Yes, what thoughts can there be,
"It's not a station anymore, it's just scrap metal."
The guys could have done it ...
but a matter of time.
First they need to warm up the station and melt. And on
this, with the charge of one battery, will take at least 2 days.
"When it melts, everything will be in the water, all the appliances."
"So they will dry it." The question is, how many?
Well, even if they dry, and then
what? All the electronics to touch?
There Alekhine. He this station
I collected my own hands!
- There food for only 10 days.
- It's great that they do not have 10 days?
What 10 days? The station is below zero temperature!
They will not last so long.
They will bask on the ship.
There plus twenty.
Valery Petrovich, oxygen will come from
ship. Hence, the transition hatches will be open.
With such a temperature difference,
the ship will cool very quickly.
They will not last a week.
What Russian peasant will frighten the frost?
"Valery Petrovich, you're Russian."
- Well?
Now if you, the Russian peasant,
lock in your garage in the cold, in the winter
without hot tea and with ice-cold food,
How much will you stretch?
Day? Five?
Pamirs, reception.
Dawn, as you hear me, reception.
Good morning!
We here conferred and understood,
that the most correct decision,
It is to throw the station into the ocean and
to bring you back to Earth.
Dawn, but we are already here. Give us
work at least a couple of days.
Yes, there are a couple of days that is not enough.
Too much risk.
Valera, listen to me,
if you were in our place,
you would just be back home now, right?
- "2 days".
- Valera,
Pamirs, let's do it.
You have five days.
On the sixth, if we do not find a solution,
dump the station into the ocean
and fly home.
There is. Accepted. End of communication.
This week it became known that
Russians are sending a rescue expedition
to his dead station.
"Has the air gone?"
- Come on! Breathes like in the mountains of the Caucasus!
But the American specialists practically
sure that there is no chance to save the station.
Creepy dope ...
This requires a level of technology
still not accessible to mankind.
Natasha, look,
with each turn the temperature
on the ship falls to 0.2 degrees.
So that in all news there is information about
that our cosmonauts are doing well.
Experts believe that the operation
Russian is doomed to failure.
Today everything will be done.
This means that the Soviet
cosmonauts will die.
"But this is unlikely to convince the Americans."
- So, let them speak more convincingly.
Orbit station passes
across the entire territory of the United States.
It is possible that the Russians
the station may have weapons
and, perhaps, even nuclear.
And then the consequences of this
falls can be comparable
with the explosion in Hiroshima.
It might look like this ...
Sergei Mikhailovich, the Americans are preparing
to launch an empty shuttle.
Empty cargo hold. Empty flies.
Dawn, you need a radiator directly
connect to a solar panel,
turn to the sun,
then we get an additional charge
and start heating the station.
The volume of the station is 80 cubic meters.
40 watts per meter in cube
will be 3.2 kilowatts.
We will have a maximum of half.
The day is at a minimum to
3 degrees warmed up.
And above 5 it will not rise, unfortunately.
Not Sochi, of course, but still.
I'm starting the U-turn.
Have jumped. Come to the left!
We are in space! Where to the left?
For us? By the sun? On the batteries?
Oh, of course, by the sun!
And slower, Vova.
- Hush hush. Stop! Brake!
- I fixed it.
Has earned. Try it.
Fuck.
You see, engineer!
In the spacesuit.
Your mother.
Handsomely.
Cold.
Let's try something.
Well ka. So effective.
See that water on the ship does not
has flown in, it's all to hell.
We're watching.
I'm on the attack, Victor on the gate.
Blow off the water to the engine compartment,
then we will clean.
Eh, we would like several
cleaners with rags.
With this, my brothers, it is taut, of course.
And music is fun for the mood.
Well, we'll organize the music for you right now.
And about rags, you have there than to get hold of yourself:
kombezy, additional. clothes, well, and so on.
Volod, and there is much water there in general?
Valer, how can I tell you.
Uncensored quantity.
Okay, and here's the music for you.
"Wahler, is there anything else?"
- Come on, okay, we joked.
- Oh, another matter.
"That's much better."
- Volodya,
- Yes
- Try to blow ventilation.
- Come on.
Dry like.
Opa.
Victor! Lock the hatch, come on!
Come on! Lock the hatch!
Pamirs, reception. Collected the water?
Yes, almost collected. Only
all rags have already ended.
Even personal things in the course allowed.
Is it warm on the ship?
Well, warmer than at the station.
Tolerant, in general.
Do not forget to measure the temperature
and drink vitamins.
Good good. Do not forget.
Look, do not burn your hands.
- How many do you have?
- Yes, 36.6.
- And you have?
- As many.
Look, see how there between
bags over the sofa,
is there what?
- Good joke.
- And you open it, open it.
How did you carry it?
You fly from mine, you can donkey
in space to take.
Stunned.
Well, on a small? For warming.
"On Earth, it's a dry law."
- The same on Earth. It does not apply to us.
We are still on the territory of the USSR.
Outside the window, like, the police do not fly.
And the truth does not fly.
Well then, give one more.
Volod, you see no one but us?
Cockroach. The first in space.
And I already thought everything, carbon dioxide
breathing in, glitches have begun.
Also what with it to do?
On Earth, I would have crushed it.
It's a pity after all, fellow countryman.
Well, fellow countryman, will you be third?
Stepanich, what are we fighting for, eh?
Why do we risk children.
It's a piece of iron.
20 tons of iron and all.
This is the reputation of Soviet cosmonautics.
Vova Komarov,
Yura Dobrovolsky, Vitya Patsayev,
Vladik Volkov. I remember
about them every day.
Every time I think we should
were made to return them.
- Here's the reputation.
- Then, we could not do anything.
And now I do not understand. What I should do?
I'm not there. I do not see what they see.
I can only hear them.
20 minutes every half hour.
And then with interference.
You can make the right decision.
Bring them back.
Is this the right decision?
They are the best guys.
They are created for the cause,
which is now being done.
And this concerns their honor.
And the honor of their country.
And then it's not just 20 tons of metal.
"Pamirs, do you hear me?"
"Dawn, welcome." We hear you.
How are you?
We clean the components of electric circuits.
How much more water is left?
Yes, it comes out from all angles.
We catch it by drop.
- Pamirs, and you rested?
- Yes. Yes, they rested.
So, go to the ship
and hang up. Without rest it is impossible, children.
Not until the rest, Valer. You would have seen,
that here it is created.
While the water is not understood,
it is better not to stop.
That's an order.
- Good. Only the chains will ring and immediately
... - Guys, and how did CSKA play?
What CSKA? And, we'll find out the account.
- Valery Petrovich ...
- A little bit later.
Valery Petrovich! They both have a temperature
under 38, it's time to start antibiotics prick.
And be sure to have a hot tea, you hear me! Them
you need at least a day not to leave the warm ship.
My dear, they have nothing left.
Now they chain will ring, and all they will have - and tea
hot, and warm, and half board, and Sochi - everything will be!
- Do you even understand what is at stake?
- Yes, I understand.
Take it.
Now the battery is connected to solar
batteries, and start the station.
- There is a contact.
- Has a reorientation begun?
Now the sensor is trying to find the sun.
To make the batteries unfold to him.
Do you hear, did the gear go for a turn?
I can not hear.
Sorry the recorder does not work ...
Inside everything is fine.
I say, we must go out into space
doing external inspection.
At the next communication session
Pamir-1 comes out, get ready.
He opened the hatch. The pressure is normal.
Excellent.
So, I'm outside.
The station photo shows minor distortions
The shape of the sensor orientation of solar cells.
Start checking with him.
Accepted. I'm starting to move.
- Get around the middle battery on the left.
"I understand, I walk around to my left."
And here nothing has changed. Everything is familiar.
- The same Earth, the same Sun?
- Yes, all the same.
Batteries are worn out, of course, strongly.
Like sails after a circumnavigation.
Well, cosmic dust is normal.
It is necessary to replace. Volod, move to the sensor.
I understand you, I'm moving.
The body of the station is corroded.
Aging, beautiful.
It's too early for her to grow old.
Where are you, above the control room?
Yes, I turn to the body of the working compartment.
"Can you see the sensor already?"
"Not yet, I'm moving to him."
"Are you watching the pressure?"
- Yes, it's normal.
- Dawn, it's all clear.
"Well, have you found it?"
Found. It seems that I found.
Vitya, you were right.
What, sensor?
Yes. Battery orientation sensor housing
bent. Pressed against the surface of the station.
How could this happen?
- Traces are there?
"What about without them, Sash!" You would have seen it.
Scratch your finger in three thicknesses to the sensor.
Asteroid?
Well, what else could it be?
It looks like the truck drove in.
And it will turn out?
Unscrew, I'm afraid, will not work.
You can not get close to the nuts. They are pressed.
And if you beat her off?
Guys, there's a thick metal,
you can not beat him like that.
Let the technicians repeat the same
position of the sensor on the layout.
I'll do it now.
Okay, guys,
it's good that they found the reason.
We will think what to do.
Come back for now.
I would stay here for now. I would have examined the station.
I have enough oxygen, which I will
go here to run, the atmosphere to waste.
And while you are thinking about the next
session decide what to do.
Confirm the connection, the reception.
Pamir, can you hear me?
Dawn, dawn, I'm Pamir-1, reception.
Vitya, have you lost the Earth, too?
Victor, answer me, reception.
Pamir-2, I'm Pamir-1,
how do you hear me, reception?
Victor! Pamir-2!
Victor.
Dawn, we have smoke at the station!
Victor! Victor!
Dawn, we have a fire on the ship!
Victor, Vitya, put on your spacesuit! Obgorish!
Victor! Dock the ship for fuck!
Close the hatch and shoot!
Shooting until the station caught fire!
Hold on! Hold on.
Victor!
Come out come on.
- Why are not you sleeping?
- I'm fine, but why are you awake?
Pamirs, reception. How do you hear me?
This is the Earth, answer.
Pamirs, reception.
Volodya, Victor. How do you hear me?
Valery Petrovich, station in the shade,
there is no connection.
Well, comrades, it's time.
It's time to decide something ...
- We will wait for the next communication session.
- We have been waiting 8 hours.
Because of your haste, we are without
training flew,
so now we will wait
as much as we need, okay?
Do you think that I do not know what it is
you left the astronauts at the station,
when he could and should return them!
It's you who ditched them!
Stop it!
I'll see, I'll make sure
you answered for all this!
And I will not look at the fact that you
Hero of the Soviet Union!
Twice a hero.
And if necessary, I will answer.
You answer.
CNN broadcast the launch
American Shuttle.
Display on the big screen?
Have we seen their Shuttles take off?
So, in places. We are waiting for communication.
Vםt, how are you there?
The shuttle flew up the American shuttle.
Oh, Vitya, Vitya, you're not lightly sunburned ...
Yes, yes, we check.
Apogee 52 555 Perigee 25 554
Room temperature 0
- Temperature of the instrument compartment ...
- Dawn, I'm Pamir-1. Do you hear me?
- Dawn,
- Pamirs, reception.
- this is Pamir 1.
"Pamirs, welcome!" The Pamirs are in touch!
Pamirs, reception, we listen to you!
"Welcome, Volodya!"
- Yes, Valera.
What's wrong with you? You were not connected for 9 hours.
We had a fire. The ship was burnt.
Vitya extinguished it by depressurization.
We're at the station now.
- How is he? What about Vitya?
- Scorched heavily.
"Is he conscious?"
- Yes, in the mind. Only the smoke heavily inhaled.
"Can you get on the ship and report the situation?"
- I can.
I'm worried about Vitya.
Vladimir Petrovich, Pamir-2
2 capsules of MP-24 and one BK-12.
Repeat after 6 hours.
OK I understood. Valer, in general, so ...
The oxygen supply station is burned out.
Most likely, the saber caught fire.
The ventilation system also does not work.
There is nothing to breathe. There is almost no air.
Look, on the ship though
anything works?
So, I'm checking. Central unit
data does not reflect.
The ship does not react to commands.
- Is the wiring fused too?
"Valer, everything is melted here."
Everything is not very good. I'm afraid that
You can not dump the station into the ocean any more.
The ship is now unmanageable.
Understand you.
Now we will think how
you to return to the land.
We can not allow Americans
to our station.
I agree.
We know what they need.
It is impossible to let Americans
Our advanced technologies have fallen into the hands.
So, we will shoot down the station before,
how the Americans will fly to it.
Comrades, do you remember, in general,
that there are two of our astronauts?
And what can you do?
Give me three hours.
- Has the control unit been opened?
- Opened it! Everything is melted here.
Bad. Disconnect everything,
until the batteries have sat down.
It is done.
- You heard?
- What?
Did you hear the sound of the docking?
Wait, you what, what docking?
We must open the hatch, the shuttle docked.
Whatever ...
American ship! I saw him
flying. He will help us, bring us back to earth!
Vitya, are you crazy? He can not
to us to dock!
He docked.
Victor, stop it! There is nothing there,
you can not open the hatch!
Let go! I heard the sound of docking.
You have misunderstood it!
This is a glitch! This is from lack of oxygen and from
obezbalivajushchego, that I have pierced you.
Let go, you bastard! It's you
to die here flew,
but I want to live! On Earth, you hear!
"Do not touch the pen!" Do not touch!
- Let go!
"There's no one there!"
- Let go, you bastard! Let go!
You have misunderstood it! It happens.
I also thought that the angels,
but there were no angels.
And remember ... remember you brought chestnuts?
I remember.
And what is in them such, I do not understand.
Potatoes are like potatoes.
Yes, I did not understand myself.
Technically undock
a ship by hand is possible.
There are pyrobolts. The team is mechanical,
there is no binding to electronics.
And how much will they fall?
Now they are at an altitude of 180 km perigee.
Through four turns they will cross the conventional boundary
with the atmosphere and will begin to fall precipitously.
And when they land?
In 67 hours and forty minutes.
With an error of 20 minutes.
The place of the fall?
Tentatively - here in this area.
"What does it mean in this area, it's the entire Indian Ocean!"
- It is not possible to calculate precisely.
"Valery Petrovich, they can not reach the ground."
- Why?
To restore the atmosphere at the station
they used almost all the oxygen.
Look, there are 5 cylinders left.
with oxygen for 4 hours - this is for 20 hours.
Plus large air tanks
mixture is at 40
And in gas masks 8 more hours.
Total 68 hours is in general.
For 34 hours for each.
How much do they lack in the end?
The same amount. And no more ...
What do you mean no! Which means no,
then we think! We think!
We communicate with the Pamirs, we search everywhere.
In every used cylinder!
Every breath of air,
every molecule of oxygen!
Valera, we checked everything.
We can only return one person.
And that is not guaranteed.
They have too little oxygen.
"One will be enough for one."
- What did you say?
They have 8 ampoules omnopon.
It depresses breathing and slows down
oxygen consumption.
One can definitely be returned.
That's just who to return?
The commander must remain on the ship.
Such an order.
It is necessary to undock exactly
at 17 hours, 34 minutes, 40 seconds
It is necessary to tell them now.
Otherwise they will not have time to prepare.
Sash, connect me in the office.
Volod, Vyt, can you hear me?
Dawn, I'm Pamir-1, we hear you.
How is Vitya?
In the mind.
He hears us?
No, he does not.
There is no time, I'm short.
You have little oxygen.
You can return only one to the ground.
Do you hear me?
Yes, I do.
Collect all the oxygen
and undock Alyokhin exactly
at 17 hours, 34 minutes, 40 seconds.
How did you understand me?
I understood you. Will be fulfilled.
It will land in the Indian region
of the ocean. The cruiser had already gone there.
- And how did CSKA play?
- I won from Spartacus. 2: 1.
It's good.
Well, see you then.
Volod,
forgive me.
And what were you thinking about Madagascar?
I thought it would be if I
from space will land on Madagascar?
Probably, the local Papuans will see
as I fall, they will find me,
and make the leader of his tribe,
but I'll tell them about space,
about the universe, about the stars,
and very little what I have
there was life in the USSR
And what was your life like in the USSR?
Well, tell me.
Daughter, wife, football
and the building of communism.
Yes, it sounds very boring.
Compared to the view from space
on the African continent.
But I love it all.
Nina!
- Hi!
- Hi.
Hey.
Something happened?
You need to talk to him.
Now...
"Hello, Nin.
- Hi.
- There they have problems, and we decided to give you
opportunity ... - I know everything. When is the connection?
They are in touch. Let's go to?
The Pamirs,
- Guys, Pamirs
- Yes, Dawn, welcome.
Volodya, Nina is here.
I want to talk to you.
"Nina, can you hear me?"
"Yes, I hear you."
Thank you for coming.
- How is Olya?
- She is here. She wants to talk to you.
Dad, hello, where are you?
"Hello, daughter."
- Dad, hello, where are you?
"You know, I'm far away."
- In the sky?
- Exactly, in the sky.
"Will you come back soon?"
- Well, at first I need something here
Finish - Okay then. We are waiting for you.
Volodya,
can you hear me?
I love you.
I love you too.
Come back.
There is nothing to breathe here. What for?
Well, it's time to undock.
You're flying home.
Every 8 hours you will stab yourself
omnopon from the first aid kit.
Then you have enough oxygen to the Earth.
You know how to undo manually.
You'll land somewhere in the Indian
the ocean. You've wanted to go there for a long time.
Why can not we both be together?
For two oxygen is not enough ...
I'm not going anywhere alone.
Do not say nonsense, your wife gives birth.
"I'm not going anywhere alone."
"And I order you."
We're wasting time.
Listen, we must go out into space and
gouging this sensor housing to the limit,
then the batteries will start working.
And we will get electricity.
Regeneration will give oxygen, and we
we can receive a rescue ship.
It is necessary only to gouge this case.
- Yes, than we gouged it, a sledgehammer or what?
- We did not even try to do it!
Listen, Vitya, you understand that if we go out and
do not break this body, no one will return home!
No one will have enough oxygen,
Do you understand this?
- I understand it.
"Well, let's go home."
If I return alone,
as I am to my child
in the eye I will look?
And how am I to your child
I'll look into my eyes?
Do not hold tight. Hands will be ill.
How do you know that I hold tight?
I, when I first left,
also held fast.
Hands then ached.
- Well, how about you?
- Well. As on the ground.
Vitya, it turns me.
Secure from the other side.
- Like this?
- Yes, it is.
Vitya, look, go no?
Just so far.
We enter the shadow of the Earth. Now
it will become very cold.
That's all, Vitya.
All.
Well, back to the ship
or will we stay here?
Never thought why
do some of the cosmonauts have births?
Well, like this. Thought.
All the tough guys, and some
the girls go out.
Well yes.
Maybe because the girls are cool?
There is no doubt about this.
And I do not even know how it is there
now. Can give birth already.
Look at least once.
No, Vitya. Once in a while it's not enough.
Yes, once - a little.
We will shoot down the station.
We did everything we could.
And you too.
As a child my father drove the forest.
In the cold, the chains were torn.
Viscosity decreases in the cold,
brittleness increases.
If you wait until the metal cools down
degrees to a hundred, it can crack.
Let's try.
Before sunrise can be done.
Come on.
Come on. Come on!
- Volodya, this is all
- Not all!
Yet!
Guys, your mother. Do you hear me?
We see you!
What are you doing there?
Dawn, I'm Pamir-1, I hear you.
We repair the station. Although no.
It seems that we fixed it.
Pamirs, reception. Why are you silent?
How was Lily?
Has given birth. Girl.
Congratulations,
Now you are a real astronaut.
This is the perfect order, yes, Volodya?
- How can we see now?
- Perfectly.
Come on, breathe. This is not visible, excellent.
Now, can you take off the caps?
And one minute without hats to stand?
Because we owe you all the same
show without hats.
It's all right. if you have
say something, then we are ready.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org