OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN
These people were set on fire
while they were still alive!
You must investigate this.
A young woman...very frightened.
Looking for help.
Making accusations.
Wild accusations.
What were these accusations?
Drugging and robbery.
Keep him a little sick
and he will do anything for you.
And murder? Yes.
KNOCK ON DOOR
I am searching for a woman
who has been looking for help.
WOMAN SCREAMS
MUSIC: Le Responsable
by Jacques Dutronc
PEOPLE CHATTER
# J'ai des soucis j'ai des ennuis
# J'ai des tracas
j'ai des tourments... #
Hey, Papa!
CAPTAIN WELCOMES PASSENGERS
IN FRENCH
Excuse me. Do you have a light?
Yes. Erm...
Please. Thank you.
So, I was given this diary
at the British Embassy.
Alongside a note
with your address on it,
which is how we came to find you.
I believe this diary belongs to...
..BELONGED to this man...
..Willem Bloem, or Wim.
You do know this man?
No.
Not really, Monsieur Knippenberg.
You did see...
..you did see this couple
at the same apartment as Gautier.
No. I didn't.
But I believe they were there.
Madame Gires.
Did you ever actually see them?
Sorry, but no.
Then why take did you take this?
Madam Gires, please.
Look. This man. Yes? This man...
He now looks like this. Hey.
What do you think you're doing!?
You brought us here?
Remember?
You're supposed to be helping us.
I...
Nadine...
I am sorry.
He didn't mean to be
so...insensitive.
But he found the bodies of these
two Dutch, do you see?
And he identified them.
It was awful for him.
We very much want to find out
what happened to them.
What happened to them?
The same thing that happened
to all of them.
What do you mean by that?
All?
All is more than two Dutch.
How many?
A number? How many people
are we talking about here?
I don't know.
Many.
HE SCREAMS
HE CHEERS
MOANING AND COUGHING
What? The radio here,
Alain gave it to me.
He gave it to me as a gift.
As a reward, you mean.
I brought clients to him.
To Gautier? Yes.
Clients for his gem business?
Yes. You see,
I used to take him
to parties at the Alliance Francaise
and introduce him to people there.
Alain is very good at going
to parties.
They all were.
Party, party, party.
You marry a chef,
get used to your own loneliness.
So, yes, I was lonely.
I think that is what he saw.
That he looked for it
in the people he met.
So, if you were lonely
or sad or lost,
whatever you may have needed,
even if you didn't know it yourself,
you see, he saw it.
And he fixed it.
It was like the sun shone on you.
Charles.
You call me Alain.
Ready to go to work?
Yeah.
Let me introduce you to Ajay.
Time to party, girls.
Hey, look who I found.
You have a girlfriend?
MUSIC: Funk #49
by James Gang
# Out all night, sleep all day
# I know what you're doin'
# If you're gonna act that way
# I think there's
trouble brewin'... #
You both look very handsome.
You live with these guys?
Yeah, they're cool.
7am.
As soon as it starts ringing,
I've got to go.
BANGING
MONKEY CALLS
STOMACH GURGLES
HE SIGHS
HE BREATHES DEEPLY
HE GROANS
CLOCK TICKS
CLOCK TICKS LOUDER
BELL PEALS
COCO SCREECHES
Coco?
You ought to be more careful,
Dominique!
It's medication for a grown man.
He was only a tiny little monkey.
What do you think is going on here,
Dominique?
You think we like having you
shitting yourself four times a day?
That we want to spend all of this
money on toilet paper?
No. Of course not.
Dominique is asking
that I return his passport.
I feel...I feel much better.
And I cannot stay with you
for ever, after all.
I went to Australia to, erm...
..try working on the boats.
I was travelling back to France
when you found me.
I don't buy gems, I have no money.
I want to finish my journey...
..and I want to go home.
Of course, I will change it
back for you.
As you can see,
I am very good at it.
But your tourist visa has expired
because you were too sick
to renew it.
And they will not let you
travel without it.
But don't worry, my friends at the
French Embassy owe me a few favours.
Stay close to the apartment.
If the police stop you,
you will go to jail for this.
Any more information you could give
us would be very helpful,
and information about the people
you mentioned coming and going...
Never mind about them for now,
Cloggy.
Tell me about him. Gautier.
That's his real name?
That's the only name
I heard him use, yes.
The same for Monique. Or Ajay.
He had the initials CS
on his shirts.
But maybe he stole them.
Ajay who is Indian.
Monique who is French-Canadian.
But what is Gautier? French, yes?
I thought so, yes.
He speaks like a Frenchman.
He said he went to school in France.
But he's also...
Yes. He talked about growing up
in Saigon.
And that he and Ajay met in India.
Right. And that's it -
perhaps he lived in Saigon,
perhaps he's from India,
but he's French.
And he might be called Gautier.
Where is he now?
We don't know.
We haven't seen him since Christmas.
But every night we are scared
they'll walk through the door.
Christmas.
That's over two months ago.
Herman, this is a waste of time,
it's... No, it is not.
He could be out there killing
people right now.
And we must take them to the
police station today.
No. No. No, we don't. Why not?
Major General Janthasin
of the Bangkok Central Division
has encouraged Herman to report
back. The one who said
he was welcome to keep on
investigating? Yes.
You have a very German
faith in authority,
but none of this is evidence, woman!
OK...
Well, over to you, then,
Mr Siemons, sir.
What is it you suggest we do?
You come with me to my car
where I will collect my pistol.
Then we find this might-be-yellow,
might-be-brown, whoever he is,
and I shoot him through the mouth.
We are not going to shoot him.
Then what are you going to do?
I can and I will find a way to
corroborate the details
she has given us elsewhere, I...
Like a report, then. Yes. Yes.
Like a report. The kind you take
to your ambassador?
Assemble statistics and costs?
Cross-reference your sources.
Yes. Yes. A case I can present
to Janthasin that will force
him to make the arrests.
You're a functionary.
A functionary whose efforts have
meant the parents of Wim Bloem
and Lena Dekker will now be able
to bury their children.
A functionary who at each turn was
told to leave it and forget them,
and who you now insult in his own
home! Angela. Angela. Please.
No! I won't stand for it.
My apologies, Mrs Knippenberg.
What? What? You don't think
we need him?
Paul. Paul, wait, please!
Paul.
We need to protect these witnesses.
I already told you how I'd do that.
Let me know if you change your mind.
I'm sorry if I upset
your new friend.
They think I've saved them now.
But what if Gautier returns
and finds them gone?
He'd be suspicious
and he would target them next.
We've a big house.
They don't have to go back.
They can stay here
until we've worked out what to do.
I don't know what to do.
I mean, Paul is right.
I am just a functionary.
That's not true.
You have valuable
and important qualities.
That fat Belgian mocked you for it,
but so what?
We'll do exactly as he said.
Assemble the information?
Research the facts?
Cross-reference our sources?
Write a report, Herman.
Nadine and Remi know more
than they realise.
Keep them talking.
Thank you.
Dominique, let's go to
the Santa Cruz.
You know what kind of girls
there are? Japanese girls.
German girls. Any kind of girl
you want, I'll help you get one.
I think I am just going to
stay here, Ajay.
You know you don't always have
to be a little pussy.
Do not call him that.
Huh? He's a nice person,
not a fucking pig like you.
Whoa. Take it easy, Monique.
Please don't get
sand in your vagina.
Oh, Jesus!
Shit.
DOOR BANGS
HE BREATHES DEEPLY
Hello?
THEY GIGGLE
Oh, hi, Dominique.
I am going to get dressed.
While the cats are away, right?
Alain said that he was taking
Monique to Pattaya for the weekend.
Said she deserved a break.
Which is weird, because it's
not like she ever does anything.
But I'm here.
If you need anything,
you let me know, OK?
OK.
Maybe tonight we can go out. Yeah.
OK. You want to join?
No. No, man.
LAUGHTER AND SPLASHING
THEY CHAT
Nadine! Ajay! Hey!
How are you doing?
DOOR CLOSES
And you had never been suspicious of
Gautier before this point, Nadine?
You said you liked him, you worked
with him, went to parties.
Yeah.
What changed your mind?
It's not what changed it.
Who.
Dominique.
Who is Dominique?
My friend.
And where is he now?
We don't know.
CLATTERING
DOOR OPENS
I would like to make a call to
France, please. Yes.
Telephone number?
LINE RINGS
HE WEEPS
SHOVE ON DOOR
LOCK RATTLES
HANDLE RATTLES IMPATIENTLY
BANG ON DOOR
AJAY: Dominique?
HANDLE RATTLES AGGRESSIVELY
Wakey-wakey.
RATTLING CONTINUES
Dominique. Open the door.
BANGING ON DOOR
I'm not going to say it again.
BANGING CONTINUES
One second. Open the fucking door!
CHAIR SCRAPES ACROSS FLOOR
Why did you lock the door? Er...
What happened to the lights?
Damn power cuts.
Alain wants to see you.
Now? Mm-hm.
SHE GROANS
Alain?
ALAIN: Have Wim and Lina
taken their medicine? Yes, Alain.
AJAY: Did you meet Stephane?
You would've liked her.
It's a good life that
I provide here.
I have been good to you.
Yes. Of course.
Then you understand
why it's hard for me
to accept that you just
want to leave.
I just haven't seen my parents
in so long, you know?
KNIFE FLICKS
Ajay, do you miss your parents
and want to go home?
No, Alain. I like it here.
You see,
Ajay understands what you do not.
What is it that I don't understand?
That the man you have become
is not the boy
your papa and mama waved goodbye to.
Your family. Your home.
You can never go back now.
You have been away too long...
..and seen too much.
Now, I know I said that
I would help you,
that I would fix your passport
and your visa.
But the truth is,
I don't want to help you leave.
You are not my friend, Dominique.
You are my brother.
And this is where you belong.
WOMAN CRIES OUT
ALAIN: Hurry up!
SHE RETCHES AND GROANS
Did Dominique say if Monique was
directly involved in the murders?
She drugged Dominique.
But murder? No.
When they left, before Christmas,
she looked scared.
Yeah, scared of going to jail.
No, scared of Alain.
Scared of what he may do to her.
I haven't heard from her since.
Ajay, has he told you what we're
going to do with her?
You can't take dogs on airplanes.
No, Monique, he hasn't.
Maybe we should drop her in a canal!
Monique needs a holiday.
Doesn't she, Ajay? All these guests
she has to care for.
How long are you going? I may return
for a day or two, here and there.
Don't worry, I have asked
Colonel Romyen to pass by from time
to time to check in on you.
OK.
Merry Christmas, Dominique.
Ciao!
Dominique?
SHOUTS: Dominique!
Shh!
Oui.
KNOCK ON DOOR
I think my neighbour is a murderer.
I tried to get
help from the embassies.
But nobody wanted to help me.
You are my only option.
The worst part is that we don't know
if Dominique made it.
He was so scared of running into
Alain coming back from Hong Kong.
So we said write to us
from France.
Let us know. Where?
Of course, not at the apartments,
because...
..in case it was intercepted...
Of course.
..but care of Poste Restante.
She goes every week.
But, erm...
Nothing. I'll go
and check my mailbox again today.
Well, we know how to check whether
he left the country, don't we?
Angela... I'm coming.
Do you remember me?
Mr Knippenberg.
This is my wife Angela.
She will translate.
I am looking for an exit stamp
of a French citizen.
Male. Rennelleau Dominique.
Someone left under his name
using his passport.
It might just as well have
been Gautier.
He forged it once.
He could have done it again.
You mean to actually travel on,
not just use his victim's
passports to cash their stolen
traveller's cheques?
Hold on... Sorry.
You remember a Dutch couple
last time?
A Miss Helena Dekker
and a Willem Bloem.
Nueng.
Erm, no. Herman, eat it.
Yes, that is them.
Both flew out on the same day,
18th December.
When we know they were both burned
alive in a roadside ditch
on 16th December.
Gautier must have flown as Willem,
and the girl as Lena.
I think he's killing people
and using their passports to
travel on to confuse the police.
Then what about Dominique?
Is he dead on a roadside
and the other one, Ajay,
now using his passport?
TANNOY: Air France flight 37 to
Paris is delayed.
Please wait for more information.
TANNOY: Attention, please.
Air France flight 37 to Paris
is now ready to board at gate 12.
SHOUTING
SHE SHOUTS
Have a great trip.
This is your seat.
So how was the trip?
It was beautiful.
And good for business, too.
Good news?
Yeah, it's just my father.
He thinks Remi doesn't make money
so he sends me cash!
And you've had
nothing from Dominique?
No.
Why would I?
It's only we, erm...
..we just got back and he's clearly
been gone for quite some time.
We were getting worried.
Did you see him?
No.
Is Remi with you?
No. He's working.
We have the car outside.
We can take you home if you like?
Yes, with pleasure.
I just need to, you know...
OK.
Nadine? Remi?
Godver...
Scheisse...
We can't possibly go.
It's the Ambassador's birthday,
it will be remarked upon
if we're not there.
And God forbid
we might be remarked upon.
Hey... Remi.
You're going to a party?
Yeah. A silly embassy thing.
There is documentation that
says Dominique left the country.
Actually, we don't know that it
was him that left.
We also have evidence that
suggests that Gautier
and Monique travelled on the
passports of my two Dutch.
Well, who knows where
they've ended up
and how many people
they have murdered...? Herman!
Yes.
Sorry, Remi.
Where is Nadine?
She went to check her mailbox again,
to see if Dominique has written...
..and she should have been home
an hour ago.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org