Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.
Welcome...
Ladies and Gentlemen.
My name is Israel
and I'm here
to take you to a fantastic world
filled with bizarre
and mythological characters.
Returned from a successful tour
across Europe
meet extraordinary creatures
capable of memorable and stupefying feats!
Because only at the Half Penny Circus
does imagination become reality.
And nothing
is as it seems.
Mommy!
Herr Franz...
My Lord...
My Lord.
It's your turn.
They are waiting for you.
Half of Rome came to hear you play.
I was in the future.
You must stop it with the ether.
I will stop only after I've found them.
They have extraordinary powers.
It will be my gift to the Führer.
Come.
Herr Franz...
Your trousers.
Irina, you do realize
it's the only hope of winning the war?
War has no winners, my Lord
only defeated.
Where are they hiding Irina?
Where are they hiding?
Rome!
- What the fuck are you saying?
- We don't say "fuck".
New York, America.
We're leaving.
- And us?
- You'll come with me.
Once we arrive in Sicily
we'll sell the cart and set sail.
What do you mean?
And the circus?
And the circus...
- I don't know.
- What the fuck are you saying?
All we'll need are travel papers
but with 300 liras apiece the Spizzichino
can make them better than the originals.
- 300 liras?
- Eh.
With 300 liras I can fuck
the best whores in Rome for a year.
I'll put them all in a row
and screw them.
In what world?
They'll be waiting for me
tomorrow morning in Via Caetani.
With 300 liras.
Just so I understand
once we arrive in America
without a circus
what are we going to do?
The freaks show?
I'm tired. How many years
can I go on doing this?
- The audience loves us.
- What audience, they're all dead!
Not even the tent is left.
But the war is ending.
Badoglio signed the armistice...
- And the worst is still to come!
- The king declared...
Who "King Little"? He's a coward.
He fled like a rabbit.
That's exactly what
you're asking us to do.
Since when are we responsible for
an entire country?
What are you talking about?
So let's join the German circus
they have a full house every night.
They say this Franz guy is incredible.
Yeah, the six fingered Nazi.
He's a crazy drug addict.
And what am I going to do at
a German circus?
A Jew at the German circus.
- Are you joking?
- What am I supposed to do?
Have you seen me?
Where do I go?
In America they wouldn't even
let me wash dishes.
You could be a sheep dog.
You'd be rich!
Shut up you filthy freak, you're so dirty
they wouldn't let you off the boat.
- What the fuck are you laughing at?
- Mamma mia you're ugly.
And you're Greta Garbo.
It's easy for you
because you're normal.
And you too.
What are you talking about?
I can't even touch you guys.
But for us it's different
without the circus we're finished.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is goddammit!
Without the circus we're only
a pack of freaks!
Calm down Fu.
I'll wash your dishes in New York.
Good evening Rome
welcome to Zirkus Berlin.
Matilde!
Matilde, what's wrong?
It's nothing, it's nothing.
I've told you a thousand times
not to touch me.
You didn't hurt me.
- It's dangerous.
- I didn't get hurt.
Don't touch me!
Come here!
Matilde!
I didn't get hurt,
come here.
You didn't hurt me.
Understand?
You are a special girl,
you should be proud.
"Special" at what?
At turning on light bulbs?
You have a gift.
Well I don't want it.
I hate it. I hate myself.
And on this Fulvio is wrong
because I'm the only real freak.
I don't want to hear that anymore.
That's enough.
You just have to make peace
with the past.
- Why not?
- Because I can't.
Anyway I know how things will
end up once we get to America.
- How will it end?
- Everyone will go his own way.
And how will I do without you?
I won't let you go.
You all are the best misadventure
that's ever happened to me.
So we won't split up?
No one will tear us apart.
Not even the war.
Now let's go inside
because my ass is frozen.
Let's go.
- Aren't you tired?
- No, we're hungry.
So we'd better fuck off
and get some sleep.
America.
Here.
Once we arrive
we're putting the circus back on its feet.
See you tonight.
Be careful.
Shalom.
Fulvio! There's a pig,
I swear. Fulvio!
A pig!
There he is!
Damn it!
Little black pork
with flour
with beans
and sheep's ricotta.
Maybe he stopped to get provisions
from some peasant.
That caciotta cheese
that I like
with a quart
or half a liter when possible.
- What if he was arrested?
- "Arrested" my ass.
That piece of shit fooled us
and went to America on his own.
- I gave him 300 liras...
- And me no?
- What are you talking about?
That damned vile jew,
tricked us with his little smile.
You're talking about Israel here,
he promised me.
If you say so...
Say what'?
He's like a father to us.
- Now you're going and trusting fathers.
- My father always used to beat me.
Mine locked me in a cage for 10 years.
At least I had some books.
Mine left me in front of a church
under a beehive full of bees.
The stings!
I was one big boil.
And who saved you without
expecting anything in return?
Israel saved you
and if it weren't for him
who knows where we'd be now.
- But who knows where he is.
- With my 300 liras goddammit.
That's enough!
You'd think you're talking about a bandit.
Worse... worse.
Israel is a good person
and he cares about us.
That's the tragedy of war kid.
It takes the best men
and turns 'em into the worst.
And so let's take care it won't
happen to us.
Let's go look for him.
Okay, but if we don't find him
we're all going to Zirkus Berlin
to Franz.
He isn't the strongest
but this son of a bitch
is one of the four.
I'm telling you.
Do you see the gills?
He can breathe underwater.
I'm sure it's him.
He has super powers!
He's drowning.
That's impossible!
Yesterday he did it for 20 minutes.
Breathe!
Breathe.
Breathe, please.
Hello!
Breathe.
Breathe, hey!
Hey, breathe!
Amon, hey, Amon.
I swear, he did it yesterday.
It's over.
Next week you return to Berlin.
Give me another month, please.
I'm almost there.
You've been looking for them
for three years
- and I can't cover your ass anymore.
- But this time it's different.
It's getting embarrassing.
The fort is needed to transfer soldiers.
What do you need it for
if you're going to lose the war.
I am our only hope.
They are our only hope.
We must get them on our side.
The ether has melted your brain.
Germany will be razed to the ground.
There will be a trial in Nuremberg,
you'll be condemned to die.
I see the future, Amon!
Me too. And I'm telling you that
yours is 1500 kilometers from here.
You're going home Franz.
I've already arranged a series
of concerts for you.
Fuck the music.
I want to be on the front lines with you.
Take care of yourself my brother.
- Hitler will kill himself.
- You've gone crazy, lower your voice.
He will shoot himself in the head.
Goodbye Franz.
- Do it for our mother.
- Stop that!
Amon.
Please, you can't do this to me.
Please, Amon.
Try to maintain a shred of dignity.
- You are a German!
- But you are my brother.
You can't do this to me.
I'll give you exactly one week
until the big show.
After that, if you haven't found them
you'll close down your shanty
and puppet show and go away.
- Got it?
- Yes.
And play something new.
Kesselring is all over my ass about
wanting to come and hear you play.
Okay.
Man, look how run down it is.
It's falling apart.
Let's go!
- Shut up.
- What's that, a party?
Come on, get in.
Let's go.
You on the truck!
Come on!
Forward.
On the truck, let's go!
Come on!
- Leave them alone!
- What are you doing?
What's going on?
They're combing the area.
- What do you mean?
- They're taking the Jews away.
All in a single line.
Come on, come on, come on!
Are you ready?
Hey!
- Can we load them up?
- Yes, everything's ready!
Come on, come on!
On the truck!
Hey!
Shit.
Another bullet wasted.
Move! Go, go!
Let's get out of here, come on, go!
Halt! Halt!
Anna!
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
We're street artists.
- Buskers?
- Yes.
You look like a fleabag to me!
- Have you seen anything like it?
- Look at him!
- What are you laughing at?
- Shut up!
They laugh because he looks like a dog.
- It's crazy, look at it!
- Do you see it?
Please, let us go.
No, no, no, little doggie!
Look at him.
Touch me again and I'll kill you.
Halt!
Or I shoot you.
- I shoot you!
- Did it hurt you?
Did it hurt you?
- Now get in the truck.
- Asshole!
I said move!
- On the truck, fast!
- I said move, walk!
- Go, Fulvio.
- I said move!
- Go, move along!
Hurry up, get in line.
- Halt!
- Get in line or I'll shoot.
Cencio! Fulvio!
- It's mine...
- Come on!
He's my son, she is the nanny...
- What happened?
- He's my son.
- What?
- I'm not Jewish!
She isn't Jewish and this
is her son, she says...
Give her the baby, come on!
Thank you. Thank you.
Why is it taking so long?
Come on, I told you to go!
- Come on, up.
- Come on.
- Line up! Walk!
- Walk! Walk!
- Hurry up!
- Move, get in line.
Fulvio!
Have you ever seen such a thing?
- So what?
- Little dog!
- So?
- Sit!
- What about this one?
- Move, get in!
Everyone in!
Move! Get in!
Out of the way!
Go there!
Go away! Go! Disappear.
Shut up, we won't touch you.
Why the fuck are you yelling?
Don't worry.
Fulvio, break his fucking face.
Are you hurt?
I guess he's not well, eh?
I killed him.
I told you not to touch me.
Look at what you've done.
Everyone out, come on!
- Get down! Quick!
- They are getting away!
Halt! Halt!
Give it here.
Fulvio!
Cencio!
Matilde! Matilde...
Shock! Shock!
- Hello!
- Hello.
How are you?
- I don't talk to rabbits.
- What could I do?
You could've electrocuted
them all for starters.
Donkey head, they're people
not insects.
But when they fry
they make the same smell.
- How is it you do?
- You're disgusting.
- Coward.
- Brute!
That's enough damn it!
Enough my ass!
Al least I distracted them with flies.
You didn't do anything!
- Again with this?
- Yeah, why? It's not okay by you?
- Come off.
- You come off "mudlark."
Mudlark?
Who you calling mudlark?
You're a rag man okay?
A rag man!
Get off.
You're hurting me.
Give me a kiss and I'll move.
Don't run off, just one.
I'd rather kiss a dead rat
than a filthy freak like you.
You don't just have rubber gloves
you have a rubber heart, do you?
No. The normal kind.
- So stay away.
- Watch out, you'll hurt yourself.
Nothing hurts me Fu.
Don't you dare...
What a spark!
- I told you.
- You suck at kissing.
- Don't you dare ever again.
- You're the one who dared.
What did I dare?
I've had enough!
Maybe we'll see each other,
maybe we won't.
Bye!
- Fu!
- Fulvio!
- Where are we going Fu?
- To Tiburtino Fort.
- Where?
- To Zirkus Berlin. To Franz.
- And Israel?
- Fuck Israel!
I have to get back on track.
What if the Germans arrested him?
- Again with this whinging.
- Please, let's look till tomorrow.
No, I've got things to do.
What?
You only think about yourself.
It's you who only thinks
about herself
you who can't get by without Israel.
And you, who immediately has to find
himself another master?
I have only one master:
People who buy tickets to see me.
Ok, but if we separate
what do we do alone?
In fact, come with me!
- But let's be clear: We do what I say.
- Ah puppy,
lower your fur,
you're not ordering anyone around.
So don't come.
In fact, who's going!
I'm volunteering to defend the homeland.
Right, we'd be better off
surrendering immediately.
Take care.
Go, go.
Who needs you!
He can't...
Fulvio wait!
Come on!
Let's go?
Come on it's getting dark.
I'm not coming.
Matilde...
Come on, me with Matilde...
Come on, Mario...
It's dangerous for us to be outside.
Matilde with Mario.
Mario with Matilde.
Matilde...
Israel was right about one thing...
make good use of your powers.
And you?
So you can see the way girlie.
Shalom.
Please! Please!
Italy...
Shithole country
full of Italian shitheads.
But the wine isn't bad.
And the whores are even better.
Ahhh look at this.
Who do we have here?
Don't you know there's a curfew?
Answer!
Where are you going?
Hey!
What's your name?
Can't you hear us?
- How old is she you think?
- I don't know.
Fourteen or fifteen.
Do you think she's still a virgin?
I'll tell you right away.
We'll just play a little bit.
- Don't worry...
- No, no, don't touch me.
We'll just play a little bit, okay?
- Please don't touch me.
- My little sweet Italian.
Moritz!
Is she dead?
Dunno.
- If she stays here she'll surely die.
- No, you think? What a genius!
Pick her up.
- What's wrong?
- Damn it to hell, she's electric.
What? Electric?
Your head is electric!
Electric...
- Pick her up.
- We can leave her here...
And leave a little girl
alone in the woods? Come on.
What are you laughing about?
What the fuck are you laughing at idiot?
Osvaldo!
Pick her up.
Come on!
Heil!
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Zirkus Berlin.
What'd I tell you?
Is it or is it not the most
beautiful place in the world?
It's beautiful, Fulvio.
You like it?
Let me do the talking.
Please...
We're looking for work...
we're artists.
- Thanks.
- I'm Mario.
Lions! Lions!
Look! How beautiful.
- Hello.
- Look!
Look!
I fought a hippopotamus one time.
I pulled his tail
and kicked him in the balls.
- Of course!
- A camel!
I touched his hump!
Hello.
Look at her! How talented.
Hi dancers!
Come on, let's go in!
Oh wow!
There he is.
That's Franz.
Look at that stage.
- But what's this music?
- It's beautiful.
Beautiful my ass.
- No, Mario, it's shit.
I've heard beautiful music,
this is garbage.
He wrote it.
Wow, what a hottie!
Beautiful!
It's sublime.
A light. Please.
Et voilà.
Your fur is wonderful.
Don't be ashamed of it.
You kidding?
I never joke about fur.
- Me neither.
- Will you shut up?
You're such an asshole!
What did I say?
- Are you the new ones?
- Yes.
Come with me.
I told you! Back on track!
You should always listen to me.
- Always!
- We're gonna make so much money.
Wow...
And these?
Were you born with them?
I'm good, eh.
Nice to meet you, I'm Cencio
I work with all the insects
of the world except bees
which piss me off.
You.
And you.
- You 3, come with me.
- Fulvio...
Let's go.
- I'm with them.
- The others with me, this way.
- Let's go.
- Fulvio!
Fulvio!
They're my friends.
- Come on.
- Where are you going Fulvio!
- Come here.
- I'm with them...
- Fulvio!
Thanks.
I could've washed myself on my own.
You know how many tits
like yours I've seen?
They're like two camel humps, right?
Is that milk?
Shall we bathe together?
Come take a bath with me?
Please, let me touch them.
Please.
Damn you sweet tits.
Fulvio!
Mario!
Hi Cencio.
You, come, come.
Who are you? Where are we?
You're with the Crippled Devils.
- Who?
- You're safe.
It's a pleasure, Hunchback.
Matilde.
- Are you hungry?
- Yes, like a wolf.
Didn't you hear?
Goddammed good for nuthin.
Our guest is hungry.
Go get some rations!
You haven't resolved a damned thing!
Get outta here, mongoloid!
You pissant.
Excuse him...
They're a bit rough.
- What happened to me?
- You fainted.
What's a young girl doing
wandering around Rome alone?
I'm looking for someone.
Who?
- His name's Israel.
- Your dad?
Yes.
No... more or less.
The food's arrived, eat.
Have a seat.
Go away, get, clear out.
Eat.
She's hungry, eh?
Listen, girl...
not to mind your business
but to straighten out mine...
How the fuck d'ya do it?
- Do what?
- The shock, the lightning.
The shock?
When we found you,
you almost shocked us.
- Why, did anyone get hurt?
- Bumleg almost bought the farm.
- But no, he's fine now.
- I'm fine.
Don't worry, he's always
been a little messed up.
If I were electric!
You know how many Nazis
I'd have killed? Tons.
I don't kill anyone.
You know how many I annihilated myself
since the beginning of the war? 35!
24 Nazis
and 11 fascists.
One just yesterday, right Osva?
A shot in the forehead and boom.
He fell just like a wild pig.
Girlie why don't you join us?
I'll make you into a guerrilla.
You know how much fun we'd have?
Killing people?
War is war.
That's enough, you'll frighten her.
Don't you see she's just a girl.
Listen...
Israel, right?
Yes.
You'll find him, you'll see.
Don't worry.
When Germans catch Jews,
where do they take them?
They put them on trains
and deport them to Germany.
What if all goes well?
- They kill them.
- Stop it.
Don't listen to him, the polio
virus melted his brain.
The polio my ass!
I'll bring you a little bread.
Listen, this electricity you've got,
can you shoot it far? How far can it go?
- With this again?
- Let me see.
There's nothing to see.
If you show me, I swear I'll
help you find your friend.
- Really?
- My word as a hunchback.
Come on, shoot.
No.
You really are thick headed. You're crude,
smelly, but fucking hell!
- And you're an arrogant jackass.
- And you're special.
You have a gift.
It isn't a gift.
It's a curse.
Come on, you afraid of killin' somebody?
The first kills hurt, I know, but you
get used to it and the guilt disappears.
But I know how to expiate your sins.
- How?
- On the battlefield with us.
- I'm just a circus performer.
- And I'm just a poor hunchback.
...A pocket full of posies,
Ashes, ashes.
We all fall down.
What the fuck is this?
Ring a round the rosie,
A pocket full of posies,
Ashes, ashes.
We all fall down.
- Bastards!
- Fulvio!
Let me out of this cage.
Oh, bastards!
You miserable fucks.
Where are you?
Bald bastard!
Come here. Oh!
Baldy!
Come here.
Baldy.
Oh! Come on...
Oh! Let me out of here.
I swear I won't hurt you.
What the fuck you laughing at?
I'll kill you.
Laugh, laugh at this you fuck.
I'll kill you, you fucking Nazi.
- I'll kill you, I'll kill all of you!
- Bye!
Mommy!
Let me outta this cage!
Bastards!
They are special, but not exceptional.
I'll kill all of you!
Bastards!
With this ugly situation with the jews
there's a coming and going of Krauts
that's a beauty to behold!
You like fireworks?
- Yes.
- Cause tomorrow the boom'll be so loud
even that psycho asshole
Hitler's gonna hear it.
- What boom?
- A boom.
Imagine a boom.
Now ten times bigger.
And all the Jews?
Give me the binoculars.
What's happening?
Let me see.
Angle it.
Otherwise they'll see the reflection.
What do you see?
Oh, where are you going?
Stop, oh.
Wait, Matilde!
She's crazy.
- Where the fuck's she goin'?
- She's after her father.
Look at this.
- Israel!
- Matilde.
What are you doing here?
- I knew you hadn't abandoned us.
- Go away.
- I told Fulvio, he wouldn't believe me.
- Go away, they'll kill you.
- I'm getting in.
- No! Don't get in, no!
Look at that.
She's really stupid.
Where are they taking you?
- To Tiburtina station.
- Go Away. Don't worry about me.
Go back to them.
- Go to them.
- They are going to Zirkus Berlin.
Stop them. Franz is crazy.
He's a killer.
Honk the horn! Come on!
Get down.
Don't get in, no!
No!
Matilde!
God damn...
Cesira! Cesira!
Where the fuck's she going? Why
does no one do what I say goddammit.
Stop.
What are you doing you little whore?
What are you doing here?
I just wanted to go with them.
- What happened?
- She tried to climb on the truck.
She tried to give him something.
- What did you give him?
- Calm down.
I'm Jewish! I'm Jewish!
- Take me away, I want to go with him.
- Her hat fell off.
- What did you give him?
- Jewish. Jewish. Jewish.
Stay calm, she's just a girl.
No!
Nazis!
Nazis?
Who's she?
What's going on here?
Nazis...
My my how bad you are.
So?
- Shall we play war?
- What?
I don't understand you.
- What did you say?
- I don't know... Hold this a second.
Come on!
Fuck.
Die, you son of a bitch!
No! No! Israel!
No!
Israel! No!
Fuck.
- Take this. Eat.
- Thank you.
Drop that bone. Like hell
you'll eat our rations.
You ruined my attack
and my jacket too. Fuck you, fuck you!
- I just wanted to go with Israel.
- You could've saved him you whiner.
Why didn't you zap all them Nazis?
- I don't want to hurt anyone.
- Well then, fuck you!
Get out.
You're no use
to the war effort. Get out!
Don't meddle.
Come here.
- You're hurting me.
- I'm hurting you?
So then react. Come on.
Shock me.
Defend yourself.
Defend yourself. Shock me.
- Show some grit.
- No.
- Why?
- Why not.
- You're hurting me.
- Chickenshit, are you scared?
- You're hurting me, stop!
- React then. Stop me, shock me.
- Please stop.
- Let me see.
- No.
Why? Answer me!
Come on, talk.
Tell me why!
Why?
Because I killed my mother.
I killed my mother.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Clean her up
and take her to One-Eye.
Light!
He's One-Eye.
- Hello.
- Go away.
Raus.
Don't worry.
Bring him something to eat.
Go.
You know the Zirkus Berlin, don't you?
Never heard of it.
I don't know anything. Leave me alone.
And Franz?
Who the fuck is Franz?
Franz is the pianist.
The pianist... The pianist...
Oh yes.
Franz...
Thanks.
Everyone knew him in Berlin.
They would've listened to him
play for days at a time.
Poor bastard.
He just wanted to be a soldier
like his father and his brother.
Instead he became a freak show.
I'm a freak show too,
what's wrong with that?
Yes, but you don't have 6 fingers.
Franz has 6 fingers
and he wanted to fight
for his country.
- And...
- And they wouldn't let him do shit.
I was there...
at the military medical exam.
The doctors laughed
when they saw his hands
I still remember it.
Since that day, god knows why,
he's been convinced that freaks
of nature like him exist
with special powers.
When they don't meet his expectations
he kills them.
It's his gift to Hitler:
A small squad of super men
with him in command.
Can you imagine?
Not me. I can't imagine it.
My friends are with him.
With who?
- With Franz.
- What do you want from me?
UNKNOWN
ANSWER
A dark shadow has fallen
on the movement...
...To give the German people a new idea.
Welcome to Zirkus Berlin.
Fire!
No, my Führer!
Excuse me.
Who are you?
- Nice to meet you, I'm Matilde.
- Really? You look like Dorothy.
- Are you searching for the Wizard of Oz?
- Who?
This is for Franz.
Give it to him immediately.
- All right here?
- Yes.
Anything suspicious?
Who's she?
...Cencio's an albino, filthy,
he always whines, unmistakable.
- Have you seen him?
- Halt! Hey, you!
Who let you in?
Come here.
No, I haven't see them, sorry.
Bye!
You can't come in.
It's forbidden, understand?
Come. Come here. Come here.
You, get out of the way!
Halt! Halt!
Get out of here. Go away!
Halt!
Where are you?
Damnit!
Welcome to Zirkus Berlin.
Ring a round the rosie,
A pocket full of posies,
Ashes, ashes,
We all fall down.
You're givin' me a headache.
Ring around the rosie.
Feels round and cozy.
Just like a donut...
Mario! What the fuck are you doing?
You filthy bastard. You're sick!
- What are you doing?
- Shut up a moment...
What is it?
No, nothing.
What do you mean nothing?
What do you mean... Mario stop!
I'll chop off that eggplant of yours,
don't you dare...
What the fuck is it?
Matilde!
They've killed her!
These bastards've killed her.
Matilde!
How is Matilde?
Why...
Damn you.
- Bastard!
- Damned bastard.
What do you want from us?
What do you want?
Finally home.
My fantastic 4!
The time has come...
to put out the lights
and illuminate your dreams.
You murderer.
- No.
- Murderer!
Nooo...
Smile!
- Go, go.
- Forward, forward.
Come on.
Move it.
The luggage remains here.
Keep calm.
Push.
Come on! Come on!
Get in line, damnit.
Have a safe journey.
Go!
Heil Hitler!
Field Marshal.
It's an honor to welcome you.
- Good evening.
- If you'll follow me please.
I'm positive the show will be
to your liking.
Heil!
This time we go home Irina
but as winners.
Heil!
When we return to Germany,
I'm going to marry you.
Don't tell me you've seen
our future?
The future starts now Irina.
Right now!
Heil Hitler.
Ladies and gentlemen,
tonight you won't hear me play.
Tonight I submit something to you
much more important than music.
Something that will allow us
to win the war.
I see the future
and what I see
is not reassuring for us
or for Germany,
but the strength of our dreams
can change the future
and I have many dreams.
Many of you didn't believe me.
Starting with my brother.
Amen, you've tolerated me here only
so as not to displease our mother.
But you were wrong.
You all were wrong.
The future of tomorrow
will not be that of today
thanks to me and me alone
because it is I who found them!
Three men and a girl
will bring the Third Reich
into the future.
He'll play, I assure you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is with great pleasure
that I present to you...
The Wolf Man, the Human Magnet,
Insect Boy...
and...
The Electric Girl!
She's alive. She's alive!
- Matilde!
Fulvio!
Cencio! Mario!
I found him!
I found Israel!
I know where Israel is. Fulvio!
- Really? Where is he?
- Matilde.
Mario...
- Cencio.
- ...She found Israel.
Whether you believe it or not
this little girl and these three vagrants
are our only salvation.
Shock it.
Show everyone what you're capable of.
Show them I'm right.
That it's all true.
The gloves. Take off your gloves.
Matilde!
- Get those fucking gloves off!
- Matilde zap that tiger.
- Zap the tiger!
- Take off your gloves.
Matilde!
Hey! Shock it.
I said shock it.
Show off your super powers.
Show them to me!
No!
No! Mario!
Do as I say
or I swear to god I'll shoot
this asshole in the head.
No, please.
And then the others.
- Mr. Franz, please, no! I beg you.
- One...
Shoot me if you're a man.
Shoot me you nazi shit.
- Two...
- ...No really?
- Are you going to shoot me?
- Shoot me. Oh! Coward.
Coward!
Shoot me, you fucking bastard,
I'll kill you.
- I can't.
- I'll kill all of you, fucking Nazis!
- Three.
- Bastard, shoot!
You're standing in piss you ugly shit.
- Matilde.
You're so beautiful.
What do we do with the four?
Burn them!
Yes sir.
What do you want from us?
Why?
Bloody hell!
Screw you!
They're gonna burn us alive.
Open up, let us out!
Please let us out.
Son of a bitch, open the door.
Piece of shit, open the door.
Do something Fulvio.
It's my fault... it's all my fault.
It's my fault. It's all my fault.
- You stuck on repeat? Do something!
- Spit in my face.
What the fuck are you saying?
Knock the door down!
Aren't you the Wolf Man? Smash
the door down with a punch.
- Give this Nazi shit door a punch!
- Move Mati.
Ugly son of a bitch,
piece of shit, open the door!
Cencio can't die in here.
Cencio the Great can't die this way.
- I'll do it.
- I don't wanna burn to death!
Come on!
It won't open.
Do something Fulvio.
Franz.
Well, let's go, shall we?
- Let's go.
- Yes.
Go Mario.
Oh my god.
It's all true!
I am "the Cassandra" of the Third Reich.
- Like hell I'm gettin' in there.
- Come on.
- Trust me. You wanna get shot?
- Maybe it'll hurt less.
Hurry, we've got to get that train.
- Go, go get shot.
- Cencio, come on!
Can't you blow something up again
and we'll walk out nice and easy.
"Nice and easy", you think
I'm an anti-aircraft gun?
I don't know how it works.
If you're afraid, I'll go alone.
He's afraid.
- I'm not afraid.
- So come on.
You know how many cannons I've seen?
- Then come on.
- We'll land down there.
- Just don't shock me.
- I really won't touch you.
- Hey Fu.
- Eh?
- Warn us before you shoot.
- Okay.
We need a countdown done well.
From 10 to 0, count all the numbers.
Yes.
Come on Fu shoot.
- Ready?
- Eh?
- Yes.
- No!
One.
- Come on Fulvio, hurry up, go.
- I'm going.
- Come on, fast.
- Okay.
There they are!
Halt! Halt!
The soldiers are coming.
They're coming!
Get in, Mario!
Bon voyage my friend.
Here's the dwarf.
What a crazy flight!
Are you trying to shoot me
with a dwarf?
Go.
Fuck.
- Little Mario!
- He's dead!
Here I am!
I'll kill you with my hands.
What a blowhard you are.
I told you I'd kill you.
Bye bye.
Hey!
Come.
That damned son of a bitch.
Sooner or later you're going
to give me a heart attack.
Come on, let's go!
Franz, where are you?
What the fuck were you doing?
Do you realize the shit I'm in?
- I only told the truth. As always.
- Kesselring is livid.
You're a loser. You've failed
your entire life. You're scum.
You think you're a German
but you're not, you're just scum.
- It's a...
- Don't touch me.
It's really a nice jacket.
It's over, Franz.
You're going back to Berlin,
I'm telling you right now.
Goodbye, my brother.
Come on!
Fulvio!
Come on, fast!
- No, Fulvio!
- Come on.
- Fu, stop!
- Come on!
- They'll hit us!
Shit!
You're a dead dog Fu.
God damn you.
Did you see what I did, Mario?
Almost shit yourself eh?
- What now?
- Perfect! Come on!
What's perfect Fu? Eh?
Where the fuck are we going?
Attention! Yessir!
Who is the highest rank?
Sergeant Bern Schmidt, sir!
Why don't you have a helmet?
Put it on immediately!
Gather your men.
We have 4 fugitives.
But we're on patrol.
That's an order!
Yessir! Lieutenant!
- Come on, didn't you hear?
- Let's go!
Move!
- Move, come on.
- Move! Let's go.
Franz. Wait for me.
So listen.
Here's the plan:
We jump on the train,
we find Israel,
we grab him and go.
Where do we jump?
- I'm in.
- Me too.
Of course you are.
Laugh. Laugh. I want to see
where you land now.
Come on, get ready.
What a shitty plan.
3, 2, 1...
Go!
Bravo, eh?
Miscreant!
Get off me! Get off me!
Voilà!
No.
- Oh God!
- No! Stop.
- We're just circus performers.
- We're circus performers.
Hello.
Assholes!
Up there. Come on!
Yummy!
- Finally something to eat!
- Let's tuck in.
Everything is exactly
as I've seen it.
Yes!
Come on.
Come on. Get down, come on.
Get down.
Come on, everyone out.
Is there anyone named Israel here?
Is Israel there?
Cencio, give them a hand,
I'm going to open over there.
Come on, come on down.
Everyone out.
Israel... is there anyone named Israel?
- Fulvio...
- Israel...
- Israel! Israel!
- Fulvio!
Mario!
How did you do it?
Cencio!
Where's Matilde?
She's there.
- Where?
- There she is.
Matilde.
Stop! No!
Fire!
No!
Matilde!
Matilde...
Are you deaf? Go inside.
Matilde!
I would hug you if only I could.
How sad a life it must be
not being able to touch anyone.
Come with me.
I swear to you, with me
the future will be much better
than how we imagined it.
Come with me.
Yes?
Climb on, pigs!
Bring her up.
Those three as well.
The hairy one, the albino
and the dwarf.
- Come on, freaks.
- Step back.
Come on! Come on!
What are you doing?
Leave him!
That's an order.
Leave him! Leave him!
- No.
- Halt! Halt!
Halt!
- Where is she?
- I don't know, sir.
- Move!
Where is Matilde?
In your mother's ass!
Forward! Burn these shitheads!
Come on! Burn, go burn!
Take this!
Hit 'em with the grenades!
Go! Go!
Burn!
- Which way Fulvio?
- Here!
- Go, Mario!
- Get under there.
Shoot!
Forward you fucking nazis, come here!
Bravo.
The tank!
Hit the tank!
Shoot!
- Franz!
- Take cover!
Shoot into the trees!
Sniper!
Fire!
Come on!
Shoot! Shoot!
Come on, Bumleg!
Come on, guys!
Bastards!
Die, you assholes!
Medic!
Fulvio!
Matilde, come here...
Stay here. Stay here.
- Stay here.
- I'm here.
Come on!
What do we do?
Mario!
I'm okay. Go!
Don't panic.
Cover fire!
Fire!
Let's go! Let's go!
Burn!
Take out the catapult.
Sons of bitches.
No!
Take cover!
Shoot at that machine gun!
Take down that machine gun!
The grenades are ready.
Go to hell!
God damn it!
I'm tired of this shit.
I'm sorry, guys...
Fire!
There, in the trees, fire!
They're coming!
Bumleg, don't let it through!
The Killer Cow, go!
Where are you shooting?
Stop the tank!
Sara!
No!
Fuck these bastards.
- Bumleg, the Killer Cow!
- Go with the Cow, go!
Surprise, assholes!
Quiet! Keep quiet!
Hold your position!
Let's go, now.
Don't panic!
Look! Look!
Well done, Cencio!
Come on!
Come out, come on!
There was a boy on the train
that kept crying, poor thing.
He reminded me of you
when I found you.
You remember?
Fuck, you were wailing!
Mati...
you shouldn't be afraid of anything.
Understand?
You shouldn't be afraid of anything.
"Next year we'll meet..."
"...in Jerusalem".
No! No!
Israel! Please, no!
Be calm.
Shoot!
Hit the tank!
Go!
Start it up!
- It won't start!
- What do you mean it won't start? Fuck!
It won't start!
Shoot!
Company, fire!
Come on!
Let's go! Come on, come on!
Bastards!
Bumleg!
- Son of a bitch!
- Antonio, stay down!
Take cover, Antonio!
Stay down!
Antonio!
I said take cover goddammit.
Why do you never listen you fool!
Victory!
We won!
- Halt!
- Fuck!
What...?
She's a monster!
What's happening?
Fire!
No!
Matilde!
Fuck!
Get him up.
So listen...
Can we be together now?
Just to know,
cause I gave a half-answer to...
- To who!?
- Mind your own business.
Come here.
What are the two of us
doing to do, Fulvio?
We'll be a third wheel, Mario.
Sorry, Sorry.
Translation: Ian Richard
Subtitles: Studio Arki
Someone needs to stop Clearway Law.
Public shouldn't leave reviews for lawyers.