VIDEO INSTRUCTOR: To field strip
a Glock.
The first thing you want to do is
make sure the Glock is empty.
Lock the slide back,
remove the magazine.
The magazine is empty,
open up the slide.
Keep your finger off the trigger. Double check.
No round in the chamber.
With the Glock, you need to pull the
trigger to disassemble it.
It's bad boy bitch,
Scram Jones,
the Clipse B I G, let's go.
Niggaz in my faction
don't like asking questions.
Strictly gun testing,
coke measuring.
Giving pleasure in the Benzito.
Hitting fanny, spendin' chips at
Manny's.
Hope you creeps got receipts,
My peeps get dirty like cleats.
Run up in your crib, wrap you in
your Polo sheets.
Six up in your wig piece,
nigga decease.
May you rest in peace.
With my Sycamore style,
more sicker than yours.
Four, four, and fifty four draw.
As my pilot steers my Leer.
Yes my dear, shit's official,
only the Feds I fear.
Here's a tissue, stop your blood
clot crying.
The kids, the dog,
everybody dyin', no lying.
So don't you get suspicious,
I'm Big dangerous,
you're just a Likkle Vicious.
As I leave my competition,
respirator style.
Climb the ladder to success,
escalator style.
Hold y'all breath, I told y'all,
death controls y'all.
Big don't fold y'all.
I spit phrases that'll thrill you.
You're nobody till somebody kills
you.
Do you know where you're going to.
Just a memory, everybody dying,
death controls y'all,
Your nobody till somebody kills you.
Biggie Duets,
or Born Again,
Life After Death...
VIDEO INSTRUCTOR: Once you've done
that, reach up behind the Glock ear,
roll your finger over the top
and slowly squeeze back.
It'll come back about
a quarter of an inch.
There's a release button on both
sides of the Glock.
It's called the slide lock.
Go ahead and pull both of them at the
same time and let the slide go forward.
Shit!
KNOCK ON DOOR > Nigel?
> Nigel, open the door, will you?
> ...and now your Glock is
field-stripped.
> Nigel!
What? What are you doing with the
door locked?
Updating my Bebo page.
Updating my Bebo page?
Yesterday, I'd Warren on my lap here
looking for The Tweenies.
And do you know what pops up
instead?
Some young one with two big...
I'm not even going to say it.
It was disgusting.
What are you talking about?
Nidge, I don't want you looking up
that filth on the computer.
I was updating my Bebo page.
Updating my Bebo page!
Where are you going? I have to get
Warren a new pair of runners in Dundrum.
They come with a free football.
All his friends have them.
What friends?
His friends at the creche.
Do you want to come? Shopping?
Shopping, yeah. Okay.
Just give me 5 minutes.
I've to change.
This jumper is too tight.
Aw, c'mon if you're coming!
Updating my Bebo page!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
'99 nigga. Guess who's back.
Still, still doing that shit,
huh Dre?
Oh for sho', yeah, check me out.
It's still Dre day nigga,
a.k. nigga.
Though I've grown a lot,
can't keep it home a lot.
Cause when I frequent the spots
that I'm known to rock.
You hear the bass from this truck
when I'm on the block,
Ladies, they pay homage,
but haters say Dre fell off.
How nigga? My last album was
'The Chronic'.
They want to know if he still got
it.
They say rap's changed, they want
to know how I feel about it.
If you ain't up on pace.
Dr Dre is the name,
I'm ahead of my game.
Still puffing my leafs,
still fuck with the beats,
Still not loving police.
Still rock my khakis with a cuff
and a crease, fo sho.
Still got love for the streets,
repping 213, fo life.
Still the beats bang,
still doing my thang.
Since I left, ain't too much
changed, still...
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
Yeah?
> Alright, brother? Who's that?
It's me, you eejit. Darren? Yeah.
Oh man, I'm just after getting out
there now.
Just this minute there.
I'm out on the road now
waiting for Tony.
Where are you? I'm in a taxi
on my way from the airport.
Did they not stop you coming
through?
No, I breezed on through.
> Oh man! Ah, that's brilliant.
Brilliant!
Here, are you going to Mary's first?
No, I'm heading straight into see
you. > Ah yeah, man, can't wait.
Who's number is this?
It's my number.
I bought the SIM card at the airport.
Are you on your Spain mobile as
well? No, no.
This is my number for when I'm here.
Hey, listen, I've to get credit for
my phone
so will you give Tommy a ring there
and see where he is.
Okay, no worries.
I bring the fire til you're
soaking in your seat.
It's not a fluke, it's been tried,
I'm the troop.
It's 'turn out the lights' from
the world class wreckin' cru.
INSTRUMENTAL
What are you looking at? You.
You want to watch some TV, Mary?
No.
I have to pick up the kids and get
the place ready for Robbie.
Shit! What? Robbie!
I said I'd pick him up. I forgot.
MOBILE PHONE RINGING.
You said you'd pick him up?
Aw, he's not waiting for you, is he?
Where's my phone?
Hello?
Tommy, it's Darren.
What are you at?
Darren! Are you back in Dublin?
Yeah, I just got in.
Where are you?
Robbie is waiting for you.
I know. I'm on the way.
Are you banging some young one? No!
No way, what are you talking about?
Well, what then?
Look, Darren, I'm sorry, I forgot.
What are you doing? Getting dressed.
Ah, I knew it! I knew you were
banging some young one.
Go on, hurry up, will you?
I'll call you back.
I've to ring my sister.
He's in the country, is he? Yeah.
Eejit!
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
That's him now.
Hello, Darren, does nobody tell me
anything?
How did you know it was me?
What are you doing back?
You'll get arrested.
I won't. You will!
That's two of yous I have to be
worrying about now.
Ah, Mary, don't be worrying,
will you?
I'm going back to Spain in two days.
Mary!
Where are you now?
I'm on my way in to see Robbie.
Tommy is late to meet him.
I just rang him there now and he was
in bed with some young one.
He's a sap is what he is.
I thought you'd a soft spot for him.
He's a sap.
MOBILE PHONE RINGING
Nigel, where are you?
I'm coming, yeah?
We've been waiting here for
10 minutes now.
What are you talking about?
It's 5 minutes. It's 10 minutes!
Look, the shops won't be closing any
time soon, will they?
I'm giving you two minutes.
Otherwise, we're gone.
If you'd get off the phone,
I'd be there now, wouldn't I?
TENSE MUSIC
20 euro phone credit.
HE KEYS IN CODE
I like your magazine.
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
Yeah?
Yes, hello. I'd like to place an order, please,
for a 2A balls of banger, 20 Jimbobs...
Yeah, Robbie? ...And a couple of
Russian hookers.
Hello? Yeah, Robbie,
I'm in the car with Trish.
I have you on speaker.
Howya, Robbie? Alright, Trish?
How's things?
How's little, uh...
your little fella. Warren?
He's great.
So are we meeting up?
That's why I'm ringing you.
Is that alright?
What are you looking at me for?
I've to go over to Mary's and all but I was
thinking we could go for a few quiet ones later.
Yeah, for sure, man.
Listen, I've to go. I'm meeting
Darren now so I'll talk to you later.
Hey, Robbie?
Yeah, Robbie?
PHONE LINE CUT OFF
What! You're not going out with that
headbanger! Ah, he was joking.
Aw, it's been nice and quiet for the
last year.
If you start getting up to that shit
again, Nigel, I'm telling you,
you're out the door.
He was joking.
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
Yeah? > Where are you?
Just getting credit for my phone.
I was trying to call you back there.
Ah, that's because I was on the
phone to the Nidge man.
(HE SIGHS) Is he coming out later?
If he can get Trish to let go of his
nut sack he will.
Does Rosie know you're back? No.
You're a madman for leaving without
her, you know that? Yeah.
Are you going to see her? Yeah.
Good luck with that.
What do you mean?
Nothing... I mean,
it's been nearly a year, man.
Is Tommy not there yet, no? No.
> Please, buy this magazine or put
it back. Alright, alright!
It's shite anyway.
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
Howya. What are you doing?
Taking a bus or something?
Man, I'm in the car. Hurry up, will you?
Robbie is waiting on you.
He's at the shop. Yeah, okay.
I'm not saying you can't go out. If
you want to go out, go out. I will.
I can't stop you. No, you can't.
But I don't want to get some disease you pick
up from some junkie giz bucket. It was a joke!
Ah yeah, genital warts is hilarious.
That was years ago.
Jeez, are you going to bring that up
every time?
I'm sick of this.
Are you sulking? No.
You ARE sulking.
I'm not sulking.
It's because I don't want all that crap to
start now that Robbie's out, that's all.
It's one night, alright?
I'm going out with him,
having a laugh, end of story.
I won't look at another woman, okay?
What are you going to get?
I don't know.
I need a new jacket or something.
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
Alright, brother, what's the story?
> Tommy is on the way.
In the scratcher with some young
one, was he? > Yeah.
Hey, where are you now?
I'm on the M50, I'll be there in 10.
You wouldn't believe it. What?
A little cracker, she is.
Just walked in. Yeah?
Alright? Yeah.
Unbelievable!
> What are you going to do?
Wait till she comes out
and see what happens.
She's got a nipper with her, though.
> Well, I'll babysit for you!
Oh man, I'm getting married now,
that's it. Right.
You go talk to her.
I'll call you back.
Sure you might as well talk to me
now while I'm...
SIX GUNSHOTS
Robbie!
How about this?
No, look! No, sorry!
Listen, you don't understand.
It's my brother. Get out of my way!
Get out of my way!
SIRENS BLARING IN THE DISTANCE
What did they say?
What's the excuse this time?
They have to wait for the main guy
from the Technical Bureau. Wait?
Wait for him to finish his tea,
is it?
This is your fault,
you know that? I'm sorry.
You should have been here.
I know, I just... I forgot.
You forgot!
Leaving him here waiting for you.
You didn't even ring him to tell him
you'd be late.
I don't know what to say, man.
I'm sorry.
You knew he was getting out.
I told you he was getting out.
All you had to do was be here.
Was that too much for you?
I don't know, I just... I forgot.
You forgot!
Do you want me to call Mary for you?
No, I'll ring her.
What's it got to do with you?
You've done enough for one day.
OMINOUS MUSIC
I don't want to go in.
I don't want to. Okay.
I knew this was going to happen.
You always know.
I knew it was going to happen.
I knew it was.
Cops say if anyone saw anything?
They won't say anything, will they,
Mary?
I'm sure they've an idea.
I'm sure they'll get them.
It could have been half a dozen of
them.
Are you going to be alright?
Yeah, come on.
FUNEREAL MUSIC
Darren. Yeah?
Mary is here.
Mary is outside.
Yeah.
Do you want me to get her?
No.
FUNEREAL MUSIC
Fucking Tommy!
Do you think...? No.
No?
No.
Right, I'll go out to her.
Here Nidge, will you stay here with
him, will you?
I don't want him on his own.
Just say a prayer or something.
Okay.
Just say a prayer that we find...
whoever.
Because when I find them,
I'm going to kill them.
Mary.
(SHE SOBS)
(SHE HEAVES)
Mary, come here.
(SHE SOBS)
Ssshh.
(NIDGE SNIFFS)
MOURNFUL MUSIC
CAR PULLS UP OUTSIDE
Bastards!
There's more of them newspaper
bastards outside.
Can you believe the neck of them?
Vultures!
Who do they think they are?
How do they all know where we live?
Where are they getting it from?
I'll get rid of them.
No, stay where you are.
That's what they want,
to have you arrested.
What are you doing?
I'm going out to them.
Mary, sit down, I'll go out... No!
You'll get arrested.
I'm your big sister.
Will you do what I want for once?
Are you happy now?
Have you got your photographs?
We're not taking any photos of you,
love.
But you were taking photographs of
my house, weren't you?
You know we're burying my brother, Robbie, tomorrow?
You know that? All I'm doing is my job.
I want to show you something. Can I show you these?
It'll take 5 minutes.
All I want is 5 minutes to show you that my little
brother wasn't a nobody. I didn't say he was.
This is a picture of the 3 of us
all together.
That's him there.
That's my brother.
This is a school picture of him.
This is another school picture of
him. That's my brother.
This is us at my eldest child
Grainne's Christening.
He was the godfather.
That's him with his football team.
See him there?
That's him before a match at Croker.
See him smiling? That's my brother.
And this is one of the last
photographs I have of him.
That's my brother.
And what does gangland mean anyway?
Call Nidge, will you, Mary?
Okay.
What are you waiting for?
A receipt?
Is that him clear now?
No, he owes another 2 grand.
But that's 20,000 I've given you.
Yeah, but he owes us 22. Could you
not have asked them for 22?
20, that's the most the Credit Union
will give me.
What about the bank, no?
I don't know where I'll get it from.
You'll have to borrow it from
someone, won't you?
What did you say to the
Credit Union?
Will he be alright? I don't know.
Will he?
TRISH: Darren has been arrested.
I know. Arseholes!
You'd think they'd wait till after
the funeral.
Will you tell her it's going to be
okay.
He's got the best criminal brief in
town, Mary.
I rang the Gardai.
They won't tell me anything.
He's before the District Court at
11.
Will he get bail, do you think?
Of course he'll get bail, Mary.
I don't know.
He should, but you never know.
Shut up, you!
You're making it worse.
Mary, of course he'll get bail.
I'm going down the courtroom now.
You can come if you want, Mary.
Darren said it was mandatory 10
years he could get for it. For what?
For possession. For having a gun in
the house. Aw Mary, Mary, Mary.
It was a 9-millimetre
semi-automatic.
Not a bleedin' rocket launcher he
had, okay?
Jesus, he'll get 5 tops.
Shut up, you!
You're making it worse.
Mary, don't worry about it.
I'll get it sorted, okay?
(MARY SOBBING)
MUSIC
Good man, Pat.
The cops are stupid.
Imagine putting the wrong date on
the search warrant.
It doesn't matter now that he bungs
off to Spain, no?
Well, he was never arrested,
so technically,
this is the first time the bench
warrant has been served on him. Magic!
You've got to love the law.
DARREN: So Pat, what happens now?
They set a trial date
and they'll let me know.
That's bullshit!
It was a defective warrant.
What are you? Judge Judy? I'm saying
the warrant doesn't apply.
Am I right, Pat?
It doesn't make any sense.
What's the use in going to trial if
the warrant isn't worth shit? I know.
I'm going to write a letter to the
Chief State Solicitor's office
and we'll take it from there.
But they mightn't pursue it.
See? I told you. Shut up, you.
What do you mean they mightn't pursue
it?
Well, if the whole basis of a potential
trial rests on a defective warrant...
Sure all that was wrong with it was
the date. It doesn't matter.
If they think they'll get a
conviction, they'll run with it
but there's a good chance they won't
because of this. Why not?
The cost to the State.
Serious? I told you.
Why not just tell me this now,
get it over and done with?
Because there might be some little
bollix in here,
he'll think he wants to piss away
a couple of million going after you.
There's always a little bollix
somewhere, isn't there?
So I don't have to do anything then?
No.
I'll write that letter and we'll
take it from there. Right, cheers.
But you won't be able to leave the
jurisdiction until all this is sorted,
and keep your head down.
You'll have to get a job!
Here, how are we going to work this,
by the way? For paying you.
You don't have to pay me.
It's sorted.
I spit phrases that'll thrill you,
you're nobody until somebody kills
you.
Do you know where you're going to?
Just a memory, everybody dying.
When I throw my clip in the AK,
may you rest in peace,
you're nobody till somebody kills
you.
Do you know where you're going to?
Just a memory,
everybody dying,
you're nobody till somebody kills
you.
Label limbo,
I treat it like the wind blows,
my back don't bend,
see papi is my kinfolk.
Spin out the work
as if it's on a ten spoke,
sole benefactor, the Benz,
he made the rims poke.
Trust me, they can't touch P
in one touchy,
Turn drop-head coupe to
dune-buggy.
Admire the verses,
they're inspired by the hearses
that carried my niggas
and had the church mothers cursing.
Imagine the glamour that comes out
the flow
of a nigga who still play in the
snow like Santa.
The wrist is rushing
my ears is blushing
and the diamonds in my chain
big as grandma's buttons...
Howya, Stumpy. Is Rosemary coming to
pay her respects as well?
Brendan, you should sit with us.
You're still family.
Thanks very much.
John Boy. Howya, Darren.
You got bail okay, yeah? Yeah, yeah.
That's the business, you know?
Thanks, I appreciate it.
I'm sorry about Robbie.
It's terrible.
I know this is no use to you
but I'm going to say it anyway.
Whoever did this...
you know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Because we don't forget.
I'll talk to you later.
You know we're going to sort this
out. I'll talk to you later. Yeah.
Sorry, brother. Thanks.
Sorry, Darren. Cheers.
Thanks for coming.
Trish.
Thank you.
Nidge, man. Good to see you.
See you soon. Thanks for coming.
Hey, Rosie.
I'm so so sorry. Yeah, I know.
I would have come over last night
except I didn't find out till late.
I should have just... No, no.
We weren't able to bring him home
till now.
I'm so so sorry.
Are you saying hello, Grainne?
Remember Darren's Rosie?
Hi, girls.
They've got so big in a year.
Here, I heard last night
Jimmy Byrne has skipped town.
Is he the fella Robbie glassed
inside?
The scar he has on the side of his
face from it!
Where did you hear this?
I was down the Chinaman last night.
Are you going to say it to Darren?
The brother is going to say it to
him after this.
JOHN BOY: Did you not have your
breakfast, no? I'm hungry.
Could you not have eaten it inside?
I can't eat with your man in the
coffin in there.
Rosie?
Will you...
Will you hold back? Of course.
> Sorry.
Here, Nidge!
STUMPY: What's keeping her?
NIDGE: Okay, family only now,
please. Just the family, yeah?
You can't come in, Stump.
I need to take a piss.
I have to lock the door.
They're closing the coffin now.
I'm closing the door.
I won't be two minutes.
You can fuck off.
DARREN: I hate this. I know.
I have to close the lid.
It can wait if you want.
You don't have to do it now.
I just don't want this to be
happening, you know? I know.
Yeah?
If you want to spend more time with
him, do it now, okay?
Is that what you want?
No, I have to do it now.
Yeah, yeah.
Will you stay here? Okay.
Here, girls, do you want to put your
teddies in now?
Okay, here.
Good girl.
MOURNFUL MUSIC
(BOTH SOBBING)
(BOTH CRYING LOUDLY)
What's Tommy doing over there?
Tommy! Hey, just leave him,
will you?
Where were you? > She was paying
her respects, wasn't she?
FUNEREAL MUSIC
(SHE SOBS)
I got these scapulars for the both
of yous.
I meant to get them before but...
They're supposed to protect you,
so...
I forgot to put it in the coffin.
Put yours on.
Are you alright?
I always knew this was going to
happen.
Except I always thought it would be
you. It should have been me.
It's so final.
At least he's with ma.
I would have loved if he had
children. Yeah.
Well, maybe he does.
I don't want to leave him. I know.
I don't want to leave him.
Fucking Tommy!
All he had to do was pick him up.
It's not Tommy's fault.
Yeah, it is.
It's not just his fault.
JOHN BOY: I didn't know you were
coming back. No-one really knew.
I could have hooked you up over
there, you know? Where? Spain.
I said it to Robbie, you know?
Don't know if he said it but
I bought this place over there.
You know the other side of Puerto Banus, the
road to Estepona, do you know that? Yeah, yeah.
4 bedroom, marble floor, stunning.
Not like over here.
If you ask for marble floor, they think
you're talking about brushed concrete.
But you really should have given me
a call, you know?
Everything is coming from Spain now.
Up from West Africa.
Save me going to Amsterdam.
Do you need money? No, I've
enough for a bit. Alright.
Are you going to stick around? Yeah.
Well, I have to for the court case.
Ah yeah.
He's a top bloke, Pat. Oh yeah, thanks for that.
I'll sort you out.
For Pat's fees? Yeah.
Ah, I give him tons of business.
It's nothing.
No, I'll pay you back.
Ah no, it's nothing.
Here, I'd better go over...
Go on. Right.
I WILL pay you back. Whatever.
How are you bearing up?
I'm tired. Are you?
That was depressing. Yeah.
I hate funerals.
I'm not a big fan myself.
Do you not think that was a bit
morbid? What?
Having the body in the house like
that.
What else was she going to do with
him?
Leave him in a funeral home.
How long do you think we've to go to
this thing for?
Do you not want to stay, no?
It's going to be depressing is all.
What do you expect?
It's not The X Factor, is it?
We'll stay an hour tops, yeah? Say we've
got to get back for Warren or something.
Get a few rum and Cokes in me and
I'll be alright.
A few rum and Cokes and you'll be up dancing on a
table, trying to get your kit off. Yeah, right!
Yeah, right, you know it.
It'll be grand, okay?
HUGHIE: Aw, sandwiches again?
JOHN BOY: Stop moaning, Hughie.
There IS hot food, you know.
Where's the hot food?
It's over the other side of the bar.
John Boy, do you want anything?
Yeah, get us another one of them.
What?
Nothing.
Get yourself something to eat,
will you? I'm not hungry any more.
Brendan is going to take the kids
for a few days.
Come here.
GENTLE MUSIC
TRISH: Someone knew he was getting
out, that's for sure.
Obviously they knew he was getting
out. That's how they shot him.
Don't be such a prick, Nigel!
I'm only saying.
My Tony is dead 5 years now.
They got the fella, didn't they,
Mrs Curry?
Sure it was his best buddy.
I near reared him myself.
It was an accident,
he said in court.
I suppose you all know he went and
hid Tony's body for a few weeks,
which is something, as God is my
witness, I'll never forgive him for.
Bastard judge wouldn't let me read
a victim impact statement
so I got no justice in the end.
Do you want a drink, Mrs Curry?
I'm just popping out for a smoke.
Hey! Oh!
Are you back on the smokes? I know.
I thought you were going.
What, and leave without saying
goodbye?
What are you doing? Keeping warm.
Come on and go in the car.
Why, where do you want to go?
Nowhere.
I mean to keep warm. Oh right.
Yeah, okay.
Otherwise people will keep coming
out and we won't be able to talk.
NIDGE: Here.
Where were you?
Waiting outside.
What were you doing that for?
Talking to Darren yet? No.
I shook hands with him earlier.
He's not even talking to me.
Would you blame him? No.
Do you think I should say something
to him?
Are you mad?
You'll get your head kicked in.
Just leave him alone, will you?
What's wrong with you?
I don't know what to do.
Have a drink and leave him alone.
I'd love just not to go back in.
Just leave right now.
Like the last time?
I'd bring you with me this time
though.
And I'm sorry for all the way it
happened.
It doesn't matter. No, it does.
Because I was thinking when the cops
raided the house,
they'd know that you didn't know anything
because I didn't say anything to you.
And you didn't know, did you? No.
I didn't think you'd come with me.
What did you think I was going to
do?
JOHN BOY: Have you seen Darren?
He's outside.
Playing catch-up with Rosemary.
She's paying her respects... again.
You're a mouth!
Do you know that, Hughie?
You don't know when to shut up.
It's not even funny.
I thought it was funny.
You're a mouthy little queer!
Ow!
(HUGHIE LAUGHS)
What did you go and do that for?
What did I do? It was an accident.
ROSIE: I would have gone
if you'd asked me. Yeah?
Yeah, but you didn't ask me. I know.
Why didn't you?
Because I'm stupid, aren't I?
A bit.
KNOCK ON WINDOW
Where were you?
What happened you?
Ah, Hughie mouthing off.
I swear sometimes, if he wasn't John Boy's
brother, half-brother, whatever he is,
I'd kill him, I would.
Sorry, Darren, no of fence, yeah?
No, right.
I thought you were gone or
something. No.
I'm here talking to Darren.
I'll go back in.
You shouldn't be smoking, Rosemary.
You shouldn't be smoking, no?
No.
I was going to say.
OMINOUS MUSIC
NIDGE: Alright, Joe? Alright.
You know Tommy. That's
my brother, Joe. Howya.
Alright?
Where's Mary? She's over there.
Alright, catch you later.
Seeya later.
And this is my niece, Siobhan.
Buy us a drink, Nidge, will you?
You're too young to be drinking.
What are you talking about? I'm 17.
My da lets me drink.
Uh... no, he doesn't.
Go on, I'll get you one.
What do you want? Vodka.
You can have a beer.
Don't let your da catch you with
that.
You look sad.
It's a funeral, isn't it?
Was Robbie a good friend of yours?
Yeah.
What are you doing there?
Bluetooth.
Is that you, is it? Uh...
yeah.
CAR STARTS UP
I need to talk to you about
something.
Do you know Jimmy Byrne?
Jimmy Byrne? I thought he got
transferred.
Yeah, he did, but he's been out for
2 months now.
Yeah, but Robbie has been in a lot of
scraps.
Well, he got this peacock right down
one side of his face.
Your man had been mouthing off
apparently,
saying about how he was going to get
Robbie done.
(DARREN SIGHS)
And where is he now? He's done a runner.
No-one knows where he is.
He came in the Chinaman the other
night, though,
grinning from ear to ear like he won
the Lotto, Hughie was saying.
And no-one has seen him? No.
He's done a bunk.
And the only other thing is...
I don't even want to say this but
I'm going to say it anyway. What?
Tommy.
Tommy was supposed to pick him up,
wasn't he? Yeah.
Maybe it's nothing.
OMINOUS MUSIC
How are you doing?
I have to get out of here for
a couple of hours, okay?
I'm not going anywhere. Yeah, okay.
He's not even looking.
Shut up, here he comes.
DARREN: Where did you get the suit
anyway? I had it.
Looks like you're going to the
Oscars.
Come on, man, I've to get out of
here. Alright.
You as well.
NIDGE: I have to get something from
the house, alright?
I'll just be a minute.
Um...
TURNS ON RADIO
DARREN: Can you believe this guy?
Changing again.
What's this shit you're listening
to?
RAP MUSIC
That's better.
Here, what do you think of this?
(HE LAUGHS)
Are you alright back there, Tommy?
Yeah.
RAP ON RADIO: You celebrate
the minute you was having dough.
I'm like fuck critics
you can kiss my whole asshole,
if you don't like my lyrics
you can press fast forward.
I got beef with radio
if I don't play they show,
they don't play my hits,
I don't give a shit, so.
Rap mags try and use my black ass
so advertisers can give 'em more
cash for ads, fuckers.
I don't know what you take me
as...
OMINOUS MUSIC
NIDGE: Come on, over here.
Come on, would you?
TOMMY: What are we doing?
Target practice.
DARREN: So Tommy,
Mary was telling me why you were late
to pick up Robbie.
The Glock 17, the preferred weapon
of choice of NYPD, US Air Force
and bad fuckers the world over.
What's wrong with you?
(NIDGE LAUGHS)
Look, Darren, it was only...
once or twice with Mary.
I'm sorry.
NIDGE: So you're like...
fuck buddies.
You're an eejit, Tommy.
Do you know that?
You think I'm going to shoot you because
you're a useless lazy pussy hound.
If he was riding my sister,
I'd shoot him.
Stop messing around, would you?
Which is worse, Tommy?
Being late for Robbie
or riding my sister.
Being late for Robbie. Yeah.
So if I'm not going to shoot you for
that,
how do you reckon I'm going to shoot
you for being with Mary?
(HE FIRES THREE GUNSHOTS)
Tommy, if Mary wants to ride you,
what do I care?
As long as you don't hurt her, yeah?
Come on, we need to film this before
it gets dark. Yeah.
I thought you were going to...
I know what you thought.
Hold on.
CAMERA PINGS
Right, go.
The Glock 17, the preferred weapon
of choice of NYPD, US Air Force
and bad fuckers the world over.
(HE FIRES FOUR GUNSHOTS)
Bollix, what was that?
Ricochet.
You hit the ground.
You should aim properly.
I AM aiming properly.
TWO GUNSHOTS
MARY: Darren, what's the point in
waiting outside his house?
Because he'll be back.
I don't care what you think.
Jimmy didn't kill your brother.
NIDGE: If I see one copper,
I'm dumping it.
I don't do 10 years for being
stupid.
You drive that van until I get this
sorted, do you hear me?
MARY: Are you working tomorrow?
DARREN: Yeah. With John Boy?
JOHN BOY: Yeah, I heard.
If you're taking the piss out of me,
I'll take your head off!
Is Rosie coming over? > Yeah.
Does Stumpy know you're meeting her?
ROSIE: I wish I could just click my heels and
go back and all this was different. I know.
Frances Carr RTE 2010
OpenSubtitles recommends using Nord VPN